<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fans warned: Possible RABIES exposure at NBA PACERS game...</title>
      <link>https://www.wane.com/news/indiana/department-possible-rabies-exposure-from-bat-at-pacers-game/1771180212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wane.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indiana health officials say people who had contact with a bat last week during an Indiana Pacers game have possibly been exposed to rabies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picassos, glass piano, missing billions: 1MDB scandal reaches court...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/11/1mdb-scandal-court-najib-razak-malaysia-picassos-glass-piano-missing-billions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday the former Malaysian prime minister Najib Razak will go on trial for his alleged role in the 1MDB saga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of sleep could damage DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/2185589/lack-sleep-could-damage-dna-and-affect-gene-repair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research conducted on doctors who worked long, overnight shifts, and results may apply to those in other jobs with similar working patterns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAKE SLAMS GRAMMYS, CUT OFF MID-SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/drake-ends-beef-with-awards-shows-picks-up-rap-song-grammy-1203135340/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Normally, someone merely showing up to accept a trophy he’s earned doesn’t count as the shock of the night at any awards show. So give Drake credit for having the cachet to pull off the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Journalism Isn't Dying. It's Returning to Roots...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/journalism-isnt-dying-its-returning-its-roots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of journalism is more partisan and supported by more diverse revenue streams—in other words, like the journalism of 200 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On pace for worst year since '07 wall-building spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/illegal-immigration-mexico-border-pace-worst-2007/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration across the southwest border is on pace for the worst year since 2007 — or the last time the country began a massive wall-building spree — according to new Homeland Security numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congresswoman Goes on Anti-Semitic TWITTER Rampage...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-rep-ilhan-omar-goes-anti-semitic-twitter-rampage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She accused deep-pocketed Jews of buying American politicians and retweeted a post calling Jews 'hook nosed'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE OOOOOOO</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/michelle-obama-grammy-awards-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And brings the house down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Social Media Addicts Struggle To Make Friends In Real Life</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/social-media-addicts-struggle-make-new-friends-keep-old-ones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media addiction makes it harder for people to make -- and keep -- friends in real life, a new survey of 3,053 British adults suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAMMY AUDIENCE MELTDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/michelle-obama-shows-up-at-the-grammy-awards-the-audience-lose-their-sht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years, 700 victims: Southern Baptist sexual abuse spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/investigations/article/Southern-Baptist-sexual-abuse-spreads-as-leaders-13588038.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As leaders decline to act, the numbers grow. In the past 20 years, about 380 Southern Baptist church leaders and volunteers have faced allegations of sexual misconduct, the newspapers found. They were pastors. Deacons. Ministers. Youth pastors. Sunday school and Christian school teachers. Church program volunteers. They left behind more than 700 victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pablo Escobar's hippos multiplying, running wild, destroying Colombia ecosystem...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pablo-escobars-hippos-keep-multiplying-and-colombia-doesnt-know-how-to-stop-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not uncommon to spot a three-ton hippo walking around town</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK SUIT: Cop pulls down man's pants, TASES TESTICLES...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/local-news/investigations/abuse-of-force-body-camera-video-shows-man-tased-11-times-by-glendale-officers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video obtained by ABC15 Investigators shows what experts called "sadistic" and "outrageous" conduct by Glendale police officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian fighters in Arctic power play at top of world...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/strategic-messaging-russian-fighters-in-arctic-spark-debate-on-canadas-place</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearing the end of its term, the Liberal government has yet to table an official Arctic policy as Russia expands its influence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dem Field Grows, 2020 Race Sharpens in Tone...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-democratic-field-grows-the-2020-race-sharpens-in-tone-11549843990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and a growing field of Democratic presidential contenders are entering a more confrontational phase at the start of the 2020 campaign, with the incumbent seeking to define his opponents long before the general election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schultz Adviser Storms Off Own Podcast -- When Asked About Schultz...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/steve-schmidt-storms-off-own-podcast-when-asked-about-advising-howard-schultz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is bullsh*t,” Schmidt exclaims. “I’m not doing this.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress already laying groundwork for impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressofatlanticcity.com/news/ap/nation/doyle-mcmanus-congress-already-is-laying-the-groundwork-for-impeachment/article_0ead30da-3507-59c9-b900-ccc141b6d15a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressofatlanticcity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Last week, no fewer than six committees of the House of Representatives were investigating potential grounds for impeaching President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TRUMPS SKEDS LEAK</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-schedule-leaks-4840f751-e663-49c0-b288-2dd39bde9c79.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crackdown has not stopped the leaking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters rants: We're going to get your tax returns!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-waters-rants-about-trump-at-mlk-celebration-were-going-to-get-your-tax-returns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Congresswoman Maxine Waters took some time during an event honoring the legacy of Rev. Martin Luther King, Jr. to rant about President Trump’s tax returns. @RepMaxineWaters “@realDonaldTrump, we are going to get those tax returns” pic.twitter.com/zlXpi3YUY7 — Jay Nelson 🇺🇸 (@Jay_Nelson2020) February 9, 2019 “I’m not backing down from this fight,” Waters said at …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos's Journey From Private Family Man to Tabloid Sensation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/jeff-bezoss-journey-from-private-family-man-to-tabloid-sensation-11549837862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon CEO cultivated a persona of the billionaire who did dishes, until his company moved into Hollywood. There, he took on the trappings of a very different lifestyle, where people and events are much harder to control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle's snowiest February in 70 years --  more coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/10/seattle-snowiest-february-70-years-more-coming/2830164002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a weekendÂ snowstormÂ pummeled normally mild Seattle, making this month the city's snowiest February since 1949, more is on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plummeting number of insects threatens 'catastrophe for planet'...    </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/feb/10/plummeting-insect-numbers-threaten-collapse-of-nature</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Insects could vanish within a century at current rate of decline, says global review</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE INFOWARS: MUELLER SET TO END RUSSIAN PROBE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/live-sunday-exclusive-mueller-probe-to-end-march-1st-new-york-dc-chicago-to-announce-criminal-indictments-of-trump-after/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infowars is the epicenter of cutting-edge news and analysis tyrants everywhere fear -- please spread the live link!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Trump Fashion at Grammys...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/pro-trump-fashion-joy-villa-dress-ricky-rebel-grammys-2019-1203134993/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAGA is having a small fashion moment at the 2019 Grammys. Singers Joy Villa and Ricky Rebel both used the red carpet to spread their pro-Trump messages. First up is Villa, who dressed as President…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW GLOBAL POLL:  'Climate change' seen as top threat, but U.S. power growing worry...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190210225154-k96v7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-SECURITY/ (EMBARGOED):Climate change seen as top threat, but U.S. power a growing worry -poll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOKGOOGLE Worsen Media Bias...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-and-facebook-worsen-media-bias-11549829040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silicon Valley’s advertising monopoly translates into editorial influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga loses Best Actress -- Again!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/feb/10/baftas-2019-winners-full-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Favourite won the most Baftas, but Roma carried off the big prizes, including best film and best director</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE INFOWARS: MUELLER SET TO END RUSSIAN PROBE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-alex-jones-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' Named Best Film at BAFTAs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/bafta-award-winners-2019-complete-list-1178566</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rami Malek won leading actor honors, while 'BlackKklansman' earned Spike Lee a best adapted screenplay award.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff concerned Mueller's scrutiny of president's finances isn't adequate...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/schiff-vows-to-continue-investigation-into-trump-finances-russia-links</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff, D-Calif., vowed on Sunday to continue for as long as it takes the investigation into President Trump's finances and foreign connections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP Latin American Poll Shows 42 Million Want to Move to USA...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/gallup-latin-american-poll-shows-42-million-want-to-move-to-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five million Latin Americans want to come to the US this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SHUTDOWN THREAT</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/shutdown-threat-us-budget-talks-stall-163535759.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US budget talks have hit another impasse over immigration, a key Republican negotiator said Sunday, raising the prospect of a second government shutdown if no agreement is reached by this week's deadline. "I think the talks are stalled right now," Richard Shelby, the chairman of the Senate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ: Internet splits in two...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-internet-divided-between-the-u-s-and-china-has-become-a-battleground-11549688420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As China and the West race for 5G dominance, two digital powers with very different approaches to technology are staking out their corners. Some Silicon Valley executives worry the divergence risks giving Chinese companies an advantage in new technologies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMING SOON:  The Real World, With GOOGLE Maps Layered on Top...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/its-the-real-worldwith-google-maps-layered-on-top-11549807200?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coming Google Maps augmented-reality navigation feature will look through your phone’s camera to figure out where you are and show you where you are going.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky sheriff suspends all law enforcement over lack of funding...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/john-kirk-martin-county-kentucky-sheriff-suspends-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kentucky sheriff has told the local fiscal court he is suspending all law enforcement activities because of lack of funding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOW OF FORCE:  100 police vehicles line 1-mile stretch of border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/show-of-force-100-vehicles-line-one-mile-of-texas-border-to-deter-caravan-on-other-side</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAGLE PASS, TEXAS — The Trump administration has flooded the Texas border town that sits just over the river from the Mexican city where 1,800 caravan migrants arrived earlier this week with hundreds of law enforcement personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Hip-Hop Make Long-Awaited History at GRAMMYS?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-hip-hop-make-history-at-grammys-wins-record-song-year-1184619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music awards show has had a pretty dodgy past with recognizing the genre’s merits — and diverse winners in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal murder of 19-year-old girl shocks Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-israel-police-identify-body-of-19-year-old-woman-stabbed-near-jerusalem-1.6916811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROWING CALLS TO TAX RICH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/05/warren-sanders-ocasio-cortez-propose-taxes-on-the-rich-ahead-of-2020-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Railing against inequality is a pertinent message, but scholars also warn that the gap between the rich and poor can lead to bigger issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Brown Shade at Kamala: Can't Beat Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/10/willie-brown-throws-shade-at-ex-girlfriend-kamala-harris-cant-beat-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former San Francisco mayor Willie Brown says none of the Democrat candiates so far, including Harris, can beat President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>None Dare Call it a Hoax: The Jussie Smollett Saga Continues...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/none-dare-call-it-a-hoax-the-jussie-smollett-saga-continues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops are still investigating the "hate crime" against the actor but have yet to find any evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madam Lagarde sees global economic storm brewing... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/imf-warns-global-economic-storm-growth-undershoots-143827334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Monetary Fund on Sunday warned governments to gear up for a possible economic storm as growth undershoots expectations. "The bottom-line -- we see an economy that is growing more slowly than we had anticipated," IMF Managing Director Christine Lagarde told the World Government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Heavy clashes' as US-backed forces make final push against ISIS... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/heavy-clashes-us-backed-forces-final-push-against-101643002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US-backed forces were locked in fierce fighting Sunday as they pressed the battle against the last shred of the Islamic State group's "caliphate" in eastern Syria. The jihadists overran large parts of the country and neighbouring Iraq in 2014, but various military offensives have since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at HIV data leak in conservative Singapore... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fury-hiv-data-leak-conservative-singapore-034041326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rico has lived with HIV for almost a decade, confiding in only a small number of people in socially conservative Singapore, fearful of the reaction. Rico was one of 14,200 people whose HIV status, name and address were dumped on the internet by an American man who is believed to have obtained the confidential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX shows successful? Who knows?</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/are-netflix-shows-successful-who-knows/505567322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming company refuses to release viewership figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional talks to avert shutdown stall over detention policies...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190210155342-h936n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Congressional talks to avert shutdown stall over detention policies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungarian PM announces new loan, tax cuts to boost birth rate...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190210153311-3wihw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNGARY-ORBAN/BENEFITS (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Hungarian PM announces new loan, tax measures to boost birth rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss voters reject plan to curb urban sprawl...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190210120200-qwltc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The initiative preserves the beautiful landscapes in Switzerland and thus our quality of life as well'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel feels pressure as boycott movement gains global support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-fights-bds-movement-pro-palestinian-campaign-gains-global-support-n965691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign is also reverberating in the U.S., where the Senate passed a bill Tuesday that would allow states to punish businesses that take part in Israel boycotts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran revolution: Political quake still shaking Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190210-irans-revolution-political-quake-still-shaking-middle-east</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's revolution: Political quake still shaking Middle East</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans feel alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/feeling-lonely-you-are-not-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Americans say they sometimes or always feel alone, which can have health consequences: doctors say loneliness can lead to increased mortality equal to smoking 15 cigarettes a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Middle Class Joe' Biden Courts Wall Street Oligarch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/middle-class-joe-biden-courts-wall-street-oligarch-blackrocks-larry-fink</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-veep says he's the working man's friend. How does that square with currying favor with financial world titan Larry Fink?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg's Quiet Rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-political-scene/pete-buttigiegs-quiet-rebellion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Against the image of the millennial left, Buttigieg appears to be a relatively prosaic Presidential candidate, but, in his own understated way, he is suggesting a sharp break with the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT to get $210 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/reddit-strikes-deal-with-chinese-censorship-powerhouse-users-expose-chinas-worst-atrocities/news-story/2412b1bc5381b344c7695a03e55c196d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reddit is reportedly set to land a massive investment from a Chinese censorship powerhouse in order to keep the “Internet’s front page” rolling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-year-old passes out at school, tests positive for cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/crime/article226012090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Clark County, Ky., mother was arrested after her 4-year-old became unresponsive at school and tested positive for cocaine. Winchester police were called to Clark Regional Medical Center to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie risks getting crowded out in field of progressives...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-08/sanders-risks-getting-crowded-out-in-2020-field-of-progressives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parking lot suicides:  Taking their lives on VA doorstep...</title>
      <link>https://expo.oregonlive.com/news/g66l-2019/02/a3c833579f4689/the-parking-lot-suicides-they-take-their-lives-at-the-doorstep-of-the-va.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;expo.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wingers rally in Madrid, demand Socialist PM resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/madrid-protests-thousands-demand-pedro-sanchez-soc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Spaniards in Madrid are joining a rally called by right-wing political parties to demand that Socialist Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez step down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitler paintings go unsold at Nuremberg auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/hitler-paintings-go-unsold-nuremberg-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five watercolors attributed to Nazi dictator Adolf Hitler from his early days as a struggling artist have failed to sell at auction in the southern German city of Nuremberg, possibly over fears they could be fakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Most African Americans in Virginia want Gov to stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/virginia-politics/virginians-split-on-governors-fate-amid-blackface-scandal-poll-shows/2019/02/09/93002e84-2bc1-11e9-b011-d8500644dc98_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;African Americans and Democrats say by wide margins that Gov. Ralph Northam should remain in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi: 'Nothing to do' with dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bezos-saudi/saudi-arabia-says-has-nothing-to-do-with-bezos-ami-dispute-idUSKCN1PZ0BG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia had "absolutely nothing to do" with the National Enquirer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year 3 aims for dramatic sequels to rival originals...</title>
      <link>https://www.avpress.com/news/newsline/trump-aims-for-dramatic-sequels-to-rival-originals/article_838ce970-2cf1-11e9-9430-930c77278130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.avpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As President Donald Trump prepares to meet North Korea’s Kim Jong Un for a second time, he’s out to replicate the suspenseful buildup, make-or-break stakes and far-flung rendezvous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimps make ladder, escape zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/feb/10/chimps-use-branch-as-ladder-to-escape-belfast-zoo-enclosure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breakout is second in recent weeks after runaway red panda found in a nearby garden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  How AMAZON gets whatever it wants...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/politics/how-amazon-gets-whatever-it-wants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two power plays this past week show why it's Amazon's world, and we're just living in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEMSON coach admits college may have given players banned drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/sports/clemson-s-dabo-swinney-says-college-may-have-given-players/article_24ab729a-2bdf-11e9-9a3f-97cd28b8ce04.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dabo Swinney says it's possible three Clemson players suspended after failing drug tests before the Cotton Bowl may have mistakenly received the banned performance-enhancing drug from the school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido won't rule out authorizing US intervention...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190209-venezuela-guaido-not-rule-out-authorising-us-intervention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s self-proclaimed acting president Juan Guaido refused to rule out on Friday the possibility of authorizing United States intervention to help force President Nicolas Maduro from power and alleviate a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea to Pay More Under New Military Deal With USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/south-korea-to-pay-more-under-new-military-deal-with-u-s-11549794220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and South Korea signed a one-year deal outlining the shared costs of their military alliance, removing a potential distraction ahead of the second summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un scheduled for late this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mumps at Houston ICE facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c4511e01dbc04b2d8fb3807d34b5d005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Health officials say seven cases of the mumps have been confirmed at a U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement detention facility in Houston. The Houston Health Department said Saturday that the seven adults were detained during their infectious period. Health officials say there's no evidence the disease was transmitted outside the facility. The health department is working with the facility on infection control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi gets rock star treatment at pre-GRAMMY gala...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5f069b167aa84bd0b85465c707507892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The audience at Clive Davis' white-hot gala included Barbra Streisand, Joni Mitchell and Kareem Abdul Jabbar, but it was House Speaker Nancy Pelosi who got the most requests to take a selfie. Pelosi received rock star treatment Saturday night from attendees at the annual pre-Grammy event, which also featured a stunning tribute to the late Aretha Franklin, an artist Davis worked closely with for decades.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
