<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WALMART boycott launched after outcry over 'Impeach 45' clothing...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/2018/07/03/walmart-boycott-campaign-launches-after-outcry-over-impeach-45-clothing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart drew outrage Monday after it was discovered that the superstore was selling “Impeach 45” apparel on its website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally ill dogs at canine hospice treated to steak dinners, trips to MCDONALD'S and birthday parties in their final days...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/terminally-ill-dogs-canine-hospice-12842554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former nurse Nicola Coyle runs the Grey Muzzle Canine Hospice Project in Mansfield - thought to be the first of its kind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREWORKS COSTING MORE THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/03/washington-dc-4th-july-fireworks-price/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government is shelling out more dough on the National Mall 4th of July fireworks this year ... $30k more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAS PRICES HIT HOUSEHOLDS</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Oil-Prices/This-Is-How-Much-US-Households-Lose-As-Gas-Prices-Rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. households are feeling the pinch and are expected to have around $440 less disposable income as higher gasoline prices are offsetting part of the tax cuts from earlier this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Serial Killer Arrested After Death of Eight Babies at Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/suspected-serial-killer-arrested-in-britain-after-death-of-eight-babies-in-hospital?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health-care worker has been arrested on suspicion of murdering eight infants and trying to kill six more at a hospital in northwest England.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man threatens to burn down TV station, calls journalist 'dead man walking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article214251504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Eric Bewley, 47, is charged with transmitting threats through interstate communications, a federal crime, after authorities say he threatened to burn down Texas TV station KBTX and called the general manager 'a dead man walking.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin court OKs unconscious drunk drivers' blood draws...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsin-court-oks-unconscious-drunk-drivers-blood-draws-140047075.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — The Wisconsin state Supreme Court says police can legally draw blood from unconscious drunken drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenpeace activists 'crash' drone into nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/greenpeace-activists-crash-drone-french-nuclear-plant-134507827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenpeace activists said Tuesday they had flown a drone fitted out as a flying Superman into a nuclear energy plant in southeast France, aiming to show how the country's reactors are vulnerable to terror attacks. A video released by the environmental group shows the drone zipping through restricted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vampire' killer caught after seen drinking blood of victim...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5912437/Vampire-killer-caught-seen-drinking-blood-woman-throat-slit-Zimbabwe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Sibanda struck his elderly victim several times with a log in Sikhewu village before allegedly cutting her throat with a sharp implement. A passerby saw him sucking her wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Surgeons argue, flirt, throw things while patients under the knife...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5912371/Medics-fight-flirt-throw-things-patients-knife-study-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Emory University in Atlanta, Georgia have revealed medical staff dance to music and quarrel with one another to gain status while operating on unconscious patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Arnold's bonkers strategy for nailing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/07/03/tom-arnolds-bonkers-strategy-for-nailing-trump-218944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-energy comedian says he knows exactly how to take down the president. Now, if he could only get his hands on one little tape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water main break floods downtown Philly streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/water-main-break-flooding-downtown-philly-streets-100206398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA (AP) — A large water main break has flooded a number of streets in downtown Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five-ton tractor 'missing' following tornado...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/07/02/tornadoes-five-ton-tractor-missing-south-dakota-following-tornado/752475002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornadoes have been known to toss around everything from cars and trucks to cows and people, but usually the objects don't vanish completely. But last Thursday, a tornado near the Montana/South Dakota border lofted and destroyed some farm machinery including a 5-ton tractor that has yet to be found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS adds MORE stores to closings list...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/nation-now/2018/07/02/sears-closings-78-kmart-and-sears-closing-september/750127002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings list of closing locations is growing. Now, 62 Sears and 16 Kmart stores are expected to close in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pruitt becomes latest Trump official to be harassed at restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/02/scott-pruitt-becomes-latest-trump-official-to-be-harassed-at-a-restaurant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt became the most recent Trump administration figure to get an earful while trying to get a mouthful at a DC restaurant, according to a Face…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bono warns existence of UN, EU, NATO threatened...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/prime-minister-honors-87-irish-un-peacekeepers-died-175547438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Irish rock star Bono warned Monday that the United Nations and other international institutions including the European Union and NATO are under threat — and nations must work together to ensure their continued existence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tow-an-iceberg plan being floated to ease Cape Town drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tow-iceberg-plan-being-floated-ease-cape-town-030704601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a plan as crazy as the situation is desperate -- towing an iceberg from Antarctica to Cape Town to supply fresh water to a city in the grip of drought. Earlier this year, Cape Town came within weeks of shutting off all its taps and forcing residents to queue for water rations at public standpipes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
San Fran appalling street life repels residents -- now it's driven away convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-s-appalling-street-life-repels-residents-13038748.php?t=0c15a3045e&amp;f?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that is alarming San Francisco's biggest industry, a major medical association is pulling its annual convention out of the city - saying its members no longer feel safe.         "It's the first time that we have had an out-and-out cancellation over the issue, and this is a group that has been coming here every three or four years since the 1980s," said Joe D'Alessandro, president and CEO of S.F. Travel, the city's convention bureau.         D'Alessandro declined to name the medical association, saying the bureau still hopes to bring the group back in the future.         As a rule, major conventions book their visits at least five years in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-apocalypse now: End of the world at the movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/post-apocalypse-now-end-world-moviespost-apocalypse-now-045458539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Bible to Nostradamus, the Mayan calendar and the Millennium Bug, fatalists, fantasists and the fervently religious have long been fascinated by the end of the world. Movie directors love nothing more than feeding our deepest fears concerning overpopulation, pestilence and nuclear armageddon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA DEVELOPS 'LASER GUN'</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-firm-develops-laser-gun-064153947--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese firm has developed a laser gun designed for police use that can set fire to protesters' hair or banners from a range of almost one kilometre. The general manager of the ZKZM fiber laser company, who asked to remain anonymous, said the weapon would "immediately" produce a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN: FAMILY AND COUNTRY 'FIRST LOYALTY'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michael-cohen-family-country-president-trump-loyalty/story?id=56304585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen told George Stephanopoulos that his family is his "first loyalty."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malls Vacancies Hit Six-Year High as Online Shopping Takes Toll...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mall-vacancy-rate-hits-six-year-high-1530588600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malls are the emptiest they’ve been since 2012, when the U.S. economy was still struggling to recover from the last recession, as more consumers shifted their shopping online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian General Accuses Israel of Stealing Clouds to Cause Drought...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/03/iran-thinks-israel-stealing-clouds-cause-drought-7679005/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brigadier General Gholam Reza Jalali, head of Iran's Civil Defence Organisation, alleged that his country was facing cloud 'theft' during a press conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters is done with 'nice guy politics'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/395250-maxine-waters-is-done-with-nice-guy-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the perspective of some House Democrats, Rep. Maxine Waters (D-Calif.) has the right message. She’s just not always the best messenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AMLO earthquake might rattle Mexico...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/782498/how-amlo-earthquake-might-rattle-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does Mexico's new president want?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA BUILDS 'LASER AK-47' THAT BURNS THROUGH SKIN...</title>
      <link>http://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy-defence/article/2153310/china-brings-star-wars-life-laser-ak-47-could-set-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Handheld weapons that could set fire to targets from long distances are no longer confined to science fiction but a fact of life, according to researchers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPKINS nurse files suit, saying doctor squirted patient's bodily fluids on him...</title>
      <link>http://www.baltimoresun.com/health/bs-hs-hopkins-bodily-fluids-20180629-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Johns Hopkins nurse has filed a lawsuit against a doctor who he said sprayed bodily fluid from a patient on him while he was assisting with a surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
San Fran appalling street life repels residents -- now it's driven away convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/matier-ross/article/SF-s-appalling-street-life-repels-residents-13038748.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that is alarming San Francisco's biggest industry, a major medical association is pulling its annual convention out of the city - saying its members no longer feel safe.         "It's the first time that we have had an out-and-out cancellation over the issue, and this is a group that has been coming here every three or four years since the 1980s," said Joe D'Alessandro, president and CEO of S.F. Travel, the city's convention bureau.         D'Alessandro declined to name the medical association, saying the bureau still hopes to bring the group back in the future.         As a rule, major conventions book their visits at least five years in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Dems Say Bernie Too Right-Wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/socialist-dems-say-bernie-too-right-wing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America can move far-left if Trump voters grow too complacent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can zapping brains reduce violence? Controversial study sees potential...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/07/02/brain-electric-stimulation-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers hailed their results as evidence that increasing activity in the prefrontal cortex can reduce "intentions to commit aggression."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New threat for famous wild horses: Tourists offering junk food...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article214180694.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corolla Wild Horse Fund kicks off effort to stop tourists from feeding the herds of wild horses roaming NC's Outer Banks. Foreign food, even apples and carrots, is making the animals sick and can kill them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bid to split California into 3 states gains traction...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/02/bid-to-split-california-into-3-states-gains-traction-could-it-really-happen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a midterm season marked by primary upsets and the prospect of Democrats claiming a congressional check on President Trump’s power, another sensational development has been the momentum behind a ballot measure to split up the unwieldy, high-tax state of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH: RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT WOULD KILL ME...</title>
      <link>http://www.vogue.co.uk/article/august-cover-vogue-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the issue, the media icon discusses race, feminism, and the loves and losses in her life with writer Decca Aitkenhead in the rarest of one-on-ones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanist strangles boyfriend during sex; Chops up body in devil sacrifice...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/713809/satanist-murder-russia-dismembered-bdsm-sex-anastasia-onegina-dmitry-sinkevich-baphomet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest boots family from funeral after chalice knocked over...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/archdiocese-of-washington-apologizes-after-maryland-family-kicked-out-of-funeral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Archdiocese of Washington has issued an apology after a family was kicked out of a funeral in Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PROBE FACEBOOK STATEMENTS</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-facebook-investigation-broadened-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal investigation into Facebook's sharing of data with political consultancy Cambridge Analytica has broadened to focus on the actions and statements of the tech giant and involves three agencies, according to people familiar with the official inquiries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives Sound Alarm Over Potential Supreme Court Pick's Christianity...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2018/07/amy-coney-barrett-under-progressives-religiou-ignorance-bigotry-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Efforts to block the highly qualified Barrett from the Supreme Court because of her faith betray our nation’s founding ideals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for threatening to chop Rand Paul, family with ax...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/politics/2018/07/02/man-threatens-kill-sen-rand-paul-ax/751211002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rand Paul has faced several threats and attacks in the past year: A shooting, a dispute with a neighbor and now a man threatening to ax him, literally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-lb Bag Of 'Human Poop' Dumped On San Fran Sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/San-Francisco-human-waste-feces-homeless-Reddit-13044317.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A foul odor permeated from a massive bag of human excrement sludge left on a street corner in San Francisco's Tenderloin district Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel chain uses biometric data to find guest vacation spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90179273/this-hotel-chain-is-using-biometric-data-to-find-you-the-perfect-vacation-spot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new program from AccorHotels will use your own biometrics to determine the destination of your dreams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA-Bron Move Ups Hollywood Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/lebron-james-move-la-should-up-his-producing-game-1124391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After signing a four-year $154 million deal with the Lakers, the NBA’s biggest star will only need to travel 11 miles from his new basketball home at the Staples Center and his SpringHill offices on the Warner Bros. lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Solitary confinement' retreats free guests from modern life distractions...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/capital/story/20180702-a-south-korean-prison-for-people-seeking-peace-and-quiet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former lawyer came up with a bizarre antidote for stressed-out workers: being locked in a cell for two days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED GETS SHREDDED DOCS...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jasonleopold/here-are-the-documents-recovered-from-michael-cohens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“NEVER MET: Donald Trump, George Lucas, Harrison Ford, Steven Spielberg, Michael Jackson, The Jackson’s family, Sony.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans To Make History Competing in Miss Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.advocate.com/people/2018/7/02/trans-woman-makes-history-will-compete-spain-miss-universe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.advocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety of lions in captivity no longer guaranteed...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/02/demand-big-cat-parts-fueling-lion-killings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surge in demand for big cat body parts on South Africa&amp;rsquo;s black market is endangering the future of the country&amp;rsquo;s captive lion population, conservationists have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock As Boston 'Duck Boat' Tour Spots Floating Body...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/07/02/boston-duck-boat-body-found-charles-river/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body was found near the Longfellow Bridge Monday morning, according to the Coast Guard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAWS: Monster alligator stalks, chases FL girl up tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.wftv.com/news/local/lake-county-teen-gets-trapped-in-tree-after-being-chased-by-aggressive-alligator-deputies-say/781473858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wftv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lake County teen gets trapped in tree after being chased by aggressive alligator, deputies say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanging by branch for an hour!</title>
      <link>http://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-alligator-lake-deputy-killed-girl-tree-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida alligator was shot and killed by a Lake County deputy with an AR15 Bushmaster rifle that had trapped a girl in a tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA faces first large group of concussion-related lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/sports/wp/2018/07/02/feature/former-alabama-player-les-williams-is-one-of-more-than-100-suing-ncaa-over-brain-injuries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Les Williams is one of more than 100 former college football players claiming the sport damaged his brain: “I didn’t sign up for that.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRANSON: America should give 'free cash' to fix inequality...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/02/virgin-groups-richard-branson-on-universal-basic-income.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s a disgrace to see people sleeping on the streets with this material wealth all around them,” says the iconic entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMLO' offers migration cuts in Trump call...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexicos-amlo-offers-migration-cuts-trump-call-192528451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican president-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Monday he had spoken with President Donald Trump on the phone and offered to reduce US-bound migration in exchange for American assistance. "I received a phone call from Donald Trump and we spoke for half an hour," the fiery leftist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topless woman drives stolen bulldozer across town...</title>
      <link>http://www.krtv.com/story/38550755/woman-crashes-through-fence-with-excavator-in-great-falls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It happened at the Fox Hollow apartments on 10th Street SW, behind the Best Western Heritage Inn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Damon to Star in Marc Rich Movie...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/matt-damon-marc-rich-bill-clinton-pardon-movie-the-king-of-oil-john-krasinski-tap-universal-1202420589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Matt Damon is in the early stages of attaching to star as the fugitive billionaire commodities trader Marc Rich in The King of Oil. Universal Pictures has optioned the project for Sunday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA spacecraft sending back close-ups of dwarf planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nasa-spacecraft-sending-back-close-ups-dwarf-planet-191716077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA's Dawn spacecraft is sending back incredible close-ups of the dwarf planet Ceres.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING SHOT...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trumps-former-personal-lawyer-says-silence-broken-040937565--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After once boasting he would "take a bullet" for Donald Trump, the president's longtime personal lawyer and fixer Michael Cohen fired a possible warning shot toward the White House, saying he now puts "family and country first."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle bans plastic straws, utensils...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/seattle-bans-plastic-straws-utensils-becoming-first-major-us-city-to-do-so#/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle has officially become the first major U.S. city to ban restaurants from giving plastic straws and utensils to customers in an effort to help the environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog bitten by rattlesnake called 'hero' for saving owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.app.com/story/news/weird/2018/07/02/brave-dog-saved-his-owner-rattlesnake/751541002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.app.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd, a very brave Golden Retriever saved his owner Paula Godwin from a rattlesnake during a walk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech's 'Dirty Secret': Developers Sifting Through YOUR GMAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/techs-dirty-secret-the-app-developers-sifting-through-your-gmail-1530544442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Software developers scan hundreds of millions of emails of users who sign up for email-based services. Disclosures are often buried in user agreements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Purges Top Hamas, Hezbollah Accounts...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/national-security/twitter-purges-top-hamas-hezbollah-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media networking website Twitter has either banned or blocked at least 35 accounts affiliated with the Hamas and Hezbollah terrorist groups following a call for such action by a top Israeli official, according to regional reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area choked by wildfire ash, smoke...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/bay-area-ash-fires-yolo-county-pawnee-wildfire-13041670.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bay Area residents woke up to streets blanketed with ash, and a surreal sky right out of an Instagram filter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Now Have 1.3 Million Files...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/prosecutors-now-have-1-3-million-michael-cohen-files/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after President Donald Trump’s embattled attorney Michael Cohen suggested he would cooperate with the government, a judge disclosed Monday that federal prosecutors now have more than 1.3 mill…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Ross leaving ABC after botched Flynn report...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/07/02/brian-ross-leaving-abc-news-after-botched-michael-flynn-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Ross was suspended last year as chief investigative correspondent for a faulty report on Michael Flynn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Coffee boosts longevity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d11c85d6c654c52ac6c099bdb92b30b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Go ahead and have that cup of coffee, maybe even several more. New research shows it may boost chances for a longer life, even for those who down at least eight cup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under pressure, afraid to take bathroom breaks? Inside AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon/under-pressure-afraid-to-take-bathroom-breaks-inside-amazons-fast-paced-warehouse-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon warehouse workers afraid to go to the bathroom or take a sick day. Unattainable productivity targets. Constant surveillance. How accurate is author James Bloodworth’s portrayal? A tour in Kent delivers some answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran calls for calm after water protests, clashes...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180701133006-34bvj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-UNREST/ (PIX, TV):Iran calls for calm after water protests, clashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small butcher shop renaissance...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article213600564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of downturn, Miami's butcher shops and carnicerias are fighting back against big box convenience with quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL GET SLAMMED WITH TAXES...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/devin-nunes-to-lebron-james-prepare-to-pay-the-highest-taxes-you-ever-have-in-your-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Devin Nunes, R-Calif., late Sunday warned LeBron James that he's about to get hit with a huge tax bill after signing a four-year deal with the Los Angeles Lakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman found alive inside mortuary refrigerator...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/world/ny-news-woman-alive-morgue-south-africa-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After she was declared dead following a car accident, a South African woman was mistakenly brought to the morgue and stored in a fridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI STING OP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/demetrius-pitts-charged-cleveland-bomb-plot-after-fbi-sting-n888336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's no indication the Ohio man could have carried off an attack himself</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon starts 'cyber carrier' to launch attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fifthdomain.com/dod/cybercom/2018/06/29/cyber-command-moves-closer-to-a-major-new-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fifthdomain.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal for the next generation cyber operations platform went out to industry recently, however, details are scarce.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
