<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>White House ordered top-secret system upgraded to prevent leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/01/white-house-trump-leaks-code-015194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY LAWYERS UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/01/politics/giuliani-hires-watergate-prosecutor/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida attorney Jon Sale, who worked as an assistant prosecutor on the legal team investigating the Watergate scandal, is representing Rudy Giuliani in the matter of the congressional impeachment inquiry, Giuliani and Sale both confirmed to CNN on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLPHINS Stadium Vendor Charges Fan $724 For 2 Beers...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/10/01/hard-rock-stadium-beer-vendor-accused-of-using-personal-card-reader-to-charge-fan-724-for-2-beers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A football fan who went to see the Los Angeles Chargers beat the Miami Dolphins at Hard Rock Stadium on Sunday was shocked when he received a message from his credit card company saying he had just been charged $724 for two beers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARTIAN SOUNDS CAPTURED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0c9f5e3d9a2240a69ea73dcf317b7b89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA's InSight lander on Mars has captured the low rumble of marsquakes and a symphony of other otherworldly sounds. Scientists released an audio sampling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer banned 3 years for obscene gesture...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2019/10/01/bio-kim-korean-tour-obscene-gesture/40229311/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Korean Professional Golfers Association suspended Bio Kim for three years for making an obscene gesture towards the gallery during a final round.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runner killed by lightning as he finishes 50k race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/runner-killed-by-lightning-while-finishing-50k-race-in-southeast-kansas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A runner has been killed by lightning as he was about to finish a 50 kilometer (31.07 miles) race in southeast Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian alcohol consumption down 43%...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-49892339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 43% decline follows a series of alcohol-control measures implemented by the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters: Trump should be 'imprisoned &amp; placed in solitary confinement'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/463859-maxine-waters-trump-should-be-imprisoned-and-placed-in-solitary-confinement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan, Harry sue MAIL ON SUNDAY over publication of private letter...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/meghan-and-harry-to-sue-mail-on-sunday-over-publication-of-private-letter-11824783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry issued a powerful statement criticising some of the press for "continual misrepresentations" of his wife, Meghan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sword-wielding student kills 1, wounds 9 at Finland school...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5048f34db7a408295d543c35e2fb5b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — A man wielding a sword and a firearm killed a woman and wounded nine others Tuesday at a vocational school inside a shopping center in central Finland, police said. The attacker...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In memorializing Khashoggi, WASH POST gives platform to top jailer of reporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/1/memorializing-jamal-khashoggi-washington-post-give/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been a year since the murder of the Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in Istanbul. Mr. Khashoggi wore many professional hats throughout his career, one of which was as a freelance online blogger for Washington’s other newspaper — I believe it’s called the “Post?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When NASA finds life on Mars, world may not be ready, agency chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/30/us/nasa-life-on-mars-jim-green-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's next mission to Mars will be its most advanced yet. But if scientists discover there was once life -- or there is life -- on the Red Planet, will the public be able to handle such an extraterrestrial concept?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges Now Offering Degrees In Esports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/college-esports-universities-launch-degrees-in-esports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shenandoah University and The Ohio State University are among training students to enter the growing esports field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH!</title>
      <link>https://1010wins.radio.com/articles/woman-enters-exhibit-dances-front-lion-bronx-zoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;1010wins.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (1010 WINS) -- A woman that climbed over the safety barrier and entered the African lion exhibit at the Bronx Zoo over the weekend can be seen waving and dancing in front of one of the lions in a video posted to Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar after research claims red meat poses no health risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/food/2019/sep/30/research-red-meat-poses-no-health-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One expert says findings by international experts represent ‘egregious abuse of evidence’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark trends in American society call for 'spiritual warfare'?</title>
      <link>https://www.patheos.com/blogs/thefreethinker/2019/10/dark-trends-in-american-society-call-for-greater-spiritual-warfare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.patheos.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Oregon exorcist, who claims he has had the ability to conquer satanic forces since he was four, warned last week that modern American society, with its interest in things such as drugs and ouija boards, needs to take demonic possession more seriously. "Archbishop" James Cloud, above, insisted that, "as the years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Woman climbs into Bronx Zoo exhibit, taunts lion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Bronx-Zoo-Lion-561880561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman climbed over a visitor safety barrier at the Bronx Zoo's African lion exhibit over the weekend, according to the zoo and video of the encounter that was posted online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Congratulates Communist China on Its 70th Anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/while-trump-congratulates-communist-china-on-its-70th-anniversary-senate-republicans-condemn-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy years ago today, Mao Zedong declared the People’s Republic of China after his Communist forces had conquered most of the mainland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRASSLEY: Whistleblower Followed Law and Should Be Heard...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/grassley-whistleblower-followed-the-law-and-should-be-heard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal policy wasn’t secretly changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Robots hurting your pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-10-01/robots-are-hurting-u-s-workers-wages-regional-fed-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Sets Second American Civil War TV Series For 2020...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/10/ava-duvernay-hbo-max-pilot-dmz-roberto-patino-1202749125/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hot off a big Emmy win for When They See Us, Ava DuVernay is set to launch her second project based on a DC Comics property Already primed to directed a big-screen adaptation of Jack Kirby’s New Go…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE FIRES BACK!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/elizabeth-warren-tears-into-facebook-over-leaked-mark-zuckerberg-audio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook CEO railed against the presidential candidate’s plan to break up big tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Raises Massive $25 Million, Largest Of Cycle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-raises-massive-dollar253-million-in-third-quarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quarter is among his best in both presidential campaigns he’s run and perhaps the largest of the 2020 cycle thus far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four earthquakes in 13 hours rattle Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article235663322.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quake swarm hits San Francisco area with 5 shakes in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/california/article235664912.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani's Ukraine ally leaves trail of debts:  'He conned us from day one'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article235626327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St starting to believe she may win nomination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/01/elizabeth-warrens-rise-has-some-analysts-uneasy-on-health-care-tech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raymond James says Wall Street is underestimating Elizabeth Warren's odds of winning the White House in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Captured After 17 Years Living in Cave...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/crime/2019/09/30/chinese-fugitive-captured-after-17-years-living-cave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Convicted human trafficker Song Jiang was apprehended on September 19, after 17 years spent hiding alone in a remote cave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAT FALLS FROM WHITE HOUSE CEILING!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/463815-reporters-scramble-after-mouse-falls-from-white-house-ceiling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House reporters were sent into a panic Tuesday morning after a mouse fell from the ceiling of the press booth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodel confronts prankster who stormed Paris runway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/01/gigi-hadid-confronts-crasher-who-stormed-chanel-runway-at-paris-fashion-week/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gigi Hadid escorted her off the stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon fired official trying to cut billions in waste...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-promised-to-save-billions-of-dollars-on-military-contracts-then-the-pentagon-pushed-out-the-official-responsible-for-doing-that-090005221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shay Assad was known as the Defense Department’s toughest contract negotiator and was praised for saving the government billions. Yet within two years of Donald Trump’s entrance into the White House, Assad would be removed from his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French ex-president Sarkozy to face trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/french-ex-president-sarkozy-face-campaign-finance-trial-135003150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French court on Tuesday ordered Nicolas Sarkozy to stand trial for illicit campaign financing, adding to the ex-president's legal woes as he also prepares to answer charges of exerting pressure on a judge. Sarkozy, 64, lost his final appeal to France's highest criminal court, and risks a year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Audience Chants 'Lock HIM Up'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-colbert-crowd-chants-lock-him-hillary-begins-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I created a monster — I apologize’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Gas Prices Soar Past $4...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/09/30/southern-california-los-angeles-4-dollar-gas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks of daily price hikes have sent the average price of a gallon of self-serve regular gasoline well over the $4 mark across the region, even in outlying areas where prices are usually cheaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Sentences U.S. Spies to Death...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-issues-death-prison-sentences-for-accused-u-s-spies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has issued a death sentence for an individual it has accused of spying for the United States, according to the Islamic Republic's judiciary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Pompeo accuses Dems of bullying; Rejects subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d98be4ffbaa4462b9454cca0a8a7e88a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Secretary of State Mike Pompeo on Tuesday declared that House Democrats are trying to "intimidate, bully and treat improperly" five current and former career officials in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off message: A Republican takes heat for impeachment remarks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8f2925fda234310b0eb3e795e6d076f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — GOP Rep. Mark Amodei's comment seemed harmless enough. Asked what he thought of the Democrats' impeachment probe into President Donald Trump, the Nevada Republican gave reporters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can posture devices pull you out of constant slump?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/article/Can-these-posture-devices-pull-you-out-of-your-14482655.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like a lot of people, I spend much of my workday staring at various screens - and, like a lot of people, I have the back and neck issues to prove it. Hunching and its associated symptoms are a hallmark of the digital age. Though I have a makeshift ergonomic setup in my home office, I often catch myself with my chin jutting forward as I lean toward my laptop - despite the fact that I'm a regular Pilates student and former yoga teacher.  Clearly, my athletic training hasn't done enough to reinforce good habits. So, searching for a path to better posture, I spoke with two doctors about the problem and tried a few gadgets that promised to help me straighten things out.  "We get into this stooped posture to get our faces close to the screen, which puts a lot of unnatural stress on the cervical spine," says Kaliq Chang, a double board-certified physician in interventional pain management and anesthesiology with Atlantic Spine Center in West Orange, New Jersey. Ideally, when you're sitting at your desk in front of a computer monitor, "You're meant to have the weight of your head situated over your neck in a manner that forces your chest out and your shoulders back, which requires having a monitor close to eye level," Chang says.  When you hunch forward, whether at your desk or looking at your phone on the couch, the muscles in your neck and back extend while the ones in the front contract; over time, this can create an imbalance where they pull on one another unevenly. The effect would be minimal if we were only putting our necks and backs in awkward positions for minutes at a time, but people often spend hours out of whack.  "That's where the problem lies," says Charla Fischer, an orthopedic surgeon at New York University's Langone Spine Center. When muscles are stretched in uncomfortable ways for prolonged periods of time,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: U.S. Navy Isn't Ready to Take On Iran...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/09/30/the-u-s-navy-isnt-ready-to-take-on-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s why, for now, tough talk may remain just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Wobbles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-factory-gauge-sinks-10-140000670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Explore what’s moving the global economy in the new season of the Stephanomics podcast. Subscribe via Pocket Cast or iTunes.A measure of U.S. manufacturing unexpectedly fell deeper into contraction, posting the weakest reading since the end of the last recession as a global slowdown and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMCAST emerges as new GOOGLE antitrust foe?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-comcast-alphabet-antitrust-exclusive/exclusive-comcast-emerges-as-new-google-antitrust-foe-sources-idUSKBN1WG3J7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast Corp , one of America’s largest media and communications companies, is w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD TO DEPLOY OFFICERS FOR 'JOKER' OPENING...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/joker-nypd-have-additional-officers-at-theaters-opening-weekend-1244515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To date, there have been no "credible threats" connected to Todd Phillips' R-rated take on the DC character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery object hovering over NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-object-likened-death-star-20377926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strange object supposedly changed colour as it emerged in the night sky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In leaked audio, Zuckerberg rallies FACEBOOK against critics, competitors, Elizabeth Warren...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/10/1/20756701/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-leak-audio-ftc-antitrust-elizabeth-warren-tiktok-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook employees are frustrated with the direction of the company, and they’re pressing Zuckerberg for answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet users must actively consent to use of cookies, EU court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-court-cookies/internet-users-must-actively-consent-to-use-of-cookies-eu-court-rules-idUSKBN1WG3NF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet users must actively consent to companies storing cookies that are used ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several injured in deadly 'sword' attack at Finnish college...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/several-injured-deadly-sword-attack-124421897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person was killed and 10 injured in an attack at a vocational college in eastern Finland on Tuesday, police said, as local media quoted witnesses as saying a young man with a sword had burst into a classroom. The suspected attacker, who was detained, was among the injured in the town of Kuopio, police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Doctor dogs' sniff out cancer, anxiety, superbugs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/30/doctor-dogs-can-sniff-out-cancer-anxiety-and-superbugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Danielle Brooks, 23, was diagnosed with narcolepsy at age 15, her peers taunted her with the nickname Bobblehead — how she looked nodding off. But since receiving her service dog, Rollo, in 20…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Gigi Hadid confronts gatecrasher on CHANEL Paris catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/model-gigi-hadid-confronts-gatecrasher-chanels-paris-catwalk-03202535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moria is hell': Asylum seekers protest conditions at Greek camp...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191001121559-5t4cg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EUROPE-MIGRANTS/GREECE-LESBOS-PROTEST (PIX, TV):'Moria is hell': asylum seekers protest conditions at Greek camp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People Living Near Coast Happier; Fewer Mental Health Disorders...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/seaside-serenity-study-finds-living-near-a-coast-linked-to-improved-mental-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that living close to the coast may have long-lasting benefits and supports better overall mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tears as military extravaganza stirs patriotic passion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-anniversary-reactions/tears-as-chinas-military-extravaganza-stirs-patriotic-passion-idUSKBN1WG3FN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the roar of tanks rolling through a residential street in central Beijing a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Mid-Century Modernism Architecture Remains Global Success...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/photo-essays/2019-10-01/why-mid-century-modernism-architecture-remains-a-global-success</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Man: Tom Cruise meets president in Kiev...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ukraine-man-tom-cruise-meets-president-kiev113519927.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company starts mass production of humanoids -- that look like you!</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/business/469969-russian-human-like-android/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian startup has launched serial production of unique life-like robots that not only look the way you want and mimic facial expressions, but are also able to work for you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Is Moment Maddow Has Been Waiting For...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/10/01/this-is-the-moment-rachel-maddow-has-been-waiting-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - Rachel Maddow was trying to get to work. She only had to get from the glass door of her doctor’s office to the tinted-windowed S.U.V. that was idling at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrows and smartphones: Daily life of Amazon tribe...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/71f76164eb2f4b9aa887c17a655ec93c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALTO RIO GUAMA INDIGENOUS RESERVE, Brazil (AP) — They hunt with bows and arrows, fish for piranhas and gather wild plants, while some watch soap operas on TV or check the internet on phones inside...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom accused of making up toddler's medical problems, forcing unneeded surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article235483297.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ASKS AUSTRALIAN PM TO HELP DISCREDIT MUELLER</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-pressed-australian-leader-to-help-barr-investigate-mueller-inquirys-origins/ar-AAI4KVh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi says nation leads the world...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/on-eve-of-china-s-th-anniversary-parade-president-xi/article_fffd82bb-6a8d-572f-b14e-f57419eacb5e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING — The No. 1 rule for media attending a grand banquet at the Great Hall of the People on the eve of the 70th anniversary of the People’s Republic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran had no family to bury him. He won't be laid to rest alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/local/article235620562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China unveils doomsday nuke that can strike  USA in 30 minutes!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10039105/china-set-to-unveil-dongfeng-41-nuke-that-can-strike-us-in-30-minutes-at-70th-anniverary-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA will unveil the “ultimate doomsday weapon” on Tuesday during one of the nation’s biggest military parades, say worrying reports. The super-nuke is expected to take centre stage at a huge arms…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Impeachment Plan Is the Opposite of Clinton...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/09/trumps-impeachment-plan-opposite-clintons/599095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the Lewinsky scandal, Clinton focused on doing his job. Trump isn’t even pretending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 earthquakes hit Missouri in less than an hour... </title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article235639232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy killed during exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/reports-tucson-area-man-accused-of-killing-his-son-while-trying-to-exorcise-a-demon-from-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man in the Tucson area admitted to killing his son while trying to exorcise a demon from him, according to media reports there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial blood 'better than the real thing' made in lab by scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/artificial-blood-better-real-thing-20376298  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Defense Medical College have revealed the all-purpose blood which they created in a lab</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists stunned after unearthing 3,000-year-old penis statue used by cult...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/archaeologists-stunned-after-unearthing-3000-20375086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The girthy penis rock is 21 inches tall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Why Trump's Removal Wouldn't Lead to 'Civil War'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-trumps-removal-wouldnt-lead-194533639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- President Donald Trump warns that removing him from office would “cause a Civil War-like fracture in this Nation from which our Country will never heal.” He is quoting Robert Jeffress, a prominent evangelical supporter, who also says that Democrats are trying to remove Trump from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Men Drawn Into Focus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-allies-giuliani-pompeo-barr-220834158.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s personal lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, his Secretary of State Michael Pompeo and Attorney General William Barr were all drawn deeper into the House impeachment inquiry after new details of the administration’s foreign contacts emerged on Monday.Three House committees said they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global opera legend Jessye Norman dies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/global-opera-legend-jessye-norman-dies-74-family-225031290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Superstar singer Jessye Norman, an American soprano who showcased her majestic yet intimate voice at opera houses and orchestras around the world, died Monday, her family said. One of the contemporary era's most revered opera singers, the Grammy-winner died "surrounded by loved ones" at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startup eyes launch of electric helicopter taxis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-aviation-volocopter-singapore/volocopter-eyes-launch-of-its-electric-helicopter-taxis-in-singapore-idUSKBN1WF0ZO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German startup Volocopter said Singapore is emerging as one of the most likely d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR ASKED FOREIGN OFFICIALS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/attorney-general-barr-personally-asked-foreign-officials-to-aid-inquiry-into-cia-fbi-activities-in-2016/ar-AAI4Q6S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How risky is eating red meat? New papers provoke controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.krmg.com/news/national/how-risky-eating-red-meat-new-papers-provoke-controversy/GPv56ebSK9vIW7FaDd44jI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krmg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;102.3 KRMG Tulsa's News &amp; Talk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Handful of nuts a day prevents weight gain...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/world/eat-this-amount-nuts-day-prevent-weight-gain-study-suggests/bpzBW2Io3or9dqHOtbUG6O/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nuts have quite a few health benefits, including weight loss, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern Baptists ready to put spotlight on sex-abuse crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d338c01ad6bc475b8a34225ae1eae68d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entangled in a multifaceted sex-abuse crisis, the Southern Baptist Convention is preparing to host a high-profile conference on the topic that has kindled skepticism even among some of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter of adults haven't read book in past year...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/30/more-than-a-quarter-of-us-adults-have-not-read-a-book-in-past-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a quarter of US adults say they haven’t read a book — either in whole or in part and whether in print or electronic form — in the past year, according to a new survey. Twenty-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US violent crime down again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-violent-crime-down-again-2018-says-fbi-175314395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Violent crime in the United States fell for a second straight year in 2018, underscoring a long-term downward trend that was briefly interrupted by an uptick in 2015 and 2016, the FBI said Monday. The Federal Bureau of Investigation said there were some 1.2 million violent crimes in 2018, down 3.3 percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo creates panic with missing cougar alert...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/cougar-escapes-kansas-zoo/story?id=65959311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cougar escaped from a zoo in Kansas on Monday morning, officials said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
