<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tech glitches, swamped websites impede distribution...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/tech-glitches-swamped-websites-impede-us-vaccine-distribution/article_8d70b24b-784c-56c8-86db-c3bdcdf52455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mississippi, an online vaccine registration system buckled in a sudden onslaught of traffic. Officials at a local health department in Georgia had to resort to counting every dose they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rita Moreno Rages Against Persistent Hollywood Racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/rita-moreno-hollywood-racism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rita Moreno, the subject of a new documentary premiering at Sundance, let loose on Hollywood racism against the Latinx community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Donald know what was about to happen?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/536612-did-trump-know-what-was-about-to-happen-jan-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have the tools to obtain the information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene touts Trump call amid growing backlash...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/536617-marjorie-taylor-greene-touts-trump-call-amid-growing-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.) said Saturday that she spoke with former President Trump as she faces growing bipartisan criticism over past social media posts in which she expressed support for violence against Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump Focus on Antifa Distracted Attention From Far-Right Threat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/30/how-trumps-focus-on-antifa-distracted-attention-from-the-far-right-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As racial justice protests erupted nationwide last year, President Donald J. Trump, struggling to find a winning campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump Focus on Antifa Distracted Attention From Far-Right Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/01/30/us/politics/trump-right-wing-domestic-terrorism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement shifted resources last year in response to Donald Trump’s insistence that the radical left endangered the country. Meanwhile, right-wing extremism was building ominously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How she rose with support from key Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/How-Rep-Marjorie-Taylor-Greene-promoter-of-15910788.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As Marjorie Taylor Greene entered a runoff last year to be the Republican nominee for a U.S. House seat in Georgia, her opponent sounded the alarm. He warned top party officials that she had made a series of dangerous, baseless claims, and that she would tear apart the GOP if she won.  But Greene's widely reported comments about the radical ideology of QAnon and other matters had not stopped a coterie of top Republicans from urging her to run for the seat representing a deeply conservative district in north Georgia, and then issuing fervent endorsements.  Greene was "exactly the kind of fighter needed in Washington to stand with me against the radical left," declared Rep. Jim Jordan, R-Ohio, a founding member of the conservative House Freedom Caucus. Debbie Meadows, who ran an influential political action committee and whose husband, Mark Meadows, became Trump's chief of staff, gushed, "We cannot wait to welcome her to Congress."  Greene trounced neurosurgeon John Cowan in the runoff and easily won in the fall - paving the way for her emergence as a symbol of the radicalized ideology that believes in QAnon, which inspired the pro-Trump rioters who stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6 and has enveloped much of the Republican Party while sparking fears of additional violence.  While some Republicans have tried to portray Greene as a political anomaly, her ascent demonstrates the extent to which key party leaders embraced her and propelled her to victory despite her well-documented history of spreading false claims and violent rhetoric. Critical to Greene's success was the early intervention on her behalf by some of the party's most staunchly pro-Trump figures and Greene's ability to tap into the far-right online world where baseless claims thrive.  "She really got ingratiated with the House Freedom Caucus, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious blogger who made bitcoin donation killed self in hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9202857/French-blogger-killed-drugs-overdose-day-520-000-Capitol-rioters-donation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurent Bachelier, 35, was a mysterious French blogger who donated $520,000 to far-right organisations on December 8 killed himself later that day at the Hyatt Regency Etoile Paris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major nor'easter developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/winter-storm-bearing-down-on-mid-atlantic-and-northeast/890164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather meteorologists break down where the storm will head across the eastern U.S., and how forces in the atmosphere will dictate which places see heavy snow – and which places could miss out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman infected after SECOND shot..</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/coronavirus/rep-stephen-lynch-tests-positive-for-covid-19/2288818/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcboston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Stephen Lynch, D-Mass., has tested positive for COVID-19, his office announced Friday. Lynch was tested for coronavirus after a staff member in his office tested positive earlier in the week. The congressman received his positive test Friday afternoon. A statement from Pfizer said that it can take seven days for protection from the second dose to kick in. However,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears deadly fungus could be next global medical emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/fears-deadly-fungus-could-next-23367018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious fungus first identified in 2009, that one expert describes as 'a creature from the black lagoon', could represent the next major global health menace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA BRACES FOR PROTESTS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-moscow-coronavirus-pandemic-arrests-germany-5d28e7a7975254a038bc909a3086663b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian police have issued a strong warning against participating in protests planned for Sunday to call for the release of jailed opposition leader Alexei Navalny, the Kremlin's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing favorites? Hospital boards, donors dosed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-washington-coronavirus-pandemic-russ-seattle-c453fc84e9378ba4259715d3e0ad50d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While millions of Americans wait for the COVID-19 vaccine, hospital board members, their trustees and donors around the country have gotten early access to the scarce drug or offers for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As California cases fall, more people than ever dying...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-coronavirus-pandemic-ea238ef75c3f5a6a7cabb6dc8b353a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — As a hospice nurse, Antonio Espinoza worked to ease people’s passage into death. Just 36 years old, it seemed unlikely he soon would be on that journey. But when the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden first 10 days dominated by jab mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/01/30/biden-covid-vaccine-states-463953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s team is still trying to locate upwards of 20 million vaccine doses that have been sent to states — a mystery that has hampered plans to speed up the national vaccination effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cruise branded 'nightmare' as new rules distress film crew...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/tom-cruise-branded-a-nightmare-23411657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh issues have struck the troubled production after filming moved to the United Arab Emirates – with UK crew worried over how they will return home after Covid travel corridors were slammed shut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: War fears as Chinese jets simulate attack on US carrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1391053/World-War-3-news-Taiwan-Chinese-China-USS-Theodore-Roosevelt-conflict-Joe-Biden-ont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEARS of open war between the United States and China surged after Chinese fighter jets carried out mock missile strikes on a US aircraft carrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDS origin revealed? First person infected caught virus hunting chimps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9202531/First-HIV-case-soldier-World-War-One-caught-virus-hunting-chimps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is what happens when Buddhist nun joins heavy metal band...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/happens-buddhist-nun-joins-heavy-213130305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's quite a contrasting sight on stage alongside the other members of the band, some in goth makeup, Grim Reaper robes and fake blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Who pours the kibble?' And other answers about daily life for dogs in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Who-pours-the-kibble-And-other-answers-about-15910495.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After a four-year vacancy, the position of DOTUS was filled this week by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady out to join Robertson, Robinson in exclusive club...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-mlb-nba-football-super-bowl-304604f4236498044dc65b3d3fb759a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long before fleeing the New England winters for the Florida sunshine, Tom Brady knew exactly how it felt when a superstar changed teams. Brady was a sophomore at Junipero Serra High School...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD Meteoric Rise Feels Pull of Wall St Physics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/robinhood-meteoric-rise-feels-pull-123007639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Robinhood Markets’ emergency ban on trading eight stocks this week ignited rage across the political spectrum, swiftly drew state and federal scrutiny and sent furious customers into the arms of competitors.That was Thursday. By Friday afternoon, it was limiting purchases of shares in 23 companies. Soon, it was about 50.A drama that began with a quirky jump in GameStop Corp.’s shares this month has grown into a full-blown rebellion of retail investors against Wall Street’s status quo and left Robinhood, long their beloved brokerage, caught between customers and the cold demands of finance’s gatekeepers. Mounting strains on the firm forced it to grab more than $1 billion in fresh capital and hundreds of millions more in loans.The startup, which set out to “to democratize finance for all,” is now in the awkward position of telling clients they can’t buy whatever they want. An online job ad hints at the complexities the Silicon Valley company faces, with Robinhood seeking a federal lobbyist.“Obviously this is not a good position for a brokerage firm to be in,” said James Angel, an associate professor at Georgetown University. “No firm wants to turn down customers who want to use their service. I’d be shocked if that lasted very long.”In a blog post Friday night, the firm described the restrictions as necessary and temporary.“It was not because we wanted to stop people from buying these stocks,” Robinhood said of its decision to impose limits. “Our goal is to enable purchasing for all securities on our platform. This is a dynamic, volatile market, and we have and may continue to take action to make sure we meet our requirements as a broker so we can continue to serve our customers for the long term.”A company spokeswoman declined to comment beyond the blog post.‘Trading and Confetti’At the center of all the controversy is Robinhood’s highly polished app, which has lured millions of investors with an experience that seemed to defy Wall Street’s usual physics. With a focus on immediacy, the firm lets new arrivals start trading as soon as they set up a bank transfer. It awards them a free stock for signing up. And then there’s the shiniest lure of all: No fee for trades.It’s no wonder Robinhood created legions of fans who expect to buy stocks, options and even cryptocurrencies with little sensation of guardrails. But this week, that culture slammed into reality. Wall Street trading is a strictly regulated business that can require brokerages to have mountains of cash available.After Robinhood’s customers picked a fight with hedge funds by sending shares of GameStop and other beaten-down companies into the stratosphere, the market’s central clearing hub required the firm to post much more collateral to limit the risk such volatility can pose to the system. In its blog post, Robinhood said the deposits it had to make for equities jumped 10-fold during the week.That meant Robinhood needed more money. And to keep its burden from getting bigger, the firm -- like some others -- began restricting certain trades. Initially, it barred purchases of some of the most volatile stocks. Though it later allowed them in limited amounts, the list of tickers grew. As of Friday night, customers hoping to buy GameStop were allowed one share.“What Robinhood promised was free trading and confetti when you trade,” said Georgetown’s Angel, who specializes in market structure. But the financial system’s rules apply everywhere. Any investors considering leaving Robinhood to further the crusade they started there “will find, at the end of the day, most other brokers are pretty much the same.”(Angel humbly noted he put a small short on GameStop mid-week only to watch the price double.)‘Growing Pains’Founded in 2013, Robinhood courted long-ignored small-dollar and novice investors with innovations including its zero-commission promise. It offered, for example, fractional stocks to let people who can’t afford to pay around $800 for a share of Tesla Inc. to buy just a piece of one instead. Those features became standard in the industry: free trading is the norm, and Charles Schwab Corp. and Fidelity Investments allow customers to buy stock “slices” too.As the coronavirus pandemic erupted last year, retail investors flooded into the market, looking to earn extra cash and pass time during lockdowns. Robinhood’s customer base surged beyond 13 million. Even amid this week’s turbulence, its app has dominated download rankings. But at times, its popularity has outpaced the build-out of its operations.The firm repeatedly suffered outages as the coronavirus pandemic erupted in the U.S. last year and sent markets into a tailspin. Later in the year, when hackers accessed thousands of accounts, panicked users discovered the firm had no phone number for customer service.Financial-technology disruptors need to learn the intricacies of Wall Street’s mechanics and compliance systems faster, said Jim Toes, head of the Security Traders Association.“We’ve got to find a way to get those growing pains to occur in a much shorter window,” Toes said in an interview on Friday. “We have a lot of fintech companies coming into our marketplace where the in-house expertise is more around technology.”Clients’ CampaignIn recent months, Robinhood has been enlisting legal help, recruiting attorneys from Goldman Sachs Group Inc., Wells Fargo &amp; Co., Schwab’s TD Ameritrade and WilmerHale, a law firm known for its securities-law expertise.But this week’s rush for cash contrasted with past snapshots of the firm’s financial health.Robinhood’s subsidiary that handles trading reported ample capital in a mid-year financial statement. At the end of June, the broker-dealer unit had 14 times the minimum level required by Securities and Exchange Commission rules for capital relative to what trading customers owe. That level exceeded those of larger competitors. The trading unit of Charles Schwab’s TD Ameritrade, for example, had six times the SEC minimum at Sept. 30.A few months ago, groups of enthusiasts on Reddit began laying the groundwork for the frenzy that swept up Robinhood this week. In online postings, they identified favored short positions by hedge funds, eventually setting in motion a squeeze by bidding up shares of GameStop and AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc. to inflict billions of dollars in losses on money managers.The degree to which traders relied on Robinhood to carry out their strategy is visible in data from Atom Finance, an investment researcher that plugs into its users’ brokerage accounts.Just over half of Atom’s users who made trades at Robinhood on Wednesday were active in the volatile stocks that the brokerage ended up restricting one day later. About 17% of users adjusted bets on GameStop, and 25% on AMC.DTCC’s DemandsBut the stock moves had other repercussions. By around 10 a.m. on Thursday, the Depository Trust &amp; Clearing Corp. demanded significantly more collateral from member brokers, prompting Robinhood and rivals to slam the brakes on certain trades. By the end of the day, industry-wide collateral requirements jumped to $33.5 billion from $26 billion -- an already elevated level.Robinhood drew at least several hundred million dollars from bank credit lines, a person with knowledge of the situation said that day. And several of its venture investors participated in a financing round. Robinhood has said it raised more than $1 billion, which it called “a strong sign of confidence from investors that will help us continue to further serve our customers.”The company has been planning to hold an initial public offering this year. This week’s fundraising, structured as a convertible note, was priced at a discounted percentage to the upcoming IPO, according to people familiar with the matter, who asked not to be identified because the information was private.Index Ventures, Ribbit Capital and Sequoia Capital were among the venture investors involved in the effort, the people said. The final size of the financing is still being determined, one of the people said.‘Rapidly Shifting Priorities’While Robinhood works to shore up its finances, customers are furious.At least 18 lawsuits have been filed against the firm in California, Connecticut, Florida, Illinois, New Jersey, Oregon, Pennsylvania and Texas, mostly alleging trading limits amounted to a breach of contract.Robinhood also was among a slate of entities issued a civil investigative demand by Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton because of this week’s investor restrictions. New York Attorney General Letitia James said she’s reviewing the brokerage’s actions. The SEC said it, too, is examining brokerages’ decisions to limit buying.“There has been a lot of misinformation out there about why Robinhood did this,” Robinhood Chief Executive Officer Vlad Tenev told Bloomberg Television in an interview this week. “We first and foremost did it to protect the firm and our customers.”Robinhood’s job posting for a lobbyist underscores how much work it has ahead to patch things up with those clients and authorities.“We are looking for a highly adaptable and collaborative person,” the ad reads. Someone “who can handle ambiguity and rapidly shifting priorities with flexibility and patience.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asylum camp swells at U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210130005928-phd9x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/BIDEN (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-As asylum camp swells at U.S.-Mexico border, Biden aide calls for patience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bomb-making manuals' found in home of member...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210130000726-eznwu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/PROTESTS-ARRESTS (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-'Bomb-making manuals' found in home of Proud Boy who stormed U.S. Capitol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Critics of Many Stripes Rally Around Him...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/30/as-protests-grip-russia-putin-critics-of-many-stripes-rally-around-navalny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — Aleksandr Pasechnik, a socialist, sees the jailed opposition leader Aleksei A. Navalny as part of the “liberal intelligentsia.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man's penis held for ransom by hackers who took control of digital chastity belt...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/bloke-penis-held-ransom-hackers-23412940</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qiui, the company which makes the Cellmate cage, says it believes that a true chastity experience is one that 'does not allow the wearer to have any control over'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach reviewing residency...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/536593-palm-beach-reviewing-trumps-residency-at-mar-a-lago</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The town of Palm Beach, Fla. confirmed to The Hill Friday that it's performing a legal review of former President Trump's residency at Mar-a-Lago after suggesting that they might do so in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC mandates masks for planes, public transportation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/536602-cdc-mandates-masks-for-planes-and-other-public-transportation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) issued a sweeping order late Friday that mandates the use of masks on airplanes and other public transportation as the U.S. seeks to contain the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Producer SOPHIE Dies in Tragic Accident...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/sophie-has-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The visionary producer, who was 34, died in a sudden accident in Athens, Greece</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tragic Curse of Being 'Most Beautiful Boy in World'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-tragic-curse-of-being-the-most-beautiful-boy-in-the-world </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAE to offer citizenship to select expats in rare move for Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210130-uae-to-offer-citizenship-to-select-expats-in-rare-move-for-gulf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UAE to offer citizenship to select expats in rare move for Gulf</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese fighter jets, bombers simulate attack on US aircraft carrier near Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://theaviationist.com/2021/01/29/chinese-h-6-bombers-heard-on-radio-confirming-orders-for-simulated-attack-on-u-s-aircraft-carrier-near-taiwan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theaviationist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsurprisingly, the package of 13 Chinese combat aircraft, (including eight H-6 bombers) entering Taiwan’s ADIZ last Saturday were carrying out a mock attack on USS Theodore Roosevelt. As alr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds protest Amazon expansion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-protest-amazon-expansion-france-130427463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds rallied in several French towns and cities Saturday in protests called by anti-capitalist and environmental groups against Amazon, including at one site where the US e-commerce giant plans a massive warehouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic movies shot during pandemic hit SUNDANCE...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/apocalyptic-movies-shot-during-pandemic-054651512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A virus horror and a last-day-on-Earth comedy -- both entirely devised, shot and edited during the pandemic -- brought an apocalyptic flavor Friday to the Sundance film festival, which has moved online due to Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's vaccine delays symbolize national decline for some...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/France-s-vaccine-delays-symbolize-national-15910410.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS - France's Pasteur Institute this week abandoned its project to develop a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman charged in riot said she wanted to shoot Pelosi 'in the friggin' brain'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Woman-charged-in-Capitol-riot-said-she-wanted-to-15909972.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Federal authorities arrested two women in Pennsylvania on Friday on charges...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warehouse orgy with 100 men and women raided in Paris!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/warehouse-orgy-100-men-women-23412294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fined up to 100 people and arrested three as they broke up an orgy in Collegien, Paris, which was in breach of current rules to stop the spread of Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Sinatra: My advice is don't get married so young. Have affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/music/features/nancy-sinatra-interview-marriage-frank-sinatra-b1794647.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sixties icon is Hollywood royalty but she rarely gets given the credit for paving the way for women in pop. She talks to Kate Hutchinson about regret, about the art of reinvention, being shunned by Stevie Nicks and driving a hard bargain with Hugh Hefner</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OJ GETS ONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2236253/oj-simpson-trolled-getting-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OJ Simpson was brutally trolled online after he shared a photo of himself getting a Covid vaccine while wearing a “The Juice” mask. Twitter users had jokes and complaints, with many bri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUMPING THE LINE:  Guantanamo inmates to get Covid jab, including alleged 9/11 mastermind...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2235958/911-mastermind-guantanamo-bay-inmates-covid-vaccine-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ALLEGED terrorist behind 9/11 and other detainees at Guantanamo Bay will get Covid-19 vaccines as soon as next week – before most Americans. Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, the supposed principal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems building elaborate, emotionally charged Impeachment case against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-democrats-building-elaborate-emotionally-charged-case-against-trump/ar-BB1ddVdf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House managers are scouring for new video evidence and police witnesses, even as the Senate tries to limit former president Donald Trump’s impeachment trial to a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercuts Optimism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/covid-mutations-undercut-optimism-even-as-more-vaccines-get-near/ar-BB1ddUW7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world could be on the verge of having two more vaccines to fight the Covid-19 pandemic, but virus variants popping up worldwide are forcing companies that make the shots to develop boosters for a disease that could remain active for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLE TROUBLE: DOW BELOW 30,000</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/stock-futures-decline-as-volatile-wall-street-week-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heightened speculative trading by retail investors continued to unnerve the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED STILL BAILING OUT</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-daly-pushes-back-against-234022779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. central bank should not prematurely withdraw pandemic support for the U.S. economy just because some people are getting rich in the stock market, said San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly.“We’re building this bridge, which is barely having many communities hang on, and the stock market is running pretty good and many people who already have money are getting more money,” she said Friday during a virtual discussion hosted by the Stanford Graduate School of Business.“I am not willing to pull that bridge away and injure, in my judgment, the livelihoods of people -- because they don’t have jobs, they don’t have income, they don’t have wage growth -- simply to ensure that some people who already have stock market wealth don’t get more.”Daly, who votes on monetary policy this year, was asked to comment on the frenzy around GameStop Corp.’s meteoric stock-price rise. Some people have blamed the central bank’s ultra-easy policy for fanning a bubble in financial markets, but policy makers have shown no inclination so far to step back.The Fed held interest rates near zero at its meeting this week and repeated an assurance it would continue its massive monetary assistance for some time to come. Fed Chair Jerome Powell, who was also asked about excessive market speculation, sidestepped several attempts to get him to comment directly on GameStop, saying instead that financial-stability vulnerabilities overall are “moderate.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guantanamo inmates  to get Covid jab as early as NEXT WEEK including alleged 9/11 mastermind...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2235958/911-mastermind-guantanamo-bay-inmates-covid-vaccine-americans/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ALLEGED terrorist behind 9/11 and other detainees at Guantanamo Bay will get Covid-19 vaccines as soon as next week – before most Americans. Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, the supposed principal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even with pardon, Bannon not off hook...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Even-with-Trump-s-pardon-Stephen-Bannon-is-not-15909197.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his last day in office, President Donald Trump issued pardons to 74 people and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Actions by Proud Boy at Capitol show 'planning, determination, and coordination'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Two-more-accused-in-chase-of-Officer-Eugene-15908418.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A police riot shield used to break a window, then a door kicked open from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii wants tourists. Tourists want Hawaii. But rules are complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Hawaii-wants-tourists-Tourists-want-Hawaii-But-15909101.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Derrick has run an online guide to Hawaii travel for nearly 20 years, so he's used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washingtonians navigate new normal: Razor-tipped wire fences and armed soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/washingtonians-navigate-new-normal-razor-tipped-wire-fences-and-armed-soldiers/ar-BB1ddgcE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After rioters attacked the Capitol, D.C. residents adapt to the imposing security measures that have taken over their home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America 'flying blind' to mutations racing across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/why-america-is-e2-80-98flying-blind-e2-80-99-to-the-coronavirus-mutations-racing-across-the-globe/ar-BB1ddwSU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America currently has so little of the genetic sequencing needed to detect mutated versions of coronavirus - like those first discovered in Britain and South Africa - that such variants are likely proliferating quickly, undetected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines push back on potential testing for domestic flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/covid-testing-airlines-push-back-on-testing-for-domestic-flights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC said it's "actively looking" at mandating Covid tests for domestic flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moves to isolate Navalny allies, shut part of central Moscow ahead of protests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129192431-t917q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-COURT (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Russia moves to isolate Navalny allies, shut part of central Moscow ahead of protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper publisher sues FACEBOOKGOOGLE over advertising monopoly...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-media-newspapers-west-virginia-huntington-02c267f9ee9474f20b4c9afc24523485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A West Virginia news publisher has filed an antitrust suit against Google and Facebook, who together receive roughly half of all digital ad dollars in the U.S. and are facing antitrust charges...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges dropped against activist who exposed Iowa hog deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-iowa-city-iowa-trials-subpoenas-50332a3905f4913d108865d27ee5d21d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — Prosecutors have dropped trespassing charges against an activist who helped secretly record Iowa’s largest pork producer using heat to kill thousands of hogs last year as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France tightens borders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-france-restaurants-9a3b99454b98ce6d1379fc781fa52f90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France says it's closing its borders to people arriving from outside the European Union starting Sunday to try to stop the growing spread of new variants of the virus and avoid a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
