<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Army debunks fake texts telling people they've been drafted...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article239073053.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S WAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7865171/Trump-address-world-Iran-Ayatollah-calls-missile-attack-not-revenge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The high-stakes address comes just hours after Iran launched what it promised would be a 'crushing revenge' strike over the death of General Qassem Soleimani but only damaged two airbases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 quakes have rattled in 10 days. May be more to come...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/08/us/puerto-rico-region-hundreds-of-earthquakes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 6.4 magnitude earthquake that killed one person in Puerto Rico on Tuesday is one of hundreds of tremors that have rattled the island for more than a week. And experts say the shaking is not over yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY: I STILL HAVE MORE TO PROVE...</title>
      <link>https://weei.radio.com/blogs/ryan-hannable/tom-brady-thanks-patriots-fans-in-instagram-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weei.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady reflected on the season, future via Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbings, shootings, assaults weigh on US Jewish youth...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cce65f400c17b004d4ec7d5ff5a0ff8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When a man spewed anti-Semitic slurs and spat on her face, Shoshana Blum remembered her ancestors who survived the Holocaust, and instead of looking down - she defiantly stared at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-tech plane joins search for mysterious drones in Colorado...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/high-tech-plane-joins-search-mysterious-drones-colorado/story?id=68128257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane, intended for use in wildfires, carries sophisticated cameras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA had advance warning of attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2020/01/08/us-officials-warned-missile-launch-iraq-bases-troops/2842200001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials had advance warning of Iran's missile assault that damaged two Iraqi bases housing U.S. and coalition forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to address nation 11 a.m. ET...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/01/08/donald-trump-address-nation-iran-attacks/2842056001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no casualties in the missile barrage that Iran described as retaliation for last week's U.S. attack that killed a top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shot down?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694922/iran-plane-crash-ukrainian-airline-black-box/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN has refused to hand over the black box of a plane that crashed killing 176 people to international investigators. The Kiev-bound Ukraine International Airlines jet came down shortly after taki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot lab producing 'human replicas' laid bare in video tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-lab-producing-human-21239270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll guided viewers through its groundbreaking lab producing AI-powered dolls. It is currently testing models with futuristic AI vision and touch sensors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Fewer Than Third of American Voters Can Point to Iran on Map...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020/01/08/can-you-locate-iran-few-voters-can/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As tensions between the United States and Iran rise in the aftermath of the American drone strike that killed the country’s most powerful commander, Gen. Qassem Soleimani, a new Morning Consult/Politico survey finds fewer than 3 in 10 registered voters can identify the Islamic republic on an unlabeled map.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What next?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/what-next-awaiting-trumps-response-to-iranian-missile-attack-on-us-bases-in-iraq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALL IS WELL: Once it seemed clear there were no U.S. casualties from Iran’s missile strike on two U.S. bases in Iraq, the White House called off plans for President Trump to address the nation, and instead Trump went to bed after sending a single tweet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Survey of Media Executives Shows Dire Views About Industry's Future...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/media-and-entertainment-exec-survey-business-model-ey-1203456357/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With media and entertainment sectors continuing to be whipped by winds of digital disruption, many industry execs believe they need to change the ways they’ve done business — or see the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China facial-recognition case puts Big Brother on trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-facial-recognition-case-puts-big-brother-trial-045846432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial-recognition technology has become embedded in China, from airports to hotels, e-commerce sites and even public toilets, but a law professor had enough when asked to scan his face at a safari park. Guo Bing took the wildlife park to court, raising the temperature in a growing debate about privacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child found dead in plane's landing gear at Paris airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10696574/child-found-dead-in-planes-landing-gear-at-paris-airport-on-flight-from-ivory-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHILD has been found dead in the landing gear of a plane at a Paris airport. The Air France flight was travelling to Paris-Charles de Gaulle airport in the French capital from Abidjan in Ivory Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left launches pre-Iowa assault on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/08/progressives-pre-iowa-assault-biden-095934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many activist groups expected the former veep to crumble by now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will not give black box to BOEING...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Iran-civil-aviation-org-says-will-not-give-black-box-to-Boeing-613548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Ricans sleep outside, wait for power after 'devastating' quake...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108102705-whjbu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a week of tremors, many fear their homes will crumble if there's another earthquake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian drug lord El Tio arrested after son tips off police because dad had affair with his wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694600/drug-lord-arrested-affair-sons-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE of the world’s most wanted drug lords has been arrested, reportedly after a tip-off by his son. At one stage, Colombian Luis del Rio — known as El Tio — was trafficking at least ten tons of coc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red devil horns appear over Persian Gulf during eclipse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10694515/red-devil-horns-sunrise-photos-captured-rare-solar-eclipse-mirage/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE incredible images appear to show giant devil horns rising over the Persian Gulf during a solar eclipse. A photographer waited in just the right place to snap the rare spectacle as the sun was…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to war, bro': Fort Bragg's 82nd Airborne deploys to Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security-usa-fort-bragg/were-going-to-war-bro-fort-braggs-82nd-airborne-deploys-to-the-middle-east-idUSKBN1Z616W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many of the soldiers, it would be their first mission. They packed up ammuni...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader tweets flag -- like Trump did...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/article239060528.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg to appear in FOXNEWS town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/477158-pete-buttigieg-to-appear-in-fox-news-town-hall  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News will host a town hall with former South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg on Jan. 26 from Des Moines, Iowa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi tells colleagues to 'pray'... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ill-call-him-back-pelosi-puts-house-business-first-as-pence-calls-about-missile-attack-on-iraq-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi was huddling with Democratic colleagues when she was alerted of the missile attack on an Iraqi base that hosts U.S. troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas facing 10,000 potential cybersecurity attacks from Iran per minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article239042893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security upped in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/news/article/Security-upped-in-D-C-region-after-threats-by-14957314.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Authorities across the Washington, District of Columbia, region are boosting security at military bases, Arlington Cemetery and at sites along the National Mall following threats by Iran to retaliate against the United States for the killing of Maj. Gen. Qasem Soleimani.  In some cases, entry gates at military facilities have been closed, and officials are carrying out more thorough identity checks. A spokesman for the U.S. Park Police said the agency's uniformed officers will have a more visible presence because of the tensions with Iran.  "There's no specific threats," said Sgt. Eduardo Delgado, spokesman for the U.S. Park Police. "It's just an abundance of precaution."  But the rollout of the enhanced security has not been smooth in every case, leaving some people facing a chaotic return to work at the beginning of the new year. The Navy command that runs Walter Reed National Military Medical Center in Bethesda, Maryland, modified some of its new precautions and issued a lighthearted mea culpa on its Facebook page Monday evening after the security changescaused monstrous traffic in the area that morning.  "Today's traffic was awful. It was horrible," the post read. "It looked at normal D.C. Monday traffic and said, 'Hey, watch this!' "  Nevertheless, officials wrote that the enhanced security was necessary to keep people safe.  Last week, President Donald Trump ordered the drone strike that killed Soleimani, Iran's most important military commander. Iran's leaders quickly promised to take revenge. And an Iranian official said Tuesday that the country was considering 13 scenarios for retaliation and had American bases in the Middle East under surveillance.  Over the weekend, the Department of Homeland Security issued a bulletin warning that Iran and its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN settles lawsuit with Covington Catholic student...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/cnn-settles-lawsuit-with-covington-catholic-student-nick-sandmann/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN, on Tuesday, settled a lawsuit with Covington Catholic student Nick Sandmann — who alleged that the network made "vicious" and "direct attacks" against him following a viral co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm sorry, I have a sick child,' Philly robber writes in demand note...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/robber-claims-he-has-a-sick-child-during-philly-robbery-20200107.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case eerily echoes a similar robbery last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSILES FIRED AT BASES</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/missile-attacks-target-us-forces-in-iraq-senior-military-source-says-iran-suspected</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missiles were fired early Wednesday in multiple locations across Iraq, a senior U.S. military source in the country told Fox News, describing it as a series of attacks on U.S. forces from Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S WAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7862453/Multiple-rockets-hit-Taji-military-base-Iraq-American-British-troops-based.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran has tonight launched missile attack on two US bases in Iraq housing US and coalition troops, defense sources have revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL UP 4%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/07/oil-prices-surge-4percent-following-attack-on-iraq-airbase.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices surged in early trading on Tuesday night following attacks on bases in Western Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA GETS RAVES AT CES...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/digital/news/ivanka-trump-ces-keynote-tech-jobs-impeachment-1203459163/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump talked about the current and future state of the U.S. workforce at CES — an appearance that was met with a fair amount of enthusiasm among the tech-industry attendees. In a keyno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOLLYWOOD,' '1917' boosted by producer, director nods...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/once-upon-time-1917-boosted-producer-director-nods-190416514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino's "Once Upon a Time... in Hollywood" and Sam Mendes's "1917" boosted their awards charges Tuesday, collecting key nominations from Hollywood's producing and directing guilds just days after bagging the top Golden Globes prizes. Tarantino's homage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack came in three waves just after midnight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-launches-missiles-iraq-housing-us-troops-state-003842838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran on Wednesday launched a missile attack on an Iraqi airbase where US forces are based, threatening "more crushing responses" if Washington carried out further strikes, Iranian state media said. It said the missiles were in response to a US strike last week that killed Iranian general Qasem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell to begin impeachment trial with no deal on witnesses... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4b1b786420b4468dbe5da3b334e037db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Tuesday he has the votes to start President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial as soon as House Speaker Nancy Pelosi releases the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Author Wurtzel dies at 52...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3bc202902e8baa8b479d39acbee38102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Elizabeth Wurtzel, whose blunt and painful confessions of her struggles with addiction and depression in the best-selling “Prozac Nation” made her a voice and a target for an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URGENT MEETING AT WHITE HOUSE...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108002323-ne7v3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ATTACK-WHITEHOUSE (URGENT):Pompeo, Esper arrive at White House after Iran attack on Iraqi base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone's scared'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108000251-zv8o8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUERTORICO-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 12, PIX, TV):UPDATE 12-'Everyone's scared' - Puerto Rico declares emergency after earthquakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation 'Martyr Soleimani'... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200107234619-cb330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ATTACK-PENTAGON (URGENT):Iran launches large attack on U.S.-led forces in Iraq, Pentagon says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most prolific rapist' in UK history was cheerful, friends said...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2020/01/07/reynhard-sinaga-most-prolific-rapist-uk-history-cheerful/2832902001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reynhard Sinaga lured victims with a place to stay for the night, as many were intoxicated, while others had lost their cell phones or credit cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSV 'particularly bad' this season...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/what-rsv-respiratory-virus-particularly-bad-season-doctors-warn-t171208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Respiratory syncytial virus is similar to cold or flu, but patients have trouble breathing and it can cause other severe infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry &amp; Meghan moving to Canada for most of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10693487/prince-harry-meghan-move-to-canada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry and Meghan are looking to move to Canada for a significant portion of this year as they actively consider their future role in the Royal Family. Long-term options being floated include…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Online DNA Services Vulnerable To 'Genetic Hacking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/online-dna-services-may-be-vulnerable-to-genetic-hacking-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more people continue to share their genetic information online DNA servies, they may be opening themselves up to a form of data theft they probably didn't even know was possible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Days after ending cash bail, NY has second thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/fair-or-dangerous-days-after-ending-cash-bail-new-york-n1111346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Bail reform is well meaning, but there are unintended consequences," a prosecutor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lance Corporal's Selfie Got His Marine Unit 'Killed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2020/01/07/lance-corporals-phone-selfie-got-his-marine-unit-killed-29-palms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phones are proving to be a major potential vulnerability in military operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio considers if being BROWNS or BENGALS fan qualifies for medical pot use...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox19.com/2020/01/07/state-medical-board-ohio-consider-if-being-browns-or-bengals-fan-qualifies-medical-marijuana-use/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox19.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being a professional football fan in Ohio is stressful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN settles lawsuit with Covington Catholic student...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox19.com/2020/01/07/cnn-settles-lawsuit-with-nick-sandmann/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox19.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amount of the settlement was not made public during a hearing at the federal courthouse in Covington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President now says we'll leave Iraq 'at some point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7860735/Letter-telling-Iraq-troop-pullout-Arabic-version-despite-Pentagon-calling-draft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the U.S. government saying a letter describing plans for a mass troop withdrawal was a premature draft, Iraq's prime minister says he has received the missive and will hold the Pentagon to it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gayle King called fallen newsman 'Charlie 'F*ckin' Rose'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/07/gayle-king-called-fallen-newsman-charlie-f-n-rose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rose admitted to the nickname during a deposition in the case brought by former employees accusing him of sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES unveils AVATAR concept car...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/ces-2020-mercedes-benz-unveils-concept-car-inspired-by-film-avatar-11902857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, the Japanese car manufacturer Toyota has announced its plans to build an entire city at the base of Mt Fuji.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to drop $10 million on Super Bowl ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/07/donald-trump-10-million-dollar-super-bowl-ad-095623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's is about to unleash his massive war chest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg too...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/bloomberg-campaign-buys-10-million-super-bowl-ad-target-trump-n1111881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The game is set for Feb. 2, the day before the Iowa caucuses, and could be watched by roughly 100 million people in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim religious leader in Texas charged with sex crimes against four children...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/07/muslim-religious-leader-in-texas-charged-with-sex-crimes-against-four-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-known Islamic religious leader in Texas has been busted for sexually assaulting four children — though authorities believe he’s victimized others. Mohamed Omar Ali, a 59-year-old…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sudan bans newspapers, TV stations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sudan-bans-newspapers-tv-stations-over-bashir-ties-193448446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sudan banned two newspapers and two television stations on Tuesday, saying they had received funding from the government of former president Omar al-Bashir who was ousted last year following protests. The decision was made by a committee tasked by Sudan's transitional authorities with dismantling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POMPEO: Trump Ready to Launch More Strikes...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/pompeo-trump-admin-ready-to-launch-more-strikes-on-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said the Trump administration would not hesitate to conduct further military strikes against Iran following the killing of Iranian military leader Qassem Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEDED OUT: Chicago Dispensaries Run Out Of Recreational Marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/06/no-more-weed-local-dispensaries-suffer-from-shortages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's not what happens on day one, or day two or day three. It's what happens at month six. It's what happens at month 12, at month 18, at month 24. That's the roll out of this program. It's intended to be rolled out over years, not days."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New incident at Mar-a-Lago under Secret Service 'criminal investigation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article239028168.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran military displaying 'heightened state of readiness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/iran-news-qassem-soleimani-funeral-deaths-today-revolutionary-guard-threatens-us-allies-live-updates-2020-01-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. defense official called Iranian military movements "very troubling" after Qassem Soleimani was killed by an American drone strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French publisher pulls books by writer accused of child sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/french-publisher-pulls-books-writer-182153062.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French publisher Gallimard said Tuesday  it was halting sales of books by a writer accused of raping children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Atrocious' child cancer ward reveals ills of Russian healthcare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/atrocious-child-cancer-ward-reveals-ills-russian-healthcare-015707176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Underfunding, corruption allegations, internal feuding, facilities in disrepair -- flaws revealed at a Moscow paediatric cancer ward have shone a harsh spotlight on the afflictions plaguing Russia's public healthcare system. The Blokhin cancer centre, housed in a brutalist 1970s-era compound in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Burkle's son found dead at Beverly Hills home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aacd190a1876a9241c16f4793c7c6937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — California billionaire Ronald Burkle’s adult son Andrew was found dead, his family told People magazine. “It is with the deepest regret and sadness that we...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Most Valuable Car Company In America Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/articles/tesla-stock-most-valuable-car-company-51578415861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla stock hit another all-time high on Tuesday. The shares’ persistent rise has made the electric vehicle pioneer the most valuable U.S. car company in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Series winning RED SOX accused of 'cheating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/28440015/report-red-sox-used-replay-room-steal-signs-2018-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Athletic, citing anonymous people who were with the Red Sox in 2018, reported that Boston players would visit the replay room to decipher their opponents' sign sequence and then relay the information to the dugout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds recommend Michael Flynn get up to 6 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/michael-flynn-sentencing-memo-russia-investigation-65254f39-e9a8-46ba-8b89-209d482ce7ec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They argued that he should not receive credit for cooperating with the government after recent behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada moving troops from Iraq to Kuwait...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/newsalert-canada-relocating-some-troops-from-iraq-to-kuwait</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military has about 500 Canadian soldiers in Iraq, mainly to help train local forces to fight ISIL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell moving forward on trial rules without Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/07/mcconnell-prepares-to-move-forward-on-impeachment-trial-rules-without-democrats-095537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP leaders have enough votes to ignore Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer’s demands for witnesses and new evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PROZAC' author dead at 52...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/elizabeth-wurtzel-prozac-nation-author-who-spurred-a-memoir-boom-dies-at-52/ar-BBYHYZ0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid rising spy concerns, 2 more Chinese held after shooting base photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/florida-keys/article239010873.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Judge Denies Request to Delay NYC Trial After L.A. Indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/weinstein-judge-denies-request-delay-new-york-trial-la-indictment-1267523</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Burke denied the motion, arguing that the new charges are "next to meaningless" as far as Weinstein's criminal case in New York is concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE ON PELOSI...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/07/politics/nancy-pelosi-impeachment-strategy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington is once again awaiting House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's next chess move as she returns to Capitol Hill on Tuesday, continuing to withhold the articles of impeachment from the US Senate while attempting to place another check on President Donald Trump to address his actions on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australians scoop up koalas, kangaroos to save them from bushfires...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/07/australians-scoop-up-koalas-kangaroos-to-save-them-from-bushfires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australians are doing their best to save local animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE THREATENS WEINSTEIN WITH JAIL FOR USING PHONE AT TRIAL</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-jail-threat-new-charges-adjournment-request-1202823277/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Events over on the West Coast and cell phones dominated the early part of the second day of Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial in New York City this morning – and almost landed the disgraced producer be…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers Track Repeating Radio Signal Across Space to Unexpected Origin...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/that-newly-discovered-repeating-frb-has-been-tracked-to-a-really-puzzling-origin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious repeating radio signal from space revealed last year is now the fifth fast radio burst to be tracked back to its source galaxy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 50 killed in stampede at Iranian general's funeral...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security/at-least-50-killed-in-stampede-at-iranian-generals-funeral-tehran-weighs-response-to-u-s-attack-idUSKBN1Z60NL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 50 people were killed in a stampede as mourners packed streets for the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin lands in Damascus on unannounced visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/putin-syria-damascus-assad-russia-a9273781.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic triangular craft spotted above Texas days after New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/gigantic-triangular-ufo-spotted-above-21231036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge object slowly moved across the night-time sky on New Year's Day and it bears a startling similarity to a so-called UFO seen above the US state of New York just days before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos of grinning 'poachers' with gorilla 'shot dead' spark outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/disturbing-photos-grinning-poachers-gorilla-21229775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primate was “shot dead illegally” in a “crime against nature” in Brazzaville, Democratic Republic of Congo, animal rights campaigners fear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to Hand Over Roger Stone Records to Media Outlets...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/feds-to-hand-over-roger-stone-records-to-media-outlets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors told a judge Monday they are prepared to release sealed materials in search and seizure warrants against Roger Stone issued during the FBI probe into the Trump campaign’s ties to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone attacks?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/07/politics/us-iran-high-alert-drone-attacks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US forces and air-defense missile batteries across the Middle East were placed on high alert overnight Monday to possibly shoot down Iranian drones as intelligence mounted about a threat of an imminent attack against US targets, two US officials tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORM OF GOVT CENSORSHIP...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2020/01/06/monopoly-is-speech-policy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In my latest Locus column, Inaction is a Form of Action, I discuss how the US government’s unwillingness to enforce its own anti-monopoly laws has resulted in the dominance of a handful of gi…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
