<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Israel feels pressure as boycott movement gains global support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/israel-fights-bds-movement-pro-palestinian-campaign-gains-global-support-n965691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campaign is also reverberating in the U.S., where the Senate passed a bill Tuesday that would allow states to punish businesses that take part in Israel boycotts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran revolution: Political quake still shaking Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190210-irans-revolution-political-quake-still-shaking-middle-east</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's revolution: Political quake still shaking Middle East</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans feel alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/feeling-lonely-you-are-not-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Americans say they sometimes or always feel alone, which can have health consequences: doctors say loneliness can lead to increased mortality equal to smoking 15 cigarettes a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Middle Class Joe' Biden Courts Wall Street Oligarch...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/middle-class-joe-biden-courts-wall-street-oligarch-blackrocks-larry-fink</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-veep says he's the working man's friend. How does that square with currying favor with financial world titan Larry Fink?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg's Quiet Rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-political-scene/pete-buttigiegs-quiet-rebellion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Against the image of the millennial left, Buttigieg appears to be a relatively prosaic Presidential candidate, but, in his own understated way, he is suggesting a sharp break with the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT to get $210 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/reddit-strikes-deal-with-chinese-censorship-powerhouse-users-expose-chinas-worst-atrocities/news-story/2412b1bc5381b344c7695a03e55c196d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reddit is reportedly set to land a massive investment from a Chinese censorship powerhouse in order to keep the “Internet’s front page” rolling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-year-old passes out at school, tests positive for cocaine...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/crime/article226012090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Clark County, Ky., mother was arrested after her 4-year-old became unresponsive at school and tested positive for cocaine. Winchester police were called to Clark Regional Medical Center to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie risks getting crowded out in field of progressives...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-08/sanders-risks-getting-crowded-out-in-2020-field-of-progressives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parking lot suicides:  Taking their lives on VA doorstep...</title>
      <link>https://expo.oregonlive.com/news/g66l-2019/02/a3c833579f4689/the-parking-lot-suicides-they-take-their-lives-at-the-doorstep-of-the-va.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;expo.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wingers rally in Madrid, demand Socialist PM resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/madrid-protests-thousands-demand-pedro-sanchez-soc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Spaniards in Madrid are joining a rally called by right-wing political parties to demand that Socialist Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez step down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hitler paintings go unsold at Nuremberg auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/10/hitler-paintings-go-unsold-nuremberg-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five watercolors attributed to Nazi dictator Adolf Hitler from his early days as a struggling artist have failed to sell at auction in the southern German city of Nuremberg, possibly over fears they could be fakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Most African Americans in Virginia want Gov to stay...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/virginia-politics/virginians-split-on-governors-fate-amid-blackface-scandal-poll-shows/2019/02/09/93002e84-2bc1-11e9-b011-d8500644dc98_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;African Americans and Democrats say by wide margins that Gov. Ralph Northam should remain in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi: 'Nothing to do' with dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-bezos-saudi/saudi-arabia-says-has-nothing-to-do-with-bezos-ami-dispute-idUSKCN1PZ0BG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia had "absolutely nothing to do" with the National Enquirer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year 3 aims for dramatic sequels to rival originals...</title>
      <link>https://www.avpress.com/news/newsline/trump-aims-for-dramatic-sequels-to-rival-originals/article_838ce970-2cf1-11e9-9430-930c77278130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.avpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As President Donald Trump prepares to meet North Korea’s Kim Jong Un for a second time, he’s out to replicate the suspenseful buildup, make-or-break stakes and far-flung rendezvous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chimps make ladder, escape zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/feb/10/chimps-use-branch-as-ladder-to-escape-belfast-zoo-enclosure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breakout is second in recent weeks after runaway red panda found in a nearby garden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  How AMAZON gets whatever it wants...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/politics/how-amazon-gets-whatever-it-wants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two power plays this past week show why it's Amazon's world, and we're just living in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEMSON coach admits college may have given players banned drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/sports/clemson-s-dabo-swinney-says-college-may-have-given-players/article_24ab729a-2bdf-11e9-9a3f-97cd28b8ce04.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dabo Swinney says it's possible three Clemson players suspended after failing drug tests before the Cotton Bowl may have mistakenly received the banned performance-enhancing drug from the school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaido won't rule out authorizing US intervention...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190209-venezuela-guaido-not-rule-out-authorising-us-intervention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s self-proclaimed acting president Juan Guaido refused to rule out on Friday the possibility of authorizing United States intervention to help force President Nicolas Maduro from power and alleviate a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea to Pay More Under New Military Deal With USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/south-korea-to-pay-more-under-new-military-deal-with-u-s-11549794220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. and South Korea signed a one-year deal outlining the shared costs of their military alliance, removing a potential distraction ahead of the second summit between President Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un scheduled for late this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mumps at Houston ICE facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c4511e01dbc04b2d8fb3807d34b5d005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Health officials say seven cases of the mumps have been confirmed at a U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement detention facility in Houston. The Houston Health Department said Saturday that the seven adults were detained during their infectious period. Health officials say there's no evidence the disease was transmitted outside the facility. The health department is working with the facility on infection control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi gets rock star treatment at pre-GRAMMY gala...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5f069b167aa84bd0b85465c707507892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The audience at Clive Davis' white-hot gala included Barbra Streisand, Joni Mitchell and Kareem Abdul Jabbar, but it was House Speaker Nancy Pelosi who got the most requests to take a selfie. Pelosi received rock star treatment Saturday night from attendees at the annual pre-Grammy event, which also featured a stunning tribute to the late Aretha Franklin, an artist Davis worked closely with for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC BLAMES RNC...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/the-mysterious-case-of-aocs-scrubbed-green-new-deal-details</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Feb. 5, the congressional office of Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez posted a new blog entry under “energy issues” detailing her "Green New Deal" proposal and answering “frequently asked questions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
China unleashing killer drones that carry out airstrikes on their own...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8394455/china-killer-robots-drones-airstrikes-autonomous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA is aggressively unleashing lethal fully autonomous drones that can carry out targeted military strikes, a think tank has warned. The killer drones and pilotless aircraft fitted with AK-47 rif…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREEN BOTCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/huge-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-caught-in-major-lie-claims-green-new-deal-document-from-her-own-website-is-a-fake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National reckoning... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/09/jeff-bezos-blackmail-ami-national-enquirer-parent-go-under/2811938002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida-based supermarket's new attacks on Amazon owner Jeff Bezos is shining a harsh light on the underbelly of tabloid journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisons to get transgender wings in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/prisons-to-get-transgender-wings-6b2xpr88g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Prison Service is to stop many transgender inmates, including sex offenders, serving their sentences in women’s prisons. The justice minister Ed Argar said the government was “revising”...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEGOOGLE REACH DEAL WITH RUSSIA, CHINA, &amp; SAUDI ARABIA TO CENSOR POPULATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/google-apple-reach-deal-with-russia-china-saudi-arabia-to-censor-populations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Tech in league with authoritarian dictatorships to crush dissent and control free thought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS BUILDING SURVEILLANCE STATE ON EVERYONE ELSE!</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/02/08/jeff-bezos-protests-the-invasion-of-his-privacy-as-amazon-builds-a-sprawling-surveillance-state-for-everyone-else</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world's greatest privacy invaders just had his privacy invaded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Turks and Caicos overwhelmed by Haitian influx... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/tiny-turks-caicos-overwhelmed-haitian-influx-014847098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Handmade wooden boats and the artisans who craft them line a lengthy stretch of Haiti's north coast. "As a British territory we don't have our own defense force. There's no other way to describe it." Each year, thousands of young Haitians try to escape the poorest economy in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker Stumps in Iowa Seeking Position as Obama's Heir...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cory-booker-stumps-in-iowa-seeking-position-as-obamas-heir-11549749749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Cory Booker is betting the path to the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination runs through young people and African-Americans—the same groups that propelled Barack Obama’s campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In country music capital, political divides rock the industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/a-country-music-artist-navigates-an-art-form-altered-by-americas-poisoned-politics/2019/02/09/8b9a1d28-24cb-11e9-ad53-824486280311_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margo Price, a best new artist Grammy contender, finds her audience in a deeply divided country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Purple Heart Triple-Amputee Undergoes Invasive TSA Groping... </title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/awful-purple-heart-triple-amputee-brian-kolfage-undergoes-invasive-tsa-groping-at-tucson-airport-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen's secret agenda as Trump's fixer...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-xer-s-secret-agenda-13604305.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - At first, Michael Cohen appeared indifferent as he listened to the group of Republican leaders urge his boss to run for governor. It was the fall of 2013, and Donald Trump was already fixated on "the big thing," as he referred to running for president. But the Republicans knew they were getting somewhere when Trump signaled to his attorney that he wanted more talks. "So Michael," Trump would say, "you get us a date on the calendar." Soon enough, no one in the billionaire's coterie was more enthusiastic than Cohen about the prospect of a Governor Trump. Albany, Cohen believed, was a great opportunity not only for his boss but also, as it happened, for himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal murder of 19-year-old girl shocks Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Brutal-murder-of-19-year-old-girl-shocks-Jerusalem-580105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ori Ansbacher, from Tekoa in Gush Etzion, was murdered in Jerusalem on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN BANKS ON POPULISIM</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-refocuses-populist-message-in-official-13604175.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAWRENCE, Mass. - Sen. Elizabeth Warren formally launched her presidential bid Saturday by reemphasizing her signature issues of fighting economic inequality and corporate wrongdoing, an effort to move beyond new questions that arose in recent days about her previous claims that she was a Native American. The outdoor rally - on the steps of a former cotton mill and the site of a historic labor strike led by women and immigrants - was intended to position Warren as the leader of a renewed crusade against what she called the "corrupt" influence of large companies and powerful politicians. "The story of Lawrence is a story about how real change happens in America," Warren told a crowd that the campaign estimated at 3,500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump divides Dems with warning of creeping socialism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/429207-trump-divides-democrats-with-warning-of-creeping-socialism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump hadn’t had much success dividing Democrats until he found a word that would provoke very different responses from different members of the party during his State of the Union address: socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress closes in on deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d6f8067a647b4a67bb1fe628e2d8a084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Congressional bargainers are working toward a border security deal amid indications that the White House is preparing to accept a bipartisan agreement that would give President Donald Trump a fraction of the money he's demanded for his proposed southern border wall. Participants said they expect money for physical barriers to end up well below the $5.7 billion that Trump has sought to begin construction of the wall, which has attained iconic significance for him and his conservative supporters. Underscoring the clout he's lost during a battle that's dominated the opening weeks of divided government, the amount seems sure to fall much closer to $1.6 billion, the participants said, a figure that was in a bipartisan Senate bill last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-govt protests again turn violent in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/64582c7c8c0c4d17bdde5f0a5c162796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A French yellow vest protester's hand was ripped apart Saturday during violent clashes in Paris as demonstrators tried to storm the French National Assembly in a 13th consecutive week of unrest. Police said the injured protester lost four fingers as police swooped in to stop protesters from breaching the parliament's exterior. Police could not confirm French media reports that the hand of the demonstrator, who is now being treated in the hospital, was blown up by a grenade used to disperse unruly crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Bezos and his complexifier... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/09/opinion/sunday/jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-blackmail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-in-a-billion chance: a heroic billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Hit by Unusually Heavy Snowfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/photos-heavy-snow-slams-washington-and-oregon-triggering-major-travel-disruptions/70007391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio journalist shot dead in Mexico's latest media killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/429889-radio-journalist-shot-dead-in-mexicos-latest-media-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenews.com.pk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesus Ramos Rodriguez was killed in the town of Emiliano Zapata, an official from the local prosecutor´s office told AFP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENQUIRER pushed envelope with Bezos, but was it crime?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-bezos-national-enquirer-legal-explainers-20190208-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Enquirer has undoubtedly pushed the envelope in its dealings with Jeff Bezos, but proving a crime of extortion might prove difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 minors charged in deadly shooting of Nashville musician...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/5-minors-charged-in-fatal-shooting-of-nashville-musician-kyle-yorlets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five kids -- three girls and two boys -- range in age from 12 to 16. They were arrested at a Walmart in Nashville</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Hip-Hop Make Long-Awaited History at GRAMMYS?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-hip-hop-make-history-at-grammys-wins-record-song-year-1184619 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music awards show has had a pretty dodgy past with recognizing the genre’s merits — and diverse winners in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren kicks off bid with challenge to wealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/09/politics/elizabeth-warren-campaign-kickoff-massachusetts/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren officially launched her 2020 presidential campaign Saturday at a rally in Lawrence, Massachusetts, using the backdrop of Everett Mills -- the site of a historic 1912 labor strike led by women and immigrants -- to issue a call to action against wealthy power brokers who "have been waging class warfare against hardworking people for decades."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOTTI DAUGHTER: My Father Would Be President If Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-news-john-gotti-president-victoria-gotti-20190206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Gotti supported a Rudy Giuliani presidency and could have himself been elected President in 2020 according to his daughter Victoria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More states adopting gun-seizure laws...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d5722abc06245b4b931933f253e3743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the year since the deadly mass shooting at a Florida high school, more and more states have passed laws making it easier to take guns away from people who may be suicidal or bent on violence against others, and courts are issuing an unprecedented number of seizure orders across the country. Supporters say these "red flag" laws are among the most promising tools to reduce the nearly 40,000 suicides and homicides by firearm each year in the U.S. Gun advocates, though, say such measures undermine their constitutional rights and can result in people being stripped of their weapons on false or vindictive accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Geyser Gushing at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.travelbreakingnews.net/2019/02/yellowstones-steamboat-geyser-is-gushing-at-a-record-pace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.travelbreakingnews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sections SEARCH Skip to content Skip to site index Science Subscribe Log In Log In Today’s Paper Science | Yellowstone’s Steamboat Geyser Is Gushing at a Record Pace Supported by Trilobites It’s the talk of the national park these days, erupting a record 32 times last year and keeping up its showstopping pace this winter.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Firefighters battling inferno forced to dodge moving robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/ocado-robots-at-andover-warehouse-hampered-firefighters-gwtj0zqd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters trying to put out flames at an Ocado warehouse had to dodge robots as they battled through the smoke to find the one that started the fire. The company’s customer fulfilment centre in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York prosecutors pose greatest threat to president?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/feb/09/new-york-southern-district-donald-trump-inauguration-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separate from the Mueller inquiry, the southern district of New York’s pursuit of the inauguration committee could herald more pain for the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siesta no more? Spanish sleeping habits under strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/feb/09/why-spanish-sleeping-habits-under-strain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spaniards eat later and stay up longer than their European neighbours because of the siesta. But now that’s under threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange could be given asylum in Switzerland after vote in Geneva...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/758757/julian-assange-latest-asylum-switzerland-wikileaks-geneva-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Military Warns of Threat From Chinese-Run Space Station in Argentina...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/02/08/us-military-warns-of-threat-from-chinese-run-space-station-in-argentina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense officials are worried about a remote compound Beijing says helped it land on the far side of the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chief Justice Roberts emerges as Supreme Court swing vote...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190209115114-alni0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/ROBERTS (PIX, REPEAT):RPT-Chief Justice Roberts emerges as U.S. Supreme Court's swing vote</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
