<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dems eye Russia probe revival if win House...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e796619e55d040b3b742da21b0187fd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats are expected to re-open the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election if they win the majority in November. But they would have to be selective in what they investigate. California Rep. Adam Schiff, the top Democrat on the House intelligence panel, has said his party would have to "ruthlessly prioritize the most important matters first." The Republican-led Intelligence Committee was the only House panel to investigate Russian meddling, and its investigation is now closed. Republicans say they found no evidence of collusion between Russia and President Donald Trump's campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada installs Chinese underwater monitoring devices next to US nuclear sub base...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2169474/canada-installs-chinese-underwater-monitoring-devices-next-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocean Network Canada confirms addition of hi-tech sensors built by Chinese scientists to its marine observatories in Pacific OceanUS state department has ‘nothing to say’ on matter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging Japan: Unclaimed burial urns pile up... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-ageing-urns/aging-japan-unclaimed-burial-urns-pile-up-in-japan-amid-fraying-social-ties-idUSKCN1MT0RH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unclaimed urns containing ashes of the dead are piling up by the thousands acros...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti Lived High Life While Owing Millions to IRS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-avenatti-lived-the-high-life-while-owing-millions-to-irs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Michael Avenatti floats a 2020 presidential run, court records reveal the lawyer and his companies owed millions in unpaid taxes and judgments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller examines conflicting accounts of Roger Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/special-counsel-examines-conflicting-accounts-as-scrutiny-of-roger-stone-and-wikileaks-deepens/ar-BBOHEWo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Says Took DNA Test to Rebuild 'Trust in Govt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2018-10-21/warren-took-dna-test-to-help-rebuild-trust-in-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL ANTHEM DRAMA: Player pregame scuffle over NOT kneeling...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6301147/Eric-Reid-earns-praise-Colin-Kaepernick-scuffling-field-Malcolm-Jenkins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident between Eric Reid of the Panthers and Malcolm Jenkins of the Eagles took place before the start of the teams’ Week 7 matchup at Lincoln Financial Field in Philadelphia on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Neocolonialist aligns with oppressors'...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/sports/eagles/eric-reid-malcolm-jenkins-analysis-players-coalition-colin-kaepernick-philadelphia-eagles-carolina-panthers-20181021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Panthers' safety, Colin Kaepernick's closest ally, accosts the Eagles' star on the field then excoriates him in the locker room. Malcolm Jenkins declines to fight back, says he's proud of Reid and Kaepernick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS warns of cartel role...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/21/kirstjen-nielsen-warns-cartels-role-migrant-carava/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen warned Sunday that the illegal immigrant caravan heading toward the U.S. could be exploited by cartels that control most of the illegal flow of people through Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Pulls 3,000 Body Cameras After One Explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYPD-Pulls-Nearly-3000-Body-Cameras-After-One-Starts-Smoking-Explodes-498152731.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD has suspended the use of a certain kind of body camera “effective immediately” after one of them exploded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy carrier in Russia's Arctic haunts for first time in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2018/10/19/the-navy-sends-a-carrier-back-to-russias-arctic-haunts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aircraft carrier Harry S. Truman's arrival in the Norwegian Sea Friday marks the first time in nearly 30 years that a U.S. carrier has operated there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves steal giant infatable colon from hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksn.com/news/kansas/ku-cancer-center-looking-for-inflatable-colon-that-was-stolen/1536142668</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The colon, valued at $4,000, was stolen from a pickup truck that was parked in Brookside, Kansas City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who follows Speaker Ryan? Power play looms for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/whos-next-speaker-ryan-battle-power-looms-gop-143141924--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Win or lose in the race for the majority, House Republicans are at risk of plunging into a messy leadership battle after the November election, with the party lacking a clear heir apparent to take the place of House Speaker Paul Ryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans give migrants water, clothes, rides...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-growing-migrant-caravan-renews-march-us-124650144.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — The Latest on the caravan of Central American migrants hoping to reach the United States (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNSTEIN:  President preparing to call midterm elections 'illegitimate'... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/carl-bernstein-trump-preparing-to-call-midterm-elections-illegitimate-if-democrats-take-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalist Carl Bernstein said Sunday that President Trump has discussed ways to challenge the results of the midterm elections if the GOP's grasp on power slips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling palm tree kills woman in hammock in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/florida-woman-lying-on-hammock-killed-after-palm-tree-falls-on-her/1538871025</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a woman lying on a hammock was killed after a palm tree came crashing down on her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS CEO to media: Quit TWITTER! Your liberal bias so obvious...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fake-news-fix-suggestions-politicians-social-media-f20fa11b-5a19-4015-bc30-fdc19896ca50.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quit sharing stories without even reading them. Quit tweeting your every outrage. Quit clicking on garbage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't know where' body is...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/saudis-dont-know-where-khashoggis-body-170049575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking in an interview on Fox News, Jubeir said the Saudi leadership initially believed Khashoggi had left its diplomatic mission in Istanbul, where he was last seen on October 2. "The individuals who did this, did this outside the scope of their authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slowing Sales Growth Hobbles Bull Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/slowing-sales-growth-hobbles-bull-market-1540137601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firms from BlackRock to IBM report disappointing quarterly sales, citing such factors as cautious customers, rising costs and a stronger dollar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-20/trump-says-new-tax-cut-plan-may-come-days-before-november-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump approval jumps ahead of Obama midterm...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412445-trumps-approval-rating-jumps-higher-than-obamas-ahead-of-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's approval rating before the November elections has jumped to a higher level than former President Obama's ahead of the 2010 midterms,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employees and execs are failing drug tests at shocking rates...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/employees-and-execs-are-failing-drug-tests-at-shocking-rates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City employers are squarely blaming a raging drug epidemic for much of the trouble they have filling jobs in one of the tightest labor markets in a generation. More local prospective worke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Opening Ever for Female Star Over 55...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/box-office/box-office-halloween-jamie-lee-curtis-1202987627/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Halloween” made a killing in North America, earning $77.5 million when the slasher film launched in 3,928 locations. David Gordon Green’s “Halloween,” a direct sequel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOWS TO REACH USA</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/thousands-hondurans-u-bound-migrant-caravan-head-mexico-164248142.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The migrants pose a challenge to Mexican President Enrique Pena Nieto's promise late last week to stop the travelers' plans to press ahead to the U.S. border without the proper documents. The multitude of migrants clogged the highway leading north from the border city of Ciudad Hidalgo in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who foiled Nazi nuclear plan dies aged 99...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/man-foiled-nazi-nuclear-plan-dies-aged-99-163410027.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of a daring World War Two raid to thwart Nazi Germany's nuclear ambitions has died aged 99, Norwegian government officials said on Sunday. Joachim Roenneberg, serving behind enemy lines in his native Norway during the German occupation, in 1943 blew up a plant producing heavy water, or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARAVAN SWELLS TO 5,000</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b709e05ec83c49e6876ff612141ae942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — A growing throng of Central American migrants resumed their advance toward the U.S. border in southern Mexico on Sunday, overwhelming Mexican government attempts to stop them at the border. Their numbers swelled to about 5,000 overnight and at first light they set out walking toward the Mexican town of Tapachula, 10 abreast in a line stretching approximately a mile (1.5 kilometers). Several hundred more already had applied for refugee status in Mexico and an estimated 1,500 were still on the Guatemalan side of the Suchiate River, hoping to enter legally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who follows Speaker Ryan? Power play looms for Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a0a4487d92fd49dcbd9b9a1218ce869e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Win or lose in the race for the majority, House Republicans are at risk of plunging into a messy leadership battle after the November election, with the party lacking a clear heir apparent to take the place of House Speaker Paul Ryan. President Donald Trump has signaled he'd be happy with next-in-line Kevin McCarthy, the majority leader, a longtime ally whom the president calls "My Kevin." But Trump is also saying kind words about the No. 3 Republican, GOP Whip Steve Scalise, whom he calls the "legend from Louisiana." Scalise survived life-threatening injuries after he was shot at a congressional baseball practice in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely to survive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/525425f708394345b4f69aa43095f532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi at the kingdom's consulate in Istanbul is unlikely to halt Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's rise to power, but could cause irreparable harm to relations with Western governments and businesses, potentially endangering his ambitious reform plans. International outrage over Khashoggi's Oct. 2 slaying at the hands of Saudi officials, under still-disputed circumstances, has marked the greatest crisis in the 33-year-old's rapid rise, already tarnished by a catastrophic war in Yemen and a sweeping roundup of Saudi businessmen and activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheep replace traffic in heart of Madrid...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/sheep-replace-traffic-heart-madrid-134833931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (Reuters) - Sheep replaced the usual traffic in central Madrid on Sunday as shepherds steered hundreds of the animals through the Spanish capital to proclaim their right to use ancient migration routes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Catholics urge Vatican to issue inclusive LGBT message...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c51dab8700745abb6e02384c8d1188f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Catholic bishops are entering their final week of debate over hot-button issues facing young Catholics, including how the church should welcome gays and respond to the clerical sex abuse scandal that has discredited many in the church hierarchy. The monthlong synod of bishops ends next Saturday with the adoption by the 260-plus cardinals, bishops and priests of a final document and approval of a separate, shorter letter to the world's Catholic youth. Some of the youth delegates to the meeting have insisted that the final document express an inclusive message to make LGBT Catholics feel welcome in a church that has often shunned them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 injured at SC party in floor collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dozens-injured-party-south-carolina-floor-collapse-133106972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — New outlets report that some 30 people were hurt when a floor collapsed early Sunday during a party at an apartment in South Carolina near the campus of Clemson University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unprecedented enthusiasm' fuels both parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/first-read/nbc-wsj-poll-democrats-hold-nine-point-advantage-midterm-elections-n922266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks out, Democrats retain an edge but "unprecedented enthusiasm" is fueling both parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACKWATER-Style Firm for Jihadists Opens Training Camp with Donor Help...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/blackwater-style-firm-for-jihadists-opens-training-camp-with-donor-help/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contracting and consulting group led by fighters from former Soviet regions appeals to supporters for funds to arm and outfit more jihadists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue wave hope ebbs?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Blue-wave-hope-ebbs-as-GOP-rebounds-13323537.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic hopes for a wave election that would carry them to a significant House majority have been tempered in recent weeks amid a shifting political landscape and a torrent of hard-hitting attack ads from Republicans. Democrats remain favored to win, but GOP leaders believe they can minimize the number of seats they would lose - and, perhaps, find a path to preserving their advantage in the chamber. The tightening, with just over two weeks left, reflects how President Donald Trump's rising approval rating and the polarizing fight over Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh appear to be boosting the party's candidates in a number of conservative and rural districts that have been considered up for grabs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birth of new Ukrainian church brings fears of violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/916f1eb16da24aedace5c39e9f13f94f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIEV, Ukraine (AP) — The rough-looking young men brought clubs and brass knuckles to the Pechersk Monastery in Kiev , one of Orthodox Christianity's most important pilgrimage sites, apparently seeking to disrupt worship. Police spread-eagled them against a wall decorated in faded centuries-old frescos of solemn saints, then hauled them away. On the other side of the dispute, at a small church in the center of Kiev, a dozen men organized round-the-clock guard duty, worried that nationalist radicals might make their third attempt in a year to seize the place of worship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan cancels part of peace agreement with Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/jordan-cancels-part-peace-agreement-israel-121121484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMMAN, Jordan (AP) — Jordan's King Abdullah II says he has decided not to renew parts of his country's landmark peace treaty with Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARC Wants Tourists to Come Stay in Jungle -- Voluntarily...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/farc-wants-you-to-come-stay-in-the-junglevoluntarily-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of the most unlikely career about-turns imaginable, former FARC guerrillas—best known for high profile kidnappings—want you to come stay with them in the jungle as tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain backs...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/oct/21/gavin-williamson-says-britain-backs-donald-trump-u/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain’s defense secretary says his country stands “absolutely resolute” with the United States as President Donald Trump says he’ll pull out from a landmark arms control agreement with Russia. Gavin Williamson blames Russia for endangering the treaty. He’s calling on the Kremlin to “get its house in order.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona cancels vaccine program after backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona-health/2018/10/18/arizona-course-vaccines-canceled-after-parental-backlash/1149710002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona parent education program with scientific information about vaccinations has been canceled because of pushback from anti-vaccine parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA pulls out of nuke treaty with Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/10/20/president-trump-pulling-out-nuke-treaty-russia/1712994002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Saturday he would pull out of a Cold-War era treaty with Russia that limited the number of missiles in each country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Michael unearthed 19th century shipwrecks in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2018/10/20/ships-wreck-dog-island-1899-unearthed-hurricane-michael/1697720002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two ships that washed ashore on Dog Island during the 1899 Carrabelle Hurricane wereÂ unearthed completely by Hurricane Michael's vicious storm surge last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada running out of marijuana days after legalizing drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/canada-marijuana-legal-weed-shortage-pot-running-out-a8593861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government expected ‘a bit of a run on supply,’ MP says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOWS TO REACH USA</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/migrant-caravan-forms-mexico-members-vow-reach-us-040050654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Despite Mexican efforts to stop them at the border, about 2,000 Central American migrants swam or rafted across a river separating that country from Guatemala, re-formed their mass caravan in Mexico and vowed to resume their journey toward the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Critical:  'Deception' and 'Lies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Post-interview-Trump-calls-Crown-Prince-a-13324029.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump retreated late Saturday from his stance that Saudi Arabia's story about the killing of journalist Jamaal Khashoggi inside their Turkish consulate was credible but still gave a strong vote of confidence to Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, arguing the United States' relationship with the kingdom is key to his administration's policy objectives in the Middle East. "Obviously there's been deception and there's been lies," Trump said in an interview with The Washington Post when pressed on the many discrepancies in the changing accounts from the Saudis. "Their stories are all over the place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight mars LeBron's home LAKERS debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bc0358b77dfd4fb2a053388a6e3022e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Once the fists started flying late in the fourth quarter, LeBron James' home debut with the Los Angeles Lakers was relegated to the undercard. A wild multiplayer fight that included the normally mild-mannered Chris Paul and Brandon Ingram stole part of the spotlight shining on LeBron's official landing on the West Coast. The Houston Rockets stole the rest with a gritty victory. James scored 24 points, but Paul, Ingram and Rajon Rondo all were ejected after trading blows late in the Rockets' 124-115 win Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Count on Hillary running again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/count-on-hillary-clinton-running-again-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is beyond odd, but here goes. I rise to defend Hillary Clinton. She is under attack and this time, the long knives are wielded by members of her own clan. Suddenly, after two years of indulgin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS, RED SOX World Series Set...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c8dea8857bb84ac1850121ea1810440d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sandy Koufax, Jackie Robinson and the Boys of Summer. Ted Williams to Yaz and the Impossible Dream. Manny Ramirez. Pedro Martinez. Bill Buckner. Fenway Franks and Dodger Dogs. Ebbets Field, the Green Monster. "Sweet Caroline" or "I Love L.A." Yet for all their rich history — dating back to Babe Ruth on the mound — the Boston Red Sox and Los Angeles Dodgers have rarely crossed paths heading into this World Series. Only once before in October, and that was more than a century ago. In fact, Clayton Kershaw has never even pitched at Fenway Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/trump-rallies-in-clinton-won-districts-ahead-of-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is in his happy place – the campaign trail. With the crucial midterm elections just over two weeks away, he’s headlining up to four rallies a week – and staging many of them in toss…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
