<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NIKE-Kaepernick protest backfires on sports store...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ftw/2019/02/13/sports-store-closing-after-nike-colin-kaepernick-protest-backfires/39053759/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turns out a sports store without Nike gear isn't profitable. An owner blamed his protest of Nike for his store closing after 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another wave of store closings coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/02/13/more-store-closures-expected-2019-new-report/2865505002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a report from Coresight Research, more stores closings are on the horizon and there's "no light at the end of the tunnel."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 2020 campaign decision: Quietly agonizing as months go by...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Biden-continues-to-mull-2020-decision-13615997.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden was going to decide whether to run for president by the end of 2018. That deadline slipped. Just after New Year's, he said he would decide "soon." Mid-January came and went with no decision. By the end of January? "We'll make the decision soon," he said at the time. Now into mid-February, with a burgeoning field of Democratic candidates, Biden is still on the fence, neither in nor out, in a lingering state of political limbo. Some potential staffers have already defected, and some of his supporters worry the prolonged indecision could begin to threaten his chances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior at Age 6 May Predict Adult Income...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/13/well/family/behavior-at-age-6-may-predict-adult-income.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez and Trump couldn't be more different -- except for dunks on media...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/When-it-comes-to-calling-out-the-news-media-13614045.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A novice politician hailing from the New York borough of Queens gains enormous media attention and a huge and wildly passionate following in part by lobbing irregular critiques at the news media. Donald Trump in 2015? Yes. But also Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, circa 2019. Their backgrounds, gender and - especially - their politics are different, but the Republican president and the outspoken freshman Democratic congresswoman from New York share at least one similarity: Neither has been shy about using social media to pummel the press. And like Trump, Ocasio-Cortez has been cheered on by millions of followers when she does so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Michael Sanchez? Low-level Hollywood manager pivotal figure in Bezos-Pecker storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-michael-sanchez-20190213-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A previously small-time talent manager has emerged as a pivotal figure in a widening scandal involving the world's richest man — Jeff Bezos — and the National Enquirer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face tattoos: Trend here to stay?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190214-face-tattoos-trend-here-stay-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Face tattoos: a trend that is here to stay?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Usain Bolt? Meet 7-year-old who might be fastest ever seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/sports/hc-sp-usain-bolt-fast-kid-20190213-20190213-wsgjy5q5svc5zlvg7gik2phb5i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was his return to the track over the weekend that drew the latest round of attention to Rudolph Ingram Jr. The Tampa, Florida, youngster, who said he began training when he was 4, left the competition in his wake, winning the 100-meter dash in 13.48 seconds - which would be a U.S. record for his age group. He appears to be picking up where he left off last summer, when he won the 100 and finished second in the 200 in his age group at the AAU championships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's PM May could face another Brexit defeat in parliament...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190214092340-aa88l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (PIX):Britain's PM May could face another Brexit defeat in parliament</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Tax Collectors Look to Divvy Up Tech Giants' Billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/worlds-tax-collectors-look-to-divvy-up-tech-giants-billions-11550145601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development is seeking public input on proposals, including one from the U.S., to determine where the profits of digital companies such as Facebook should be allocated, and therefore which countries get to tax them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro Shows No Sign of Leaving. Now What?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/venezuelas-maduro-shows-no-sign-of-leaving-now-what-11550097501 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s opposition and its U.S. backers figured President Nicolás Maduro’s regime would crumble quickly after Washington threw its support behind a plan to sap his military support and spur his exit. It hasn’t happened that way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Was Supposed to Make LAKERS Great. But When?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/14/sports/lebron-james-lakers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was supposed to be the year Los Angeles, behind James, reclaimed the N.B.A. Five months of drama have a young core wondering when the fun begins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Collect Record Individual Income Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/1665484000000-feds-collect-record-individual-income-taxes-calendar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump signs the Tax Cuts and Jobs Act, Dec.22, 2017. (Getty Images/Chip Somodevilla)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black critics of Kamala, Booker battle 'Russian bot' claims...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/02/13/ados-kamala-harris-cory-booker-russian-bots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Rye and Joy Reid have speculated that American descendants of slaves using the hashtag “ADOS” to critique Harris and Booker are Russian bots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOK Forced to Pay Creators Under New EU Rules...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-facebook-forced-pay-creators-040001510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new rules mean music producers and publishers could come gunning for more money from Alphabet Inc.’s Google and Facebook Inc. to compensate for the display of their songs, video and news articles. If artists and music producers refuse to grant platforms licenses, tech firms will be required to remove</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Exposure to weed killing products increases risk of cancer 41%...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2019/feb/14/weed-killing-products-increase-cancer-risk-of-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evidence ‘supports link’ between exposures to glyphosate herbicides and increased risk for non-Hodgkin lymphoma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ probing leak of Michael Cohen bank records...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/13/politics/michael-cohen-personal-bank-records-charges/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is investigating the leak last year of confidential reports about Michael Cohen's personal bank records which led to revelations that the former Donald Trump lawyer was profiting by selling his access to the White House, two people familiar with the matter say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Singer Ryan Adams accused of sexual misconduct by seven women...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/ryan-adams-accused-of-sexual-misconduct-by-seven-women-1203120264/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer-songwriter Ryan Adams has been accused of sexual misconduct and manipulative behavior, according to a New York Times article published Wednesday. Seven women and more than a dozen associates…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule change sharpens Dem investigations into Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/429934-rule-change-sharpens-dem-investigations-into-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A change to House rules is putting sharper teeth into Democratic investigations of President Trump and his administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETANYAHU: Meeting With Arab Leaders to Combat Iran...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/netanyahu-meetings-in-warsaw-with-arab-leaders-are-in-pursuit-of-war-with-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on Wednesday that his meetings with Arab leaders in Poland are in pursuit of "war with Iran."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With smart sneakers, privacy risks take great leap...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/with-smart-sneakers-the-potential-for-privacy-risks-take-a-great-leap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Privacy experts are waiting for the other shoe to drop on connected kicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 stages, 16 spots for first Democratic debates...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/96040a1e27f04f2f944dddcf2ed4a412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic National Committee Chairman Tom Perez says he'll announce details of the first two presidential primary debates by the end of the week. Perez says he plans to include a grassroots fundraising metric as part of the qualifying threshold. He wants that to make the debate more inclusive than just using polling. The first two debates are slated for June and July. They'll be the first two of six debates in 2019, with at least six more to follow in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Cosby says won't feel remorse because is 'political prisoner'...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/2019/02/13/bill-cosby-says-he-wont-feel-remorse-because-hes-a-political-prisoner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first public statement from prison, Bill Cosby said he will never have remorse for his crimes and called himself a political prisoner. "My political beliefs, my actions of trying to humanize all races, genders and religions landed me in this place surrounded by barb wire fencing, a room made of steel and iron," the comedian said in a statement released through his press spokesman, Andrew Wyatt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: LIAR, LIAR, LIAR</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/judge-rules-paul-manafort-made-false-statements-in-violation-of-plea-agreement-11550101738</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge ruled former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort made intentional false statements to investigators about his contact with a Russian associate despite agreeing to a plea deal requiring him to tell the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racketeering trial shows opioid salesmen used rap video in effort to get more doctors to prescribe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/business/2019/02/13/rap-video-opioid-salesmen-boasted-their-prowess/YsPTTbiDYDq1ZIpEtobmXL/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Insys Therapeutics, that is our name,” the associates sang. “We’re raising the bar and we’re changing the game. To be great it takes a decision, to be better than the competition.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas oil production breaks 1970s record!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/energy/article/Report-Texas-crude-oil-production-breaks-1970s-13606658.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crude oil production in Texas has beat a previous record set in the 1970s, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE insider-trading enforcer accused of insider trading...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2019/02/lawyer-who-wrote-apples-insider-trading-policy-accused-of-insider-trading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer accused of avoiding $377,000 in losses by selling ahead of bad news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-author accuses McConnell of 'sabotage' for calling resolution vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/green-new-deal-co-author-sen-markey-mocked-for-accusing-mcconnell-of-rushing-senate-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the co-authors of the Green New Deal is slamming Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., for announcing he’s bringing the resolution to a vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Motion to Force Mueller to Prove Didn't Leak to CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/13/roger-stone-files-motion-to-force-mueller-to-prove-he-didnt-leak-to-cnn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone filed a motion requesting a federal judge force Mueller to prove he did not tip off CNN about his January 25 arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' jurors warned: Cartel 'strong presence' in NY, stay anonymous...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-mexico-el-chapo-jurors/post-verdict-el-chapo-jurors-rely-on-anonymity-to-stay-safe-idUKKCN1Q230J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When U.S. District Judge Brian Cogan read the verdict finding Joaquin "El C...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Set to Vote on Trillion-Dollar Spending Bill Lawmakers Have NOT Read...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/13/house-vote-spending-bill-read/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is worse than under Speaker Ryan'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegans strike deal with abattoir to give cows 'last rites'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/13/vegans-strike-deal-abattoir-give-cows-last-rites-arrive-slaughterhouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vegan activists have struck a deal with an abattoir to allow them to stage 'last rites' ceremonies with incoming cows to tell them, &amp;quot;we love you, we are sorry&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts blame obesity crisis as average bra size grows to DD...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6698259/More-half-bras-sold-Selfridges-34DD-bigger-34B-just-11-years-ago.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government figures show 36DDs are now the most commonly sold size, while in 2008 it was a 34B. Now, more women are a voluptuous 36DD today, the same size as curvy Kim Kardashian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Lady selfies with damaged car after plowing into woman walking with ex...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/video-woman-struck-in-nc-hit-and-run-while-walking-with-drivers-ex/5129396/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have identified the at-large suspect in a dramatic hit-and-run that was caught on surveillance video last week in Wilmington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor, 100, killed in UK street for $25...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8421315/horrific-injuries-holocaust-survivor-100-killed-street-robbery-cctv-derby/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRUESOME photos show the horrific injuries of a 100-year-old Holocaust survivor who was killed in a cowardly street robbery as CCTV footage revealed the extent of his victim’s ordeal. Self-co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ dioceses names 188 priests accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/news/2019/02/first-nj-diocese-opens-decades-of-secret-files-to-reveal-the-names-of-48-priests-accused-of-sexual-abuse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newly released records date back to 1940, church officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it love? Maybe not, as romance scams proliferate...</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/business/hc-biz-romance-scams-20190213-mahni4mvzfa7zh4ephy2m4qpbe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FTC announced this week that romance-related scams have surged recently and generated more losses than any other consumer fraud reported to the agency last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon releases blueprint for accelerating AI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-releases-blueprint-for-accelerating-artificial-intelligence-204022996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The publication of the Pentagon strategy’s core concepts comes eight months after a Silicon Valley revolt against the military’s premier AI research program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Beating Denver In Snowfall...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/02/12/seattle-beats-denver-snow-to-date/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unusual weather pattern has allowed back-to-back storms to drop record snow across the Pacific Northwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Texas children found in dog cage...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/texas-children-found-dog-cage-placed-foster-care/QXf7idoiu3olbqcjFVQDcK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four malnourished siblings, all aged 5 or younger, have been placed in foster care after authorities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Hires Combat Vets With Rifles To 'Put Down' Active Shooters...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/02/13/school-hires-combat-vets-with-rifles-to-put-down-active-shooters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A charter school in Florida has hired two combat veterans to patrol the grounds with semi-automatic rifles to protect students from any active shooters, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suicide bomber targeting Revolutionary Guard kills 27...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bfb5d18dd16a417eb1bdc87b8c786270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — A suicide car bomber claimed by an al-Qaida-linked group attacked a bus carrying members of Iran's elite Revolutionary Guard paramilitary force Wednesday, killing at least 27 people and wounding 13 others, state media reported. Tehran immediately linked the attack in Iran's restive southeastern Sistan and Baluchistan province to an ongoing U.S.-led conference in Warsaw largely focused on Iran, just two days after the nation marked the 40th anniversary of its 1979 Islamic Revolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating in San Fran 'total nightmare': 'Everyone poly'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/why-dating-is-terrible-hard-apps-tinder-single-13611204.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I spent about six years actively dating around the Bay Area. In that time I dated, for varying amounts of time, three self-described indie rockers, an amateur hockey player, an elementary school teacher with a drinking problem, a yoga teacher who didn't drink alcohol (or consume processed sugars and carbohydrates of any kind), an English teacher living in his mom's in-home daycare, and a skateboarding enthusiast who worked as a manager at a tech company.  These budding relationships ended for various reasons. At least three of the aforementioned men were still in love with their exes. One said he couldn't handle the pressure of texting me "witty responses," and thus could not go on seeing me. Most of the rest were "not looking for something serious."  I attributed these failures not to the region in which I was dating, but to the fraught Millennial dating landscape as a whole. Perhaps I was wrong in thinking this, according to a popular San Francisco Reddit thread, posted just in time for Valentine's Day.  The poster asked, "What annoys you the most about dating in SF?" More than 100 comments later, it appears there is much to be perturbed by. We've included some of the most insightful comments in the above thread. The comments have been lightly edited for clarity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to pay $0 in taxes -- for second year in row...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/823590/amazon-pay-0-federal-income-taxes-second-year-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, which doubled its profits and made more than $11 billion in 2018, won't pay any federal income taxes for the second year in a row, the Institute on Taxation and Economic Policy reported on Wednesday. The company will not be required to pay the standard 21 percent income tax rate on its 2018 profits, and is claiming a tax rebate of $129 million, which ITEP describes as a "a tax rate of negative 1 percent." Amazon drew ire in 2018 for not paying federal taxes on its $5.6 billion in profits the year before, which was made possible due to tax credits and stock-based compensation, reports Politifact. Last year was the first time Amazon paid no federal income tax whatsoever. From 2011 to 2016, Amazon payed federal income tax at a rate of 11.4 percent â€” less than half of the national rate of 35 percent. Due to President Trump's corporate-friendly tax cuts, Amazon will pay any deferred or postponed taxes at the lowered rate of 21 percent rather than the previous rate of 35 percent, per Politifact. Based out of Washington state, which has no income tax, Amazon has also been free from state filings on income. Marianne Dodson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny 320-Square-Foot NH Cottage Hits Market At $2 Million!</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/02/13/portsmouth-nh-cottage-2-million-real-estate-price-for-sale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The home may appear shabby, but it's on prime real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA rover finally bites the dust on Mars after 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/868e731d260f4919b28218dcf345071f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA's Opportunity, the Mars rover that was built to operate just three months but kept going and going, was pronounced dead Wednesday, 15 years after it landed on the red planet. The six-wheeled vehicle that helped gather critical evidence that ancient Mars might have been hospitable to life was remarkably spry up until eight months ago, when it was finally doomed by a ferocious dust storm. Flight controllers tried numerous times to make contact and sent one final series of recovery commands Tuesday night along with one last wake-up song, Billie Holiday's "I'll Be Seeing You." There was no response from space, only silence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Build the Wall' jersey at NBA game sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/sports/nba/sacramento-kings/article226148250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking snowfall cloaks Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190213-record-breaking-snowfall-cloaks-moscow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record-breaking snowfall cloaks Moscow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking cannabis in teens linked to depression later...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6700547/Smoking-cannabis-teens-linked-depression-later-life-damages-brain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cannabis use was also linked to an high risk of suicidal thoughts and attempts. Researchers in the UK and US said tackling under 18s use of the drug should be a public health priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Man steals 69-year-old's purse, groceries...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/watch-video-shows-man-steal-year-old-purse-groceries-south-fulton/jcMWwJsVzIMQhlITiIce0K/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are searching for a man who snatched a purse and groceries from a 69-year-old woman in the Ci...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man releases monster white rat in MCDONALD'S, total chaos ensues...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/02/13/video-shows-man-releasing-rat-inside-new-jersey-mcdonalds-sparking-total-chaos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Total chaos erupted at a McDonald's in Newark, New Jersey after a man released a large white rat inside the crowded restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake doctor promised to cure cancer by injecting own blood...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox13news.com/news/local-news/florida-man-accused-of-being-fake-doctor-claiming-to-cure-diabetes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hernando County man was arrested after deputies say he posed as a doctor and claimed he could cure diabetes.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONER:  Kamala Harris says she smoked pot in college while listening to music [that didn't exist yet]...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/12/kamala-harris-says-she-smoked-marijuana-in-college/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala D. Harris, California Democrat and 2020 presidential hopeful, appears to have fibbed during an interview Monday about smoking marijuana in college while listening to music by Snoop Dogg and Tupac Shakur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Ignores Own Exclusive: Senate Probe Found No Evidence of Collusion...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/nicholas-fondacaro/2019/02/12/nbc-ignores-own-exclusive-senate-probe-found-no-evidence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to an NBC News exclusive that first aired during the 10 o’clock hour of Tuesday morning’s MSNBC Live, both Republican and Democratic sources on the Senate Intelligence Committee admitted they had not found any direct evidence of collusion between the Trump campaign and Russia. Despite the fact the exclusive was filed by NBC News intelligence and national security reporter Ken Dilanian, NBC Nightly News hid it from viewers. Meanwhile, ABC’s World News Tonight and CBS Evening News also turned a blind eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOMBUST:  Record number of Americans 90 days behind car payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/12/a-record-number-of-americans-are-90-days-behind-on-their-car-payments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The level of serious delinquencies broke past the heights reached just after the financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Wall Beto Used Fences, Barricades at Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/12/photos-anti-wall-beto-orourke-uses-fences-barricades-at-el-paso-rally/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While railing against border walls, Rep. Beto O'Rourke stood safely on a stage that walled off supporters behind barriers and barricades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANERA BREAD 'Pay What You Want' Experiment Fails...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/panera-breads-socialist-pay-what-you-want-experiment-fails-miserably/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprising no one who understands history, economics, and human nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Has Most Mosquitoes?</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/lifestyle/dallas-washington-d-c-top-list-of-american-cities-plagued-the-most-by-mosquitoes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some practical tips for combatting the pesky insects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET SHOP BOYS MOCK SOCIAL MEDIA, USERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UuNBJkLLnOs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pet Shop Boys' new four-track â€œAgendaâ€� EP is out now via digital services: https://petshopboys.lnk.to/AgendaID The second song on the EP, â€œOn social mediaâ€�, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STARTS 6 MILES OF  WALL IN TX</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/its-true-trump-really-did-start-building-more-wall-in-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Trump said Monday at a campaign rally in El Paso that, “We’ve actually started a big, big portion of the wall today at a very important location, and it’s going to go up pretty quickly over the next nine months," I assumed it was nonsense he was spreading in hopes that his supporters…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trophy hunters allowed to slaughter thousands of endangered hippos...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8415871/trophy-hunters-hippos-cull-zambia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Zambian government stands to make MILLIONS by letting sick trophy hunters slaughter thousands of hippos in the country, a charity has said. Zambia says the mass killing is being carried out to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usher, Rich the Kid FLASHED CASH before armed robbery...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8415726/usher-rich-the-kid-shooting-hollywood-recording-studio-bodyguard-pistol-whipped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USHER, rapper Rich the Kid and their entourage came under fire in an armed robbery at a Hollywood recording studio on Tuesday, according to reports. A gunman fired up to 10 shots outside Westlake R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson edited out of MOTOWN history in new TV special...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/02/13/motown-60-tv-special-smokey-stevie-diana-but-nary-a-mention-of-michael-jackson-or-the-jackson-5-plus-lionel-richie-drops-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When they edit together the three hour “Motown 60” for CBS (to air in April) it will have some brilliant moments and some headscratchers. Mary Wilson, still Supreme Just about completel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Outfits Thousands of Border Canines With Wearable Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/02/dhs-wants-outfit-its-dogs-wearable-tech/154824/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency is investing in a smart harness that would monitor the health of Border Patrol’s K-9 units.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man releases monster white rat in MCDONALD'S, total chaos ensues...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Chaos-Ensues-After-Man-Releases-Large-Rat-Inside-NJ-McDonalds-505775861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man released a large, white rat into a McDonald’s in New Jersey last week, sending patrons scrambling for the exit in an incident that was caught on video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet personality faces charges over 'invasive' viral videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/internet-personality-plainpotatoess-faces-charges-over-invasive-viral-videos/article_a980e169-403f-519e-b0e6-e487d83ce314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — When Baltimore resident Marquel Carter assumes his viral internet persona called “Plainpotatoess,” he has two goals — to push people to their limits and to catch it on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead mayor advances to runoff in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://newsok.com/article/5622812/voters-keep-late-edmond-mayor-on-ballot-for-general-election-select-new-norman-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsok.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Living in DC Luxury  Apartment Building...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/ocasio-cortez-living-in-luxury-navy-yard-apartment-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After fretting about whether she'd be able to afford rent, Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D., N.Y.) has moved into a luxury apartment building</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker Goes After Meat And Cheese!</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/13/cory-booker-go-vegan-meat-not-sustainable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I remember by last non-vegan meal’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT WANTS TO PICK THE NEWS YOU READ...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/12/dhillon-microsoft-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has developed a browser that directs readers not to look at conservative websites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing photo of lion siblings' tender greeting tops awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8418659/wildlife-photographer-of-the-year-2018-peoples-choice-winner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CAPTIVATING photo of two male lions – brothers – sharing a tender moment has won this year’s Wildlife Photographer of the Year Lumix people’s choice award. The image was snapped by David Lloyd, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accusations of socialism...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article226141885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL GATES: Nobody deserves to be this rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.iol.co.za/news/world/nobody-deserves-to-be-this-rich-bill-gates-19277011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iol.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates said he does not deserve to be so rich, and that he doesn't think leaving his fortune to his children will be good for them or for society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYMARVEL FIRST FEMALE SUPERHERO TAKES FLIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/captain-marvels-brie-larson-cant-save-womankind-but-shes-doing-her-best-1185915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar winner and fierce gender-equality activist is proud to be starring as Carol Danvers in the Disney-owned studio's first female-fronted franchise — just don't conflate its success with the fate of women in Hollywood: "We have been opening movies since the silent era."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST DRAMA: Jussie Smollett cries as he gives his first interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6700077/Jussie-Smollett-cries-gives-interview-homophobic-racist-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor spoke to ABC for an interview that will air on Thursday morning. In a brief promo for the interview, he is seen tearing up after being asked if he feared for his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Californians consider fleeing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/12/growing-number-of-californians-considering-moving-from-state-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of Californians are contemplating moving from the state due to the sky-high cost of living, with sentiment highest among millennial residents, according to a study released Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliens? Strange light spotted in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/society/aliens-strange-light-spotted-in-sugar-land-sky/5136028/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have we made first contact? A bizarre sight in the Sugar Land area has some thinking aliens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte's Media Critic Arrested in Philippines for Libel...</title>
      <link>https://www.malaymail.com/news/world/2019/02/13/colleague-philippines-arrests-journalist-maria-ressa-on-libel-charge/1722671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.malaymail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Feb 13 — Philippine journalist Maria Ressa, who has repeatedly clashed with President Rodrigo Duterte, was arrested in her Manila office today in what rights advocates called an act of “persecution”. Her detention on a charge of “cyber libel” is a dramatic escalation in the legal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON streamlined plastic packaging jamming up recycling centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-amazon-plastic-recycling-20190213-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has been using more plastic mailers instead of cardboard boxes. That plastic needs special recycling and can contaminate other recyclables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KETAMINE nasal spray for depression wins FDA backing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6697129/U-S-FDA-panel-recommends-approval-J-Js-depression-drug.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, the party drug ketamine, or 'special K' has shown promise for treating tough cases of depression. A key FDA panel has given its support to Johnson &amp; Johnson's ketamine-derived spray.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's Boy Wonder Prime Minister Aging as Elections Loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/canada-s-boy-wonder-prime-minister-is-aging-as-elections-loom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadaâ€™s Boy Wonder Prime Minister Is Aging as Elections Loom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired ESPN sportscaster: I'm not leaker...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/12/fired-espn-sportscaster-adnan-virk-im-not-a-leaker/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired ESPN sportscaster Adnan Virk denies he leaked any confidential or proprietary information that caused his termination. In a statement Virk texted to The Post on Tuesday night, Virk said he an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER DEAL KEEPS IT OPEN</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190213132523-hvu9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Trump expected to sign bipartisan funding deal -reports</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
