<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Man caught in landing gear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9901013/Horrific-video-Afghan-caught-landing-gear-c-17-clambering-plane-emerges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage which appears to have been taken from a C-17 military plane leaving Kabul shows a man's legs protruding from the wheel arch and failing against the side of the plane as it cuts through the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghans scramble to delete digital history, evade biometrics...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817111442-4d73x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are fears that government offices and aid agencies may fail to secure databases, leaving people vulnerable to attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As murders surge, Dems find new message: Fund the police...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817110011-4y0w0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-POLICE/DEMOCRATS (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-As murders surge, Democrats find a new message: Fund the police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Star mothers' hearts ache after takeover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817100004-snltv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/GOLDSTAR (PIX, TV):Gold Star mothers' hearts ache after Taliban takeover of Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSE: China holds assault drills near Taiwan after 'provocations'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817050008-3oull</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-TAIWAN/SECURITY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China holds assault drills near Taiwan after 'provocations'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this beginning of end of American gas station?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/17/end-american-gas-station-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A movement in California seeks a moratorium on new pumps – and a transformation of the US transportation system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Giant Purple Nipple Digital Nose of Future?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-08-17/replicating-our-sense-of-smell-is-one-of-the-hardest-problems-in-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new generation of companies is homing in on one of the hardest problems in tech: replicating our sense of smell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Newsom Keep Job? Recall Effort Shows Dead Heat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/17/can-gov-newsom-keep-his-job-a-recall-effort-in-california-shows-a-dead-heat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden sent an urgent message last week to the most populous state in the nation: Keep Gov. Gavin Newsom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces even greater test in preventing extremist resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/after-taliban-triumph-biden-faces-even-greater-test-in-preventing-extremist-resurgence-in-afghanistan/ar-AANosZZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Taliban in power and no neighboring countries willing to permit U.S. bases, the administration will be forced to rethink its strategy for monitoring and targeting extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants announce 'amnesty,' urge women to join govt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-joe-biden-middle-east-kabul-taliban-1d4b052ccef113adc8dc94f965ff23c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban declared an “amnesty” across Afghanistan and urged women to join their government Tuesday, seeking to convince a wary population that they have changed a day after deadly chaos gripped the main airport as desperate crowds tried to flee the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel requests international aid amid masive wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jerusalem-area-blaze-continues-for-second-day-residents-evacuated-676852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency services have evacuated thousands of residents from a number of towns as the fires continue to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Trump 'peace' plan released 5,000 Taliban from prison...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5794643/trumps-disgraceful-peace-deal-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Afghanistan peace plan will strengthen the Taliban and make America less safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan sued for allegedly sexually abusing 12-year-old girl in '65...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/08/16/bob-dylan-sued-for-allegedly-sexually-abusing-12-year-old-in-1965/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dylan allegedly used his star status to groom, gain the trust of and control the victim “as part of his plan to sexually molest and abuse” her, according to the Manhattan Supreme Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REALLY?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/08/16/bob-dylan-hit-with-bogus-lawsuit-claiming-molestation-in-nyc-april-may-1965-not-possible-he-wasnt-there</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On April 26, 1965 Bob Dylan arrived in London. He didn’t return to the United States until June 2nd. In April. he was mostly on the West Coast. All of this is recorded in calendars tracking D…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges dropped for man who crashed autopilot TESLA into cop car while watching movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/car-crash/tesla-crash-pass-659230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla owner who was watching a movie when his car, traveling in autopilot mode, struck a North Carolina police cruiser has walked away from the crash legally unscathed, records show. Prosecutors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks double from pandemic bottom -- fastest rally since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/16/sp-500-doubles-from-its-pandemic-bottom-marking-the-fastest-bull-market-rally-since-wwii.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broad equity benchmark has rallied 100% on a closing basis from its Covid trough of 2,237.40 on March 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as strange 'UFO' flashing light spotted in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3485530/mystery-ufo-flashing-light-beams-river-thames/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOCALS have been left baffled after a strange “UFO” flashing light beams out of the River Thames. People living in Canary Wharf were perplexed last night by the mysterious light that ap…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chant 'Death to America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3484441/taliban-fighters-chant-death-america-protesters-scream-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment Taliban fighters were heard chanting “Death to America” in Kabul while outside the White House protestors scream “Biden you betrayed us”. It comes as President Bid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>640 Pack In to Get Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/policy/2021/08/inside-reach-871-us-c-17-packed-640-people-trying-escape-taliban/184563/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force evacuation flight from Kabul to Qatar came near the record for most people ever flown in the Boeing airlifter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS' Black Rock HQ Building in NYC Sold for $760 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cbs-sells-black-rock-headquarters-760-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Network to lease back its space on short-term basis from new owner Harbor Group International</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osaka Cries, Walks Out of Press Conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/naomi-osaka-breaks-down-in-tears-walks-out-of-first-press-conference-since-withdrawing-from-french-open-for-mental-health-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her first press conference since withdrawing from the French Open citing mental health concerns, tennis superstar Naomi Osaka was reduced to tears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 states set new records as hospitalizations rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/16/we-are-on-fire-five-us-states-set-new-records-for-covid-cases-as-hospitalizations-rise-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital bed capacity correlates closely with vaccination rates. The states with higher vaccination rates are seeing fewer Covid patients take up hospital beds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Monument gets struck by lightning, shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/08/16/washington-monument-gets-struck-by-lightning-closed-down-for-repairs-national-park-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Monument was struck by lightning on Sunday and is closed Monday for repairs, according to the National Mall National Park Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Monument closes after dramatic lightning strike...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/08/washington-monument-closed-for-repairs-after-dramatic-lightning-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Monument will be closed Monday because of a lightning strike that hit it during Sunday morning’s thunderstorms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighters go door to door in Kabul with 'kill list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3482499/taliban-reign-of-terror-fighters-kill-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE TALIBAN’S reign of terror has begun as fighters are reportedly going door-to-door with a kill list and women face torture &amp; execution under brutal new rules. Disturbing reports are al…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Bible Belt preachers silent on shots as Covid surges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-7a03fed8e7548797487f2b7a20161e4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Danny Avula, the head of Virginia’s COVID-19 vaccination effort, suspected he might have a problem getting pastors to publicly advocate for the shots when some members of his own church referred to them as “the mark of the beast,” a biblical reference to allegiance to the devil, and the minister wasn't sure how to respond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Lt. Gov. says unvaccinated may cause lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-hawaii-c87f3f14ba91a55a84b927a7a2af72f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii Lt. Gov. Josh Green, who works as an emergency room doctor on Hawaii's Big Island, says a minority of unvaccinated people are pushing the state toward another lockdown. “I say we are two to four weeks at this rate from seeing major adjustments in what we’re able to do,” Green said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 'undercover incel' world...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3483181/inside-incel-movement-undercover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEN people hear about incels, they often react with sympathy. Shouldn’t we just feel sorry for these losers, these lonely men, they ask? But this isn’t a small group of sad men including Plymouth …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seize thousands of fake vaccination cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Federal-agents-seize-thousands-of-fake-covid-16389769.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bundles of counterfeit coronavirus vaccination cards printed with the Centers for Disease...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo posed with leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9898321/Freed-jail-help-Donald-Trump-Abdul-Ghani-Baradar-head-Afghanistan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here MailOnline reveals the top Taliban chieftains who will rule the new Afghanistan, including Mullah Abdul Ghani Baradar, who was freed from jail just three years ago on American orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Society Dwindles as Permission Requirements Grow...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/16/free-society-dwindles-as-permission-requirements-grow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many things once done as a matter of right are now privileges to be dispensed or withheld by those in power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury scenic train line debuts first US route...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/rocky-mountaineer-train-route-united-states/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Western Canada's luxury scenic train lines, the Rocky Mountaineer, launched its first US route on August 15 between Denver, Colorado, and Moab, Utah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More cops on first day due to 'tensions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-colorado-school-district-brought-more-cops-in-on-the-first-day-of-classes-due-to-tensions-over-its-mask-mandate/ar-AANnM4z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Eagle County School District urged people who disagree with the mask mandate to protest at "locations other than schools" to avoid disruption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODBYE, AFGHANISTAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/talibans-rapid-advance-across-afghanistan-2021-08-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of civilians desperate to flee Afghanistan thronged Kabul airport on Monday after the Taliban seized the capital, prompting the U.S. military to suspend evacuations as the United States came under mounting criticism at home over its pullout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100-Year-Old Woman Sets World Record As Powerlifter!</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/meet-edith-murway-a-100-year-old-powerlifting-great-grandma-officially-in-the-guinness-book-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edith Murway began lifting weights at the young age of 91.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo posed with leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/afghanistan-peace-talks-begin-doha-qatar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protection of rights, particularly women's, will be high on the peace talks agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Badu Apologizes To Obamas After Posting Video From Maskless Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/celebrities/news/2021/08/14/erykah-badu-terrible-guest-barack-obama-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find out why she’s apologizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood Test Tells Whether Patients Will Suffer 'Long Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/long-covid-blood-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one fourth of patients have developed some form of long COVID, per research out of the University of California, Davis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CURE Bassist Exits Band After 40 Years: 'Fed Up of Betrayal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/the-cure-bassist-simon-gallup-leaves-band-1212406/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“With a slightly heavy heart I am no longer a member of the Cure! Good luck to them all,” Gallup writes, adding he’s “fed up of betrayal”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All US personnel safely evacuated from Kabul embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/world-reactions-to-fall-of-afghanistan-676772?_ga=2.19433343.656415151.1628837090-1969581575.1579377799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia sets up contacts with Taliban * 60 countries, including US, issue joint statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches Offer Religious Vaxx Exemption For Parishioners...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/08/16/church-religious-exemption-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some local churches are providing religious exemptions for people who don’t want the vaccine but feel forced as more jobs are starting to require vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SET FOR SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-afghanistan-taliban-5abab9d1a552dc93b10a76973a8b3d25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will address the nation on Monday about the U.S. evacuation from Afghanistan, after the planned withdrawal of American forces turned deadly at Kabul’s airport as thousands tried to flee the country after the Taliban’s takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CURE Bassist Exits Band After 40 Years: 'Fed Up of Betrayal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/the-cure-bassist-simon-gallup-exits-band-after-40-years-fed-up-of-betrayal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News is not "Just Like Heaven" for fans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: California voters split on recall election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/567994-california-voters-split-on-recall-election-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California voters are split on the upcoming recall election of Gov. Gavin Newsom (D), according to a CBS News poll released Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUATION BREAKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-taliban-784681c4400b097cf73b93cec34c5c61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Thousands of Afghans rushed onto the tarmac of Kabul's international airport Monday, so desperate to escape the Taliban capture of their country that they held onto an American military jet as it took off and plunged to death in chaos that killed at least seven people, U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Henri could form soon, Fred forecast to hit Florida, Grace menaces Haiti...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article253517959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tropical depression passing near Bermuda is forecast to turn into Tropical Storm Henri soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'America's back' vow torched...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/biden-s-america-s-back-vow-torched-as-taliban-storm-kabul/article_00e9c7ff-22f0-5a28-bc20-58fed170600c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just last month President Joe Biden defended his Afghanistan pullout by saying that “the likelihood there’s going to be the Taliban overrunning everything and owning the whole country is highly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Youngest Billionaires: How Johnny Boufarhat Built Fortune...</title>
      <link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/how-a-27-year-old-built-a-us-3-billion-fortune-after-an-allergic-reaction-054042845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials are increasingly among the world's ultra-wealthy. Johnny Boufarhat, 27, is one of the world's youngest self-made billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple caught having sex on cliff top during Sydney lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3481875/couple-sex-bondi-beach-cliff-coronavirus-lockdown-sydney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FRISKY couple were spotted having sex on Sydney’s Bondi Beach in front of shocked onlookers, despite the ongoing coronavirus lockdown. Photographer Scott Robinson spotted the pair from the sea as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two women claimed to be dead man's wife. Suit says funeral home deceived one with empty urn...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-women-claimed-to-be-a-dead-man-e2-80-99s-wife-a-lawsuit-says-the-funeral-home-deceived-one-with-an-empty-urn/ar-AANmUUy </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device Makes Seawater Drinkable In Minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drinking-water-device-makes-seawater-drinkable-freshwater-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 785 million people around the world lack a clean source of drinking water, according to the World Health Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Afghan 'Helpers' Cling to Planes as USA Escapes Kabul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/desperate-afghan-e2-80-98helpers-e2-80-99-cling-to-planes-as-us-abandons-them-at-kabul-e2-80-99s-airport/ar-AANnnlD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than 24 hours after the Taliban regained power in Afghanistan, scenes of chaotic desperation played out at Kabul’s main airport as people climbed onto the wings and sides of departing military jets and clambered up gangplanks to try to get onto the last flights out of the capital. At least five people were reported killed after the U.S. military, which has control of the airport, opened fire. It was yet unclear on Monday if they were shot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE FROM KABUL...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/16/afghans-cling-to-us-air-force-plane-as-it-takes-off-in-kabul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Afghans have been filmed desperately chasing after and clinging to a US Air Force plane as it taxied down the runway, as the frightened civilians frantically attempt to flee the countr…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
