<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis on edge as 1st officer charged in George Floyd case goes on trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/minneapolis-on-edge-as-the-first-officer-charged-in-killing-of-george-floyd-goes-on-trial/ar-BB1ekzNy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials have prepared for Derek Chauvin's trial with stepped-up security and community outreach intended to prevent a repeat of last year's subsequent unrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask burning rally in Boise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14259120/idaho-kids-toss-covid-masks-burning-trash-cans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment Idaho kids tossed Covid masks into burning trash cans at a #BurnTheMask rally. Video footage of the mask-burning rally in Boise, Idaho, captured people of ages, includin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near Abraham's birthplace, lone Christians put hope in Francis...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210306-near-abraham-s-iraq-birthplace-lone-christians-put-hope-in-pope</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Near Abraham's Iraq birthplace, lone Christians put hope in Pope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children's hospitals see surge in rare complication...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/06/health/mis-c-covid-19-case-increase-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Katharine Dunn's son, Nolan had been running a low grade fever for about a week, when it started getting higher, she took him to the doctor who said it was likely a regular virus, but she found out it was much worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLCE&amp;GABBANA seeks $600M damages from 2 US bloggers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-milan-boycotts-asia-26f639d44796a5aa5ae9673bd988b46f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The Milan fashion house Dolce&amp;Gabbana has filed a defamation suit in an Italian court seeking over $600 million in damages from two U.S. fashion bloggers who reposted anti-Asian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA may return beachfront land seized from Black family a century ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/mar/07/los-angeles-county-beachfront-land-black-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan Beach used eminent domain in 1924 to force Willa and Charles Bruce, the city’s first Black landowners, off the land</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: #METOO MEANS #HIMTOO</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/05/opinion/sunday/andrew-cuomo-sexual-harassment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats agonize over the fate of a falling star.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOV IN ISOLATION</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-governor-in-isolation-how-andrew-cuomo-lost-his-grip-on-new-york/ar-BB1ej9QC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo came under fire just a few weeks ago over his handling of nursing home deaths in the pandemic, he and his top advisers followed their usual playbook to stem the fallout: They worked the phones, pressing his case in private calls to legislators and other New York Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss 'burqa ban' vote on knife-edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210307-swiss-burqa-ban-vote-on-a-knife-edge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swiss 'burqa ban' vote on a knife-edge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones vs hungry moths: Dutch use hi-tech to protect crops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-netherlands-3fb76e95fefbe0f9a160f330f3c4a075</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONSTER, Netherlands (AP) — Dutch cress grower Rob Baan has enlisted high-tech helpers to tackle a pest in his greenhouses: palm-sized drones seek and destroy moths that produce caterpillars that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Clash With Partying College Students in Boulder...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/news/local/destruction-at-party-on-hill-near-cu-boulder-police-say-we-have-the-scene-dispersed-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boulder police are dealing with a large party on 10th and Pennsylvania on the hill on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students struggling to read behind masks and screens...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/education/2021/03/07/learning-read-amid-covid-online-school-person-kids-lag-behind/4545832001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early data show elementary students are dramatically falling behind in reading. We visited schools to find out how teachers are meeting the challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala caught between restless base and traditionalist Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Harris-caught-between-a-restless-base-and-a-16006074.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea, USA scale back drills over virus, NKorea diplomacy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seoul-diplomacy-south-korea-north-korea-coronavirus-pandemic-5c71968ba53f66ad6c12a7189c184673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — The South Korean and U.S. militaries are scaling back their annual exercises this month due to the COVID-19 pandemic and to support diplomacy focusing on North Korea’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Films! Novels! Springsteen! The Obamas and Clintons seem to be having the time of their lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/Films-Novels-Springsteen-The-Obamas-and-16004880.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former presidents long slipped into a life soaked in sepia. They farmed on bucolic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narcissism contagious...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/03/06/narcissism-can-be-contagious--and-the-repercussions-extend-beyond-relationships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Narcissists can "infect" those they are close to — with devastating results for relationships as well as politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard intercepts vessel carrying 25 Haiti migrants off Jupiter coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/us-coast-guard-intercepts-vessel-carrying-25-haiti-migrants-off-jupiter-coast/article_6c75cdfb-34e8-5ef2-a8ea-de029118cff3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUPITER, Fla. — Authorities intercepted a vessel carrying 25 Haitian migrants northeast of the coast of Jupiter this week, the U.S. Coast Guard reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many white Evangelicals are reluctant...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/the-spiritual-problem-at-the-heart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why are so many white Evangelicals reluctant to consider the health of their community?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus reaches previously Covid-free New Caledonia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210307-virus-reaches-previously-covid-free-new-caledonia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virus reaches previously Covid-free New Caledonia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE WOMEN ACCUSE CUOMO</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/06/two-more-women-accuse-gov-andrew-cuomo-of-inappropriate-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more women came forward Saturday to accuse Gov. Cuomo of sexually harassing behavior, including a former press aide who describes struggling to free herself from his repeated hugs, and a young …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Brooks Resigns From Nonprofit After More Evidence Of Conflicts Emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/times-columnist-david-brooks-told-people-to-join-nextdoor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His resignation comes amid new revelations of entanglements with Nextdoor and the Walton Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov in Isolation: How Cuomo Lost Grip on New York...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/06/a-governor-in-isolation-how-andrew-cuomo-lost-his-grip-on-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo came under fire just a few weeks ago over his handling of nursing home deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As violence surges, some question Portland axing police unit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-shootings-police-violence-coronavirus-pandemic-704eeab551b452658cf2fa91a123b483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Elmer Yarborough got a terrifying call from his sister: She wept as she told him two of his nephews may have been shot in broad daylight as they left a bar in Portland,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov in Isolation: How Cuomo Lost Grip on New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/06/nyregion/cuomo-crisis-sexual-harassment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid calls for his resignation, the governor is relying on a shrinking circle of advisers to help him navigate the biggest crises of his political life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Jack auctions first ever tweet as digital memorabilia...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210306010413-3jzpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Buzz: Crypto Mogul Bids $2 Million for Dorsey Tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/social-media-buzz-crypto-mogul-bids-2-million-for-dorsey-tweet/ar-BB1ejvG3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- What’s buzzing on social media this morning: Jack Dorsey, Twitter’s co-founder and chief executive, is selling his first-ever tweet -- “just setting up my twttr”-- on a website called Valuables that auctions tweets. The highest bid is $2 million as of Saturday morning in New York, by Justin Sun, the Chinese crypto entrepreneur who earlier won an auction for Warren Buffett’s charity dinner. Valuables said on its website that owning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Swarm of 20,000 quakes could make Iceland's volcanoes erupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/iceland-earthquakes-volcanic-eruption-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents have been 'waking up to earthquakes' every day for more than a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist warns public on danger of patronizing horror films...</title>
      <link>https://mb.com.ph/2021/03/05/priest-exorcist-warns-public-on-the-danger-of-patronizing-horror-films/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mb.com.ph&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exorcist priest said patronizing horror films or films that deal with magic and witchcraft is "dangerous" as this could lead to possible demonic possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Hypersonic Missile Set for Inaugural Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39634/agm-183-hypersonic-missile-to-make-first-flight-within-30-days-according-to-air-force</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new schedule comes after an Air Force official said just recently that the first flight test of the AGM-183 would take place this past week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American porn star sparks fury in Tehran after stripping off in Iranian music video...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2459626/porn-star-alexis-texas-sparks-fury-tehran-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORN star Alexis Texas has sparked fury in Tehran after stripping off her clothes in an Iranian music video – prompting hardliners to want her banned. Iranian pop star Sasan Yafteh – wh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen urged to 'publicly apologize'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1406401/Queen-Elizabeth-II-news-Meghan-Markle-Oprah-Winfrey-US-The-View-celebrities-latest-vn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US CELEBRITIES have rallied around Meghan Markle ahead of her interview with Oprah Winfrey, with co-hosts from popular US talk show The View calling on the Queen to publicly apologise to the Duchess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditation linked to lower cholesterol, blood pressure, blood sugar...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1406451/how-to-live-longer-meditation-lower-cholesterol-blood-pressure-blood-sugar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDITATION is "about training in awareness and getting a healthy sense of perspective", noted Headspace - an app that guides its users on how to meditate. Now a research study demonstrated the lifeskill can achieve so much more.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
