<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mystery shaking, boom heard across San Diego for third time...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-06-08/mystery-shaking-felt-boom-heard-across-san-diego-county-for-third-time-in-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the third time since February, a mysterious "skyquake" rattled San Diego County and Tijuana; authorities say it wasn't an earthquake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA asks office staff for help, offers bonuses and mandates overtime to keep checkpoints moving...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tsa-asks-office-staff-for-help-offers-bonuses-and-mandates-overtime-to-keep-airport-checkpoints-moving/ar-AAKRET9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA put out a call over Memorial Day weekend asking agency employees to volunteer to take on shifts helping at 131 airports facing a "staffing challenge."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite vow of poverty, nun stole $830,000 from Catholic school, prosecutors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/despite-her-vow-of-poverty-nun-stole-more-than-24830000-from-a-catholic-school-prosecutors-said/ar-AAKR6Zo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sister Mary Margaret Kreuper, 79, pleaded guilt to wire fraud and money laundering charges after prosecutors said she embezzled more than $835,000 from St. James Catholic School in Torrance, Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump election fraud claims propelled them to Capitol. His ongoing comments keeping them in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-s-election-fraud-claims-propelled-them-to-16235117.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Many of those charged in the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol have blamed former...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest Meme Stocks Extend Gains With No Sign of Craze Fading...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/newest-meme-stocks-extend-gains-092445847.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The newest additions to the meme-stock frenzy surged in premarket trading as retail traders latched on to their latest favorites.ContextLogic Inc. soared 32% and Clover Health Investments Corp. rose 17% as of 6:30 a.m. in New York, both extending huge gains on Tuesday. Fast-food restaurant chain Wendy’s Inc. edged higher, extending Tuesday’s 26% advance and brushing aside a downgrade from Stifel.There’s no sign of the meme-stock craze slowing as members of Reddit’s WallStreetBets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software bug blamed for global internet outage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/software-technology-business-71e6096a8fae0c44e988d3eefe9bca8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Fastly, the company hit by a major outage that caused many of the world's top websites to go offline briefly this week, blamed the problem on a software bug that was triggered when a customer changed a setting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Kim Jong Un's $12,000 IWC Watch Says About His Weight Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/what-kim-jong-un-e2-80-99s-2412000-iwc-watch-says-about-his-weight-loss/ar-AAKRAdn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un certainly looked slimmer last weekend when he emerged from his latest lengthy absence. But it may be the North Korean leader’s Swiss timepiece that provides the clearest evidence he’s been watching his weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's press plane was about to depart. Then cicadas 'invaded' engines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-press-plane-was-about-to-head-to-europe-then-brood-x-cicadas-e2-80-98invaded-e2-80-99-the-engines/ar-AAKQR6N </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Cases Surge Over 10,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/russian-covid-cases-surge-over-10-000-for-first-time-since-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Covid Cases Surge Over 10,000 for First Time Since March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive World of Diamonds in Grips of Buying Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/buying-frenzy-drives-price-surge-in-the-hidden-world-of-diamonds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spiking prices, and buyers’ willingness to pay them, are the latest sign of roaring demand in the secretive rough-diamond trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Paying 0.00%. Depositors Flocking...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-09/the-fed-is-paying-0-00-such-a-deal-depositors-are-flocking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed’s none-too-generous interest rate attracted $497 billion in funds on June 8</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyprus, Malta Warned Over Passports for Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-09/cyprus-and-malta-warned-by-eu-over-passports-for-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cyprus and Malta were warned again by the European Commission to stop so-called ‘golden passport’ programs that grant European Union citizenship to investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden heads to Europe at difficult moment for domestic agenda...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/557461-biden-heads-to-europe-at-difficult-moment-for-his-domestic-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is headed to Europe on Wednesday, an inopportune time for his first foreign trip as president as his domestic priorities hit the rocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Type of Exercise? Blood Test Holds Clues...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/09/the-best-type-of-exercise-a-blood-test-holds-clues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If we all begin the same exercise routine tomorrow, some of us will become much fitter, others will get a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Known as Max Is 55-Year-Old Woman From Russia, U.S. Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/hacker-known-as-max-is-55-year-old-woman-from-russia-us-says/ar-AAKRtxB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alla Witte’s plans for a new career as a computer programmer included helping clients make enough money to see the world, according to YouTube videos and social media posts. She was in her late 40s with a degree in applied mathematics and an itch to do computer programming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border surge sends prices soaring; Smugglers can earn $200,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/8/border-surge-sends-prices-soaring-smugglers-can-ea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victoria Perez spent 10 months as a migrant smuggler. When agents finally caught up with her, she told them she had made $200,000 over that time, working two days a week, driving migrants through a Border Patrol highway checkpoint near El Paso, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators request Supreme Court travel records...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/06/08/whitehouse-and-kennedy-request-supreme-court-travel-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key senators asked the Justice Department and the U.S. Marshals Service for information about the last 10 years of trips for justices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plexiglass Is Everywhere, With No Proof It Keeps Covid at Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/small-business/plexiglass-everywhere-no-proof-its-keeping-covid-bay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian UPS Driver Brutally Beaten, Robbed Of Package In Broad Daylight In Middle Of San Fran Street...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/08/ups-driver-attacked-viral-video-vicious-robbery-attempt-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UPS driver was just doing his job when a thief swiped a package from his car, and then beat him in the middle of a San Francisco street. The victim opened up exclusively for the first time to KPIX 5's Betty Yu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declares 'new era' for US, Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vice-president-harris-meets-mexicos-144319172.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris met with Mexican President López Obrador after visiting Guatemala and drawing criticism for telling Central Americans to "not come" to U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought-hit California scales up plan to truck salmon to ocean...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drought-hit-california-scales-plan-013704446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With chronic drought drying up rivers earlier than usual this year, California is scaling up a drastic operation to help its famous Chinook salmon reach the Pacific -- transporting the fry by road in dozens of large tanker trucks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW RICH AVOID TAX</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-secret-irs-files-trove-of-never-before-seen-records-reveal-how-the-wealthiest-avoid-income-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ProPublica has obtained a vast cache of IRS information showing how billionaires like Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk and Warren Buffett pay little in income tax compared to their massive wealth — sometimes, even nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ransomware attack: 60 members of Congress left unable to access data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9664229/60-members-Congress-parties-victims-latest-ransomware-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 60 members of Congress from both parties have been unable to access data for weeks in the latest ransomware attack to strike the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris hears criticism from all sides amid difficult first trip...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/557433-harris-hears-criticism-from-all-sides-amid-difficult-first-trip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris is enduring a difficult first foreign trip as vice president, highlighting the difficulty she faces in her role as the Biden administration’s chief official handling the flow of migrants from Central America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microscopic Animal Brought Back To Life After Being Buried For 24,000 Years!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/animal-brought-back-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say the tiny creature, dug out of the subsurface soil in a state of "suspended animation," has even reproduced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Israeli airstrike targets Syria from Lebanese airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/alleged-israeli-airstrike-targets-syria-from-lebanese-airspace-670476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OXFORD votes to remove portrait of Queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9664583/Oxford-University-college-votes-remove-portrait-Queen-common-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Common room members at Magdalen College passed the measure by a substantial majority, with one student commenting that 'patriotism and colonialism are not really separable'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global treaty to regulate plastic pollution gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/global-treaty-to-regulate-plastic-pollution-gains-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even producers have an interest in global rules on plastic waste that would resolve the inconsistencies among countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ERS rookies freak about Bay Area housing cost...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/blog/san-francisco-49ers/post/_/id/39107/sticker-shock-49ers-rookies-warned-about-bay-area-housing-cost</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average house in Santa Clara County sells for $1.96 million -- a lot more than in markets like Green Bay or Trey Lance's Marshall, Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Alyssa Milano mulls run for Congress...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/politics/actress-alyssa-milano-considers-congressional-run-for-cas-4th-district-report/10762622/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Alyssa Milano is reportedly considering a run for Congress for California's 4th District, which includes Sierra communities from Truckee, down to Kings Canyon National Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Publishes, Deletes Article Claiming Watermelons Found on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/new-york-times-watermelons-mars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This afternoon, the New York Times published an article making a surprising claim about exobiology: that watermelons had been discovered on Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid mega-drought, rightwing militia stokes water rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jun/08/klamath-falls-oregon-protests-ammon-bundy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrations have sparked fears of a confrontation between law enforcement and rightwing anti-government activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pharmacist Who Destroyed 500 Doses Of Vax Sentenced To 3 Years In Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/steven-brandenburg-sentenced-three-years-prison-tampering-covid-19-vaccine-doses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Brandenburg pleaded guilty in February to two felony counts of attempting to tamper with a consumer product.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES writer 'disturbed' by sight of American flags...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/new-york-times-editorial-board-member-disturbed-by-sight-of-american-flags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gay said the message of the American flag is ‘this is my country, this is not your country, I own this.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC eases travel recommendations on 110 countries...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210608175629-kry0s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-AIRLINES (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. CDC eases travel recommendations on 110 countries, territories including Japan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France launches 'health pass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210608-covid-19-france-resumes-indoor-dining-launches-health-pass-as-next-phase-of-easing-lockdown-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France enters its third and penultimate phase of easing Covid-19 restrictions on Wednesday as indicators continue to show the country's rate of infections subsiding. FRANCE 24 looks at the changes in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scandal Rocking the Evangelical World...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/06/russell-moore-sbc/619122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sudden departure of Russell Moore is forcing an overdue conversation about the crises of American Christendom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-To Lawyer for Embattled Politicians Now Faces Own Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/06/abbe-lowell-is-the-go-to-lawyer-for-embattled-politicians-now-he-faces-a-controversy-of-his-own/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former client says Lowell never informed her he was under Justice Department scrutiny when he negotiated her plea deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antibody tests on arrival could be Hong Kong's next step...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3136429/coronavirus-antibody-tests-arrival-could-be-hong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centre for Health Protection studying when new screening should be introduced; city confirms three new Covid-19 cases, all imported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tough questions over $56K-a-year newly approved Alzheimer's drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/08/biogen-faces-tough-questions-over-56k-a-year-price-of-newly-approved-alzheimers-drug.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biogen on Tuesday faced tough questions from Wall Street analysts over the $56,000 annual cost of its newly approved Alzheimer's drug, Aduhelm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-red Idaho sees growing clash between Republicans, far right...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/id-state-wire-idaho-gun-politics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-23bdc41f0253b1c132f08ed29f0e10a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — The dream world for Idaho’s ascendant far right is one where state lawmakers run a sovereign nation-state free of federal oversight. It would be a place where they can outlaw all abortions, dictate what is taught in schools, have complete say over public health rules and gun laws, and take control of federal public lands, which make up more than 60% of the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers Watched by 15,000+ Surveillance Cameras...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/07/new-yorkers-are-watched-by-more-than-15000-surveillance-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have only official assurances that the technology isn’t being used to invade their privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FONDA:  He's Not Acting Fast Enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jane-fonda-condemns-biden-for-failing-to-be-bold-on-climate-change-hes-not-acting-fast-enough/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just days after protesting a pipeline project in Minnesota, Jane Fonda joined CNN's Brianna Keilar to address President Joe Biden's climate policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JACK DORSEY: I'D QUIT TWITTER FOR BITCOIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/newsletters/protocol-fintech/-square-crypto-wallet-bitcoin-strategy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clean bitcoin mining and a hardware wallet are expanding Square's bitcoin exposure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapped in face!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210608-french-president-macron-slapped-during-trip-to-south-two-people-arrested</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron was slapped Tuesday in the face by a man during a visit to a small town in southeastern France, an incident that prompted a wide show of support for French politician…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why burnout won't go away, even as life returns to 'normal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Why-burnout-won-t-go-away-even-as-life-returns-16232980.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Marcia Howard, the Cheez-Its were a breaking point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tough fight looms against ransomware 'epidemic'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tough-fight-looms-against-ransomware-153209852.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest wave of ransomware attacks hitting the United States and globally portends a difficult battle against hackers, even as government and the private sector ramp up defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA, GOVT WEBSITES HIT</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/media-government-websites-worldwide-hit-114336248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major media and government websites, including the White House, New York Times, Reddit and Amazon were temporarily down on Tuesday after being hit by a global outage blamed on a glitch from cloud computing services provider Fastly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WEB OUTAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/internet-outage-down-fastly-7c607c931faba19584975da74c8fa633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Dozens of websites briefly went offline around the globe Tuesday, including CNN, The New York Times and Britain's government home page, after an outage at the cloud computing service Fastly, illustrating how vital a small number of behind-the-scenes companies have become to running the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple caught having sex inside playground's crawling tunnel...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/vero-beach-tunnel-of-love-275930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 8--Responding to a 9:10 AM tip about a couple trysting in a Florida park, a patrolman discovered a man performing a sex act on his girlfriend within the “children’s crawling tunnel” at Pocahont</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked Florida woman trashes restaurant before being 'Tasered in breasts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3037915/naked-woman-trashes-restaurant-tasered-cops-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NAKED woman destroyed a restaurant in Florida during a rampage before she was Tasered “in her breasts” by police, footage shows. Tina Kindred, 53, was acting “out of control” as staff…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven sharks circle beachgoers on rubber raft in Pensacola...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3033156/hammerhead-sharks-swarm-pensacola-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment when a group of hammerhead sharks swarmed shallow water alongside beachgoers. Jacqueline Lesso was on a boat while three other women floated on a raft when they all spot…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oops!... She Did It Again:  Britney's bizarre posts ramp up ahead of conservatorship hearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3036583/britney-spears-shocks-fans-calls-herself-motherfing-snake-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears shocked fans as the star called herself a “motherf***ing snake” in a bizarre rant. The 39-year-old wore a snakeskin bodysuit in the new Instagram post, which was shared o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sets world record by giving birth to -- 10 babies!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/woman-sets-world-record-giving-24274044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother in South Africa has smashed the record the number of babies born from a single pregnancy as she gave birth to seven boys and three girls - and they were all conceived naturally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS:  Russia's space chief threatens to leave ISS program unless U.S. lifts sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/russia-threatens-to-leave-international-space-station-program.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ISS is the largest hub for scientific research and collaboration in orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu meets fate on Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-government-confidence-vote-bennett-lapid-e8e69d30-866a-4cfa-ba86-608727164a66.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's security chief is warning of Jan. 6-style violence if Netanyahu is ousted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Sent Her iPhone to APPLE. Repair Techs Uploaded Her Nudes to FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbkey/she-sent-her-iphone-to-apple-repair-techs-uploaded-her-nudes-to-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple paid a woman millions to prevent a lawsuit, but it could have avoided all of this if she’d just been able to repair her own phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES asking employees to volunteer to help with summer rush...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/557297-american-airlines-employees-asking-to-volunteer-to-handle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines is asking its employees to volunteer at Dallas Fort Worth International Airport to help handle the travel surge occurring this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Record 70% Support Same-Sex Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/350486/record-high-support-same-sex-marriage.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. support for legal same-sex marriage continues to grow, now at 70% -- a new high in Gallup's trend dating to 1996.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL WEB OUTAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-7c607c931faba19584975da74c8fa633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Dozens of websites briefly went offline around the globe Tuesday, including CNN, The New York Times and Britain's government home page, after an outage at the cloud service Fastly, illustrating how vital a small number of behind-the-scenes companies have become to running the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As grocery prices rise, alternative meat takes bigger bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-grocery-prices-rise-alt-meat-takes-a-bigger-bite-of-big-meat-e2-80-99s-burger/ar-AAKPkhx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plant-based proteins surge in grocery sales during the pandemic, with their prices falling rapidly as companies grow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have trouble sleeping? You're at higher risk of dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2021-06/nu-hts060421.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eurekalert.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first-known study to examine the effect of the combination of insomnia and diabetes on mortality risk, participants who had both diabetes and frequent sleep disturbances were 87% more likely to die in following 9 years than those who did not have diabetes or frequent sleep difficulties. The study asked one simple question, which the study authors said clinicians and patients should be asking themselves to help address underlying causes of sleep disturbances sooner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superrich Bought Up Idaho Town. Now Regular Folks May Live in Tents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/superrich-bought-idaho-town-regular-085413034.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photo Courtesy Brad WomackAffordable housing in Ketchum—the Idaho resort community adjacent to billionaire and celebrity playground Sun Valley—has been a problem for decades.But the situation is becoming so dire in the wake of COVID-19 that city officials are considering an unusual range of quick fixes—including building tent cities and RV parks for the common folk in the ultra-rich mountain town, where the average median home listing price is hovering abo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapped in face!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210608115832-97p4v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-POLITICS/MACRON (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-France's Macron slapped in face during walkabout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man admits on FACEBOOK Live to killing partner, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-0f9fe058acc911c1c517a83c1d6ea222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIVERVIEW, Fla. (AP) — A man who announced on social media that he had killed his boyfriend and called on deputies to shoot him as well finally set his condo on fire and turned a gun on himself, a Florida sheriff said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women filmed twerking on top of cop car in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9662689/Three-women-filmed-twerking-police-car-Chicago-similar-incidents-Seattle-St-Louis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police is investigating a viral video showing women dancing and twerking on top of a CPD cruiser.. This cell phone video has gone viral on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUGATTI reveals most powerful car on planet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/money/cars/article-9661077/Ten-things-need-know-Bugattis-new-3-3m-Chiron-Super-Sport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The limited-edition road car is based on the £2.5million 'standard' Chiron but offers increased performance, improved aerodynamics and a svelte, missile-like body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/disclosetv/status/1402248572217794571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble in LA County: Too Many Peacocks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/08/trouble-in-los-angeles-county-too-many-peacocks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;County officials in Los Angeles have a request: Please don’t feed the peacocks. In that slice of Southern California, peafowl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapped in face by man in crowd...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/two-arrested-french-president-macron-124910679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were arrested after French President Emmanuel Macron was slapped by a man during a walkabout session with a crowd in the Drome region in southeastern France, BFM TV and RMC radio reported on Tuesday. BFM TV and RMC published a video clip, circulating on Twitter, which shows a man in a green T-Shirt, with glasses and a face mask shout out "Down with Macronia" ("A Bas La Macronie") and then deliver a slap to Macron's face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As DeSantis takes aim at cruise industry, Republicans step up attacks on longtime allies in corporate America...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/as-desantis-takes-aim-at-cruise-industry-republicans-step-up-attacks-on-longtime-allies-in-corporate-america/ar-AAKOXVE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise ship companies announce varying vaccine rules as they face stiff political pressure in the South.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uyghurs deported from Muslim countries; Concerns about China's growing reach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/08/middleeast/uyghur-arab-muslim-china-disappearances-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After reports of Uyghur disappearances in some major Arab countries, such as the United Arab Emirates, Saudi Arabia and Egypt, some of China's ethnic Muslims fear they are no longer safe in parts of the Islamic world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE new 'private relay' feature will not be available in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607224521-1toz4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE-PRIVACY/ (URGENT):Apple's new 'private relay' feature will not be available in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed city of Arabs and Jews remains on edge after violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-violence-voting-rights-09c80818b76620ec0b4d801a478df2f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOD, Israel (AP) — Israeli security forces guard the streets of Lod, weeks after rioters torched patrol cars, synagogues and homes. Attackers who killed an Arab and a Jewish resident are still at large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wandering elephants becoming international stars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-wandering-elephants-becoming-international-stars-05a39c9aac67013d4e7187285f55ea3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Already famous at home, China’s wandering elephants are now becoming international stars. Major global media are chronicling the herd's more than yearlong, 500-kilometer (300-mile) trek from their home in a wildlife reserve in mountainous southwest Yunnan province to the outskirts of the provincial capital of Kunming.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
