<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Something Bothering You? Tell Woebot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/something-bothering-you-tell-it-to-woebot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I understand that you’re experiencing a relationship problem, is that right?” Yes. “Okay, I’m delighted that you want to work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World Ran Out of Everything...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/how-the-world-ran-out-of-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the story of how the modern world was constructed, Toyota stands out as the mastermind of a monumental advance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variants to be given Greek alphabet names to avoid stigma...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/01/covid-19-variants-to-be-given-greek-alphabet-names-to-avoid-stigma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO unveils new names for variants of concern to replace ones linked to where they were discovered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peru leads global mortality rate after adjusting Covid toll...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/peru-leads-global-mortality-rate-183952477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peru on Monday more than doubled its official coronavirus death toll, becoming the country with the highest Covid-19 mortality per capita anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In time for summer, Europe sees dramatic fall in cases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-music-travel-premier-league-d4982700d81ae5a7cfc58c14a7d145eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — When Italy won the Eurovision Song Contest with an over-the-top glam-rock performance, the victory signaled more than just a psychological boost for one of the countries hardest hit by COVID-19: Held before a live, indoor audience of 3,500, the annual kitsch fest confirmed that Europe was returning to a semblance of normalcy that was unthinkable even a few weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correctional officers who slept while Epstein hanged himself planned to slam federal prison system at trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-mcc-epstein-suicide-correctional-officers-sleeping-20210531-mj2ifnsefzbj7g3zjltj7e747a-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two federal correctional officers who neglected their duties while Jeffrey Epstein killed himself inside a troubled lower Manhattan jail planned to defend themselves as scapegoats for a deeply dysfunctional system had they gone on trial, sources told the Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief slams Ted Cruz for claiming 'woke' policies turning military into 'pansies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/05/31/pentagon-chief-slams-ted-cruz-for-abetting-russia-and-china-with-claim-that-woke-policies-are-turning-army-into-pansies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin slammed Sen. Ted Cruz on Monday for accusing the Army of projecting an image of “pansies” because of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado man seriously injured by bear attack -- inside his home...</title>
      <link>https://www.coloradoan.com/story/news/2021/05/31/colorado-bear-attack-injures-man-near-steamboat-springs/5281453001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.coloradoan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man encountered a sow and two cubs in his garage in unincorporated Routt County near Steamboat Springs when we went to close the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  USA Covid cases near  low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/post-pandemic-40-percent-americans-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-day average for new COVID-19 cases has fallen to about 12,000 per day, numbers not seen since March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday still subdued by pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531205350-bzcmw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HOLIDAY/MEMORIALDAY (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Americans hit the road on Memorial Day holiday, a year after pandemic slammed travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat latest cyber victim as hackers hit top supplier...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meat-latest-cyber-victim-hackers-214130697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The world’s biggest meat supplier was the target of a cybersecurity attack Sunday in the latest threat to global food supply chains that have been rattled by the pandemic.JBS SA shut its North American and Australian computer networks after an organized assault on servers, the company said by email Monday. Without commenting on operations at its plants, JBS said the incident may delay certain transactions with customers and suppliers.The attack sidelined two shifts and halted processing at one of Canada’s largest meatpacking plants, while the Australian Financial Review earlier reported that cattle and sheep slaughtering had been suspended at JBS’s operations in Australia, citing country manager Brent Eastwood. There were no immediate reports of plant disruptions in the U.S.Hackers have the commodities complex in their crosshairs with the JBS attack coming just three weeks after the operator of the biggest U.S. gasoline pipeline was targeted. It comes as the meat industry battles lingering Covid-19 absenteeism after recovering from mass outbreaks last year that saw plants shut and supplies disrupted.JBS’s incident affected a Canadian beef plant in Brooks, Alberta, about 190 kilometers (118 miles) east of Calgary, on Monday, according to Scott Payne, spokesman for United Food and Commercial Workers Canada Union Local 401.“There are no unionized workers there,” Payne said in a phone interview. “That means effectively the plant’s operations have shut for the day.”JBS didn’t immediately respond to requests for comment on the Canadian closure.A JBS packaging facility in Belleville, Ontario, where beef, pork and salmon are prepared for grocery stores, was operating normally, said Tim Deelstra, a spokesman for UFCW Canada Local 175. Dakar Lanzino, an external UFCW representative, said he had no information on whether the attack had disrupted plants in the U.S. Monday, a public holiday.Sao Paulo-based JBS owns facilities in 20 countries. Australia and New Zealand account for 4% of the company’s revenue, while the U.S. represents 50% and Canada 3%, according to company fillings.A ransom-ware attack forced Colonial Pipeline Co. to stop the flow of fuel for several days earlier this month, causing severe gasoline shortages in some areas.(Updates with Ontario plant operating normally)More stories like this are available on bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico raids building project next to pyramids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-travel-lifestyle-science-c251a6dc3289adc3d64b50c5cd253a2e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico sent in 250 National Guard troops and 60 police officers Monday to seize land next to the pre-Hispanic ruins of Teotihuacán where authorities have said bulldozers were destroying outlying parts of the archeological site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, NEW HAMPSHIRE!  Nevada OKs bill in try for 1st presidential nominating state...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ia-state-wire-nevada-bills-election-2020-government-and-politics-f2a8771919ea6d6f66e6b4ea54a80fb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Nevada lawmakers passed a bill on Monday that aims to make the state the first to weigh in on the 2024 presidential primary contests. The move upends decades of political tradition and is likely to prompt pushback from other early states that want to retain their places in the calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn Backtracks on Calling For Coup...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/mike-flynn-tries-to-backtrack-on-apparent-call-for-military-coup-in-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Flynn, the first national security adviser to President Donald Trump, has backtracked on comments apparently endorsing a violent coup in the United States. Flynn, the retired general who was hired, fired and then pardoned by Trump, made the alarming comment in an appearance at a conference organized by supporters of the QAnon conspiracy theory. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge American flag stolen from veterans cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-lifestyle-veterans-f7d3182c1f7786c39d2c8d006e8c49cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Authorities said a huge American flag and several smaller flags were stolen from a Southern California veterans cemetery over the Memorial Day weekend. Les' Melnyk, a spokesperson for the Department of Veterans Affairs' National Cemetery Administration, said the garrison flag at Los Angeles National Cemetery was reported stolen sometime late Sunday or early Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon monitoring warships that may be headed to Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/29/iranian-warships-venezuela-491414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tehran's intent in sending the vessels in the direction of the Western Hemisphere remains a mystery, as does their cargo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flynn's Comment That Coup 'Should Happen' in USA Sets Off Uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/this-is-sedition-pure-and-simple-mike-flynns-comment-that-a-myanmar-style-coup-should-happen-in-the-u-s-sets-off-an-uproar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former National Security Adviser Michael Flynn set off a firestorm with comments over the weekend at a conference in Dallas organized by QAnon supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Under Renewed Pressure Following Mafia Boss Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/europe/turkeys-erdogan-under-renewed-pressure-following-mafia-boss-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Turkish government is facing accusations of arming and funding jihadists in Syria. The allegations are just the latest by an exiled mafia boss in a weekly YouTube broadcast that are putting the Turkish president in an increasingly tight spot.     Among the many allegations being spread by Sedat Peker on YouTube is one that allegedly implicates the Turkish government of arming and buying oil from Syrian jihadists. In one of his broadcasts Peker explains in detail how key aides of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan ran the scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA eyes shuttered malls, stores for new housing...</title>
      <link>https://wnyt.com/money/california-eyes-shuttered-malls-stores-for-new-housing-/6126952/?cat=12987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wnyt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LeBron's Agent Is Transforming the Business of Basketball...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/06/07/lebron-james-agent-is-transforming-the-business-of-basketball</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Paul is known for driving hard bargains for star clients, giving them new power in the N.B.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov plans to strip Legislature's pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/texas-governor-strip-legislative-branch-of-pay-2021-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"No pay for those who abandon their responsibilities," Texas Gov. Greg Abbott wrote on Twitter when announcing his plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In post-pandemic Europe, migrants will face digital fortress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-europe-migration-technology-health-c23251bec65ba45205a0851fab07e9b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEPLO, Greece (AP) — As the world begins to travel again, Europe is sending migrants a loud message: Stay away! Greek border police are firing bursts of deafening noise from an armored truck over the frontier into Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals 'bouts of depression' after shock move...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210531-osaka-reveals-bouts-of-depression-after-shock-french-open-withdrawal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Osaka reveals 'bouts of depression' after shock French Open withdrawal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds arrest man who received controversial pardon from KY gov in slaying...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2021/05/31/feds-arrest-patrick-baker-who-was-pardoned-by-bevin/5280052001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Baker, whose family hosted a fundraiser for Gov. Bevin before Bevin later pardoned him in 2019, faces new charges over Donald MIlls' murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal escorted off high school after graduation speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/education/article/stagg-high-ben-nakamura-principal-stockton-16213580.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An impassioned speech by a Stockton high school principal resulted in him being escorted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New data triples Peru death toll to over 180,000...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/peru-health-coronavirus-pandemic-64aa6bf464e40f384c5e4f108a8e75a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — Peru on Monday announced a sharp increase in its COVID-19 death toll, saying there have been more than 180,000 fatalities since the pandemic hit the country early last year. The announcement was made in the presidential palace during the presentation of a report by a working group commissioned to analyze and update the death toll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-chief of opposition group detained in St. Petersburg...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531172744-44dfy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/OPEN RUSSIA-ARREST:Russia detains ex-chief of opposition group Open Russia - report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance video shows gunmen approach Miami rap concert before shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/video-shows-gunmen-prior-to-mass-shooting-at-florida-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trio of gunmen, wearing masks and hoods, emerge from the front passenger-side door, as well as the back seat, and run toward the crowd, the footage shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise lines, DeSantis square off over vaccine passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/cruise-lines-florida-gov-desantis-square-over-vaccine-passports-n1269029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise lines are eager to set sail, but a new law championed by Gov. Ron DeSantis banning so-called vaccine passports may keep them anchored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naomi Osaka WITHDRAWS from French Open in wake of media boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-9637725/Naomi-Osaka-WITHDRAWS-French-Open-media-boycott-world-No-2-opens-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world number two won her opening match against Patricia Maria Tig on Sunday but her decision not to take part in press conferences or interviews has been the biggest talking point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison Locked Men Up For Drugs. Now Site Will Grow Marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2021/may/31/mostly-death-fills-memoriesof-war-for-101-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Strickland's lasting memories of World War II aren't of battles or parades but of camaraderie and suffering the war brought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants raise prices amid soaring costs, labor shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/restaurants-raise-prices-amid-soaring-costs-labor-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising costs of ingredients and basic supplies as well as a nationwide labor shortage are throttling restaurants just as they begin to fully reopen and ramp up for a bustling summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ bringing back gas chamber with chemical favored by Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/31/arizona-bringing-back-gas-chamber-with-chemical-favored-by-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Arizona is reportedly preparing to execute death row inmates using hydrogen cyanide — and has “refurbished” a mothballed gas chamber using primitive techniques. The Republican-co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos in African parliament after 'I'll kill you' threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/africa-c2b1ae2e673a3327c898143a59ba6b5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE TOWN, South Africa (AP) — There was mayhem at a meeting of the African Union's parliament Monday as lawmakers scuffled over a ballot box and a man appeared to aim a head-high kick at a female colleague amid shouts that there were people armed with guns in the room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN &amp; JERRY'S ice cream with CBD?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ben-jerry-s-with-cbd/ar-AAKzgsN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben &amp; Jerry’s made a bold new flavor announcement in May 2019: CBD ice cream was coming ... “as soon as it’s legalized at the federal level.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Covid cases near  low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/30/us-covid-cases-lowest-in-a-year-as-memorial-day-travel-picks-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11,976 new Covid-19 cases reported on May 29 were the lowest since March 23, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-limits-travel-most-populous-094613554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities imposed fresh travel limits, cancelled flights and tested thousands of residents in Guangdong Monday after the Indian variant of the coronavirus was reported in the country's most populous province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday still subdued by pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531140733-3ksl5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HOLIDAY/MEMORIALDAY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. travelers on the road again with Memorial Day holiday still subdued by pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES FINAL CURTAIN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531104812-din11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/NETANYAHU (TV, PIX):Israel's 'magician' Netanyahu faces final curtain after record run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS FOR FALLEN HEROES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/2988538/memorial-day-biden-lays-wreath-tomb-uknwown-soldier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden appeared to shed a tear as he laid a wreath at the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier during his first Memorial Day ceremony as president on Monday. Biden traveled to Arlington National Cemetary…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  INSTA star kills self on livestream after tying up and abusing girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2987224/s2k-wya-instagram-kills-himself-livestream-abusing-girlfriend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Instagram star live-streamed his final moments before killing himself after he led cops on a chase as they tried to arrest him for allegedly abusing his girlfriend. Angel Hernandez Grado, 28, wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of quakes rattles Disneyland visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article251798218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“After a day of rides at Disneyland I thought maybe I was still feeling the Indiana Jones ride.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'First step to sanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/opinion/a-government-for-the-people-analysis-669648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naftali Bennett spoke like a uniter, someone who believes in bringing people together. The story of Israeli politics from now on, he explained, is not about “me, but about us."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu has ruled for total of 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-netanyahu-corner-change-alliance-104809180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli opposition leader Yair Lapid on Monday said many obstacles remain before a diverse coalition can be built to oust veteran Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu but voiced hope it will achieve the "greater goal".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Detectors Sweeping Country; Record Sales...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/31/the-new-detectorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have been metal detecting since 1881, when Alexander Graham Bell invented a device to find the bullet lodged in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Underlying Racism,' 'Human Zoo' Environment...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamzagoria/2021/05/30/kyrie-irving-calls-out-underlying-racism-human-zoo-environment-after-boston-fan-throws-water-bottle-gets-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Nets guard Kyrie Irving called out what he termed the “underlying racism” and “human zoo” environment in Boston after a fan threw a water bottle at his head as he was leaving the arena Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden commemorates war dead at Arlington National Cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/veterans-government-and-politics-3c14d961839b6bf0b4ecd20b5d7d2efd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Va. (AP) — President Joe Biden honored America’s war dead at Arlington National Cemetery on Memorial Day by laying a wreath at the hallowed burial ground. The president was joined on Monday by first lady Jill Biden, Vice President Kamala Harris and second gentleman Doug Emhoff in a somber ceremony at the Virginia cemetery's Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, which is dedicated to the fallen U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is sun going into hibernation?</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/is-our-sun-going-into-hibernation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each sunspot cycle has been getting less intense. Is our star falling asleep?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wine country, newspaper war brings down mayoral 'prince' accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wine-country-newspaper-war-brings-120007624.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prize-winning Santa Rosa newspaper neglected accusations against Dominic Foppoli, until its former employee took the scoop to a competing paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Americans face eviction as housing protection expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/31/millions-of-americans-could-face-eviction-as-housing-protection-expires-in-june.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 11 million Americans are behind on their rent and many could face eviction when national housing protection expires in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ROAD FOR BIBI?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-netanyahu-fights-to-block-opposition-parties-from-taking-power/ar-AAKyz30 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning to normal not simple for everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/31/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memorial Day weekend has brought back images of family gatherings and crowded beaches, but though things may look more normal, a clinical psychologist told CNN many people may still be dealing with emotional impacts from the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magician' Netanyahu faces final curtain after record run...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-politics-netanyahu/israels-magician-netanyahu-faces-final-curtain-after-record-run-idUSKCN2DC10M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long the familiar face of Israel, Benjamin Netanyahu has held on as prime minister for more than a decade, clinging to power through a criminal indictment and four elections in the past two years alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Junk Hits, Damages ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.iflscience.com/space/piece-space-junk-damaged-part-international-space-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iflscience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A robotic arm attached to the International Space Station (ISS) has been hit by a tiny piece of space junk, resulting in damage to its thermal blanket and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists hunt for 'Su' who could be mystery 'patient zero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-hunt-patient-su-woman-24217556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelations come after British officials conceded this week that the possibility of a lab leak remains "plausible" - with mysterious "Patient Su" appearing to have been traced close to the Wuhan Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Biden, deeply personal Memorial Day weekend observance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-memorial-day-c3886def81f78c762fd1e920148ef32a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW CASTLE, Del. (AP) — President Joe Biden marked his first Memorial Day weekend as commander in chief by honoring the nation’s sacrifices in a deeply personal manner as he paid tribute Sunday to those lost while remembering his late son Beau, a veteran who died six years ago to the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hat Shop Selling Nazi-Style Jewish Stars Proclaiming 'Not Vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/more-hatmakers-cut-ties-with-nashville-hat-shop-after-controversial-instagram-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday, the owner of hatWRKS hat shop on 8th Ave South in Nashville posted a photo to Instagram with a yellow patch resembling the Star of David along with the words “not vaccinated”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious B.I.G. executed by Nation of Islam convert arranged by Suge Knight, ex-FBI agent claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9634317/Notorious-B-G-executed-Nation-Islam-convert-hit-arranged-Suge-Knight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suge Knight (top right) allegedly paid a hitman to kill Notorious B.I.G. in LA in 1997 as revenge for Tupac Shakur's (bottom right) murder even though the intended target was Sean 'Diddy' Combs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark accused of helping USA spy on Merkel, European officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-57302806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's secret service is accused of helping the US target politicians such as Germany's Angela Merkel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials worry rise in violent crime portends bloody summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/officials-worry-the-rise-in-violent-crime-portends-a-bloody-summer-e2-80-98it-e2-80-99s-trauma-on-top-of-trauma-e2-80-99/ar-AAKxyhR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the nation marks Memorial Day, the unofficial kickoff to summer, many officials are concerned violence could be especially pronounced this season as Americans emerge back into society after a year of coronavirus-related lockdowns and restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Shakeout Stirs Debate on Ether Shot at Usurping Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-shakeout-stirs-debate-on-ether-e2-80-99s-shot-at-usurping-bitcoin/ar-AAKyqGI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The relative resilience of Ether in May’s cryptocurrency rout has put the spotlight back on the idea that the second-largest digital token could one day overtake Bitcoin by market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Moves to Three-Child Policy to Boost Falling Birthrate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-57303592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Census results show China's population grew at its slowest pace in decades last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531094331-qp71v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-REFORMS (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531003534-ol0dn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-JUSTICE/OATHKEEPERS:Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case: court filing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems walk, stop TX sweeping voting restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tx-state-wire-texas-government-and-politics-92d26e25c9db88a32e0fda890773b908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Democrats pulled off a dramatic, last-ditch walkout in the state House of Representatives on Sunday night to block passage of one of the most restrictive voting bills in the U.S., leaving Republicans with no choice but to abandon a midnight deadline and declare the legislative session essentially over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do deficits matter anymore? Biden's first budget signals they don't...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/do-deficits-matter-anymore-biden-s-first-budget-signals-they-don-t/ar-AAKuHYg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s first budget predicts a $1.8 trillion deficit for 2022 and deficits of $1.3 trillion for years to come to fund big investments in education, infrastructure and the social safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shooting at Miami rap concert leaves 2 dead, 20 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/05/30/at-least-20-people-shot-2-killed-at-northwest-miami-dade-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victims were rushed to several hospitals in Miami-Dade and Broward counties after a shooting at a banquet hall, some in their personal vehicles, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS Fan Throws Bottle at Player...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/31/td-garden-fan-water-bottle-kyrie-irving-boston-celtics-brooklyn-nets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Players from both the Celtics and Nets condemned a fan who is now facing charges and a liftetime ban from TD Garden after throwing a water bottle at Nets guard Kyrie Irving.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
