<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Faces Barrage of Criticism by Ex-Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-faces-barrage-of-criticism-by-ex-aide-cummings/ar-BB1fYPTm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson, facing an onslaught of criticism from the man he until recently relied on as his most powerful adviser, denied he’d blocked an inquiry into leaks of sensitive information from within his government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz probe includes scrutiny of potential public corruption tied to medical marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/23/politics/gaetz-probe-public-corruption-medical-marijuana/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are looking into whether a 2018 trip to the Bahamas involving Republican Congressman Matt Gaetz and several young women was part of an orchestrated effort to illegally influence Gaetz in the area of medical marijuana, people briefed on the matter told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US diplomatic missions to fly LGBTQ Pride flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/23/blinken-authorizes-us-diplomatic-missions-to-fly-pride-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Tony Blinken has authorized US diplomatic missions to fly the LGBTQ pride flag on the same pole as the American flag at embassies and consulates, a department official confirmed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer complains about jail treatment: 'Epstein effect'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-not-guilty-new-sex-trafficking-charges-203305963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 59-year-old British socialite has been held without bail in Brooklyn’s Metropolitan Detention Center since her arrest last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Face-Masks The New Condoms?</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/are-face-masks-the-new-condoms-f8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some thoughts on plagues, rationality and recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frail Ghislaine Maxwell pleads not guilty to new charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9503995/Ghislaine-Maxwell-pleads-NOT-GUILTY-two-counts-sex-trafficking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell, 59, pleaded not guilty Friday to new sex trafficking charges added to an indictment three weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family indicted, accused of selling bleach as cure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-coronavirus-5f9c2732411f3a14cd6cffd04d787b16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A family accused of selling a toxic industrial bleach as a coronavirus cure through their Florida-based church has been indicted on federal charges. A federal grand jury in Miami returned an indictment Thursday charging Mark Grenon, 62, and his sons, Jonathan, 34, Jordan, 26, and Joseph, 32, with one count each of conspiracy to commit fraud and two counts each of criminal contempt, according to court records. They face possible life sentences if convicted. Mark Grenon is the archbishop of the Genesis II Church of Health and Healing, based in Bradenton, Florida. The church sells chlorine dioxide as a “Miracle Mineral Solution,” officials said. The Grenons claim the solution can cure a vast variety of illnesses ranging from cancer to autism to malaria to COVID-19. A Miami federal judge last April ordered the church to stop selling the substance, but the order was ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL draftees could hug, dap up vaccinated Roger Goodell
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/draft/2021/04/23/nfl-draft-roger-goodell-vaccinated-against-covid-19-bro-hugs/7350561002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With NFL commissioner Roger Goodell vaccinated against COVID-19, bro hugs, daps and handshakes could make their return at the 2021 draft next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dogs that stayed in Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210422-the-guards-caring-for-chernobyls-abandoned-dogs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The descendants of pets abandoned by those fleeing the Chernobyl disaster are now striking up a curious relationship with humans charged with guarding the contaminated area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More risks to pregnant, newborns than known before...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-pregnant-women-stu-idUSKBN2CA1E9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant women infected with COVID-19 and their newborn children face higher risks of complications than was previously known, a study by British scientists showed on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tells Erdogan He'll Call Armenian Massacre Genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-tells-erdogan-he-ll-call-armenian-massacre-a-genocide/ar-BB1fZ04f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden told Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Friday that he intends to recognize the early-20th century massacre of Armenians by Ottoman Empire forces as a genocide, according to people familiar with a call between the leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Rush Return To CA? Company Working To Reopen Mine Untouched Since '56...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/22/gold-rush-return-to-grass-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been decades since gold country in California has been actively mined, but a Canadian company wants to change that in Grass Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising actor, fake HBO deals. One of Hollywood's most audacious Ponzi schemes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-04-23/zachary-horwitz-hollywood-film-ponzi-scheme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Zachary Horwitz collected $690 million from investors for movie deals the FBI says were fictitious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say no safer indoors at 6 feet or 60 feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/23/mit-researchers-say-youre-no-safer-from-covid-indoors-at-6-feet-or-60-feet-in-new-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC and WHO guidelines fail to factor in the amount of time spent indoors, which increases the chance of transmission the longer people are inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small black hole, dubbed 'Unicorn,' discovered near Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/04/23/black-hole-dubbed-the-unicorn-may-smallest-one-discovered-yet/7349740002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The black hole was given the nickname because it's so rare but also because it was discovered in the constellation Monoceros, which means unicorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New malaria vaccine proven 77% effective...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210423-landmark-advance-as-malaria-vaccine-first-to-hit-who-goal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Landmark' advance as malaria vaccine first to hit WHO goal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech execs to testify at Senate hearing on algorithms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/23/facebook-youtube-twitter-testify-senate-484456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aides said they hoped to draw bipartisan interest by focusing the session on structural issues in how companies approach content moderation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owner says he won't dismantle shooting center as ordered...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ny-state-wire-shootings-business-gun-politics-c28092be0da198c2bb465ecc5562e35d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PAWLET, Vt. (AP) — The owner of an unpermitted firearms training center that has rattled neighbors in a southern Vermont town says he won't comply with a judge's order to dismantle much of the facility he has built. Daniel Banyai said he is looking for “the proper constitutional attorney" to appeal a Vermont Environmental Court order that he dismantle all structures on the property that were built without permits in the town near the New York border. He has until May 5 to appeal. “We are not going to do that," Banyai said when asked about the order during a weekend event at the center he calls Slate Ridge Vermont. “We have not done anything wrong, we haven’t done anything illegal."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist Who Says He Created Bitcoin Can Sue Mystery Website...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/scientist-who-says-he-created-bitcoin-can-sue-mystery-website/ar-BB1fYzuA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Australian scientist who says he created Bitcoin won the backing of a London court to pursue the mystery owners of the bitcoin.org website for allegedly infringing his copyright over the world’s largest cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich face tax hike with anger, denial and grief...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rich-americans-face-biden-tax-hike-with-anger-denial-and-grief/ar-BB1fWKNm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeatedly Misgendered on 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/joy-behar-apologizes-after-repeatedly-misgendering-caitlyn-jenner-in-segment-on-governor-stunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joy Behar repeatedly misgendered Caitlyn Jenner on Friday's The View, using the incorrect pronouns in a segment covering her bid for Governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actors Unload On Rudin: Hundreds Take To Streets Demanding His Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/22/scott-rudin-protest-new-york-city-march-on-broadway-actors-equity-association/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Broadway actors and theater workers came out Thursday for a "March on Broadway."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashlessness May Have Gone Too Far in Norway, Govt Warns...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/news/economy/cashlessness-may-have-gone-foo-far-in-norway-government-warns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALDS offers $50 just to show up for job interview!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-mcdonalds-offers-50-just-to-show-up-for-job-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McDonald's location is so desperate for workers that it has offered people $50 just to show up for a job interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art or activism? The Oscars' identity crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/23/art-v-activism-can-the-oscars-survive-its-identity-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s awards will be a battle between political propriety and cinematic excellence. But will medium or message finally triumph?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More flushed wipes are clogging pipes, sending sewage into homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-nasty-pandemic-problem-more-flushed-wipes-are-clogging-pipes-sending-sewage-into-homes/ar-BB1fYvix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stepped-up cleaning and people seeking alternatives during toilet paper shortages have led to increased wipes usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe sees record approval among young...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/549913-biden-sees-record-approval-among-college-age-americans-in-harvard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 6 in 10 college-age Americans approve of President Biden’s job as president thus far, according to a new youth poll from the Institute of Politics at Harvard Kennedy School, representing the highest figure for any president in the h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat dies after catching from owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2757937/cat-dies-covid-catching-bug-uk-owner-breathing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CATS have caught Covid from their owners in the UK, a new study has found – leading to fears of a pet pandemic. Two kitties were found to have contracted the virus, including a four-month-old…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study Shows Many Kept Traveling Normally -- Despite Feeling Symptoms!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/what-pandemic-people-traveling-despite-covid-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say this is the first report during COVID to trace movement patterns among people with possible symptoms of infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorkin's Lucy-Desi Movie Scraps Chateau Marmont Shoot Amid Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/aaron-sorkin-lucy-desi-movie-chateau-marmont-shoot-scrapped</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gets help from MAGA Brad Parscale...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/caitlyn-jenner-gets-help-from-brad-parscale-with-potential-run-for-ca-gov/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump 2020 campaign manager Brad Parscale is assisting Caitlyn Jenner as she mulls a potential challenge to California Gov. Gavin Newsom in this year’s recall, a source familiar with t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning to pre-covid life turning out to be hard for some...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-returning-pre-covid-life-120051678.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We seem to be on the cusp of returning to normal life, but for many people, transitioning back to Before Times is proving to be a lot more fraught than we expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where COVID kills young: Brazil shows what may await others...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/where-covid-19-kills-the-young-brazil-shows-what-may-await-others</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many causes for the alarming shift but one appears to be that the young have trouble accepting they are at risk.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN MOVES TO TAX THE RICH!</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/biden-aims-at-top-03-with-bid-to-tax-capital-gains-like-wages-2483253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Aims at Top 0.3% With Bid to Tax Capital Gains Like Wages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron crisis: Le Pen surges as French election panic sets in for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1427058/Emmanuel-macron-marine-le-pen-french-election-poll-latest-france-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL MACRON is facing an unexpectedly tight French election next year after a new poll showed rival Marine Le Pen hot on his heels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEALTHY FLEE ON PRIVATE JETS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-rips-icu-india-suffers-113653505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BENOIT TESSIEREight private jets carrying India’s super wealthy—and potentially the coronavirus—landed in London ahead of the U.K.’s 4 a.m. ban on travel from India, according to the London Times. The U.K. added India to its “red list” of pandemic-stricken countries. As of Friday, any Britons returning from India must quarantine for ten days in a government-approved hotel. All non-British or non-Irish citizens will be banned entirely from entering the country if they have been in India in the previous 10 days. British Prime Minister Boris Johnson had to cancel his own state visit to India scheduled for next week as a “precautionary measure.”The last of the luxury airliners to arrive, VistaJet Bombardier Global 6000, which left Dubai Thursday to collect passengers in Mumbai, landed at 3:15 a.m., just 44 minutes before the restrictions took place.The private jet passengers were fleeing unimaginable horror back home. At least 14 COVID-19 patients perished in a devastating fire that ripped through an ICU ward in one of India’s overcrowded hospitals about 70 miles outside Mumbai. The fire that broke out around 3 a.m. Friday morning was contained and extinguished, but not before 14 patients—many who were intubated and hard to evacuate—had died. “Around 90 patients were admitted to the hospital at the time of the incident,” Dilip Shah, the head of the Vijay Vallabh Hospital where it happened said in a statement Friday. Black Market Hospital Beds and Price-Gouged COVID Drugs Selling on Indian TwitterOne eyewitness, Avinash Patil, told reporters outside the hospital that no doctors were present at the time. “I got a call at around 3 am from a friend whose mother-in-law was admitted to the hospital,” he said. “As I reached the hospital, I saw fire engines outside. The ICU on the second floor was engulfed in smoke. Only two nurses were there, and I couldn’t see a doctor. It took firefighters about half an hour to put out the flames. We could see eight-ten bodies there.”Shah, the hospital chief, insisted all safety norms were followed and that “doctors were present,” according to local media reports. Earlier in the week, an oxygen leak in Maharashtra state, near where the fire broke out, resulted in the death of 24 COVID-19 patients who were on ventilators.To make terrible matters even worse, India reported its highest one-day number of cases, recording 332,730 new infections in a 24-hour period. In the same period, 2,263 people died with COVID-19.India has been overwhelmed by new cases coupled with a critical shortage of oxygen, hospital beds and now ventilators. Many desperate families have been forced to turn to black market price gougers who have been able to buy hospital space from corrupt administrators.The spike in cases comes as political rallies are still being held and after a month-long religious ceremony continues to bring millions of people to the Ganges River.India Prime Minister Narendra Modi has been criticized for not calling a national lockdown to try to mitigate the spread and for hosting rallies ahead of elections in May. Government officials have said the previous lockdown at the beginning of the pandemic was economically devastating to many manual laborers who then traveled by foot from home cities to their villages, carrying the virus with them. The fire at a COVID-19 hospital in Virar is tragic. Condolences to those who lost their loved ones. May the injured recover soon: PM @narendramodi— PMO India (@PMOIndia) April 23, 2021 Modi called the ICU fire “tragic” and offered condolences over Twitter. Many of the comments on his tweet begged him to call a national lockdown to try to save lives. In a shocking expose published in Time magazine, Indian journalist Rana Ayyub paints a horrific picture from the ground, writing about states essentially hijacking oxygen trucks and stealing supplies for their own hospitals, and disturbing allegations of underreporting deaths. Ayyub lays the blame for the debacle squarely on Modi’s shoulders, accusing him of ignoring the fact that his Trump-style rallies are super-spreader events, and for letting the ball drop on vaccines.“Why was India caught unprepared as the second wave ravaged a cross-section of Indian society?” Ayyub writes. “The responsibility lies with a strongman regime that has ignored all caution.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR OXYGEN</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/oxygen-gets-armed-escort-india-supplies-run-low-covid-crisis-2021-04-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens wailing, a police convoy escorting a tanker carrying oxygen reached a hospital in India's capital just in time, to the huge relief of doctors and relatives of COVID-19 patients counting on the supply to stave off death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning photos capture launch to ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/trending/spacex-launch-10-stunning-photos-captured-by-skygazers/SPUJ6JNR7ZHRPFYOOIQAMGBSMI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four astronauts lifted off Friday morning from Florida’s Kennedy Space Center on a SpaceX flight to the International Space Station. Skygazers took to social media to share their photos. Here are some of our favorites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over $200 billion wiped off crypto market in day as bitcoin plunges below $50,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/23/bitcoin-btc-price-plunges-as-260-billion-wiped-off-cryptocurrencies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin and other digital currencies plunged on Friday as U.S. President Joe Biden's proposed capital gains tax hike led to a wave of selling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed Kremlin critic Navalny says he will start ending hunger strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210423111142-4uyd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Jailed Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny says he will start ending hunger strike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC probes new death, hospitalization after J&amp;J shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210423104338-cgp31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JOHNSON&amp;JOHNSON-USA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-U.S. CDC probes new death, hospitalization after J&amp;J vaccine shots - officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER HOSPITAL FIRE KILLS PATIENTS</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Fire-kills-covid-patients-in-second-India-16123254.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire that broke out at a hospital in western India killed at least 14 coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest dozens in Jerusalem clashes; Israeli nationalists chant 'Death to Arabs'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210423075653-ilyhz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/JERUSALEM-VIOLENCE (PIX, TV):Police arrest dozens in Jerusalem clashes; Israeli nationalists chant 'Death to Arabs"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airports Step Up Mental Health Assistance as Passenger Anxiety Soars...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/airports-step-up-mental-health-assistance-as-passenger-anxiety-soars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more people return to air travel, tension is mounting in airports nationwide. Atlanta’s Hartsfield-Jackson is among those that have responded to the pandemic-related stress and fear among passen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge explosion cracks house foundations. 'Extreme' gender reveal to blame...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-huge-explosion-cracked-house-foundations-in-new-hampshire-an-extreme-gender-reveal-party-was-to-blame/ar-BB1fYgMy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gender-reveal celebration at a concrete plant in rural New Hampshire involved someone detonating 80 pounds of Tannerite, an over-the-counter explosive, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vampire facials' salon owner arrested after customers contract HIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/vampire-facials-salon-owner-arrested-23967902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maria Ramos de Ruiz, 59, allegedly offered "vampire facials" which left at least two clients with HIV in unauthorised treatments made famous by the Kardashians and Chrissy Teigen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He boasted on BUMBLE about storming Capitol. Would-be date turned him in...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/He-boasted-on-Bumble-about-storming-Capitol-feds-16123124.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One week after the insurrection at the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, Robert Chapman sent a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Hollywood set for pandemic-era Oscars, with 'NOMADLAND' out front...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-set-pandemic-era-oscars-013541677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscars on Sunday will mirror the movie industry they honor: transformed by the pandemic, forced to experiment with new venues and formats, and likely to be dominated by "Nomadland."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Black Superman? It's Happened, and Could Again...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/23/a-black-superman-its-happened-and-could-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2008, during his presidential campaign, Barack Obama told a joke at a charity event. “Contrary to the rumors you</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside horrific 'exorcisms' of religious sect; Whipped, disembowelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14698152/inside-the-horrific-exorcisms-sweeping-russia-with-sons-whipped-to-death-and-daughters-disembowelled-by-their-parents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE gagged boy screamed out in pain as the adults held him down and took turns whipping him to “drive out demons”. The nine-year-old child — David Kazantsev — died after his parents had…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada Brothels Hot to Trot for Reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gonna-fun-nevada-brothels-hot-084727082.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastFor the past 14 months, Madam Dena has sat on a sprawling, abandoned ranch outside Las Vegas, overseeing an empty empire of themed bungalows, hotel rooms, and tennis courts. Usually tasked with managing nearly 100 staffers and contractors, the madam has been almost entirely alone, save for a skeleton crew of employees and a few lone men who sidle up to the locked front gates and pound on the front door, demanding to know if they are open for business.The answer, of course, is no. Nevada’s brothels—the only legal places to buy sex in the United States—shut their doors in March 2020, when Gov. Steve Sisolak shuttered all nonessential businesses due to the coronavirus pandemic. And they have remained closed since, even as other close-contact businesses have opened up around them.But starting May 1, Nevada’s brothels are back in business—and it’s going to be a wild ride.“When we made the announcement that we were opening on May 1, I could not believe it,” Madam Dena, the manager of Sheri’s Ranch in Pahrump, told The Daily Beast this week. “The phones started ringing off the hook; emails coming through for reservations.”“I was like, ‘Whoa—it's almost like everybody was holding their breath."“Oh yeah, we’re booked out,” added Jennifer Barnes, a madam at the Mustang Ranch in Storey County, about the month of May. “Everybody’s been locked up. It’s gonna be fun.” Sheri’s Ranch is ready to open on May 1. Satori Son/Wikimedia Commons Nevada was one of the first states to begin reopening last May, even as infection rates were climbing nationwide. Since then, it has reopened most nonessential businesses at a limited capacity—casinos, tattoo parlors, even strip clubs. Brothels, however, never made the cut. “We’re going to have to look at getting kids back into schools before we look at getting folks back into brothels,” Sisolak said at the Nevada Independent’s conference in October.But the arrival of widespread vaccination programs and a declining case rate has opened the doors for the oldest profession to get back to business. Last week, Sisolak announced the state would fully reopen June 1 and gave back full control of social distancing policies to the counties starting May 1. Several counties quickly voted to reopen all businesses, brothels included.While some county politicians are charging full speed ahead (commissioners in Nye County are already attempting to override the statewide mask mandates,) brothel owners are proceeding with caution. Most are operating at a reduced capacity and heavily encouraging masks in common areas—”putting one foot in,” as Madam Dena put it. There will be the familiar trappings of pandemic life—temperature checks upon arrival, and questions about symptoms and recent travel—along with a few notable changes: Customers at the Mustang Ranch in Storey County will not be allowed to congregate at the bar, but will instead enter and meet up with their courtesans one at a time.Still, brothels say the increased safety measures haven’t put a damper on demand. All of the madams who spoke to The Daily Beast said they were nearly booked up for the month of May.“I’m not gonna lie, I was surprised,” Madam Dena said of the response from customers. “It’s like ‘Heck yeah, here we go!’”Inside the Risky Race to Reopen Nevada’s BrothelsAnd it's not just the customers who have been holding their breath: The pandemic year has been nothing short of devastating for the state’s sex workers.With the only legal place to conduct their work indefinitely shuttered, women accustomed to making six figures in a year were suddenly without a source of income. Applying for a “square job” was nearly impossible—five years at the Bunny Ranch isn’t exactly ideal resume fodder—and many found themselves locked out of the kind of government benefits provided for other service workers affected by the pandemic. It took months for lawmakers to extend unemployment benefits to independent contractors, and some pandemic-related grants and loan programs excluded sex workers completely.Katrina, a courtesan at the Chicken Ranch for more than 13 years, estimated she lost more than 30 percent of her income due to the pandemic.“It seems like anywhere I tried to go for help I was not getting it,” she said. “I'm in a legit business like everyone else, I pay my taxes. I applied for the [Small Business Administration loans] and I was denied because of what I do, and I think that is so unfair.”Katrina was one of the lucky ones: She earned her masters in computer science during the pandemic and was able to supplement her income by designing websites for friends. But others were not as fortunate. Barbara G. Brents, a sociology professor at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas and expert on the sex industry, said about a third of Nevada’s legal sex workers previously moonlighted in illegal markets. Post-pandemic, she said, that number is likely much higher.“Obviously sex workers are always resourceful and used to adjusting to the markets,” she said. “But given Nevada’s legal brothel system, one of these adjustments undoubtedly has for many sex workers been to move to a much more dangerous, illegal market.”The trend speaks to a larger problem among sex workers during the pandemic in general. Fearful of coming in close contact with other people, and facing markedly decreased demand, sex workers in both legal and illegal markets were forced to move their work online or suspend it completely. (The number of users on OnlyFans, a site where users can charge for explicit photos and videos, grew nine times between December of 2019 and December 2020.) And according to Brents, even online markets were only profitable for those who already had sizable followings or the resources to build them. “For the most marginalized, the impact has just been devastating,” she said.The pandemic’s effect on sex workers has driven calls for decriminalization, or the removal of criminal penalties for sex workers and their clients. It has also shone a light on some of the flaws in Nevada’s 50-year-old, fully legalized system.Alice Little, often described as one of the country’s highest-paid legal sex workers, sued the governor last November after being locked out of work for almost eight months. She claimed the order barring brothels from reopening was “blatant discrimination against Nevada’s legal sex workers,” and interfered with their freedom of association and right to earn a living. But a Lyon County district court judge ruled against her, claiming she could not represent the interests of the brothel owners as an independent contractor.“Had one brothel owner from Lyon County signed onto my lawsuit, it would have been successful,” Little told the Daily Beast this week. But not a single one did. In fact, none even bothered to attend the court hearings—something the judge said indicated that “owners may not desire to operate during the pandemic.” Alice Little sued the governor last November after being locked out of work for almost eight months. Courtesy Alice Little Little eventually dropped her lawsuit after incurring a six-figure bill and raising less than a quarter of her GoFundMe target.“I think that’s the most upsetting part of this: I paid $100,000 to be told that, as a sex worker, I have zero rights,” she said. “But a brothel owner would have had the rights? That’s not OK.”“We need to fix the brothel system and center the sex workers and prioritize our rights, our ability to stand up for ourselves,” she added. “And until that happens, it’s a desperately flawed industry."There are other, smaller difficulties with re-entering the sex trade after a year of social distancing: re-registering business licenses, getting up-to-date STD checks, shaking off the cobwebs on old skills. (“It’s been a year!” Madam Dena exclaimed. “Do I remember how to process a transaction? I don’t know!”) There have also been unexpected hurdles: Madam Dena said several ladies chose not to return to work rather than submit themselves to vaccinations or weekly COVID tests.But every sex worker who spoke to The Daily Beast said they were thrilled about getting back to work. Several were already back in Nevada in advance of the reopening, dusting off their social media feeds and booking appointments with customers they hadn’t seen in over a year. The reasons for their excitement ranged from a desire to reunite with customers and coworkers to a yearning—and in some cases, a deep-felt need—for the extra income. (Asked what she had missed most about her job during the pandemic, Mustang Ranch courtesan Nola Blue said simply, “The money!”)Even Little says she is excited to get back to work. She has switched from her brothel in Lyon County to the Chicken Ranch in Pahrump, where she says management has been more supportive. And she is excited to get back to her customers, who she knows have been struggling as well.“I keep joking with everyone that it’s like I’m going to see folks again and pretty much burst into tears upon being able to hold them and hug them and see them,” she said. “Because this year has been extremely stressful on everyone, to say the least.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIA COVID MAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/23/indias-second-wave-country-reports-over-330000-new-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of Friday, India has reported more than 4 million cases in April and at least 24,452 people have died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How space doctor keeps astronauts healthy on ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-a-space-doctor-keeps-astronauts-healthy-on-the-iss/ar-BB1fWwKb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From muscle loss to radiation exposure and the psychological effects of confinement, spaceflight takes a toll on those lucky enough to experience it. A: If we talk about low Earth orbit where the ISS lies, you have almost zero gravity so that takes its toll on your bones and your muscles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronomers map asteroid's 22 million-year journey to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/astronomers-map-asteroid-s-22m-year-journey-to-earth/ar-BB1fWRzj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have reconstructed the 22m-year-long voyage of an asteroid that hurtled through the solar system and exploded over Botswana, showering meteorites across the Kalahari desert. It is the first time scientists have traced showering space rock to its source – in this case Vesta, one of largest bodies in the asteroid belt that circles the sun between Jupiter and Mars. The six-tonne asteroid punched into Earth’s atmosphere at 37,000mph in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER REPORTS tricks TESLA to drive without anyone at wheel...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/22/tesla-can-drive-with-nobody-in-the-drivers-seat-consumer-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer Reports said Thursday that in testing this week it found it could "easily" get a 2020 Tesla Model Y to drive "even with no one in the driver's seat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIA COVID MAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/22/india-hits-global-record-of-315000-new-daily-cases-as-covid-wave-worsens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals pushed to brink after more than 1 million people infected in four days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans still waiting for 'Biden depression' that Trump predicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-economy-spikes-Republicans-are-still-waiting-16122150.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout last year's campaign, President DonaldTrump issued a series of increasingly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's Ontario grapples with third wave, blame piled on premier...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canadas-ontario-grapples-with-third-wave-blame-piled-its-premier-2021-04-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ontario Premier Doug Ford, facing backlash over his government's handling of the pandemic, resisted calls to resign on Thursday as Canada's most populous province grappled with a third wave of COVID-19 infections that critics said could have been prevented.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amy Coney Barrett's big book deal called bad optics for Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/amy-coney-barrett-e2-80-99s-big-book-deal-called-bad-optics-for-supreme-court/ar-BB1fV3JK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett’s reported $2 million book deal is drawing criticism from legal experts who say its size and timing create bad optics for a court that is already in the political crosshairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low rainfall leaves Mexico City residents delivering water -- by donkey!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422203222-2qlf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EARTH-DAY/MEXICO-WATER (TV, PIX):Low rainfall leaves Mexico City residents delivering water by donkey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMER REPORTS tricks TESLA to drive without anyone at wheel...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/consumer-reports-tricks-tesla-to-drive-without-anyone-at-wheel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer Reports said Thursday it was able to easily trick a Tesla into driving in the car's Autopilot mode with no one at the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan seeks 'short, powerful' state of emergency as virus rages...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422212456-yc634</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN (URGENT):Japan says to seek 'short, powerful' state of emergency for Tokyo, Osaka and elsewhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba covid infections hit new high...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210422212456-cr7ax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CUBA (PIX, TV):South African virus variant fuels record Cuban COVID-19 cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Senate advances bill banning vaxx requirements...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-government-and-politics-bills-montana-religion-321f28730b53ebe9a097ed53a69378a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) — The Montana Senate voted Thursday to advance a measure banning the use of vaccine passports and prohibiting workplaces from requiring vaccinations as a condition for employment. Dozens of supporters of the measure, mostly unmasked, packed the Senate gallery. They erupted into cheers and applause when the Senate voted to advance the measure 30-19, largely along party lines with Republicans in favor. The vote came after Benefis Health System, a health care provider in Great Falls, announced earlier this month it would require all its employees to get the COVID-19 vaccine, which has received emergency use authorization from the Food and Drug Administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Too Much Chocolate Can Lead to Death in Middle Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sweet-tooth-heart-disease-midlife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find sugary drinks and eating too much chocolate increases the risk of cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Hawaii visitors cruising around in U-Hauls? Blame the pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2021/04/22/why-are-visitors-cruising-around-u-hauls-blame-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U-Haul marketing president said Hawaii U-Haul facilities are the busiest they’ve been in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad inventory sells out despite awards show ratings declines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/22/oscars-sells-out-ad-inventory-despite-awards-show-ratings-declines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ratings for awards shows had been slipping even before the pandemic. Viewership for last year's Oscars dropped 20% to a new low, according to Nielsen.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
