<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>T. Rex Was 'Foodie,' Scientists Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avmap/scientists-find-t-rex-was-a-foodie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dinosaur had “a delicate side like other animals. It’s not a monster.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani admits liking Scotch but denies being alcoholic...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/politics/rudy-giuliani-says-u-s-has-gone-off-the-rails-denies-he-has-alcohol-problem/3243586/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 20 years after being dubbed America’s Mayor, Rudy Giuliani says he knows that people think he’s gone off the rails. He also doesn’t care, and instead believes it’s the country that has gone off the rails</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans evacuations ordered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_c59648f6-0756-11ec-858a-874da06021ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Tropical Storm Ida heads toward the Gulf coast, some parish officials in southeast Louisiana have called for voluntary and mandatory evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Lifts All Restrictions Except Entry Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidnikel/2021/08/27/denmark-lifts-all-coronavirus-restrictions-except-entry-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From September 10, Denmark will remove all domestic restrictions related to Covid-19. Travel restrictions remain in place for the time being, although many people can now travel to Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7y-lpFQ-XLs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says everyone should buy a rifle...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-08-27/brazils-bolsonaro-says-everyone-should-buy-a-rifle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizer of TX 'Freedom Rally' hospitalized with Covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-anti-mask-freedom-rally-045722778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His pregnant wife said this week that the hospital was "out of options" for her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL JUDGE OVERTURNS DESANTIS MASK MANDATE BAN...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/27/florida-judge-overturns-desantis-school-mask-mandate-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Circuit Court judge has overturned Gov. Ron DeSantis’ mask mandate ban for Florida schools, ruling the governor overstepped his authority by issuing an executive order banning the mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans inmate sues prisons over surgery denial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-prisons-virginia-4bc8a1f7c9ba60a554d099e40129c8b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. (AP) — A transgender man held at a women's prison in Virginia is suing state prison officials after being denied breast removal surgery. Jason Yoakam, who is serving sentences for murder, conspiracy to commit murder and a firearm offense, says the denial by the state Department of Corrections violates his constitutional protection against cruel and unusual punishment and his rights under the Equal Protection Clause of the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landfall with 120mph winds and 150mph gusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/271516.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repairs Of Leaning San Francisco Skyscraper Put On Hold...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/26/repairs-sinking-san-francisco-skyscraper-on-hold-engineering-expert-blasts-plan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A geotechnical engineer and professor at UC Berkeley says the current plan to fix the leaning Millennium Tower in San Francisco is "incorrect" and should be abandoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 In 5 People Worldwide Have Suffered Sleeping Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nearly-3-in-5-suffered-sleep-problems-during-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study involving people from 79 countries around the globe reveals that 56.5 percent experienced some kind of sleep disturbance in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBT NEARS $29 TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.usdebtclock.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usdebtclock.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON ALERT FOR MORE ATTACKS</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/western-nations-race-complete-afghan-evacuation-deadline-looms-2021-08-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. forces helping to evacuate Afghans desperate to flee new Taliban rule were on alert for more attacks on Friday after an Islamic State attack killed 92 people including 13 U.S. service members just outside Kabul airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court blocks eviction moratorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-blocks-biden-administration-s-eviction-moratorium-n1277765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Congress never gave the CDC the staggering amount of power it claims," a group of landlords argued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped Ally: 'Will Never Regret it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/afghan-ally-trapped-in-kabul-says-even-if-he-dies-i-will-never-regret-it-in-emotional-and-harrowing-fox-news-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A segment on Fox News’ America’s Newsroom on Friday was emotional as an Afghan ally who was only identified as “Carl” was connected with someone trying to help Afghan interpreters evacuate Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION 30 YEAR HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/27/key-inflation-gauge-rises-3point6percent-from-a-year-ago-to-tie-biggest-jump-since-the-early-1990s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inflation measure the Federal Reserve uses to set policy rose 3.6% in July from a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/26/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose Friday as Fed Chair Jerome Powell prepared the markets for the central bank start tapering its $120 billion in monthly bond purchases this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANETTA:  US troops will need to return for combat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/leon-panetta-says-us-troops-will-need-to-go-back-to-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Defense Secretary Leon Panetta says US troops will need to go back into combat in Afghanistan — as the region remains on high alert for more suicide attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE CEO says 'truly sorry' for hack of 50 MILLION users' data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-hacking-fce56107ed5982bbbbc6b1acdefb5ebc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLEVUE, Wash. (AP) — T-Mobile says it has notified nearly all of the millions of customers whose personal data was stolen and that it is “truly sorry” for the breach. CEO Mike Sievert said in a written statement Friday that the company spends lots of effort to try to stay ahead of criminal hackers “but we didn’t live up to the expectations we have for ourselves to protect our customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surge pummels Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-hawaii-097137d852609f37e4aada899da5938f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Kuulei Perreira-Keawekane could barely breathe when she went to a Hawaii emergency room. Nausea made it difficult for her to stand and her body throbbed with pain. Like many Native Hawaiians, she was not vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBERTY announces campus-wide quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-a62698ebad644853caaff077fd578cf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LYNCHBURG, Va. (AP) — Liberty University announced a temporary campus-wide quarantine Thursday amid a spike in COVID-19 cases. The quarantine is set to begin Monday and last until Sept. 10, news outlets report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED KEEPS PUMPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-5540a3115d041e10327bfcad2be043e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve will start dialing back its ultra-low-rate policies this year as long as hiring continues to improve, Chair Jerome Powell said Friday, signaling the beginning of the end of the Fed’s extraordinary response to the pandemic recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New urgency to airlift from Kabul after blasts kill dozens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bombings-evacuations-kabul-bb32ec2b65b54ec24323e021c9b4a553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Evacuation flights from Afghanistan resumed with new urgency on Friday, a day after two suicide bombings targeted the thousands of people desperately fleeing a Taliban takeover and killed dozens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellish summer in Tahoe: Choked in smoke with fire closing in fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/a-hellish-summer-in-lake-tahoe-choked-in-smoke-with-the-caldor-fire-closing-in-fast/ar-AANOjOx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the destructive Caldor fire creeps closer to the popular resort area, the boaters, hikers and beach-goers who typically descend on South Lake Tahoe have all but vanished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long COVID's daunting toll seen in study of pandemic's earliest patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/long-covids-daunting-toll-seen-in-study-of-pandemics-earliest-patients/ar-AANOkT3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study of more than 1,200 COVID survivors who were once hospitalized finds that about half have at least one symptom a year later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special forces vets launch own mission to get allies out...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9932809/Afghanistan-evacuation-continues-day-ISIS-bomb-kills-13-troops-90-Afghans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now just four days until the Taliban's August 31 deadline to get the remaining US citizens, troops and equipment out of Kabul and the mission has become even more dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama reports large spike in child cases...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/569684-alabama-reports-large-spike-in-child-covid-19-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama has reported a surge of COVID-19 cases among children as the academic school year gets underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could be Cat 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-orleans-storms-hurricanes-tropical-storms-science--d4b3399437cc5ccb7e76aa270a63f724</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Tropical Storm Ida swirled toward a strike on Cuba on Friday showing hallmarks of a rare, rapidly intensifying storm that could speed across warm Gulf waters and slam into Louisiana as a Category 3 hurricane on Sunday, the National Hurricane Center warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Sea Drone Activity Prelude to Major Naval Movement?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42154/japanese-fighters-intercept-three-chinese-drones-in-as-many-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It isn't clear if the surge in Chinese drone presence over the East China Sea is indicative of a new trend or prelude to a major naval movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliwa mayoral candidacy radical shift in NYC politics..</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-local-correspondents/the-mayoral-candidate-with-a-mouth-that-roars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curtis Sliwa, the Republican nominee, expects his opponent to paint him as racist, sexist, and homophobic. But he’s ready to strike back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How deadliest ever female sniper 'Lady Death' shot 309 Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3550775/sniper-lady-death-world-war-2-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS GERMAN troops poured into the Soviet Union in the midst of World War 2, Lyudmila Pavlichenko rushed to join the Red Army. Out-of-touch recruiters found the prospect of a 24-year-old woman joinin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One person turns up at anti-lockdown protest in Auckland...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/27/new-zealand-police-break-up-one-person-anti-lockdown-protest-in-auckland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram account had called on people to get involved in the Queen Street demonstration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darthgator nearly ripped trainer's arm off. She can't wait to work with him again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-alligator-named-darthgator-nearly-ripped-his-trainer-e2-80-99s-arm-off-she-can-e2-80-99t-wait-to-work-with-him-again/ar-AANOewg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m the one that made a mistake,” the trainer said. “Darthgator was just an alligator doing alligator things.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress hit with $46 million tax fine as China targets celeb culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-actress-hit-with-46-mn-tax-fine-as-china-targets-celebrity-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress hit with $46 mn tax fine as China targets celebrity culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive California fire creeps toward Lake Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/videos-f85b2d338bb942eb8d8e7f4310cdbca1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually impaired Paralympian hit by self-driving bus...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-visually-impaired-paralympian-hit-by-self-driving-bus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visually impaired Paralympian hit by self-driving bus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where World's Superyachts Are Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/superyachts-sail-to-europe-for-summer-as-covid-restrictions-ease</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where the World’s Superyachts Are Right Now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse dewormer flying off shelves as remedy despite FDA warnings, side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/ivermectin-flying-off-north-texas-shelves-as-a-covid-19-remedy-despite-fda-warnings-side/article_53527e72-ee9d-5ea5-a9fa-5c229499dc81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS — For the past month or so, store manager Noah Krzykowski has watched new customers trickle into the Irving Feed Store, all looking for the same thing — ivermectin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing scrutiny over Elder roils election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569458-growing-scrutiny-over-elder-roils-california-recall-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flood of scrutiny over conservative radio host Larry Elder’s California gubernatorial recall bid over past conduct and controversial remarks is giving Republicans headaches and Democrats hope in the surprisingly close contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set to Strike Louisiana Exactly 16 Years after Katrina?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/26/tropical-depression-9-could-become-hurricane-ida/5598203001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Ida is aimed at the Gulf Coast and could be a major hurricane when it arrives, possibly by the end of the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Trims Flying Schedule After Worker Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/southwest-airlines-trims-flying-schedule-after-worker-outcry/ar-AANMOub?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest Airlines Co. will reduce its flight schedule for the last four months of the year after employees assailed the discount carrier for understaffing operations during a summer marred by delays and cancellations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN NIGHMARE CHOICE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9930749/Biden-decide-leave-Americans-risk-U-S-deaths-Kabul.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden on Thursday said he would hunt down the ISIS-K terrorists behind the Kabul attacks, but must do so with limited intelligence capabilities in Afghanistan following his withdrawal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=89VvlmoNKko</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce furious after unwittingly wearing 'blood diamond'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3547464/beyonce-disappointed-angry-after-unwittingly-wearing-tiffany-blood-diamond/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEYONCE was said to be “disappointed and angry” last night after a £22.9million gem she was pictured wearing was compared to a “blood diamond”. She became the first black woman, and only the fourth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer who shot Ashli Babbitt during Capitol riot breaks silence: 'I saved countless lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officer-who-shot-ashli-babbitt-during-capitol-riot-breaks-silence-n1277736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with NBC News, Lt. Michael Byrd said he opened fire only as a “last resort” after the rioters failed to comply with his commands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unbearable Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/the-unbearable-summer/ar-AANLeQ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disastrous environmental events are converging like never before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prisons to close amid staff shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/special-reports/florida-prisons/article253769043.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida Department of Corrections will soon close multiple prisons in North Florida, a last-ditch effort to grapple with severe staff shortages, according to a union representative who talked to Corrections Secretary Mark Inch about the move on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Dressing Up Like FedEx and Arresting People for Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/08/26/cops-are-dressing-up-like-fedex-guys-and-arresting-people-for-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known agreement allows police officers to seize packages at FedEx sorting centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 TROOPS KILLED</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3544925/kabul-airport-explosion-taliban-afghanistan-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIRTEEN US troops and at least 90 Afghans have been killed in ISIS suicide bomb attacks at Kabul Airport. Two explosions rocked the airport in Afghanistan yesterday just hours before the evacuatio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. provided names of Americans, Afghan allies to evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/26/us-officials-provided-taliban-with-names-of-americans-afghan-allies-to-evacuate-506957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Basically, they just put all those Afghans on a kill list,” said one defense official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS CLAIMS RESPONSIBILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/large-explosion-at-abbey-gate-at-the-kabul-airport-report-677790</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terror group ISIS-K claimed responsibility for the suicide bombing attacks near Kabul airport that have killed over 70 civilians and 13 US troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISASTER</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/inside-seth-moulton-secret-kabul-trip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials condemned the unauthorized mission as a reckless stunt. But the congressman says it was critical oversight of a crisis he tried to prevent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR AT KABUL AIRPORT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-evacuations-kabul-9e457201e5bbe75a4eb1901fedeee7a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Two suicide bombers and gunmen attacked crowds of Afghans flocking to Kabul's airport Thursday, transforming a scene of desperation into one of horror in the waning days of an airlift for those fleeing the Taliban takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen 'taken shots' at military aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42151/american-troops-confirmed-killed-in-kabul-airport-terror-bombing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A complex attack on the heart of America's evacuation operation in Kabul has caused the deaths of multiple U.S. servicepeople and even more Afghans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time's Up CEO resigns in wake of Cuomo scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/26/tina-tchen-times-up-ceo-resigns-in-wake-of-andrew-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time’s Up CEO Tina Tchen resigned Thursday in the wake of revelations that leaders of the sexual harassment victims’ advocacy group advised former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on how to handle allegations made against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's MICROSOFT Hack May Have Had Bigger Purpose Than Just Spying...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/26/1013501080/chinas-microsoft-hack-may-have-had-a-bigger-purpose-than-just-spying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China broke into tens of thousands of email accounts in January. Now officials fear the breach wasn't just about spying. It was to build the next generation of artificial intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida adds 901 deaths, largest single-day increase in pandemic history...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article253766203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida on Thursday reported 21,765 more COVID-19 cases and 901 deaths to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, according to Miami Herald calculations of CDC data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden Art Dealer Served Jail Time, Allegedly Defrauded Investor...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/hunter-biden-art-dealer-served-jail-time-and-allegedly-defrauded-investor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The art dealer who the White House has tapped to vet Hunter Biden’s art sales for ethical conflicts was sentenced to three months in jail in 1998 for threatening to stab a man to death and was later accused of defrauding an investor in a messy 2016 lawsuit, raising alarms with ethics watchdogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Dakota AG gets fines, but walks in pedestrian death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/south-dakota-0ec1a028f08df4b63718cf12c9d232da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT PIERRE, S.D. (AP) — South Dakota Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg pleaded no contest Thursday to a pair of misdemeanor traffic charges over a crash last year that killed a pedestrian, avoiding jail time despite bitter complaints from the victim’s family that he was being too lightly punished for actions they called “inexcusable.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 remain as clock ticking...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-business-kabul-dc2898e1ff9907f3be86347876ed6b52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Joe Biden is set to speak following the deadly explosions outside the airport in Kabul that killed 12 U.S. service members and scores of Afghans. The White House says Biden will address the nation from the White House at 5 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking hearts and minds: The strategy of surrender...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/opinion/commentary/2021/08/24/breaking-hearts-and-minds-the-strategy-of-surrender/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is more than just an issue of international credibility, it is also one of national security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell barricaded herself in prison conference room, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9929661/Ghislaine-Maxwell-barricaded-prison-conference-room.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have claimed that Ghislaine Maxwell tried to 'barricade' herself in the video conference room in prison with a cart of legal documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas, Missouri fighting for nurses as beds fill up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-bidding-war-kansas-missouri-hospitals-fighting-for-travel-nurses-as-beds-fill-up/ar-AANMyVp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shifts are often long, the locations unfamiliar. No family or friends may be nearby. But the demand for travel nurses has skyrocketed as the COVID-19 case surge spawned by the delta variant is crushing hospitals across the United States. At a moment when the number of nurses at a facility may determine how many patients can be treated, advertised positions in Kansas and Missouri top $5,600 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man High On Mushrooms Shoots 2 At Miami Beach Restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/25/miami-beach-shooter-chose-victims-at-random/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 22-year-old man told Miami Beach police he felt empowered and chose to shoot two people at random Tuesday evening, killing one and wounding another, after getting high on mushrooms.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
