<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SAFRICA BEGINS SEIZING WHITE-OWNED FARMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/economy/world-economy/south-africa-begins-seizing-whiteowned-farms/news-story/8937f899bd3f131bfc4ffb648ea5c53b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE South African government has begun the process of seizing land from white farmers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Charged With Spying For Iran On Jewish Facilities In USA...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/two-iranian-americans-charged-spying-jewish-israeli-facilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Iranian-Americans have been charged by the Trump administration with spying on Jewish and Israeli-associated facilities in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE'S BACK: HILLARY 'INTIMATE' DONOR DINNERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/hillary-clinton/hillary-clinton-steps-back-fray-fundraise-democrats-fall-n902326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2016 presidential nominee will headline events in California, Illinois and New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane grows to Cat 4 as it heads toward Hawaii...</title>
      <link>http://www.staradvertiser.com/2018/08/20/weather-updates/hurricane-lane-expected-to-take-northwest-turn-forecasters-warn-of-heavy-rain-flooding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How China rules using data, AI, and web surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611815/who-needs-democracy-when-you-have-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how China rules using data, AI, and internet surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest plane has rockets to launch...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2018/08/stratolaunch-announces-not-one-but-an-entire-fleet-of-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hopefully, the aircraft will take flight for the first time this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare in DISNEYLAND as hotel pool poisons guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20180820/nightmare-in-disneyland-paris-as-hotel-pool-poisons-guests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-two people were intoxicated by a bad batch of bleach and sulphuric acid added to the swimming pool tank of one of Disneyland Paris’s hotels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hall of Famers disgusted by current MLB play...</title>
      <link>https://bleacherreport.com/articles/2791455-i-find-it-very-difficult-to-watch-why-mlb-greats-think-baseballs-in-trouble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bleacherreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As legends gathered in Cooperstown, New York, last month on the Friday evening of Hall of Fame induction weekend, it was business as usual for modern day baseball.  In Houston, the Astros and Texas Rangers struck out 19 times...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gator kills woman protecting dog on walk in SCarolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.islandpacket.com/news/local/crime/article217007570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.islandpacket.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hilton Head, SC woman Cassandra Cline was killed in an alligator attack while walking her dog in Sea Pines, police say. Witnesses saw the alligator attack the woman then drag her in a lagoon Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS: Moonves Exit Could Cost $200,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cbs-les-moonves-contract-reveals-nearly-200-million-at-stake-if-he-leaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That package includes three years' worth of salary and bonus; substantial amounts of company stock; health, life insurance and pension benefits and several one-time cash payouts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases hit record high in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-45246049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 41,000 people have been infected with measles in the first six months of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLOT TWIST: WEINSTEIN ACCUSER BECOMES THE ACCUSED...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2018/08/19/harvey-weinstein-accuser-asia-argento-paid-off-actor-sexual-misconduct-repor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asia Argento, one of the first actresses to publicly accuse Harvey Weinstein of sexual assault, reportedly paid off a young…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI HERALD endorses candidate who claims aliens took aboard spaceship...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/402686-miami-herald-endorses-house-candidate-who-claims-she-was-taken</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami Herald is endorsing a congressional candidate who claims to have communicated with aliens throughout her life and says extraterrestrials once visited her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Responds: 'Stunning Level Of Hypocrisy'...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/08/20/harvey-weinstein-responds-to-asia-argento-allegations-this-reveals-stunning-level-hypocrisy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgraced movie mogul Harvey Weinstein blasted Asia Argento, following a report that claimed she paid money to silence a man who accused her of sexual assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT:  SOCIALS 'VERY DANGEROUS'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/20/trump-says-its-very-dangerous-when-twitter-facebook-self-regulate-content-reuters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's comments come just two weeks after major tech firms suspended or banned conservative radio host Alex Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOSCOW:  Accused Russian in USA faces 'borderline torture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-russia-butina/accused-russian-in-u-s-faces-borderline-torture-moscow-idUSKCN1L515Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia accused the United States of trying to break the spirit in jail of Maria Butina, a woman U.S. authorities say is a Russian government agent, and complained she was being subjected to "borderline torture."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Decked Out Plane In World Selling for $639,000,000...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6079655/Qatari-royal-family-puts-Boeing-747-8-jet-sale-5m.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boeing 747-8 has a staggering 10 bathrooms, several lounges spread over two floors and a stunning bedroom suite. Potential buyers are instructed to ring AMAC Aerospace in Switzerland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Vows No More Cover Ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-pope-abuse-letter/pope-writes-to-catholics-on-clergy-sexual-abuse-vows-no-more-cover-up-idUSKCN1L510L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis, facing sexual abuse crises in several countries, wrote an unprecedented letter to all Catholics on Monday, asking each one of them to help root out "this culture of death" and vowing there would be no more cover ups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man severs hand in meat grinder...</title>
      <link>http://www.jamestownsun.com/news/accidents/4487448-man-severs-hand-accident</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jamestownsun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Jamestown man severed his hand while cutting meat at his home on Friday afternoon, according to Maj. Justin Blinsky, assistant chief of the Jamestown Police Department.“This was a horrific accident that someone had to endure,” Blinksy said. “There was obviously severe damage to the man’s hand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dupes dozens in weirdest TINDER date...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/20/woman-dupes-dozens-of-dudes-into-weirdest-tinder-date-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of dudes showed up to Union Square for Tinder dates on Sunday — only to learn they were all there to meet the same woman, and she wanted them to battle it out “Hunger Games”-styl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pesticide Exposure During Pregnancy Linked To Autism...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pesticide-exposure-ddt-pregnancy-linked-autism-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant women with higher levels of a banned pesticide that's still found in many foods today are more likely to have children diagnosed with autism, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 Ex-Miss Americas Call For Gretchen Carlson To Resign For Bullying...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6079395/Nineteen-former-Miss-America-winners-calling-entire-pageant-boar-step-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Miss America winners Caressa Cameron-Jackson and Suzette Charles gave separate interviews on Monday in support of the reigning pageant winner Cara Mund.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Spacey movie takes in dismal $618...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kevin-spacey-movie-takes-dismal-618-173719286.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US actor Kevin Spacey's latest movie has flopped big-time at the box office, taking in a mere $618 as it opened to dire reviews in a handful of theaters across the country. "Billionaire Boys Club," a crime drama based on a true story, in which Spacey co-stars alongside Ansel Elgort ("</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Papadopoulos to feds: Received $10K from foreign national believed was spy...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/20/papadopoulos-foreign-payment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Payment was made during meeting at Israeli hotel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO Takes Heat for Blaming Roy Cohn's AIDS Death on 'Decadent Homosexual Lifestyle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/politico-roy-cohn-aids-death-decadent-homosexual-lifestyle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The piece by senior staff writer Michael Kruse said Cohn contracted AIDS because of his "decadent homosexual lifestyle" and swiftly took heat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DroneHunter knocks 'bad' killer drones out of the sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/dronehunter-knocks-killer-drones-out-sky-n902031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the DroneHunter find and neutralize a drone loaded with explosives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberty University Journalists Say Jerry Falwell Jr. Censored Student Newspaper...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/liberty-university-censorship-of-the-student-newspaper-or-editorial-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a fine line between appropriate control and operating a propaganda machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won and done? Sportsbooks banning smart money...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/chalk/story/_/id/24425026/gambling-bookmakers-growing-us-legal-betting-market-allowed-ban-bettors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should bookmakers be allowed to refuse to take bets from customers? It's a growing debate in the legal U.S. sports betting market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London airport resorts to pens, whiteboards after technical failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.smdailyjournal.com/news/world/gatwick-passengers-need-to-check-whiteboards-after-it-glitch/article_ee9a483c-2d74-5e23-841e-a98fd238ef41.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smdailyjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Gatwick Airport has resorted to using marking pens and whiteboards to post flight information after a technical failure caused electronic message boards to malfunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument over WALMART parking space leaves 1 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/new-details-argument-over-walmart-parking-space-leaves-dead-witnesses-say/tUpH9ZlkTrWNMKuUyFcZqN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An argument over a parking space turned deadly Sunday night outside a crowded metro Atlanta Walmart,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen cruise passenger sang to stay alive for 10 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/20/uk-cruise-ship-passenger-found-alive-after-treading-water-10-hours/1040334002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 46-year-old British woman, Kay Longstaff, fell off of a Norwegian Cruise Line around midnight Saturday, plunging into the Adriatic Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pit Bull With 'Half Face' Still Smiling Despite Injury...</title>
      <link>https://patch.com/new-jersey/newarknj/despite-awful-injury-pit-bull-half-face-still-smiling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;patch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mother pit bull separated from her puppies is feeling love and human kindness for the first time in her life after being rescued in Newark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brennan Dared to Sue...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2fa0dd1094e848738a7c4d66cad28226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Monday dared former CIA Director John Brennan to take legal action to try to prevent him from stripping security clearances from other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goats spotted roaming on NYC subway tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Goats-Subway-Tracks-NYC-N-Train-491266351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goats have to commute, too. The MTA says two goats were spotted roaming on the above-ground N tracks near Green-Wood Cemetery in Brooklyn Monday, though the transit agency assured the animals were not affecting service. The MTA says...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy approaching its speed limit?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/there-are-signs-the-us-economy-is-approaching-its-speed-limit-2018-08-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few are arguing that the economy is about to enter a tailspin, but there’s some evidence to suggest the rate of growth may be approaching its limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel 'thugs' are 'looking for trouble'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/20/trump-muellers-angry-democrat-thugs-are-looking-for-trouble/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump referred to Robert Mueller’s team as “Angry Democrat Thugs” who are looking for “trouble” as he continued to rail about White House lawyer Don McGahn b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE BOWS TO BEIJING: 25,000 APPS PULLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-pulls-25-000-apps-from-china-app-store-following-state-media-criticism-1534731049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple said it removed illegal gambling apps from its App Store in China as it came under fire from state media—a move that could help quell the latest challenge for the tech giant in its most important market outside the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor's orders: Let children just play...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/doctor-s-orders-let-children-just-play/article_2feb1c29-26c9-5d7b-ae2c-2318a24a8d4f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine a drug that could enhance a child’s creativity, critical thinking and resilience. Imagine that this drug were simple to make, safe to take, and could be had for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gavin Newsom criticized for flip-flopping on California's most pressing issues...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-pol-ca-governor-race-gavin-newsom-issues-shift-20180820-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom has made several about-faces during his two decades in politics. Early in the 2018 governor’s race, his shifting stances were targeted by Democratic rivals, who accused the lieutenant governor of flip-flopping or equivocating on pivotal issues facing California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THRILLER' Dethroned! Eagles Pass Michael Jackson With Top-Selling Album Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/the-eagles-greatest-hits-michael-jackson-thriller-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Eagles' "Greatest Hits 1971-1975" album has surpassed Michael Jackson's "Thriller" to become the No. 1-selling album of all time, per the AP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  61 people shot over weekend...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/08/20/chicago-weekend-shootings-gun-violence-violent-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty-one people were shot in Chicago over the weekend, eight of them fatally, including two missing teenage boys found dead in a field late Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stevie Wonder links Aretha Franklin's cancer to 'global warming'...</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2018/08/20/stevie-wonder-blames-aretha-franklins-cancer-on-global-warming-all-these-various-diseases-that-we-have-and-all-that-is-happening-in-the-world-in-part-is-because-there-are-those-who-don/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of wanting to eat child sentenced to probation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/man-accused-wanting-eat-child-sentenced-probation-57284994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who South Carolina authorities say wanted to enslave and eat a child has been sentenced to probation. News outlets quote court records as saying 36-year-old Justin Teeter Bensing pleaded guilty to two counts of criminal solicitation of a minor and was sentenced Aug. 9 to 10 years in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen to Howard Dean: Does Hillary Have a 'Penis?'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sacha-baron-cohen-tries-to-convince-howard-dean-hillary-clinton-has-a-penis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the penultimate episode of ‘Who Is America?’ there was no sign of Sarah Palin, but we did get some awkward interactions with liberals Jill Stein and Howard Dean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: #METOO LEADER PAID OFF YOUNG ACTOR</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/asia-argento-paid-sexual-assault-accuser-report-1135872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argento was one of the first and most vocal accusers of disgraced movie mogul Harvey Weinstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1005725/south-africa-farm-seizures-white-farmers-cyril-ramaphosa-anc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH AFRICA's government has begun seizing land from white farmers, targeting two game farms in the northern province of Limpopo after talks with the owners to buy the properties collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: Man yells 'Jesus is coming' before stabbing toddler...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2018/08/19/16-month-old-boy-stabbed-death-man-thought-father-lewisville-apartments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is accused of fatally stabbing a 16-month-old boy who was thought to be his son Sunday afternoon at a Lewisville apartment complex before he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rails Against Mueller Calling Obstruction 'Phony Crime'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/20/trump-rails-against-mueller-calling-obstruction-a-phony-crime#gs.mjdaapk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Rails Against Mueller Calling Obstruction a ‘Phony Crime’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela Launches One of Greatest Currency Devaluations in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/08/19/venezuela-s-95-devaluation-adds-to-turmoil-after-drone-attack#gs.IywG49c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro announced dramatic measures to rescue the country’s flailing economy, including a staggering 95 percent devaluation of the bolivar, in a move that will test the capacity of already beleaguered citizens to stomach even more pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Luxury Apartment Sales Plummet in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/luxury-apartment-sales-plummet-in-new-york-city-1534770001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of the most expensive New York apartments fell sharply in the first half of the year, pushing sellers to cut asking prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-cigs damage DNA...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-08-e-cigarettes-dna.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popularity of electronic cigarettes continues to grow worldwide, as many people view them as a safer alternative to smoking. But the long-term effects of e-cigarette usage, commonly called "vaping," are unknown. Today, researchers report that vaping may modify the genetic material, or DNA, in the oral cells of users, which could increase their cancer risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson collapses on stage during show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/marilyn-manson-collapses-on-stage-during-houston-show-2368754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson was forced to cut short his concert in Houston on Saturday night after collapsing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Put Face on 14,000-Year-Old Woman...</title>
      <link>http://www.laht.com/article.asp?ArticleId=2463341&amp;CategoryId=13936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.laht.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy realistic humanoid robot footage sends shivers...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/436345-robot-adam-video-realistic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video has emerged on Twitter showing a faceless yet worryingly realistic humanoid robot walking in what looks like a perfectly mundane courtyard. The trip down the uncanny valley caused some to proclaim an impending apocalypse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, lies and DUIs: GOP dumps oppo...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/20/house-republicans-oppo-research-788468</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican ads are getting personal in the fight for the House majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian military braces for massive war games...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-military-braces-massive-war-games-092146547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia's military forces in the country's east were put on high alert Monday ahead of massive war games that also involve China and Mongolia, the largest show of power in nearly 40 years, the Russian defense minister said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton: I might consider running for office...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/pa/article-6078669/Chelsea-Clinton-I-consider-running-office--future.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author confirmed that she has no current plans to follow in her parents´ footsteps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA STOCK SLIDING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/20/tesla-falls-below-300-down-another-2percent-after-last-weeks-slide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's carmaker was under pressure again to start the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where's Off Switch? Videogame Developers Making Harder to Stop Playing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wheres-the-off-switch-videogame-developers-are-making-it-harder-to-stop-playing-1534757400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videogames have gotten harder to turn off, mental-health experts and parents say, raising concerns about the impact of long gaming sessions on players’ lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to Sell NFL Teams? Worries Party Winding Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/is-it-time-to-sell-your-nfl-team-1534690303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Football is the biggest sport in the country, by far. But there are worries the party is beginning to wind down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Documents Hidden LGBTQ History in South...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/Project-uncovering-South-s-hidden-LGBTQ-history-13167542.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIRMINGHAM, Ala. (AP) - A new project is documenting the history of LGBTQ people in the Deep South, a region that once all but forced gays, lesbians and others to live in hiding. Bob Burns, who is gay, both lived through some of the toughest times for LGBTQ Southerners and documented them through years of activism. Now 66, he compiled a trove of information from years that included the AIDS epidemic and the systemic oppression of gay people in the Deep South. Burns is now among the donors to a nonprofit organization that's gathering information about the hidden history of gay men, lesbians, bisexuals, transgender people and others in the Southern United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MY SON, MY LOVE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/asia-argento-called-17-year-old-actor-accused-sexual-assault-son-love-instagram-105304726.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Rose McGowan, who befriended Argento after both women shared their allegations of Harvey Weinstein's sexual misconduct, said her "heart is broken" by the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PURGE OF GAY PRIESTS?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/20/cardinal-mccarrick-scandal-inflames-debate-over-gay-priests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allegations that disgraced ex-Cardinal Theodore McCarrick engaged in sex with adult seminarians have inflamed a long-running debate about the presence of gay men in the Roman Catholic priesthood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen surfer bitten twice by shark off NCarolina coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/trending-now/14yearold-surfer-bitten-by-shark-off-north-carolina-coast/816474265</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teen was bitten twice on the leg by a shark Sunday morning while surfing off Atlantic Beach, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/19/us/asia-argento-assault-jimmy-bennett.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress and director Asia Argento, among the first women to publicly accuse Harvey Weinstein, arranged to pay an actor after he said she sexually assaulted him when he was 17, documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Shoot 'Knifeman' 'Shouting Allahu Akbar' in Barcelona...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-barcelona-police-shoot-knifeman-13108066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack happened at a police station in Cornella on the outskirts of the Catalan capital in Spain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Escort says oligarch now has tapes on Russia interference...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/78eef0ecec49412b816ac5169d63279a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PATTAYA, Thailand (AP) — A model and escort from Belarus who caused a sensation by claiming to have information linking Russian interference to the election of President Donald Tr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Issues Letter to Catholics Condemning Sexual Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.vaticannews.va/en/pope/news/2018-08/pope-francis-letter-people-of-god-sexual-abuse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vaticannews.va&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has responded to new reports of clerical sexual abuse and the ecclesial cover-up of abuse. In an impassioned letter addressed to the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO RISING: CRUZ CHALLENGER GAINS GROUND IN TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/20/beto-orourke-texas-democrat-gains-ground-ted-cruz-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O’Rourke’s opponent, Senator Ted Cruz, paints him as ‘hard left like Bernie Sanders’ but the challenger for the Senate seat is drawing crowds in conservative suburbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Isn't Paying Its Electric Bills. You Might Be...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/08/20/amazon-isn-t-paying-its-electric-bills-you-might-be </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Isn’t Paying Its Electric Bills. You Might Be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bull market in stocks poised to set record for longest ever...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/89765b4a4f9f4b1ca995bd8763b44e9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The bull market in stocks is poised this week to break the record as the longest in the history of U.S. trading.        If the market doesn't drop significa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion reigns as Maduro releases new banknotes...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180820-confusion-reigns-venezuela-braces-release-new-banknotes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Erdogan casts crisis in religious, patriotic terms...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-currency-erdogan/defiant-erdogan-casts-turkey-currency-crisis-in-religious-patriotic-terms-idUSKCN1L50OA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Tayyip Erdogan said on Monday an attack on Turkey's economy was no different from a strike against its flag or the Islamic call to prayer, responding to a recent currency sell-off in stark religious and nationalist terms ahead of a major Muslim holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary challenge to Trump? It could help him in 2020...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/402344-primary-challenge-to-trump-it-could-help-him-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump could face a primary challenger in 2020. And a contested fight for the Republican nomination might be exactly what he wants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUMMER FROM HELL': CATHOLIC CHURCH FAITH CRISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/religion/index.ssf/2018/08/catholic_church_sex_abuse_scan_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic church has lost more members in recent decades than any other major faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane passenger arrested for urinating on man during trans-Pacific flight...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/19/man-24-urinates-on-japanese-passenger-during-flight-to-tokyo-7858083/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is believed to have had 'at least five champagnes' before the incident took place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parishioners close wallets for donation baskets...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ddab5d7ca7a4ac8843209489cbc23a7/Catholics-consider-withholding-donations-amid-scandals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Michael Drweiga has opened his wallet whenever the donation basket comes around at church, but the latest revelations of priests sexually abusing children brought him to th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto tries to tap TX border region 'fierce pride'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/2018-elections/2018/08/19/beto-orourke-tries-tap-border-regions-fierce-prideanger-trumps-immigration-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROWNSVILLE -- Beto O’Rourke is trying to drive up turnout in South Texas by tapping into passions stirred by separation of immigrant children...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina to File 'Crimes Against Humanity' Case at Hague...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/20/argentina-to-file-case-against-venezuela-at-hague-macri-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argentina to File Case Against Venezuela at Hague, Macri Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUTH ISN'T TRUTH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/19/giuliani-echoes-trump-2016-tower-meeting-sought-dirt-on-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Truth isn’t truth,” Donald Trump’s lawyer Rudy Giuliani said on Sunday in discussing why having the president be interviewed by Special Counsel Robert Mueller for the probe into election interference isn’t a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists allowed off beaten path on NK's sacred volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/headline-tourists-off-beaten-path-north-koreas-sacred-013935247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNT PAEKTU, North Korea (AP) — Foreign tourists looking to go off the beaten path in North Korea can now camp out on the country's biggest volcano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gretchen Carlson Denies Silencing, Bullying 'Miss America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/gretchen-carlson-responds-miss-america-cara-munds-claim-she-was-silenced-bullied-1135867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlson wrote that she was "surprised and saddened" by Cara Mund's accusations, which have cost the organization $75,000 in scholarships, and she is "concerned that it will dilute the experience for the next woman selected to wear the crown."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$380K IN HUSH MONEY...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/asia-argento-jimmy-bennett-harvey-weinstein-sexual-assault-1202448252/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein accuser and outspoken voice of the #MeToo movement Asia Argento has handled her own sexual assault case on the down-low, making an arrangement to pay Jimmy Bennett, who accused her…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'UNDERAGE SEX ASSAULT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/asia-argento-paid-hush-money-underage-sexual-assault-accuser-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young actor/musician says Argento sexually assaulting him in a California hotel room when he was 17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: Argento Told Cannes Audience Other Perps 'Sitting Among You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/asia-argento-delivers-searing-speech-calling-cannes-festival-weinstein-s-n875846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“And even tonight, sitting among you, there are those who still have to be held accountable for their conduct against women," she added.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCRIPT FLIPPED AS WEINSTEIN ACCUSER -- FACES ACCUSATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/asia-argento-sexual-assault-settlement-1202909861/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to documents obtained by the New York Times, leading #MeToo advocate Asia Argento settled an accusation of sexual assault from former child actor and musician Jimmy Bennett for the sum of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Beijing close to establishing 'nuclear triad,' has practiced targeting US...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/08/17/pentagon-china-close-to-nuclear-triad-has-practiced-targeting-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The practice runs on Guam are just some of the worrisome changes in China's behavior, the report found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company embeds microchips in 80 employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611884/this-company-embeds-microchips-in-its-employees-and-they-love-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last August, 50 employees at Three Square Market got RFID chips in their hands. Now 80 have them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: Mortuary gives family wrong ashes -- who travel thousands of miles to scatter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/19/mortuary-gives-wrong-ashes-to-family-who-then-scatter-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island funeral home gave the ashes of a dad to the wrong grieving family — who then traveled thousands of miles away to scatter his remains, a new lawsuit claims. The Lake Ronkonkoma Moloney…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disruptor transforms to traditional TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/arts-and-entertainment/wp/2018/08/19/netflix-forever-changed-traditional-television-now-its-becoming-traditional-television/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent announcements certainly suggest that might be the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Deletes All User Reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2018/08/netflix-deletes-user-reviews-testing-ads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A step closer to a wholly “because you watched” world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Plumber stabbed to death by customer over lunch break...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7052789/plumber-killed-by-customer-claims-over-long-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PLUMBER was stabbed to death after an alleged row with a customer over a three-hour break. Gary Amer’s body was discovered next to a boiler and his tool kit. He had been hit on the head with a pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Military Faces Sweeping Commander Turnover...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/military-faces-a-sweeping-turnover-among-upper-commanders-1534700301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is planning a series of promotions to replace a wave of retiring commanders, marking the administration’s largest imprint on military leadership thus far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savage brawl between warring groups of firefighters...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/18/fdny-brawl-one-of-the-most-severe-beatings-seen-on-tape-insider/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A savage brawl between two warring groups of FDNY firefighters at a Bronx firehouse has sparked multiple investigations and shocked even hardened department brass, The Post has learned. More than a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Lawyers Got 'Limited' Info From WH Counsel's Attorney...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/19/us/politics/don-mcgahn-trump-mueller.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lapse has contributed to a growing recognition that an early strategy of full cooperation with the inquiry was a potentially damaging mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN $20,000,000 BANK FRAUD?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/19/michael-cohen-reportedly-under-investigation-for-20m-in-bank-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s former personal lawyer is being investigated over more than $20 million in loans to taxi companies owned by him and his family — and could face charges within the next…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELON MUSK: NO SLEEP...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/19/technology/business/elon-musk-huffington/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla CEO says there are no other options than working 120-hour weeks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
