<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Crypto couple inspires 3 Hollywood projects in week since arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/crypto-couple-documentaries-netflix-1235094777/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennial crypto alleged schemers Heather Morgan and Ilya “Dutch” Lichtenstein have inspired two more projects on top of the Netflix documentary that was already announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC wants to give people mask break...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/16/cdc-wants-to-give-people-a-break-from-wearing-masks-as-pandemic-improves-director-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Rochelle Walensky said the CDC is focusing more on Covid hospitalizations as the guide to whether public health measures should be lifted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zucker Lover Goes Scorched Earth as She Quits Too...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/allison-gollust-cnns-chief-marketing-officer-resigns-over-probe-into-jeff-zucker-romance-chris-cuomo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allison Gollust accused WarnerMedia of making “an attempt to retaliate against me and change the media narrative in the wake of their disastrous handling of the last two weeks.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon's Billionaire Backer Guo Wengui Reveals He's Bankrupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/billionaire-steve-bannon-gettr-backer-guo-wengui-files-bankruptcy-1679824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guo Wengui posted a video to his Gettr account showing him signing the bankruptcy documents on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  How Secret Assault Allegation Upended CNN...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/world/how-a-secret-assault-allegation-against-an-anchor-upended-cnn-7775987/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York attorney general had just announced that her office was investigating sexual harassment allegations against Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Unprecedented autopsy backlog has morgue operating in Baltimore parking garage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmar2news.com/news/local-news/morgue-operating-in-baltimore-parking-garage-as-200-bodies-await-autopsy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmar2news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 bodies are awaiting autopsy at the Maryland Office of Chief Medical Examiner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saget's family sue to block death records release...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4697347/bob-saget-death-wife-lawsuit-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOB Saget’s family is suing Orange County officials to block the release of records in connection to the investigation of the actor’s death. The was filed by Kelly Rizzo, Saget’s widow, and his thr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania Trump sold her NFT to herself for $170,000?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/money-that-won-melania-trump-nft-came-from-melania-trump-wallet/ar-AATWlKv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans credit card debt fastest in 22 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-in/money/news/2-reasons-americans-just-dove-into-credit-card-debt-faster-than-they-have-in-22-years/ar-AATHLju</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last three months of 2021, Americans swiped $52 billion in credit card debt, the fastest since the NY Fed started tracking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Magical Thinking Risks It All...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/andrewtisch/2022/02/15/how-magical-thinking-led-america-to-30-trillion-in-debt/?sh=733a50f26118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, DC must be a magical place, because the people in charge of it keep conjuring fantasies that defy belief. Our children shouldn't have to pay a heavy price for their magical thinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Wash trading'...</title>
      <link>https://senegalbgc.org/blog/2022/02/11/melania-trump-sold-her-nft-to-herself-for-170000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;senegalbgc.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED STILL PUMPING; $9 TRILLION AND COUNTING!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-minutes-likely-details-rate-110652066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The release on Wednesday of the minutes of the Federal Reserve's last policy meeting is likely to shed light on the U.S. central bank's plans to trim its massive balance sheet and hike interest rates in 2022 as well as update its shifting view of inflation. The document, due at 2 p.m. EST (1900 GMT), will provide an accounting of the Jan. 25-26 meeting, in which policymakers agreed that it would "soon be appropriate" to raise the Fed's benchmark overnight interest rate from its near-zero level, and also engaged in extensive discussion about the future of nearly $9 trillion in securities held by the central bank. Debate around both topics and the range of views expressed about the severity of the ongoing inflation surge and other economic risks may hint at just how aggressive the Fed plans to be in tightening monetary policy, and in particular how likely it is to inaugurate a round of rate hikes in March with a half-percentage-point increase in its target rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Crypto Ruined My Life': Mental Health Crisis Hitting Bitcoin Investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akvn8z/crypto-bad-for-mental-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stress, anxiety and depression of funnelling your life savings into a volatile market is no joke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-COVID conditions still confound medical community 2 years into pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.eagletribune.com/region/more-questions-than-answers-post-covid-conditions-still-confound-medical-community-2-years-into-pandemic/article_de11b23a-7683-5d49-8e6a-7583c66c32d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eagletribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — Kels Rosario tested positive for COVID-19 before there was a vaccine and again after he got the shots. He suspects an illness at the beginning of the pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guac war! Mexican president mocks avocado blockade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10519361/Mexican-president-says-Biden-using-avocado-ban-political-weapon-against-country.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's president claimed the US suspension on avocado imports was part of a conspiracy to protect American producers from losing to 'quality' Mexican products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gollust Goes Scorched Earth as She Quits Too...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ousted-cnn-boss-jeff-zucker-011509996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Groll/APAllison Gollust, CNN’s executive vice president and chief marketing officer, resigned from the network on Tuesday, less than two weeks after her boss-turned-lover Jeff Zucker also quit.Jason Kilar, the CEO of CNN’s parent company WarnerMedia, announced Gollust’s departure in a Tuesday memo. He said a company investigation into “issues” related to the recent ouster of disgraced star anchor Chris Cuomo had found that Gollust, along with Cuomo and then-network president Zucker, had com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe heads toward new normal as final virus curbs unwind...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/europe-heads-back-normal-germany-093118612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Europe looks to be gradually leaving the pandemic behind, with Germany poised to become the latest in the region to unwind restrictions that have disrupted life for two years. Most Read from BloombergElon Musk Donated $5.7 Billion of Tesla Shares to CharityTrump's Accountants Just Quit. What Took So Long?U.S. Offers Support After Banks Face Cyber Hit: Ukraine UpdateU.S. Accuses Zero Hedge of Spreading Russian PropagandaPutin Seeks Diplomatic Solution Amid ‘Partial’ Troop PullbackM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: OTC Pain Relievers Raise Risk Of Ringing Ears...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/painkillers-tinnitus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This group includes NSAIDs, acetaminophen (Tylenol), or COX-2 inhibitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennial Politician Wants to Rebrand Israel. Not All Dems Buying It....</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/02/16/idan-roll-israel-foreign-policy-00008916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idan Roll has become the face of an effort to refocus Israeli foreign policy around issues like gay rights and climate change — at a time when Democrats are more openly critical of Israel’s treatment of the Palestinians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Feinstein approval all-time low...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/california-sen-dianne-feinsteins-approval-ratings-hit-an-all-time-low-poll-says/ar-AATVqhs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian speedskater celebrates with middle fingers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/16/2022-olympics-russian-speedskater-gives-double-middle-finger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian speedskater Daniil Aldoshkin has apologized for throwing a double-bird after defeating Team USA in the men’s team pursuit semifinals on Tuesday in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Nightmare Goes On as Cops Probe Prince Charles Charity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2022/feb/16/met-investigating-cash-for-honours-claims-linked-to-princes-foundation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metropolitan police have launched investigation into allegations linked to Prince Charles charity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will RAMS McVay return next season?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hern-ndez-sean-mcvay-back-040413879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basking in the glow of Super Bowl LVI, Rams coach Sean McVay would not commit Monday to definitely being on the sideline in L.A. again next season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Woman Used Pandemic-Relief Loan to Pay Hit Man...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/16/florida-woman-used-pandemic-relief-loan-to-pay-a-hit-man-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Paycheck Protection Program is intended to help businesses meet their payroll during the pandemic, but scores of people have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN REJECTS TRUMP PRIVILEGE</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/rejecting-trump-claim-biden-orders-release-white-house-logs-jan-6-panel-nyt-2022-02-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has rejected former President Donald Trump's executive privilege claims and ordered White House visitor logs to be released to the panel investigating the deadly Jan. 6, 2021 attack, the New York Times reported on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants sew mouths shut in quest for Mexico passage to U.S. border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-migration-mexico/migrants-sew-their-mouths-shut-in-quest-for-mexico-passage-to-u-s-border-idUSKBN2KL05U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen undocumented migrants on Mexico's southern border sewed their mouths shut on Tuesday in a bid to convince the country's immigration authority to grant them passage toward the U.S. border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark kills swimmer in Sydney's first fatal attack in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-shark/shark-kills-swimmer-in-sydneys-first-fatal-attack-in-decades-idUSKBN2KL0M6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shark killed a swimmer off a Sydney beach on Wednesday in the city's first fatal attack in nearly 60 years, causing "catastrophic injuries", police and ambulance services said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary under microscope as Congress weighs stock trade ban...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/594444-judiciary-under-microscope-as-congress-weighs-stock-trade-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers are pushing for stronger stock trading rules for Supreme Court justices and federal judges as they weigh a stock trading ban for members of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Beto O'Rourke, 2020 Still Haunts 2022...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/16/for-beto-orourke-2020-still-haunts-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TYLER, Texas — Even in deep red East Texas, even on a Tuesday afternoon, even after a failed bid for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executives Quitting to Spend Time With Family...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/16/executives-are-quitting-to-spend-time-with-family-really/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some were burned out. Some were unhappy. Some were disillusioned. Some wanted their lives back. Some truly and genuinely wanted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dystopian robot dogs latest in US-Mexico border surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/feb/16/robot-dogs-us-mexico-border-surveillance-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activists have argued that the tools in use – drones and towers equipped with night vision and radar – make the region dangerous to migrants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team USA crash out of Winter Olympics men's ice hockey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/winterolympics/article-10518331/Slovakia-claim-shock-shootout-win-mens-ice-hockey-quarter-final-Winter-Olympics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slovakia claimed a shock shootout win over the United States to reach the semi-finals of the men's ice hockey tournament at the Beijing Games on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE-ESCALATION?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-europe-russia-united-states-vladimir-putin-534fb1c355ff5f135ba0261cb1448c3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russia said Wednesday it was returning more troops and weapons to bases, but NATO declared it saw no sign of a drawdown as fears that Moscow could invade Ukraine  soon persisted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas TV series glorifies fight against Israel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-arts-and-entertainment-israel-media-e4a0bdf6070927c8c817e331b5e228fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIT LAHIYA, Gaza Strip (AP) — The Palestinian militants scrambled out of the tunnel and attacked an Israeli tank in broad daylight as gunfire and explosions echoed across the Gaza frontier. This time it wasn't the start of another war, but an action scene filmed for a TV series produced by the territory's militant Hamas rulers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botched butt injection suspected after woman dumped at Bronx hospital dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-botched-butt-injection-woman-dies-bronx-20220215-atd2jk5bcva5tm4pcr7zisuaua-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two mystery women are being sought after they drove 53-year-old Maxine Messam to Jacobi Medical Center in her own BMW SUV and then walked off, leaving the vehicle behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries face new global virus divide on opening up or staying closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/countries-face-new-global-covid-divide-on-opening-up-or-staying-closed/ar-AATUD0C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada eyeing 'no-go' zones in Ottawa to quell 'Freedom Convoy' protests, official says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/canada-eyeing-e2-80-98no-go-e2-80-99-zones-in-ottawa-to-quell-e2-80-98freedom-convoy-e2-80-99-protests-official-says/ar-AATV3Eu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move fast, rename things: FACEBOOK tries to boost morale with new slogans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/move-fast-rename-things-facebook-tries-to-boost-morale-with-new-slogans/ar-AATTK6P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saget family sues to block authorities from releasing photos, videos from death investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bob-saget-e2-80-99s-family-sues-to-block-authorities-from-releasing-photos-and-videos-from-death-investigation/ar-AATVkFT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds NYT not liable in Palin defamation case...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/594355-new-york-times-found-not-guilty-in-palin-libel-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A jury found The New York Times not liable after the news organization was sued by former Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin (R) over an editorial it published linking her to a mass shooting in 2011.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court fight looms as questions swirl over Trump finances...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-manhattan-donald-trump-subpoenas-41d4e597cd6717f77bd5393c6644c9a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Questions about Donald Trump's business practices are piling up. Whether the former president is forced to answer any of them under oath could be decided in a matter of days. New York's attorney general will go to court Thursday seeking to enforce a subpoena for Trump's testimony in a civil investigation she says uncovered evidence his company used “fraudulent or misleading” valuations of golf clubs, skyscrapers and other properties to get loans and tax benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moment he shot, killed with prop gun recreated...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10516039/Family-Halyna-Hutchins-announce-wrongful-death-lawsuit-shot-Alec-Baldwin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of slain cinematographer Halyna Hutchins on Tuesday filed a wrongful death lawsuit against Alec Baldwin stemming from her shooting death on the set of his Western Rust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man attacks APPLEBEE'S employee with meat cleaver over jab proof...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/man-attacks-bellevue-applebees-employee-with-meat-cleaver-over-covid-19-vaccine-proof</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLEVUE, Wash. &amp;mdash;King County Prosecutors say a man tried to attack a Bellevue restaurant worker with a meat cleaver after being asked to show proof of a Covid-19 vaccine. Investigators say Michael Dousa, 58, lunged at an Applebee&amp;rsquo;s bartender with a meat cleaver after he was asked to leave the Bellevue restaurant when he couldn&amp;rsquo;t provide proof of vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON QUEEN'S ORDERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-andrews-12million-sex-abuse-26240437</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The on running sex abuse case against the Duke of York has been brought to an end after Prince Andrew £12million settlement outside of court with Virginia Giuffre Roberts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver found with 'bomb-making materials' at San Diego naval air station...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/15/driver-found-with-bomb-making-materials-at-us-naval-air-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Island Naval Air Station in San Diego closed its inbound and outbound gates on Tuesday after a driver tried to enter with “bomb making materials,” officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For high court nominees 'When's your birthday?' matters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/stephen-breyer-joe-biden-us-supreme-court-seniors-f70f8aeb467efc48863875fba4f2a151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Help wanted: Well-respected liberal jurist. Black.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ O'Rourke dead at 74...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4694538/journalist-former-editor-pj-orourke-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles not in top 10 market viewership!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/nielsen-releases-super-bowl-tv-ratings-after-rams-bengals-classic/ar-AATTpfK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHILLY INQUIRER set out to be 'anti-racist' paper. Meant looking at its history...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-philadelphia-inquirer-set-out-to-become-an-e2-80-98anti-racist-e2-80-99-newspaper-that-meant-taking-a-tough-look-at-its-history/ar-AATT75M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump stash of docs shows 'fragile' historical record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-mar-a-lago-6fd3ea04ea21abd0c68d37c71b234a4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As president, Donald Trump never liked to leave a paper trail. He avoided email, admonished aides to stop taking notes during meetings and ripped up documents when he was finished with them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma abortion providers still inundated with Texas women...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/abortion-health-business-texas-oklahoma-65225decf918b820801d162f14b09b80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Two abortion providers in Oklahoma said Tuesday that they’re still seeing a massive influx of women from Texas who want to terminate their pregnancies after Texas last year passed the most restrictive anti-abortion law in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New research points to possible reason for long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-696452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Spanish study suggests that SARS-CoV-2 mediated vagus nerve dysfunction (VND) could be responsible for long COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon's Latest Strategy: Promote Socialism To Combat Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/pentagons-latest-strategy-promote-socialism-to-combat-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is slated to host an event on Wednesday making "the case for global justice and democratic socialism" as a means to combat China’s rise, sparking ire on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA From Rape Kits Used to Arrest Victims Years Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjbekw/dna-from-rape-kits-used-to-arrest-victims-years-later-officials-claim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was arrested on property crime charges, and her DNA was allegedly used to identify her from a rape kit exam she took years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In death trial, MLB players reveal rampant drug use...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/in-trial-of-angels-employee-matt-harvey-and-other-players-testify-about-drug-use-in-mlb/ar-AATTzQ4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattacks hit Ukrainian govt sites, major banks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-business-europe-russia-e791990f60841b599f664c34f58403de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — A series of cyberattacks on Tuesday knocked the websites of Ukrainian government offices and major banks offline, Ukrainian authorities said, attacks that came amid strong tensions between Russia and the West over Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest used wrong word during baptisms. Church now says thousands invalid....</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/catholic-priest-andres-arango-baptisms-invalid-phoenix-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If you were baptized using the wrong words, that means your baptism is invalid, and you are not baptized," Bishop Thomas Olmsted wrote in a message to parishioners. "You will need to be baptized."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEC BALDWIN SUED FOR WRONGFUL DEATH...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/02/15/halyna-hutchins-wrongful-death-lawsuit-shooting-alec-baldwin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin is now a defendant in a wrongful death lawsuit filed by the family of Halyna Hutchins.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
