<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Inside Biggest, Most Expensive Superyacht Ever Designed...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com.au/lifestyle/travel/take-a-tour-of-the-biggest-most-expensive-superyacht-ever-designed/image-gallery/b013fc1c423a031c02607d299e1c1ab6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now simply named 'Project Valkyrie.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake adds to jewel collection with $400,000 custom iPhone case...</title>
      <link>https://hypebeast.com/2019/2/drake-jason-of-beverly-hills-custom-iphone-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hypebeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When your case is 500x more than your phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Prosecutor, Kamala Packed Prisons With Pot Peddlers...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/kamala-harris-packed-california-prisons-for-peddling-pot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris admitted in an interview this week to using marijuana, an act that landed thousands in prison while she was California's Attorney General.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick settles collusion case against NFL...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/26004715/colin-kaepernick-eric-reid-settle-grievance-case-nfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL, Colin Kaepernick and Eric Reid issued a joint statement Friday saying they have resolved the collusion grievances filed by the players against the league.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promised to 'Build That Wall,' Then Ran Out of Time and Options...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-promised-to-build-that-wall-then-ran-out-of-time-and-options-11550262854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s declaration of a national emergency to fund a southern border barrier comes after divisions and competing priorities in the White House allowed the project to languish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Authorities Relocate Hundreds of Migrants From Border City...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mexican-authorities-relocate-hundreds-of-migrants-from-border-city-11550262962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Central American migrants encamped in Mexico’s border city of Piedras Negras, across from Eagle Pass, Texas, are being relocated to other cities after a group of migrants rioted earlier this week and attempted to leave an abandoned factory where they were being held.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE reaped millions of tax breaks as it secretly expanded real estate footprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/google-reaped-millions-of-tax-breaks-as-it-secretly-expanded-its-real-estate-footprint-across-the-us/2019/02/15/7912e10e-3136-11e9-813a-0ab2f17e305b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidentiality agreements and shell companies make it nearly impossible for some communities to know, let alone protest or debate, who is using their land, resources and tax dollars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER: Trump 'total capitulation on immigration'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/why-trump-doesnt-like-ann-coulter-anymore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump cares what Ann Coulter thinks, and he proved it Friday by pretending he doesn’t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Said attackers were white but two suspects are black...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/jussie-smollett-said-attackers-were-white-but-the-two-suspects-are-black</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Chicago have arrested two Nigerian brothers in connection with an alleged racist and homophobic attack on black actor Jussie Smollett last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'basic income' become the California norm? Town starts $500 no-strings payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/article226280230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENSUS BATTLE MOVES TO SUPREME COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6710371/Supreme-Court-decide-2020-Census-ask-people-theyre-U-S-citizens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The justices will hear an appeal in late April and decide whether to overturn a lower federal court ruling that barred the Trump administration from asking about citizenship on Census forms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow jumps 400 points; Stock Market's 8th Straight Weekly Gain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/15/stocks-trump-speech-us-china-trade-and-earnings-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks surged on Friday amid increasing hopes for a U.S.-China trade deal as equities posted another solid weekly gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Woman Throws Profanity-Laced Tirade On JETBLUE Flight After Being Seated Next To Child...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/02/15/woman-removed-jetblue-flight-profanity-laced-outbursts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman's trip to Las Vegas on Valentine's Day was cut short after she reportedly got unruly on a plane and had to be taken off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Traveling 128 MPH Nearly Splits SUV In Half; Blows Through Red Light In Miami Beach...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/02/15/cbs4-exclusive-speeding-tesla-near-rips-suv-half/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla that police say was going nearly 130 miles per hour plowed into a black Infiniti SUV on the MacArthur Causeway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Cop Shot In Ambush Suing FACEBOOKGOOGLETWITTER Alleging Companies Radicalized Gunman...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/dart-officer-sues-social-media-giants-downtown-police-ambush/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DART officer Jesus Retana was shot in the arm by a short fired from the second floor of El Cento College in July 2016. He blames social media companies for playing a role in the violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inaugural receives NJ civil subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-inaugural-receives-civil-subpoena-jersey-state-attorney/story?id=61106438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's inaugural committee has now received a second subpoena as questions grow about the fundraising and expenditures around the inaugural festivities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly votes to require businesses to accept cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/02/15/philadelphia-law-would-require-retailers-accept-cash/2879664002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia's city council voted to require most local businesses to accept cash as payment, pushing back on a growing trend that asks for cards only</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men's Porn Habits Fuel Women's Eating Disorders...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-mens-porn-habits-linked-womens-risk-eating-disorders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women may be more likely to suffer from an eating disorder if their boyfriend or husband watches porn often, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California to sue...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article226333740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media companies to become sports-gambling companies?</title>
      <link>https://www.recode.net/2019/2/15/18226227/sports-gambling-media-att-randall-stephenson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.recode.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sooner than you think. But AT&amp;T, which owns HBO, TNT, and CNN, says they won’t be taking your bets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Roger Stone gagged...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/15/judge-hits-roger-stone-with-gag-order-1172114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Friday ordered Roger Stone, his attorneys and special counsel Robert Mueller to stop talking publicly about their case involving charges the longtime Donald Trump associate lied to Congress and obstructed its Russia investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe writes book about confronting white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/430255-former-virginia-gov-mcauliffe-writes-book-about-confronting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe (D) has written a book examining the Charlottesville "Unite the Right" rally in 2017 that dissolved into riots and resulted in the death of a counter-protester and two state troopers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space junk harpooned like whale in orbit-cleanup test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/066f28f2c2d04fd89ec15f7d43c99d88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A harpoon flung from a satellite has successfully captured a piece of pretend space junk, like a whale. The British-led experiment is part of an effort to clean up debris in orbit, hundreds of miles above Earth. The University of Surrey's Guglielmo Aglietti said Friday that the steel-tipped harpoon scored a bull's-eye last Friday. The harpoon — no bigger than a writing pen — pierced an aluminum panel the size of a table tennis racket attached to the end of a satellite boom. The distance was just 5 feet (1.5 meters), but researchers were delighted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Push Back on Hoax Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-push-back-against-claim-that-attack-on-empire-star-was-a-hoax-11550255540</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police said they have arrested two possible suspects in an attack reported last month by “Empire” television star Jussie Smollett and pushed back against a media report that the attack was staged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College dating classes proliferate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/failing-at-love-maybe-its-time-for-classes-11550253394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In South Korea, college-level dating courses are proliferating. They quickly fill up, as young people accustomed to spending their whole day in school make romance one more thing they need to study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: McCabe Walks Back Ousting Trump Via 25th Amendment Talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/mccabe-spox-walks-back-remarks-on-talks-to-oust-trump-via-25th-amendment-taken-out-of-context/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick settles collusion case against NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/15/colin-kaepernick-reaches-settlement-in-collusion-case-against-nfl-lawyer-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL and lawyers for players Colin Kaepernick and Eric Reid jointly announced Friday that they have settled a complaint of collusion by the players, who claimed football team owners blackballed them because they knelt during the National Anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Dodges 2020 Question...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/hillary-clinton-dodges-2020-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountains Bigger Than Everest May Lie Deep Inside Earth...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/3kgvpw/mountains-bigger-than-everest-may-lie-deep-inside-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists used the second largest earthquake on record to glimpse the terrain 410 miles under our planet's surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F: Just 1-in-4 AMERICANS pass US citizenship test...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/doh-only-1-state-passes-us-citizenship-test-dc-fails-big</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority in every state except Vermont has failed the U.S. Citizenship test, the latest sign that Americans aren’t very good history students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 potential suspects under arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/culture/story/jussie-smollett-case-detectives-probable-men-surveillance-video-61099330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men have been arrested in the atack on "Empire" star Jussie Smollett, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Denies Putting Boyfriend on Payroll...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/did-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-put-her-boyfriend-on-the-public-payroll-rumors-swirl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's the guy on the far right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain to get 3rd govt in 4 years amid fragmenting politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2615b904b41f4325b2390c4ce3e900c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain will elect its third government in less than four years after Prime Minister Pedro Sanchez's fragile socialist government acknowledged Friday its support had evaporated and called an early general election. Sanchez's eight-month-old administration met its end after failing to get parliament's approval for its 2019 budget proposal earlier this week, adding to the political uncertainty that has dogged Spain in recent years. "Between doing nothing and continuing without a budget, or giving the chance for Spaniards to speak, Spain should continue looking ahead," Sanchez said in a televised appearance from the Moncloa Palace, the seat of government, after an urgent Cabinet meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 cities go to war with feds over 5G expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/14/fcc-rules-5g-cellphone-upgrade-spark-antenna-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A turf war between federal regulators and local jurisdictions is brewing over the installation of hundreds of thousands of cellphone towers to upgrade to 5G.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA has 1,000 ISIS detainees -- unsure what to do with them...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/02/14/us-forces-have-1000-isis-detainees-and-dont-know-what-to-do-with-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“[It’s] a huge area of concern for us, especially because they’re being detained by the non-nation state that’s otherwise known as the Syrian Democratic Forces,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Lauds Hannity, Rush...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-fires-back-at-ann-coulter-taunts-i-like-her-but-shes-off-the-reservation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Amendment 'auditor' injured during argument at LA synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article226317205.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, Schumer Threaten...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6709767/Pelosi-Schumer-Border-emergency-unlawful-declaration-crisis-does-not-exist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi and Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer claimed in a joint statement that there is no 'crisis' on the U.S.-Mexico border and threatened to sue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top investigator in Green Beret murder case charged with stolen valor...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2019/02/14/lead-investigator-in-green-beret-murder-case-faces-charges-of-stolen-valor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelation could have major impact on the Army's case against the major facing a murder charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYPASSES CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-set-to-declare-national-emergency-at-border-sign-legislation-to-fund-government-11550241799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump declared a national emergency to bolster his border-wall plans, supplementing the funding contained in a spending bill passed by Congress with billions diverted from elsewhere in government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In ROUNDUP Case, Science Will Go on Trial First...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-roundup-case-the-science-will-go-on-trial-first-11550246311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in a Roundup cancer trial later this month has divided the case so jurors can focus first solely on the science and then, only if they find the plaintiff’s claims valid, on the question of negligence. The results could change the way the courts handle cases that hinge on complex science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg back at Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/430168-ginsburg-back-at-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was back at the court on Friday for the justices’ private conference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT DECLARES BORDER EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-sign-border-bill-declare-national-emergency-wall/story?id=61088949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump announced that he's declaring a national emergency to get funding for his proposed border wall that congressional Democrats refused to give him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LIVE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FFIcGqjkORk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin floored by woman during judo session -- then 'covers up' photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8435517/woman-floors-putin-in-judo-sparring-session-forcing-him-to-get-real-but-you-didnt-see-pics-due-to-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN floored Russian president Vladimir Putin in a judo sparring session, forcing him to “get real”. After the 2016 Olympic bronze medal winner Natalia Kuzyutina, 29, tackled the strongman, he g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY MUTINY: Humiliated after losing ANOTHER Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/feb/14/theresa-may-defeated-on-brexit-again-as-erg-tories-abstain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM defeated by 303 votes to 258, plunging hopes of uniting her party around renegotiated deal into chaos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK facing record MULTI-BILLION dollar fine over privacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-Facebook-negotiating-record-13617614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Trade Commission and Facebook are negotiating over a multibillion-dollar fine that would settle the agency's investigation into the social media giant's privacy practices, according to two people familiar with the probe. The fine would be the largest the agency has ever imposed on a technology company, but the two sides have not yet agreed on an exact amount. Facebook has expressed initial concern with the FTC's demands, one of the people said. If talks break down, the FTC could take the matter to court in what would likely be a bruising legal fight. Facebook confirmed it is in discussions with the agency but declined to comment further. The FTC declined to comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre 'robot marriage-hunting parties' let flirt through machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/bizarre-robot-marriage-hunting-parties-14002469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For singletons in Japan, the worry of speaking to a date is taken out of the equation - thanks to robots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPENDING BINGE WORSE THAN UNDER OBAMA, BUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/bipartisan-spending-binge-now-worse-bush-o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ve gone into deep debt for everything except the core function of the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez, Castro Plan Bill to Block...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/ocasio-cortez-plans-bill-to-block-trump-s-emergency-declaration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez,Â Joaquin CastroÂ PlanÂ Bill to Block Trump's Emergency Declaration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Skyscraper Shown Exploding in New ISIS Threat...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/l-a-skyscraper-shown-exploding-in-new-isis-promise-fulfilled-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though ISIS backers operating under a number of media alliances regularly craft and circulate threats, Los Angeles is rarely featured as a target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu widespread in USA with 15.2 million cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/02/15/flu-season-15-m-cases-widespread-puerto-rico-47-states-cdc-says/2868271002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people have received flu shots this year than last. The overall hospitalization rate so far this season is 20.1 per 100,000 people compared toÂ 30.5 per 100,000 at this period last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eerie 'witch symbols' found scratched into 'cave to hell'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8433075/witch-symbols-scratched-cave-hell-sherwood-forrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of spooky “witch marks” have been discovered in a cave once believed to lead to hell. The eerie etchings were carved into the stone walls of Creswell Crags near Sherwood Forest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fringe YouTuber Shot While Filming Guard Outside Synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/fringe-youtuber-shot-while-filming-guard-outside-la-synagogue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The YouTube personality known as Furry Potato has a long track record of confrontational ‘auditing’ videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as dogs to be killed for dental implant experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/outrage-six-dogs-killed-part-14002623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six Labradors have already had more than a third of their teeth removed as part of the experiment which is taking place in Sweden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant herd refuses to leave spot where calf died in tense stand-off with locals...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/elephant-herd-refuses-leave-spot-14003625 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING: DISTRESSING CONTENT. The animals didn't want to leave the one-year-old who was still alive but unable to get out of the deep pit in India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese protest in Madrid against mass bank account freeze...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/chinese-protest-madrid-against-mass-bank-account-freeze-133110617--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Chinese citizens staged a rare protest Friday at an office of Spain's BBVA bank in Madrid, angrily denouncing that their personal accounts had been frozen without prior warning. Waving Chinese and Spanish flags, the protesters shouted "racist BBVA" and "we want justice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man explains how he killed mountain lion with bare hands...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/travis-kauffman-mountain-lion-attack-horsetooth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who fought back when a mountain lion was attacking him while he was running on a trail at Horsetooth Mountain says he wasn't sure at first whether he would win that battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE director resigns over photos evoking slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/feb/15/vogue-brazil-director-resigns-over-birthday-photos-evoking-slavery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images show Donata Meirelles, who is white, sitting on a throne-like seat flanked by four black women dressed in white</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam mayor slams tourists who 'humiliate' sex workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/451515-sex-workers-not-tourist-attractions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amsterdam's mayor has stepped up her campaign to change the city's seedy image, scolding visitors who make the pilgrimage to its red-light district for treating sex workers like a tourist attraction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Weld launches GOP presidential exploratory committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/02/15/bill-weld-launches-gop-presidential-exploratory-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. William F. Weld is launching a presidential exploratory committee to challenge President Trump in the Republican primaries, saying the country is “in grave peril&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Taylor Swift showed scary future of facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/feb/15/how-taylor-swift-showed-us-the-scary-future-of-facial-recognition </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance at concerts is just the beginning, as fears grow around an unregulated, billion-dollar industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGAL WAR LOOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/14/trump-national-emergency-legal-challenges-1170936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers, activists and state officials are planning to challenge what they say is a presidential end-run around the Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widow, 81, sole resident of remote island disputed by SKorea, Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/14/asia/south-korea-japan-disputed-islands-one-resident-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1991, Kim Sin-yeol and her husband made the unusual decision to move to a lonely set of islands at the heart of a long-standing territorial dispute between Japan and South Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brewing STARBUCKS Protest Could Hit Coffee Giant in Blue America...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/brewing-starbucks-protest-could-hit-coffee-giant-in-blue-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brewing Starbucks Protest Could Hit Coffee Giant in Blue America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Furor over Omar puts spotlight on AIPAC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/430054-furor-over-omar-puts-spotlight-on-aipac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week’s controversial tweets by Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.), one of the first two Muslim women to serve in Congress, has put the spotlight on the American Israel Public Affairs Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns of 'backsliding' in measles fight as cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/warns-backsliding-measles-fight-cases-soar-161416903.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization warned Thursday that efforts to halt the spread of measles were "backsliding", with case numbers worldwide surging around 50 percent last year. The UN health agency pointed to preliminary data showing that the disturbing trend of resurgent measles cases was happening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar organizers struggle to keep show relevant...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/oscar-organizers-struggle-keep-show-relevant-015231766.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar organizers are struggling to keep Hollywood's biggest night relevant while dealing with a string of messy controversies. With less than two weeks to go before the February 24 gala, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences has been weathering the latest debacle over four awards to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man explains how he killed mountain lion with bare hands...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/14/travis-kauffman-explains-how-he-killed-a-mountain-lion-with-his-bare-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado man who survived a mountain lion attack while out for a run in the woods recalled thinking “this would be a crappy way to die” during his fight for survival with the animal. Travis Kau…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Burning Man Boots Camp Catering to Wealthy; Change Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/15/business/burning-man-tickets.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti President Won't Step Down as Violent Protests Grip Capital...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5530334/haiti-jovenal-moise-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics say they're fed up with soaring inflation and corruption</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGNATIUS: NO RED LINES, ENTERING NEW PHASE OF INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/were-entering-a-new-phase-of-the-trump-russia-investigation/2019/02/14/10f13b70-30a5-11e9-8ad3-9a5b113ecd3c_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite constant insistence his Moscow Tower project was above board, the money trail says differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris fundraising 'falling short'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/just-17-days-in-kamala-harris-fundraising-falling-short</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That was fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networks: 2,202 Minutes on Russia Scandal, Zero for 'No Collusion' Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2019/02/14/networks-2202-minutes-russia-scandal-zero-no-collusion-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been two days since NBC’s exclusive reporting that the Senate Intelligence Committee has found no material evidence of collusion between the Trump campaign and Russia, and as of yet none of the three major broadcast networks (ABC, CBS, and NBC) have given it even a single second of airtime in their evening newscasts. Considering these networks have given the Russia probe a massive 2,202 minutes of airtime, their silence on this major development is deafening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With smart sneakers, privacy risks take great leap...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/with-smart-sneakers-the-potential-for-privacy-risks-take-a-great-leap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Privacy experts are waiting for the other shoe to drop on connected kicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Catch and Release' expansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/14/gop-dem-deal-less-detention-of-illegal-aliens-expanded-catch-and-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GOP-Democrat spending bill offered to Trump provides less detention space for illegal aliens while expanding the Catch and Release program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paid Family Leave Next Bipartisan Win for White House?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/13/gop-senators-white-house-officials-huddle-paid-family-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several GOP senators and White House officials met on Capitol Hill on Wednesday to develop a pathway forward on a paid family leave plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Warns of Impending 'High-Tech Cold War'..</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/02/13/chinese-state-media-warns-impending-high-tech-cold-war-fueled-a-i-competition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. development of AI could trigger a “new high-technology Cold War” between the United States and China, state media said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminist Attacks Pro-Trans TWITTER as a 'Boys Club'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/gender-critical-feminist-blames-censorship-on-twitters-sexist-boys-club/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men threatened her, and a biological man got her banned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'fountain of youth' pill? Sure, if you're a mouse...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/a-fountain-of-youth-pill-sure-if-youre-a-mouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race for the cure to aging sparks hope and hype among top scientists — plus billions of dollars in investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro reveals secret meetings with US envoy...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/ee79b8c8f3a8497eab4a54741612dec8/ap-interview-maduro-reveals-secret-meetings-us-envoy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — President Nicolas Maduro said in an AP interview Thursday that his foreign minister recently held secret talks in New York with the U.S. special envoy to Venezuela, even as the Trump administration was publicly backing an effort to unseat the Venezuelan president.While harshly criticizing Donald Trump's confrontational stance toward his socialist government, Maduro said he holds out hope of meeting the U.S. president soon to resolve a crisis over America's recognition of opponent Juan Guaido as Venezuela's rightful leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Headquarters Lockdown Scare; Suspect 'With Gun'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/netflix-on-active-shooter-lockdown-1202558079/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2ND UPDATE: The LAPD has taken a suspect into custody, and the active-shooter lockdown at Netflix’s LA HQ has been lifted. The suspect did not have a gun and never entered the Sunset Boulevar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT's Plan to Steer Voters with 'NewsGuard' Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/12/dhillon-microsoft-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has developed a browser that directs readers not to look at conservative websites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HATE OR HOAX</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/jussie-smollett-attack-empire-house-raid-persons-of-interest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police raided the home of two "persons of interest" in the Jussie Smollett case Wednesday night, a relative of those men says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$8B FOR WALLS...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/landmines-border-bill-trump-hell-sign/story?id=61047358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell announced Thursday that President Donald Trump would sign the border bill but also declare a national emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC: 'EMPIRE' ACTOR STAGED ATTACK?</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/sources-smollett-staged-attack-with-help-of-others-allegedly-being-written-off-empire/5138497/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple sources have told ABC7 Eyewitness News that police are investigating whether Smollett and the two men staged the attack allegedly because Smollett was being written off of "Empire."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake doctor promised to cure cancer by injecting own blood...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox13news.com/news/local-news/florida-man-accused-of-being-fake-doctor-claiming-to-cure-diabetes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hernando County man was arrested after deputies say he posed as a doctor and claimed he could cure diabetes.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPROAR FROM ALL SIDES... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/34dde5f8a2404e039d6fe819136e92f5/border-security-brawl-seems-near-serene-resolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Congress lopsidedly approved a border security compromise Thursday that would avert a second painful government shutdown, but a new confrontation was ignited — this time over President Donald Trump's plan to bypass lawmakers and declare a national emergency to siphon billions from other federal coffers for his wall on the Mexican boundary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Owners Approach NBA Commissioner to Run League...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/25994987/adam-silver-given-thought-inquiries-nfl-owners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA commissioner Adam Silver says he hasn't "given any thought" to inquiries by NFL owners about his willingness to switch leagues and become commissioner of the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungry bear goes for ride after getting stuck on trash truck...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/hungry-bear-goes-for-ride-after-getting-stuck-on-trash-truck/18192328/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers were startled to see a hungry bear that got stuck in the back of garbage truck and took a ride across a stretch of eastern North Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: 'BOBO' Plan To Buy AMI to Find Leak Source...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/02/suspected-bezos-leaker-supplies-his-own-theory-about-the-affair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks ago, Sanchez was a minor player with a semi-famous sister. Now he’s at the heart of a complexifier-ridden scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bars lady from getting pregnant by US 'sperminator'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/court-bars-woman-from-receiving-sperm-of-us-serial-donor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York math professor Ari Nagel, dubbed 'Sperminator,' believed to have fathered at least 35 children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex-bots could crush human limbs 'and spy on you for government'... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8420080/sex-robots-spying-government-crush-limbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ROBOTS are here. Are the “sexbots” close behind? From the Drudge Report to The New York Times, sex robots are rapidly becoming a part of the global conversation about the future of sex and rela…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Drinking diet beverages 'increases risk of dying young'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8425260/diet-coke-stroke-heart-attack-dying-young/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRINKING Diet Coke everyday increases your risk of dying young, experts have warned. Two or more artificially-sweetened drinks a day ups the risk of stroke by a quarter and heart disease by a third…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines drink cobra blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8425046/us-marines-drink-cobra-blood-war-games-thailand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE stomach-churning pictures show US Marines drinking cobra blood as they take part in military exercises in Thailand. US Marines were given the cobra blood earlier today as part of their jungle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. text generator may be too dangerous to release, say creators...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/feb/14/elon-musk-backed-ai-writes-convincing-news-fiction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Elon Musk-backed nonprofit company OpenAI declines to release research publicly for fear of misuse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Every Day Is New Low in White House'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/02/andrew-mccabe-fbi-book-excerpt-the-threat/582748/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president steps over bright ethical and moral lines wherever he encounters them. Everyone in America saw it when he fired my boss. But I saw it firsthand time and time again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mother' no longer gender-specific term, UK govt lawyers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/02/14/mother-no-longer-gender-specific-term-government-lawyers-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mother is no longer a gender-specific term that applies only to women, lawyers on behalf of the Government have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Republicans Worried, Fearful Over Political Landscape...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/national-politics/article226226280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAPOLITANO: Manafort For Pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/napolitano-floats-it-manafort-is-facing-so-much-jail-time-he-might-be-candidate-for-a-pardon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Headquarters Lockdown Scare; Suspect 'With Gun'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/netflix-headquarters-lockdown-1186999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of early evening, the lockdown was lifted and employees were advised of no immediate danger or threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Leaks Video of Arab Leaders Blasting 'Toxic' Iran in Discreet Talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-netanyahu-leaks-video-of-arab-leaders-endorsing-his-message-against-iran-1.6937912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US general won't say 'winning' anti-ISIS fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190214-top-general-wont-say-winning-anti-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top general won't say 'winning' in anti-IS fight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexandria Slays 'Alexa': Beat Richest Man in World!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ocasio-cortez-celebrates-amazon-canceling-new-york-headquarters-after-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is taking a victory lap after delivering the goods in her fight against Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA Vows To Regulate Cancer-Causing 'Forever Chemicals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/02/14/forever-chemicals-environmental-protection-agency/39057585/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Environmental Protection Agency officials said they will create new standards for PFAS contaminants in drinking water but didn't share a target level</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6703509/Border-security-brawl-near-serene-resolution.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is expected to reluctantly sign a government funding bill, though the White House has yet to give a final signal on the package and its $1.4 billion in border fencing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SIGN BUDGET...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/5-insane-provisions-amnesty-omnibus-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utterly indefensible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Tracking Location of Former Employees?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/14/facebooks-security-team-tracks-posts-location-for-bolo-threat-list.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook security monitors users who have made aggressive comments, as well as former employees, through a "be on lookout" or "BOLO" list. It can use its apps and web sites to track the location of these people as it deems necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit means Chicago Obama library plan no sure thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/obamacenter/ct-met-obama-presidential-library-chicago-lawsuit-20190214-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hearing in Chicago today on a legal challenge to the Obama Presidential Center plans could ultimately determine the fate of the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority of California Residents Want to Leave!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/14/majority-of-california-residents-want-to-leave-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll reveals that 53% of California residents are considering leaving the Golden State because of the high cost of living.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spending Bill: 40X as Much on Foreign Countries as Border Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/02/14/deal-foreign-aid-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republican-Democrat spending bill being offered to President Trump spends nearly 40 times as much on foreign aid as it does on a wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considers Removing Anti-Vaccine Posts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-14/facebook-says-it-may-remove-anti-vaccine-recommendations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student charged with wiretapping after livestreaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/politics/bs-md-wiretapping-jake-burdett-20190214-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salisbury University student Jake Burdett is charged with illegal wiretapping after he allegedly streamed a meeting with a congressional staffer for Maryland Congressman Andy Harris to Facebook Live without permission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 kids hospitalized after eating Valentine's candy at school...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/breaking-candy-sends-middle-school-students-hospitals/97v5TDErsebYzDEnVG2zTP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen students were sent to hospitals on Valentine’s Day after ingesting snacks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths from 'Mexican oxy' pills hit Arizona hard...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/state/fentanyl-deaths-from-mexican-oxy-pills-hit-arizona-hard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Francisco Chavez swallowed at least one of the sky blue pills at a Halloween party before falling asleep forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia May Fine Citizens For Being Overweight...</title>
      <link>https://tsarizm.com/news/eastern-europe/2019/02/14/russia-may-fine-citizens-for-being-overweight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tsarizm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia May Fine Citizens For Being Overweight. 'Large Waistlines' Could Be Targeted For Financial Punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON 'RING' Declares War On Crime While Getting Closer to Police...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/02/14/amazon-ring-police-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video and internal emails show how Amazon's Ring has blurred line between private innovation and public law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT RIPS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/429997-trump-blasts-former-fbi-official-mccabe-after-explosive-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday lashed out at Andrew McCabe after the former FBI deputy director revealed he opened a probe into whether Trump obstructed justice when the president fired James Comey as FBI chief in 2017 amid the Russia inv</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein offer to wear wire was serious...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/429960-mccabe-said-justice-dept-discussed-25th-amendment-confirms-rosenstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former acting FBI Director Andrew McCabe in a new interview reveals fresh details of the investigations into President Trump, telling CBS that there were conversations about the possibility of removing Trump under the 25th Ame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Great Whites hunted Megalodon to extinction?</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1551034/great-white-sharks-might-have-driven-megalodons-to-extinction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say it was great whites—not cosmic radiation from an ancient supernova—that killed off the world's biggest shark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS: THE PRESIDENTIAL PHYSICAL...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/14/trump-is-in-very-good-health-but-now-obese-by-bmi-standards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s physician said Thursday the recent physical he underwent showed that he was “in very good health” — but also revealed that he had gained weight and was now considered obese under …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Flames Shoot Out Overhead Bins Vape Pen Overheats...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/02/13/vape-pen-battery-delays-laguardia-houston-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flight from LaGuardia to Houston was delayed Wednesday afternoon after flames shot out of the overhead storage bin and sent smoke billowing through the cabin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHILIP MORRIS eyes tech gadgets for 'smoke-free' market...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/philip-morris-eyes-tech-gadgets-smoke-free-market-173105773.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gadgets that monitor health, from wearable step-counters to apps tracking sleep and diet, have exploded in popularity in recent years, and now even the tobacco industry is trying to jump into the fray. While health promotion and Big Tobacco appears incongruous, Philip Morris International (PMI) says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA heading back to Moon soon. This time to stay...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nasa-heading-back-moon-soon-time-stay-230656886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is accelerating plans to return Americans to the Moon, and this time, the US space agency says it will be there to stay. Jim Bridenstine, NASA's administrator, told reporters Thursday that the agency plans to speed up plans backed by President Donald Trump to return to the moon, using private</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCABE: DOJ DISCUSSED REMOVING TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mccabe-25th-amendment-discussions-doj-remove-trump-office-140646145.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe says that after President Trump fired his boss, FBI Director James Comey, there were discussions within the Department of Justice about invoking the 25th Amendment to remove Trump from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto Races to  Wisconsin to Meet Voters...</title>
      <link>https://madison.com/wsj/news/local/govt-and-politics/potential-presidential-candidate-beto-o-rourke-coming-to-uw-madison/article_dbc7695e-2979-55cd-9f43-3b236987162f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;madison.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UW-Madison spokesman said the event is not open to the press, public or anyone not affiliated with the university.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police hunt thieves who stole 30,000 liters of iceberg water...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4960386/thieves-in-newfoundland-make-off-with-30k-litres-of-iceberg-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say the water - enough to fill a tractor trailer tanker - had not yet been bottled, and was worth between $9,000 and $12,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail sales drop the most in decade...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/retail-sales-declined-in-december-153022812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retail sector took a blow in the final month of 2018, adding to a list of consumer economic casualties amid year-end market turmoil and a protracted government shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand For Gun Permits Surging in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/02/13/first-time-gun-buyer-demand-surge-foid-card-cook-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The demand for gun permits is surging in Chicago, with thousands more Cook County residents applying for permits this past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President to warn of 'dangers of socialism' in speech...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4c241827c6be440cb52781d0b5bd744b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's chief prosecutor said Thursday he has launched an investigation into opposition leader Juan Guaido's appointment of a transitional board of directors for the state oil company. Attorney General Tarek William Saab said the appointments by Guaido and his National Assembly are part of an illegal power grab backed by foreign governments. He also said that ambassadors of Guaido's self-declared interim government are being investigated as part of the probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bathroom Warning Mistaken For Bomb Threat: 'Fixin' To Blow It Up'...</title>
      <link>http://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/02/14/im-fixin-to-blow-it-up-bathroom-warning-mistaken-for-bomb-threat-at-home-depot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report of a bomb threat at a Home Depot store in Kansas turned out to be a big misunderstanding.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
