<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump considering travel restrictions at southern border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/29/trump-considering-travel-restrictions-at-us-southern-border-over-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT'S ALREADY OUT OF THE BAG'</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-29/coronavirus-california-spread-health-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A person who was not among the previously reported coronavirus cases in the U.S. has died of COVID-19, say Washington health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Prototype Spacecraft Blows Up During Testing In Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.geekwire.com/2020/spacexs-starship-sn1-prototype-blows-pressure-test-texas-pad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geekwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 100-foot-tall prototype for SpaceX’s Starship super-rocket was destroyed tonight during a cryogenic pressure test on its pad at the company’s South Texas facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?469892-1/president-trump-holds-news-conference-coronavirus&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump holds a news conference to provide an update on the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local spread of coronavirus marks turning point in USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200229163324-v735v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/USA (PIX, GRAPHICS):Local spread of coronavirus marks turning point in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2020/2/29/21157885/south-carolina-primary-live-results-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state is critical for former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious glowing object suddenly appears in Earth's orbit leaving scientists baffled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/11069093/mysterious-glowing-object-appears-in-earths-orbit-scientists-baffled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERIOUS glowing object which suddenly appeared in the Earth’s orbit has left scientists baffled. Images of the puzzling object have been released after some speculated it appeared to be …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty stadiums and no more selfie lines? Coronavirus becomes 2020 X-factor...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/29/coronavirus-threatens-to-disrupt-2020-campaign-118238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the virus does spread, the mechanical implications for campaigns could be profound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic scenes on beach as walkers stumble across pig heads on spikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dublinlive.ie/news/dublin-news/satanic-like-scenes-portmarnock-beach-17833423</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dublinlive.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One walker even rang gardai out of concern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/south-carolina-primary-results-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolinians head to the polls today to vote in the Democratic primary. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna left in tears, struggling to walk after fall during Paris concert...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/29/madonna-left-in-tears-struggling-to-walk-after-fall-during-paris-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna took a hard fall during her Thursday night Madame X show in Paris, leaving the singer in tears as she struggled to walk off stage after the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Republican mega-donor buys stake in TWITTER and seeks to oust Dorsey...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/feb/29/paul-singer-elliott-management-twitter-jack-dorsey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Paul Singer’s Elliott Management has taken a ‘sizable state’ and intends to ‘push for changes’, reports Bloomberg News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Marine becomes first woman to lead Howitzer team...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/california-marine-becomes-first-woman-to-lead-howitzer-team/article_300e2327-0bb6-56ef-ae4a-09f47e943fc1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP PENDLETON, Calif. — A Marine stationed at Camp Pendleton became the first woman to graduate from the Corps’ Howitzer Section Chief Course this month, taking on a combat artillery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney receives standing ovation in Denver for impeachment vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2020/02/28/mitt-romney-impeachment-denver-jason-crow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOP senator, weeks after historic vote, talks democracy at DU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, Gantz neck and neck as campaign reaches climax...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-gantz-neck-neck-campaign-reaches-climax-154111486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and rival Benny Gantz were wrapping up another bitter election campaign on Saturday as voters prepared to cast their ballots for the third time in 12 months. Netanyahu, Israel's longest-serving leader, has been charged on several counts of corruption but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders look-alike enjoying the ride...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-look-alike-enjoying-ride-040809634.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up until a few years ago, Jeff Jones was going about his life, minding his own business and enjoying his passion for music. Then Bernie Sanders burst onto the national political stage, prompting many to do double takes on seeing Jones, who bears a striking resemblance to the Democratic presidential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery disease hits Africa as dying villagers 'bleed from eyes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/disease-x-feared-hit-ethiopia-21601531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: While the rest of the world is occupied with coronavirus, a gruesome mystery sickness is killing Ethiopians of all ages as hospital treatment appears ineffective</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with 'coding flaws' prone to 'sexually assaulting humans'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-coding-flaws-prone-21603652</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Dr David Levy told Daily Star Online it will be important to teach the robots of the future about consent, because they will have their own sexual desires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Empty Shelves In TARGET, WALMART Early As April'...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/02/28/chinese-products-shortage-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The label "Made in China" is more common on store shelves than "Made in America."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected patient isolated in NJ hospital...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/29/suspected-coronavirus-patient-isolated-in-new-jersey-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patient with a suspected case of the coronavirus is being treated at Bayshore Medical Center in Holmdel, NJ. The person is being held in isolation while the hospital awaits the results of a test …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS could turn this QB into Brady 2.0...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/29/patriots-could-turn-jacob-eason-into-tom-brady-2-0/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS — He lost to Fromm, but might be asked to replace Tom. This is the strange journey of Jacob Eason, who transferred from Georgia to Washington after losing his starting job to Bulldogs …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200229124626-vkh6s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/GREECE (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Greece pushes back migrants on Turkish border 'onslaught'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2020/02/mike-bloomberg-2020-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ego and the altruism of the would-be savior of the Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Eclipsed by Calabasas as Home for Rich and Famous...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/beverly-hills-eclipsed-calabasas-home-151436045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- After striking oil a half century ago, the fictional Clampett clan left their shack in the Ozarks and moved to Beverly Hills.“The Beverly Hillbillies” ran for nine years on CBS and cemented the California city as the go-to-place for the wealthy. These days, the Clampetts might pick a different</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SICK POPE CANCELS EVENTS THIRD DAY IN ROW...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49755e6f70e35fe86493d92cae349949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis canceled official engagements for the third day in a row Saturday as he battled an apparent cold. The 83-year-old pope, who lost part of a lung to a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign plans 2,400 events in 30 states ahead of Super Tuesday...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bloomberg-campaign-plans-2400-events-30-states-ahead/story?id=69300673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Mike Bloomberg's campaign on Saturday will begin a massive voter outreach push.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I have the coronavirus. So far, it isn't that bad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/I-have-the-coronavirus-So-far-it-isn-t-that-bad-15093664.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have the coronavirus. And it hasn't been that bad.  I am in my late 60s, and the sickest I've ever been was when I had bronchitis several years ago. That laid me out on my back for a few days. This has been much easier: no chills, no body aches. I breathe easily, and I don't have a stuffy nose. My chest feels tight, and I have coughing spells. If I were at home with similar symptoms, I probably would have gone to work as usual.  I caught the virus on the Diamond Princess, the cruise ship that was quarantined outside Yokohama for 14 days, at the end of a 16-day cruise I took with my wife, Jeri. When I left the ship a couple of weeks ago, I felt fine. We checked our temperatures throughout our quarantine. Jeri and I got a swab test for the virus. Our temperatures were normal; they'd get the swab results back in 48 hours. Our test results had not arrived before we boarded buses for the airport, where two U.S. government planes waited for us.  As we took off from Tokyo, I had a bit of a cough, but I chalked it up to the dry air in the cabin. I felt pretty tired - but who wouldn't, in our situation? I dozed off.  When I woke up, I had a fever. I made my way to the back of the cargo plane, where the Air Force had set up a quarantine area cordoned off with sheets of plastic. They took my temperature. It was over 103 degrees. So I took a seat in the quarantine area and fell back asleep until we touched down in California, at Travis Air Force Base.  Officials from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention came onto the plane and said that three of us who had been cordoned off would fly to Omaha (with our spouses, if they wanted to come along). The CDC had a quarantine location at the University of Nebraska's hospital. We arrived on Feb. 17, greeted by a fleet of ambulances and police cars. Officials put me on a stretcher...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independents outnumber registered Republicans for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/For-the-first-time-there-are-fewer-registered-15093062.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in history, there are more registered independents in the United States than there are registered Republicans.  It may not be for the reason you think, though.  New data from Ballot Access News, which tracks registrations in the 31 states that require voters to register by party, show that independents now account for 29.09 percent of voters in them, compared to 28.87 percent for Republicans. As recently as 2004, Republicans outpaced independents by nearly 10 percentage points.  There are still way more registered Democrats; 39.66 percent are registered with that party.  This marks the first time since party registration began in the early 1900s that the number of registered independents in the United States has surpassed either major political party, according to Ballot Access News.  But before anybody chalks this up as having to do with the current occupant of the White House, it's worth parsing the trends.  While independents have surpassed Republicans, there actually hasn't been a huge drop in GOP party registration since Donald Trump took office. Since October 2016, GOP registration has dropped by half a percentage point. Democrats have actually declined by nearly a full point over the same span. Independents have benefited from both drops.  And they have been doing so for years. Democrats are more than three points off their peak this century, which was in 2008 when Barack Obama was about to become president. At the time, 43.62 percent of voters were registered Democrats.  Republicans are also more than three points off where they were four years earlier, in 2004, when 32.79 percent of voters were Republicans and George W. Bush won reelection.  Since 2008, the trendline for each party has been relatively steady. But while Democratic registrations fell...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing under scrutiny after delays and questions over effectiveness...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/coronavirus-testing-is-under-scrutiny-after-delays-and-questions-over-its-effectiveness/ar-BB10wCe3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein conviction could pave way for more sex assault prosecutions...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-28/harvey-weinstein-conviction-could-pave-the-way-for-more-sexual-assault-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal experts say the verdict expands the possibilities for which sex crimes can be successfully tried in a court of law, and it could embolden prosecutors to take on complex rape cases that they would have previously been reluctant to file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romo agrees to $17M per year to stay at CBS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/28/nfl-analyst-tony-romo-agrees-to-17m-per-year-to-stay-at-cbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tony Romo has agreed to the largest sports analyst contract in TV history, a deal to remain at CBS which will prevent him from reaching the free-agent market, where ESPN was poised to aggressively …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos of deserted, nearly empty airports around world...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/photos-deserted-nearly-empty-airports-185813177.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Air Transport Association has predicted a $29.3 billion loss in passenger revenue this year because of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to Intensify Border Checks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-intensify-border-checks-effort-201816331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Germany announced a slew of measures aimed at preventing the spread of the coronavirus by people coming into the country from affected areas.A German government task force dealing with the crisis announced late on Friday plans to intensify health checks for cross-border travel into the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can the Fed inoculate economy?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fed-inoculate-us-economy-against-virus-impact-210605544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Federal Reserve stands ready to take action to counter the risks posed by the novel coronavirus crisis, the central bank's chairman Jerome Powell said Friday, while insisting that the US economy remains in a good position. The rare unscheduled formal statement, released as concerns mount</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carnivals, cars, concerts: Swiss crack down...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/carnivals-cars-concerts-swiss-crack-down-virus-003140634.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland on Friday cancelled football matches, carnival celebrations, concerts and the Geneva International Motor Show in a drastic bid to stem the country's new coronavirus outbreak in its early stages. The government announced it was suspending all public and private events with more than 1,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  New Coalition Put to Test in S Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-coalition-put-test-164038803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders is investing heavily in South Carolina, visiting often and building a solid organization. But the question remains whether his newfound front-runner status and momentum will be enough to attract the coalition of minority voters he needs to do well there.Saturday’s Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How long can it survive on surfaces?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200228215640-n07fz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/SURFACES (EXPLAINER):EXPLAINER-How long can coronavirus survive on surfaces?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoarding in the USA?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200228205631-ls907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/USA-HOARDING (PIX, GRAPHICS):Hoarding in the USA? Coronavirus sparks consumer concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the End Game Will Look Like...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coronavirus-end-game-look-000023845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Pandemics come and pandemics go.In the grip of a new infection spreading around a planet with no natural immunity, it can feel like the sky is falling. Over the coming months, it’s likely that a significant share of the world’s population will experience some of the dread of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuits Won't Be Far Behind...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/coronavirus-come-u-lawsuits-won-163016610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- The coronavirus called Covid-19 has spread beyond its origin in Wuhan, China, and has arrived on U.S. shores. I’m a law professor, not an epidemiologist, so my thoughts immediately turned to how the law would shape America’s collective response to a broader pandemic — and what</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie or brokered: Democratic race at critical crossroads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4bb536409519524f87a573de020a26c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — The Democrats' 2020 primary season enters a critical four-day stretch that will help determine whether the party rallies behind Bernie Sanders or embraces a longer and uglier...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA reports 1st drug shortage...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/fda-reports-1st-drug-shortage-due-coronavirus-outbreak/story?id=69276490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA announced it's been alerted to the first manufacturing shortage of an unnamed drug, due to a viral outbreak that began in China and has now reached American soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLANSKI WINS BEST DIRECTOR AT FRENCH OSCARS, PROMPTING WALKOUTS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/cesar-awards-winners-2020-polanski-protests-1203519255/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a contentious edition of France’s Cesar awards wrapped, Roman Polanski won best director prompting numerous walkouts such as nominee Adele Haenel, star of “Portrait of a Lady on Fire…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Richest Lose $444 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-richest-lose-444-billion-220432889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Last week was an expensive one for most investors, even for billionaires.The combined fortunes of the world’s 500 richest people fell by $444 billion as the coronavirus continued to spread -- and spread fear -- rattling equity markets worldwide. The Dow Jones Industrial Average tumbled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independents outnumber registered Republicans for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2020/02/28/first-time-ever-there-are-fewer-registered-republicans-than-independents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But it's not because of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to nominate Rep. Ratcliffe again as intel chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/28/trump-to-nominate-rep-john-ratcliffe-again-as-intel-chief-118239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Republican was previously announced in July as Trump's next intel chief, only to be withdrawn later amid concerns over alleged embellishments on his resume.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to invoke special powers to boost production of protective gear...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200228214309-55fn9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/USA (UPDATE 4, PIX, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 4-U.S. to invoke special powers to boost production of protective gear for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE employee tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2020/02/28/google-employee-tests-positive-coronavirus/4904871002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Google employee who tested positive for coronavirus was in the company's Zurich office "for a limited time," Google said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -3583 FOR WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/02/28/810295350/financial-markets-shudder-around-the-world-as-coronavirus-tightens-its-grip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. stock market ended its worst week since the financial crisis with the Dow Jones Industrial Average falling 12.4%. Fed Chairman Jerome Powell promises to support the economy as necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spooky 'blood snow' invades Antarctic island...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/weird-science/spooky-blood-snow-invades-antarctic-island-n1145256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blood-red algae behind the phenomenon could kick off a runaway feedback loop of warming, researchers warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUBINI forecasts 40% drop...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/899110/stock-markets-are-headed-40-percent-plunge-says-economist-who-predicted-financial-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of a very rough week for U.S. markets brought a worrying prediction. While one expert warned fallout from the global coronavirus outbreak could be 'worse than the financial crisis' of 2008, the economist who correctly predicted that very crisis is now saying the idea of a major global recession 'doesn't sound too farfetched.' Nouriel Roubini, a New York University business professor and market prognosticator who foretold the housing bubble burst, told Yahoo Finance on Friday to expect 'severe' consequences as the coronavirus continues to rattle markets. How severe? He told Der Spiegel it could be worse than investors even believe at this point, predicting 'global equities to tank by 30 to 40 percent this year.' He said people 'prefer to believe in miracles,' (not necessarily referencing President Trump's prediction the coronavirus will 'disappear ... like a miracle,') and don't realize the 'simple math' tells us that realistically, a squeezed Chinese economy will mean downturns around the globe. 'This crisis will spill over and result in a disaster,' said Roubini. Roubini, who is often nicknamed Dr. Doom for his frequent pessimistic predictions, also saw doom and gloom for Trump's future as president as a result of any economic strife. Asked by Der Spiegel, Roubini said Trump would likely try to benefit politically from the outbreak, but 'will lose the election, that's for sure.' Pointing to past incumbent presidents getting ousted amid geopolitical tensions that damaged the economy, he said 'The Democratic field is poor, but Trump is dead. Quote me on that!' Though the week just saw a 3,500-point drop for the Dow Jones Industrial Average, Roubini warned: 'It is far from being over.' Read more at Der Spiegel. Summer Meza</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man cleared after quarantine can't stop coughing in TV interview...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/28/man-cleared-after-coronavirus-quarantine-cant-stop-coughing-in-tv-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania man who was quarantined in San Diego with his 3-year-old daughter after attending a memorial service in Wuhan, China, where his father-in-law died of the coronavirus, began to cough …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI surveillance tools at risk amid bipartisan opposition...</title>
      <link>http://www.tribtown.com/2020/02/28/us-congress-surveillance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tribtown.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance authorities used by the FBI to fight terrorism could expire next month as both Democrats and Republicans concerned about overreach have complicated their renewal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want Longer, Healthier Life? Eat Less, Study Suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/want-a-longer-healthier-life-eat-less-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds eating less may slow cellular aging, reduce inflammation, lower your risk of age-related diseases, and promote a longer life overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police issuing fake warnings of tainted meth... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-are-issuing-fake-warnings-of-meth-tainted-with-coronavirus-public-health-experts-say-please-stop-now/ar-BB10vXoX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel on track for 4th election?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-Elections/Is-Israel-on-track-to-the-fourth-election-619138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Context: The final lap... until the next one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Struck With Semen-Filled Syringe At Grocery Store...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/02/28/thomas-byron-stemen-syringe-attack-churchton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anne Arundel County Police said semen was found inside syringes tested after a man was arrested for allegedly poking a woman with a syringe in Churchton grocery store.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
