<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Model Predicts 100,000 More  Deaths in USA BEFORE Winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-deaths-100k-more-united-states-prediction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is in the grip of a fourth wave of infection this summer, powered by the highly contagious Delta variant, which has sent cases, hospitalizations and deaths soaring again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands in Germany protest restrictions on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/569843-thousands-of-german-protesters-gather-in-opposition-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of protesters gathered in Berlin on Saturday to demonstrate against government leaders considering imposing additional coronavirus restrictions on unvaccinated individuals in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow docket' scrutiny at high court...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/analysis-bidens-supreme-court-losses-153205800.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's administration was dealt a double blow by the conservative-majority Supreme Court this week, raising new questions about how the justices handle cases brought via an emergency process known as the "shadow docket." The court in recent years has increasingly made substantive decisions on major issues via the shadow docket https://www.reuters.com/article/legal-us-usa-court-shadow-video/the-shadow-docket-how-the-u-s-supreme-court-quietly-dispatches-key-rulings-idUSKBN2BF16Q, deciding quickly and sometimes late at night in a process that critics from across the ideological spectrum say lacks transparency. The administration of Biden's Republican predecessor, President Donald Trump, did very well with the process, winning a wide majority of the cases it brought via emergency applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter punched in face while covering anti-mask event...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-6674fab5712fc37808a9fb08386fd8d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAVERSE CITY, Mich. (AP) — A newspaper reporter said he was punched in the face while covering an anti-mask event near Traverse City. The Grand Traverse County sheriff's office is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy family deeply divided over parole for RFK assassin Sirhan Sirhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-rfk-kids-rip-sirhan-sirhan-parole-20210828-dlbbhuey45fdhcqgwwhl6gmmny-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Kennedy's kids are divided on the decision to grant parole to his killer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evacuations From Kabul Wind Down as USA Prepares to Pull Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/08/28/world/asia/afghanistan-evacuations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of thousands of Afghans are still thought to be seeking to flee the country, but President Biden and other global leaders have acknowledged that many will not get out before the deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Soldier's Afghan Pet Rescue Sparks Row Over Defense Role...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/british-soldier-s-afghan-pet-rescue-sparks-row-over-defense-role</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Soldier’s Afghan Pet Rescue Sparks Row Over Defense Role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands march on Washington in voting rights push...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569837-thousands-to-march-on-washington-in-voting-rights-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands are marching in Washington, D.C. and across the country on Saturday in a push to pass federal voting rights legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOUSANDS FLEE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210828160737-fu09y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. Gulf Coast residents flee 'extremely dangerous' Hurricane Ida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says drone strike killed two 'high profile' ISIS targets...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pentagon-two-isis-k-targets-strike-killed-afghanistan-c27cb5cc-d6b9-42cd-9d95-e54da5b473c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can confirm, two high profile targets were killed and one was wounded."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating apps turning to video and audio to link people up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/28/the-future-of-dating-apps-match-bumble-is-much-more-social.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has caused a level of disruption that's allowed companies to consider what a more-integrated future would look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://cdn.star.nesdis.noaa.gov/GOES16/ABI/SECTOR/gm/13/20212400731-20212401201-GOES16-ABI-GM-13-1000x1000.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cdn.star.nesdis.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming embraces Jeffree Star despite homophobia, past...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-philanthropy-74a8d2c121e2a95f1653de597e24087b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CASPER, Wyo. (AP) — Jeffree Star is, inarguably, the biggest celebrity in Casper. The Youtuber-slash-makeup mogul first landed here in December, saying publicly he wanted to work on his autobiography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FALLEN HEROES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9935543/Father-fallen-Marine-says-chaotic-Kabul-airport-withdrawal-not-planned-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kareem Nikoui's father Steve told Fox News on Friday night that he was angry at the conditions the Marines were working in, calling the situation at Hamid Karzai International Airport a 'turkey shoot'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Ida intensifying, forecast to hit Louisiana as CAT 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/hurricane-ida-gulf-coast-landfall-louisiana-new-orleans/1007755</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials warned residents that final preparations should be rushed to completion on Saturday as Hurricane Ida lurked in the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer 'Achilles' Heel' Discovered By Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cancers-achilles-heel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The enzyme, called CAIX (Carbonic Anhydrase IX), helps diseased cells spread to other organs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portable MORGUES sent to state...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934991/Portable-MORGUES-sent-Florida-states-spiraling-Covid-cases-crematoriums-capacity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Central Florida Disaster Medical Coalition said each hospital system will be sent different amounts of portable morgues depending on the size of the facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder private charity was bust, and questions swirl over where money went...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/larry-elders-private-charity-was-a-bust-and-questions-swirl-over-where-the-money-went/ar-AANPg8U </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice film fest returns with blockbuster lineup...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210828-venice-film-fest-returns-with-another-blockbuster-lineup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice film fest returns with another blockbuster lineup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan Probes Deaths of Two Who Had MODERNA Shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japan-probes-two-deaths-jabs-101057799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan is investigating the death of two men who received jabs from batches of Moderna's Covid-19 vaccine suspended from use due to contamination, the health ministry said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight by Fight, Jake Paul Strikes for Credibility...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/28/fight-by-fight-jake-paul-strikes-for-credibility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jake Paul has not had a quiet moment to think. Between traveling to Miami to watch his older brother, Logan,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts warn of dangers from breach of voter system software...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-software-election-2020-1341028212960b9b4ed713620d764629</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Republican efforts questioning the outcome of the 2020 presidential race have led to voting system breaches that election security experts say pose a heightened risk to future elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port Problems Reach Worst of Pandemic Amid Crush of Imports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-port-problems-reach-worst-of-pandemic-amid-crush-of-imports/ar-AANQa2C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Supply Lines is a daily newsletter that tracks trade and supply chains disrupted by the pandemic. Sign up here. The number of ships waiting to enter the biggest U.S. gateway for trade with Asia reached the highest since the pandemic began, exacerbating delays for companies trying to replenish inventories during one of the busiest times of the year for seaborne freight. Forty-four container carriers were anchored and awaiting a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embassy warns Americans at Kabul airport gates to 'leave immediately'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/569824-embassy-warns-americans-at-kabul-airport-gates-to-leave-immediately</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Embassy in Kabul told Americans at the city's airport gates to “leave immediately,” citing “security threats” following the suicide bombing that killed 13 U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala delayed trip to Vietnam ratchets up Havana Syndrome fears...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/569791-harriss-delayed-trip-to-vietnam-ratchets-up-new-fears-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The medical evacuation of at least two U.S. diplomats in Vietnam ahead of a visit by Vice President Harris has exposed the Biden administration’s struggle to answer questions surrounding so-called Havana Syndrome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Market Risks Pile Up After Record-Setting Earnings Season...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/stock-market-risks-pile-record-063000459.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Delta cases. Inflation. Fed tapering. China’s crackdown. These are among the reasons why investors could soon get more nervous about this stock market.The S&amp;P 500 hit another record on Friday after Jerome Powell’s dovish taper speech reassured investors. However, the mood seems more cautious compared with a few weeks ago, when companies were in the middle of a record-setting earnings season.All the concerns boil down to one big debate: Has the recovery from the pandemic already pe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Life-altering' event...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-environment-and-nature-louisiana-coronavirus-pandemic-hurricanes-8870fde4261f7a3171205d9b018ee7c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Residents across Louisiana's coast Saturday were taking one last day to prepare for what is being described as a “life-altering” Hurricane Ida which is expected to bring winds as high as 140 mph (225 kph) when it slams ashore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landfall with 140mph winds and 165mph gusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/280240.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/aug/27/wall-street-hits-new-highs-after-fed-extends-covid-stimulus-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head of US central bank Jerome Powell had been expected to announce the programme would be tapered off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS propaganda app uses AMAZON Web Services...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/ISIS-propaganda-app-that-touted-Kabul-attack-16417641.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A propaganda arm of ISIS that celebrated the suicide bombing that killed at least 170...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio mandates vaccines for tourist spots, public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rio-mandates-vaccines-tourist-spots-185803462.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio de Janeiro announced Friday it will require proof of vaccination against Covid-19 to enter public spaces including movie theaters, stadiums and iconic tourist spots like the Christ the Redeemer statue and Sugarloaf Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Lifts All Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/denmark-scrap-all-covid-19-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREPARES TO STRIKE BACK</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/us-prepares-to-strike-back-after-kabul-airport-attack-grxfh5qkf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is drawing up plans for retaliatory strikes against Isis militants in Afghanistan after the killing of as many as 200 people in the Kabul airport suicide bombing.President Biden’s vow to avenge the deaths of the 13 US Marines who were among those to die in the attack raises the prospect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knocks out more oil than Katrina...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/update-5-extremely-dangerous-hurricane-ida-knocks-out-more-oil-than-katrina/ar-AANOdln</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ENERGY (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-'Extremely dangerous' Hurricane Ida knocks out more oil than Katrina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSTAGE FEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934589/Britain-pulls-plug-Kabul-airlift-UK-start-getting-soldiers-Airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ministry of Defence (MoD) has said the UK's ability to process more evacuations from Afghanistan's Kabul airport will be 'extremely reduced'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Seagal on Hook for SEC Crypto Fine Despite Move to Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steven-seagal-hook-sec-crypto-180957482.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Steven Seagal who starred in the film “Beyond the Law” found out that even relocating to Russia doesn’t mean he’s beyond the reach of U.S. courts as the Securities and Exchange Commission won a judgment against him.A federal judge in Brooklyn, New York, said the SEC can go through Seagal’s business manager to try and collect more than $200,000 that the actor owes the U.S. government for failing to disclose he was being paid to promote a digital token.U.S. District Judge William Ku</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel seeks records from tech companies in riot probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-riots-capitol-siege-michael-pence-d0324bd4b8122220e181147725078733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House panel investigating the riot at the U.S. Capitol issued sweeping document requests on Friday to social media companies, expanding the scope of its investigation as it seeks to examine the events leading to the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders sells big govt virtues in red states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-election-2020-bernie-sanders-a3760ba452dcd0fd8014a115461e8ef5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST LAFAYETTE, Ind. (AP) — Bernie Sanders has long argued — but not proved — that his big government populism can win over voters in the largely white, rural communities that flocked to Republican Donald Trump in recent elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine Commander Fired After Blasting 'Inept'  Leadership...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/marine-battalion-commander-blasts-inept-military-leadership-over-afghanistan-withdrawal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sitting Marine battalion commander on Thursday blasted the “ineptitude” of U.S. military leadership over the disastrous Afghanistan withdrawal, saying he was willing to risk losing his 17-year career and future retirement pension in order to “demand accountability” from top military brass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Religious Broadcasters fires spox after pro-vax comments...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2021/08/27/nrb-spokesman-dan-darling-fired-after-pro-vaccine-statements-on-morning-joe-evangelical-covid-hesitancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — Daniel Darling, senior vice president of communications for the National Religious Broadcasters, was fired Friday (Aug. 27) after refusing to recant his pro-vaccine statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders parents to pay $45K for tossing son's porn, sex toy collection...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/judge-orders-parents-to-pay-45k-for-tossing-sons-porn-collection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because they threw out some X-rated material, these parents will now have fork over thousands in cash. A Michigan couple will have to pay $45,000 in a smut-fueled family feud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK assassin Sirhan wins parole with support of 2 Kennedys...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/crime-shootings-california-los-angeles-san-diego-acfc333ba40e6853c6e2874281685d0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — U.S. Sen. Robert F. Kennedy's assassin was granted parole Friday after two of RFK's sons spoke in favor of Sirhan Sirhan’s release and prosecutors declined to argue he should be kept behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cancel culture' show in Warsaw stirs controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-cancel-culture-show-in-warsaw-stirs-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Cancel culture' show in Warsaw stirs controversy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid pandemic, CDC gets serious -- about gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/27/health/cdc-gun-research-walensky/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in decades, the director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention -- the nation's top public health agency -- is speaking out forcefully about gun violence in America, calling it a "serious public health threat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban kill squad hunting down Afghans --  using American biometric data...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/taliban-kill-squad-hunting-afghans-with-americas-biometric-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban has mobilized a special unit, called Al Isha, to hunt down Afghans who helped US and allied forces — and it’s using US equipment and data to do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. intel split on origins, offer no high-confidence conclusions in new report...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/27/covid-origin-report-us-intelligence-agencies-are-divided.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, Biden ordered a closer intelligence review of what he described as two likely scenarios of the origins of the Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission impossible: To rescue Tom Cruise's stolen luggage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mission-impossible-rescue-tom-cruises-162905111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission for British police on Friday, should they choose to accept it, was to recover the luggage of Hollywood superstar Tom Cruise after his bodyguard's car was stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  NEWSOM COULD BE IN REAL TROUBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/gavin-newsom-california-recall/619848/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gavin Newsom's struggles could spell trouble for Democrats everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riddle as Pentagon now says there was only ONE explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934007/Pentagon-says-ONE-explosion-Kabul-suicide-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army General Hank Taylor said on Friday: 'I can confirm that we do not believe there was a second explosion at or near the Baron hotel' and blamed the 'confusion' on the dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of Young Patients Struggling to Breathe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/at-a-children-s-hospital-a-wave-of-young-patients-struggling-to-breathe/ar-AANOZfV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a Children’s Hospital, a Wave of Young Patients Struggling to Breathe By Noah Weiland and Erin Schaff NEW ORLEANS — Helpless to improve her infant son’s breathing as he was about to be intubated, Catherine Perrilloux did the only thing that came naturally to her in that moment, the worst of her life: She looked away and prayed. The boy, known as Junior, was two months old and gravely ill with Covid-19. Sign up for The Morning newsletter from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: Nearly 100 Cats Removed From Feces-Covered Home...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/08/26/mather-greene-county-cats-rescued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of cats were removed from a home in Greene County Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T. Rex Was 'Foodie,' Scientists Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avmap/scientists-find-t-rex-was-a-foodie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dinosaur had “a delicate side like other animals. It’s not a monster.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani admits liking Scotch but denies being alcoholic...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/politics/rudy-giuliani-says-u-s-has-gone-off-the-rails-denies-he-has-alcohol-problem/3243586/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 20 years after being dubbed America’s Mayor, Rudy Giuliani says he knows that people think he’s gone off the rails. He also doesn’t care, and instead believes it’s the country that has gone off the rails</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans evacuations ordered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_c59648f6-0756-11ec-858a-874da06021ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Tropical Storm Ida heads toward the Gulf coast, some parish officials in southeast Louisiana have called for voluntary and mandatory evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Lifts All Restrictions Except Entry Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidnikel/2021/08/27/denmark-lifts-all-coronavirus-restrictions-except-entry-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From September 10, Denmark will remove all domestic restrictions related to Covid-19. Travel restrictions remain in place for the time being, although many people can now travel to Denmark.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
