<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How money has flowed from sugar fields of Dominican to tax haven of SDakota...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Bitter-sugar-How-money-has-flowed-from-the-sugar-16521558.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, the U.S. government has condemned prominent offshore tax havens, where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMOTIONS FLARE IN VIRGINIA GOV RACE</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-scramble-for-votes-in-Virginia-emotions-flare-16521483.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Carlson considers himself mainly a Democrat. He voted for Bill Clinton and Barack...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID big waves over? Experts split...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/576030-are-covid-19s-big-waves-over-experts-are-split</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts are split on whether the waning delta surge will be the last major COVID-19 wave to strike the U.S., as Americans grow eager for the pandemic to end after 19 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands march in Rome to protest workplace vaccine rule...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-italy-mario-draghi-health-436d20f53f526a11b746c262ccf84315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Thousands of demonstrators marched down Rome's Via Veneto and other main streets on Saturday, many clashing with police, to protest a government rule requiring COVID-19 vaccines or recent negative tests to access workplaces starting next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON DYNAMICS has captivated public with viral videos, now it's looking to impress paying customers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/09/inside-boston-dynamics-plan-to-commercialization-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC got a rare look at Boston Dynamics' office in Massachusetts to see two of the robots the company is working to commercialize: Spot and Stretch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican cartel fires machine gun above National Guard post as migrants flood in...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10074663/Mexican-cartel-fires-machine-gun-bullets-zipping-just-National-Guard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was captured by a reporter amid reports that Texas National Guard members have seen cartel gunfights increase near the border recently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump heads to Iowa as 2024 chatter grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/576023-trump-heads-to-iowa-as-2024-chatter-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is sending the clearest signals yet that he’s planning another presidential run in 2024 as he heads to Iowa for a rally this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA plant party in Berlin draws fans and protests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211009141131-mi4i4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TESLA-BERLIN/OPENING (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Musk’s Tesla plant party in Berlin draws fans and protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope meets Pelosi as abortion debate rages back home...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211009132430-cyoiu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN-USA/PELOSI-POPE (PIX):Pope meets Pelosi as abortion debate rages back home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of northwest Colorado wolf pack remains mystery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-lifestyle-parks-travel-wildlife-f2df9674209a7a1b10001a77ccd68ba4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — On a hazy July afternoon, wolf expert Karin Vardaman returned to a spring-fed pond in Colorado’s northwestern-most corner. Enough rain had fallen to wet the ground around the watering hole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automakers targeting audiophiles to lift sales...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/turn-volume-automakers-targeting-audiophiles-lift-sales/story?id=80404201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Automakers targeting audiophiles to lift sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabs Manhattan APPLE store guard over mask rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-mask-attack-apple-store-meatpacking-district-20211009-jshgvuj2u5a2bmbyvuawnv7hd4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unidentified man confronted the guard when he was asked to put on a face mask, said a police source and witnesses. “I heard them yelling and pushing and shoving,” longtime area resident Roberto Monticello said of the feud between the guard and the unmasked man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Ergen, Dell Brawling Over Spectrum at FCC...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-10-09/billionaires-musk-ergen-and-dell-brawling-over-spectrum-at-fcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite entrepreneur Charlie Ergen and computer whiz Michael Dell have a plan to open up little-used wireless frequencies to millions of customers with a new 5G service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local school boards emerge as hot races in November election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-ohio-school-boards-racial-injustice-election-2020-a27a6ea4b7d4acc07173ebf7fa494257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — In a school district near the Ohio state capital, school board members up for reelection this year have been subjected to a steady stream of lawsuits and attacks, both in-person and online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Media Mogul 'Degrading' Boss From Hell, Her Staffers Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/hollywood-media-mogul-degrading-boss-223009050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyIt’s like a scene from a bad Hollywood movie: an employee takes off a few hours from work to bring his fiancée to the oncologist for a cancer check-up, only to have the tyrannical boss call and curse him out for slacking off.Only, according to one former employee of the entertainment and media news site TheWrap, it really happened.“What are you thinking?” founder and CEO Sharon Waxman bellowed at the employee in the fall of 2020, he recalled. “Does she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 3 In 5 People Consider Their Pet Soulmate...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pet-owners-soulmate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The survey also reveals that pet owners often search for similar affirmations of love from their pets as they do from their partners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy crisis gripping world, with potentially grave consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/an-energy-crisis-is-gripping-the-world-with-potentially-grave-consequences/ar-AAPjcIE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advocates for renewable energy say the global crisis shows the need to move further away from coal, gas and oil as prices for those commodities spike. Their critics contend just the opposite — that wind and solar have been tested and came up lacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems edge toward dumping Iowa caucuses as first presidential vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Democrats-edge-toward-dumping-Iowa-s-caucuses-as-16521162.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is not a big fan. Former Democratic National Committee chair Tom...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamb-Human Hybrid Horror Movie Will Haunt Dreams...</title>
      <link>https://ca.movies.yahoo.com/lamb-lamb-human-hybrid-horror-033302111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.movies.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courtesy A24After more than a year mostly spent in a shoebox-sized one-bedroom apartment, the opening scenes of Lamb, A24’s latest slow-simmering horror film, felt like a much-needed breath of fresh air—specifically, a crisp Icelandic breeze. María and Ingvar, married but childless, run a farm together and raise sheep. Their existence seems idyllic at first, dyed in appealing shades of indigo and white and set against sweeping plains of fresh grass. But it doesn’t take long for this agrarian uto</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Taliban to hold first talks since Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/taliban-doha-afghanistan-middle-east-qatar-90499edaa69e582e2c1f64210e782ff0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISLAMABAD (AP) — Senior Taliban officials and U.S. representatives are to hold talks Saturday and Sunday about containing extremist groups in Afghanistan and easing the evacuation of foreign citizens and Afghans from the country, officials from both sides said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt drama masked brutal power struggle between Mcconnell and Schumer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/08/debt-drama-power-struggle-schumer-mcconnell-515612</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP leader "knows exactly what he’s doing," one lieutenant said. And the Democratic leader won't give in. That's life in a 50-50 Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coconuts and prayers: Solomons pair survive 29 days adrift at sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211009-coconuts-and-prayers-solomons-pair-survive-29-days-adrift-at-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coconuts and prayers: Solomons pair survive 29 days adrift at sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Shatner lends BLUE ORIGIN star power...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211009-beam-me-up-jeff-william-shatner-lends-blue-origin-star-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beam me up, Jeff! William Shatner lends Blue Origin star power</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chappelle embraces being cancelled in LGBTQ row...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211008-dave-chappelle-embraces-being-cancelled-in-transgender-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Chappelle embraces being cancelled in transgender row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily reinstates TX abortion law...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/576048-judge-issues-stay-of-preliminary-injunction-on-texass-6-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing number of Dems endorse abolishing borrowing limit altogether...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/576032-growing-number-of-democrats-endorse-abolishing-debt-limit-altogether</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is on the verge of narrowly averting a catastrophic debt default — and some Democrats want it to be for the last time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi vows reunification...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211009041046-q2un3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-POLITICS/ANNIVERSARY (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-China's Xi vows 'reunification' with Taiwan, but holds off threatening force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambani Joins Bezos, Musk in $100 Billion Club...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/business/companies/mukesh-ambani-jeff-bezos-elon-musk-exclusive-100-billion-club-7562293/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reliance Industries chairman, Mukesh Ambani, is now worth $100.6 billion, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, after his wealth increased by $23.8 billion this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Boris Draws Happy Face, Britons Confront Run of Bad News...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/09/as-johnson-draws-a-happy-face-britons-confront-a-run-of-bad-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Britons are lining up for gas, staring at empty grocery shelves, paying higher taxes and worrying about spiraling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA in Recession If History of Consumer Sentiment Repeats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/us-is-in-recession-if-history-of-consumer-sentiment-repeats/ar-AAPh43W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decline in consumer expectations suggests the U.S. economy is in recession even though employment and wage growth indicate otherwise, according a new study co-authored by a former Bank of England policy maker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hid foreign payments from his DC hotel as it lost money, House panel says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008142806-09e14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/HOTEL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Trump hid foreign payments from his DC hotel as it lost money, House panel says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Biden hacking sparks concern as Psaki insists just allergies...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/08/coughing-biden-sparks-concern-as-psaki-says-its-just-allergies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki on Friday assured reporters that President Biden’s ailing cough is the result of allergies and not a more serious medical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA becomes 1st state to make ethnic studies required for high school graduation...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/california-becomes-1st-state-to-make-ethnic-studies-a-required-class-for-high-school-graduation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than five years of intense scrutiny and effort, California on Friday became the first state to make ethnic studies a required class for high school graduation to help students understand…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boy Rabbi Promises Religious Exemptions for Anyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xje9/proud-boy-rabbi-promises-religious-exemptions-for-covid-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asher Meza went on YouTube to tell his subscribers he’d give out exemptions to both Jews and gentiles alike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Area 52's secret military base...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3820666/inside-area-52-secret-military-base-nuclear-bombs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AREA 51, the highly classified US Air Force base which has for years been at the center of a conspiracy among alien fanatics and ufologists, has a lesser-known sister facility that harbors its own …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert on Criminal Mind Now Suspected in Arson Spree...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/expert-criminal-mind-now-hes-123211677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LASSEN NATIONAL FOREST, Calif. — He drove out of the Lumberjacks restaurant parking lot on a Tuesday in August, up Main Street, past the fire station and the gun shop. Then, Gary Maynard left the small city of Susanville in the northeastern corner of California and headed up a steep highway into the Sierra Nevada, where, prosecutors say, he set the forest ablaze. Maynard, a criminology professor who specializes in deviancy, now sits in a Sacramento jail awaiting a hearing. The crime expert, inve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men rescued after 29 days lost at sea: 'Nice break'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/08/men-rescued-after-29-days-lost-at-sea-it-was-a-nice-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite losing themselves at sea for nearly a month, two men from the Solomon Islands have returned with a remarkably positive outlook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US delegation to meet Taliban in first high-level talks since pullout...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008202901-aturu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/USA-MEETING (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-U.S. delegation to meet Taliban in first high-level talks since pullout - officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: 9 Shot, 3 Killed, In Less Than 12 Hours...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/07/its-sad-it-really-is-at-least-9-shot-3-killed-in-less-than-12-hours-in-baltimore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least nine people were shot and three were killed in Baltimore in less than 12 hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation not going away anytime soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/08/strong-wage-gains-cast-doubt-that-inflation-is-going-away-anytime-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September's wage gains provided more fuel to the argument that the current pace of inflation could run longer than many economists anticipate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY schools to end gifted, talented program...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-new-york-city-race-and-ethnicity-education-d027be86b7d202f1d4ef62e5c3255802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City will phase out its program for gifted and talented students that critics say favors whites and Asian American students, while enrolling disproportionately few Black and Latino children, in the nation's largest school system.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
