<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China Moves on U.S. Car Tariff...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-moves-on-us-car-tariff-cut-trump-tweeted-about-after-xi-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (BLOOMBERG) - China is moving towards cutting its trade war tariffs on imported US-made cars, a step already brandished by President Donald Trump as a concession won during trade talks in Argentina.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE GRILLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/11/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-testifies-before-congress-on-bias-privacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers will likely pepper Google CEO Sundar Pichai with a broad range of questions on bias, user privacy and its plans in China when he testifies in front of the House Judiciary Committee on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: TESTIMONY...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?455607-1/google-ceo-testifies-data-collection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai testifies on user data practices before the House Judiciary Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rights Groups Turn Up Pressure...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/12/10/rights-groups-pressure-google-on-china-censorship-ahead-of-congressional-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google risks being “complicit in human rights violations” if it brings censored search back to China, said a global coalition of over 60 groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's concessions set to blow out French deficit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181211111210-9ylgg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ (PIX, GRAPHIC):Macron's concessions set to blow out French deficit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Spent $100 Million on Tropical Real Estate. They Were Scammed, FTC Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-spent-100-million-on-tropical-real-estate-they-were-scammed-ftc-says-11544535843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government’s shutdown of what it called a $100 million real-estate investment scam in Belize highlights a growing concern: the targeting of Americans retiring abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Creates World's First Trans District...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/san-francisco-creates-worlds-first-ever-transgender-cultural-district</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The creation of Compton’s Transgender Cultural District is to stop the displacement of trans people from a place they were traditionally welcomed in, and to teach trans history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Military will build border wall if Pelosi, Schumer don't agree to pay for it...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/schumer-pelosi-meet-trump-hash-border-funding/story?id=59726978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer and House Speaker-elect Nancy Pelosi are set to meet with President Trump at the White House on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doris Kearns Goodwin: 'There's No Joy' in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/presidential-historian-doris-kearns-goodwin-theres-no-joy-in-white-house-trump-might-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excavation of 'Little Foot' Skeleton Reveals Mysterious Human Relative...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64275-little-foot-hominin-excavated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following an epic 20-year-long excavation in South Africa, researchers have finally recovered and cleaned the nearly-complete skeleton of an ancient human relative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN: 'Gigantic holes in system'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/11/yellen-warns-of-another-potential-financial-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Federal Reserve Chair Janet Yellen told an audience in New York City Monday night that she fears there could be another financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR TRIBUNE film critic resigns over plagiarism...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.mprnews.org/newscut/2018/12/star-tribune-film-critic-resigns-amid-evidence-of-plagiarism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.mprnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Could smell boat approaching': Grim truth about animal exports...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/11/we-could-smell-the-boat-approaching-grim-truth-animal-exports-israel-haifa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broken bones are common for sheep and cattle held on ships for weeks in cramped pens. Jo-Anne McArthur tracked arrivals in Israel’s Haifa port</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME 'Person of Year' is killed and imprisoned journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/time-s-2018-person-year-killed-imprisoned-journalists-n946311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time magazine is spotlighting a handful of journalists who have one thing in common: They were targeted for their work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Truth isn't truth' tops list of notable quotes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/truth-isnt-truth-tops-list-of-notable-quotes-in-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assertion that "truth isn't truth," made by a personal attorney for President Donald Trump, tops a Yale Law School librarian's list of the most notable quotes of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RENT CAR WITH FACE SCAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0853260708a64136b983eadbfef694b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biometric screening is expanding to the rental car industry. Hertz said Tuesday it is teaming up with Clear, the maker of biometric screening kiosks found at many airports, in an effort to slash the time it takes to pick up a rental car. Clear hopes it will lead more travelers to its platform, which has 3 million members in the U.S. It's the latest place consumers will find biometric technology, which has migrated over the last 50 years from secure government facilities and banks to airports, stadiums and even smartphones that unlock with the touch a fingerprint. Hertz is the first rental car company to use the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Storm clouds gathering for next financial crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/11/imf-financial-crisis-david-lipton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Lipton says world is unprepared for downturn and Fund needs more resources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign investors spurn Treasuries as curve threatens to invert...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-bonds-foreigners/foreign-investors-spurn-us-treasuries-as-curve-threatens-to-invert-idUSKBN1OA0J6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worrying sign of inversion in the U.S. Treasury bond curve is dulling the appe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grass-Fed to Lab-Grown: Meat Evolving...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tasting-the-worlds-first-test-tube-steak-11544524201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is on to create lab-grown meat products. Still, little is known about their safety and potential impact. In Moving Upstream, WSJ’s Jason Bellini visits entrepreneurs, scientists, and ranchers to understand how it’s made, and gets a first taste of steak grown from cultured cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam Brothels to Get Review by City's First Female Mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/amsterdam-brothels-to-get-a-review-by-city-s-first-female-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amsterdam Brothels to Get a Review by City's First Female Mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space station crew to inspect mysterious hole on spacewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f770a821e8b24e38b1a9abb5d4aec9d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Two Russian cosmonauts were preparing to venture outside the International Space Station Tuesday to inspect a section where a mysterious leak has been discovered. The leak was spotted on Aug. 30 in the Russian Soyuz spacecraft attached to the station. The crew quickly located and sealed the tiny hole that created a slight loss of pressure, and space officials said the station has remained safe to operate. Russian cosmonauts Oleg Kononenko and Sergei Prokopyev will conduct a six-hour spacewalk to inspect the Soyuz's outer surface. They will uncover the thermal insulation covering the patched hole and take samples that will be studied by experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Made Remote-Controlled Dogs With Brain Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-10/newly-released-mkultra-docs-cia-made-remote-controlled-dogs-brain-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak may explode...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/12/ebola-vaccine-having-major-impact-outbreak-may-still-explode-west-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed conflict in the Democratic Republic of the Congo hampers health care response and vaccine distribution to combat deadly virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many Want To Have Sex With Robot? Numbers Are In...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-09/how-many-people-want-have-sex-robot-numbers-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves scandal looms over CBS shareholder meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5c2459d13df24d448f0d3ed5f177300e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With a $120 million severance package on the line, an investigation into sexual-misconduct claims against former CBS CEO Les Moonves will loom over the network's annual shareholders meeting on Tuesday. But CBS officials are unlikely to say more beyond seeking to reassure shareholders that the board is "on top of that, don't worry, when we have sufficient information we will disclose this," said Porter Bibb, a former media executive now with the advisory firm Mediatech Capital Partners. He said the scandal is likely to be mentioned "only peripherally."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Employees Sought To Block BREITBART From Ads, Emails Show...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/10/google-ads-bias/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'My team has been reviewing the site'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas bill would allow Ten Commandments to be posted in classrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article222625075.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Dan Flynn, R-Van, wants to let Texas teachers display the Ten Commandments in their classrooms, if they’d like. Others argue that this proposal is unconstitutional and will fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador feeling pain of China loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/ecuador-is-feeling-pain-of-china-loans/article_3456b756-956e-57ec-a869-94251437ae9a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador — Rafael Correa wanted to fast-track development projects when he was president of Ecuador, so he borrowed billions of dollars from China. But the loans have come back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit deal in turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5aec0aa11a15440da182cf6bd225abf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Facing almost certain defeat, British Prime Minister Theresa May on Monday postponed a vote in Parliament on her Brexit deal, saying she would go back to European Union leaders to seek changes to the divorce agreement. May's move threw Britain's Brexit plans into disarray, intensified a domestic political crisis and battered the pound. With EU officials adamant the withdrawal deal was not up for renegotiation, the country does not know on what terms it will leave — and whether May will still be Britain's leader when it does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear Gauge Warns This Selloff Is Different...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fear-gauge-warns-that-this-selloff-is-different-1544472242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street’s fear gauge settled lower Monday after erasing earlier gains—a sign investors are closely monitoring market signals on future volatility and adjusting options positions accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDakota Passes Venezuela in Oil Output...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/little-caracas-on-the-prairie-1544476509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Dakota has passed once-mighty Venezuela in oil output, but still trails in other things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the frathouse: Humiliation, homoeroticism, animal cruelty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2018/dec/10/andrew-moisey-american-fraternity-photographer-college-behaviour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photographer Andrew Moisey uncovered ritual hazing, extreme drunkenness and toxic masculinity on one college campus – from men destined to be America’s future leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEUD!  At 102, Olivia de Havilland won't give up fight with FX...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-olivia-de-havilland-interview-20181210-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare interview, the "Gone With the Wind" star discusses taking her lawsuit against the cable network to the U.S. Supreme Court. "I never imagined that anyone would misrepresent me,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Conway show rolls on...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6481853/The-Conways-Washington-power-couple-divided-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is one of Donald Trump's harshest critics.She is one of the president's closest advisers.And they're husband and wife.The marriage of George T. Conway III...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks on track for worst year in DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/stocks-set-for-worst-year-in-a-decade-four-experts-weigh-in-on-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four experts weigh in on what factors will shape global markets in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAKING IT OFF</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dc558078d0bb4b3e8aec63960a7091f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's intensifying legal troubles are unnerving some of his fellow Republicans. Despite his brash stance, they believe the turmoil has left him increasingly vulnerable as he gears up for what is sure to be a nasty fight for re-election. Trump, ever confident of his ability to bend story lines to his will, mocks the investigations into his conduct as candidate and president as a "witch hunt" and insists he will survive the threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit soars in first two months of fiscal year...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/budget/420661-budget-deficit-soars-in-first-two-months-of-fiscal-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The budget deficit in the first two months of the 2019 fiscal year was 50 percent higher than in the same period the previous year, according to the CBO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART testing robot fry cook at delis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-walmart-testing-robot-fry-cook-delis-154733360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might remember 'Flippy' the burger-flipping robot that's now a fry cook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few at BLOOMBERG wants Mike Bloomberg to run for President!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/we-asked-dozens-of-bloomberg-staffers-if-they-want-him-to-run-in-2020-only-1-said-yes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast reached out to 60+ Bloomberg News employees about the boss’ White House ambitions. Only a single staffer was psyched about Mike 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sells Iconic 'Television City'... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-sells-television-city-property-750-million-1168095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles-based real estate developer Hackman Capital Partners signed the acquisition agreement on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV's Lesbian BATWOMAN Debuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-roses-batwoman-makes-her-debut-cws-elseworlds-1168056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, who discovered Kate Kane's (Ruby Rose) alter ego?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 In 10 Lie To Doctors About Their Health...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eighty-percent-lie-doctors-about-health-study-reveals-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the guaranteed confidentiality and even though it could potentially put one's health at risk, a new study finds that as many as eight in 10 people lie to their doctors about their health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Patriotic' prepared remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-prepared-patriotic-remarks-for-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai amps up the company's patriotism in his prepared remarks ahead of Tuesday's congressional hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptions, overdoses skyrocketing for anti-anxiety drugs...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/health/benzodiazepines-addiction-philadelphia-opioid-crisis-20181210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say an explosion of benzodiazepine prescriptions in the middle of an opioid crisis is particularly concerning, because both drugs become much deadlier when mixed with each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California sued over keeping DNA from arrests with no conviction...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/12/10/watchdogs-sue-california-over-dna-retention-for-non-convicted-arrestees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Department of Justice sued by Electronic Frontier Foundation on behalf of two social-justice groups challenging practice of retaining the DNA profiles of people arrested for alleged felo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Irony: By being murdered, Whitey Bulger may help compensate his victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/12/10/the-final-irony-being-murdered-whitey-bulger-may-help-compensate-his-victims/cyAjS1WP1PIe17jYphGQdL/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One may be charitable and believe that the Justice Department, which oversees the Bureau of Prisons, will do the right thing and bring all the circumstances to light. But, historically, the Justice Department has been compromised by Bulger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: Students vow 'Black Tuesday' protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-france-high-school-students-protests-yellow-vests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as it grapples with violent demonstrations over living costs, the French government is hunkering down for a “Black Tuesday” of protests by high-school students who have jumped onto the Yellow Vest bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Immigration Hits Highest Level in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/12/10/iillegal-immigration-last-month-hit-highest-level-in-over-a-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration skyrocketed to the highest level in over a decade for the month of November as Trump's border wall remains unfunded.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo cocaine train route from Mexico to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/10/el-chapo-ran-cocaine-train-route-to-nyc-ex-cartel-member/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He should have been called El Choo-po. Mexican cartel kingpin Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman ran a cocaine train all the way from Mexico to New York City, a witness testified Monday. “Chapo decided who …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP booted after grabbing ceremonial mace amid row...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/politics/mp-booted-from-the-house-of-commons-after-grabbing-ceremonial-mace-amid-brexit-row-a4013741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Labour MP was kicked out of the House of Commons after picking up the ceremonial mace following the Brexit deal vote being delayed.  After a Government whip shouted "tomorrow" in regards to the debate and vote - meaning it will be held on an unspecified future date - jeers rang through the House.  Lloyd Russell-Moyle then went over to the silver gilt mace, picked it up and then walked away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong tops global list for super-rich home buyers...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1490218/hong-kong-tops-list-of-where-the-super-rich-buy-expensive-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2018, the highest number of residential property transactions worth $25 million or more were in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone geyser breaks historical eruption record...</title>
      <link>https://www.localnews8.com/news/kifi-top-story/steamboat-geyser-breaks-historical-yearly-eruption-record/923532758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.localnews8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Steamboat Geyser in Yellowstone National Park broke decades-old records when it erupted for the 30th time in 2018 Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACADEMY CONSIDERS HOST-LESS OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/oscars-academy-kevin-hart-replacement-1203084598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart’s abrupt departure as Oscars host has left the Academy of Motion Pictures Arts &amp; Sciences scrambling to find someone to take the gig. As of now, the situation remains fluid as …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON delivery driver turns 'porch pirate,' arrested for stealing bait...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2018/12/amazon-delivery-driver-turns-porch-pirate-arrested-for-stealing-bait-package-from-aloha-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dreaded “porch pirate” isn’t always who you expect it to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Samaritan stops to help crash victims, gets car towed by cops...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/police-tow-good-samaritans-car-after-stopping-to-help-crash-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a car in front of him went out of control, flipping into a ravine on the Suitland Parkway on Sunday night, Benjamin Davis, III could've driven by. But, he says he knew people needed help. So he stopped. "The guy is hanging out of the passenger side door. Unfortunately, his friend was crushed," said Davis. Davis managed to get the survivor out of the car, but the second person in the car, 21-year-old Kyree Payne of Northeast D. C. , died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecosystem below Earth TWICE size of world's oceans...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/dec/10/tread-softly-because-you-tread-on-23bn-tonnes-of-micro-organisms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global team of scientists find ecosystem below earth that is twice the size of world’s oceans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie-like', lives for millions of years...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-vast-zombie-like-microbial-life-lurks-beneath-seabed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast, zombie-like microbial life lurks beneath seabed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules law prohibiting secret recording of govt officials is unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/news/boston/index.ssf/2018/12/federal_judge_rules_mass_law_p.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal court judge Monday ruled a Massachusetts General Law prohibiting the secret recording of police or government officials is unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK: Get-Trump talk now campaign finance, not Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-sudden-shift-in-get-trump-talk-now-its-campaign-finance-not-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors investigating President Trump made big news Friday, but it wasn't about Russia. Rather, in their sentencing recommendation for fixer Michael Cohen, lawyers with the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York wrote that in the final weeks of the 2016 campaign, candidate Trump…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False statement charges abound, contrast to Clinton case...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/false-statement-charges-abound-in-mueller-probe-discouraged-in-clinton-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation is abounding with false statement charges against Trump campaign associates, but a Justice Department inspector general report revealed that the FBI and federal prosecutors discouraged charging witnesses under the same offense in the bureau’s probe into Hillary Clinton’s private email server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO: Masked man shoots livestreaming campaign door-knocker...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/man-recovering-from-being-shot-while-campaigning-for-15th-ward-political-candidate/4872789/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxwell Little, also known on social media as Maxwell Omowale Justice, is recovering after being shot in the leg while campaigning for 15th Ward aldermanic candidate Joseph Williams on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman plotted mass murder, corresponded with SC church shooter...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/news/ohio-woman-who-plotted-mass-murder-corresponded-with-dylann-roof/article_e84839b4-fcb8-11e8-ae4f-cb4da1e387eb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio woman accused of plotting what she referred to as an "upscale mass murder" at a Toledo bar had glorified Dylann Roof and corresponded with the self-avowed white supremacist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKEDIN billionaire backs voter data project in 'existential threat' to Democratic Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/10/linkedin-reid-hoffman-dnc-voter-data-1054857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;DNC’s top leaders have been telling people that Hoffman’s project represents an “existential threat&amp;quot; to the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NISSAN Million-Dollar Supercar...</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/news/25359/nissan-opens-orders-for-1-1-million-710-hp-gt-r50-italdesign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it Nissan's farewell to the R35 GT-R, or is it a glimpse of the R36? Doesn't matter—it's both gorgeous and knock-your-socks-off fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socials outpace print as news source for adults...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/12/10/social-media-outpaces-print-newspapers-in-the-u-s-as-a-news-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One-in-five U.S. adults often get news via social media, slightly higher than the 16% who often do so from print newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star under fire after calling moon landing fake...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/warriors/article/steph-curry-fake-moon-landing-podcast-13454284.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Curry says he does not believe humans have been to the moon, a stance which is clearly unsupported by facts and hopefully just a joke.  Curry made the proclamation on The Ringer's podcast "Winging It" with teammate Andre Iguodala and hosts Vince Carter and Kent Bazemore; you can hear the exchange around the 46-minute mark. There's some talking over each other that makes it hard to hear, but when the discussion turns to the moon landing, almost everyone seems to agree we've never been to there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record count for mysterious paralyzing illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6cc9d8f3a9c4c84b72a9f45c3a335ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — This year has seen a record number of cases of a mysterious paralyzing illness in children, U.S. health officials said Monday. It's still not clear what's causing the kids to lose the ability to move their face, neck, back, arms or legs. The symptoms tend to occur about a week after the children had a fever and respiratory illness. No one has died from the rare disease this year, but it was blamed for one death last year and it may have caused others in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs officers searching more travelers' devices...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54497b1d5f5541efb96dc25d11ee66a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. Customs and Border Protection officers are searching the electronic devices of travelers more often, and did not always follow proper protocol, a new watchdog report has found. The report made public Monday found there were 29,000 devices searched at a port of entry out of 397 million travelers to the U.S. in budget year 2017, up from 18,400 the year before from 390 million travelers. Customs and Border Protection officials note it is less than 1 percent of all travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE announces new security flaw, closes social network...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/google-announces-new-security-flaw-closes-social-network-early-n946201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Plus received its initial kiss of death in early October, when the company revealed that a security bug had exposed the information of 500,000 users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for plotting synagogue attacks in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-man-arrested-for-plotting-synagogue-attacks-in-toledo-ohio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI says Damon Joseph planned to carry out mass shooting during Shabbat services on behalf of Islamic State, told undercover agent he was inspired by Pittsburgh massacre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gets Wedding Ring Back -- After Flushing It Down Toilet 9 Years Ago!</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/10/woman-gets-wedding-ring-back-after-flushing-it-down-toilet-9-years-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paula Stanton was sure the diamond-encrusted gold ring was lost forever after she noticed it wasn't on her finger while she was cleaning her bathroom nearly a decade ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters save 100 snakes from house fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article222894925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters in Texas rescued more than 100 pythons, boa constrictors and other snakes from a home that caught fire over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusion, Despair in Hinterlands...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-france-high-school-students-protests-yellow-vests&gt;Students vow 'Black Tuesday' protests...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows NYC police pulling toddler from mother's arms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dc2801bde5e8423c85ab058bede17858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Outrage built Monday over a video showing police officers violently yanking a toddler from his mother's arms at a Brooklyn food stamp office, with public officials expressing horror and clients of the facility complaining it is indicative of how the city treats social-services recipients. A witness said a security officer confronted the woman, Jazmine Headley, who had sat on the floor of the crowded office for two hours because of a lack of chairs. Police were called when she refused to leave. The woman ended up lying face-up on the floor during a tug of war over the child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt restricts yellow vests sales to avoid copycat protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/38a1a03c66234372b2149f3013f642ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Egyptian authorities have quietly introduced restrictions on the sale of yellow reflective vests, fearing opponents might attempt to copy French protesters during next month's anniversary of the 2011 popular uprising that toppled autocrat Hosni Mubarak, security officials and retailers said Monday. They said industrial safety equipment dealers have been instructed not to sell yellow vests to walk-in buyers and to restrict business to wholesale sales to verified companies, but only after securing police permission. They were told offenders would be punished, the officials said without elaborating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron promises tax relief...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/216f4fe17e85429a82ee088ed2a73b41</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The Latest on anti-government protests in France (all times local): 8:15 p.m. Facing exceptional protests, French President Emmanuel Macron is promising to speed up tax relief for struggling workers and to scrap a tax hike for retirees. The actions were the pledges Macron made on Monday night in his first public comments since protests against his presidency devolved into rioting in the French capital. The French leader reiterated earlier promises to raise the minimum wage and pledged to abolish taxes on overtime pay starting Jan. 1, several months before schedule. He also said a tax hike pensioners faced would be scrapped. All of the measures offered had been demanded by the yellow-vested protesters who have led four weeks of increasingly radicalized demonstrations against Macron's presidency, seen as favoring the rich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Licensed Content Remains Majority of Total Streams...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/digital/news/netflix-original-series-licensed-viewing-friends-the-office-1203085230/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Netflix moving fast enough to bulk up on originals to offset programming that’s about to get pulled by studios like Disney, Fox and WarnerMedia? Original content accounted for 37% of Netfl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-BLOOMBERG Execs to Be Charged in Construction Fraud Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/10/nyregion/bloomberg-construction-fraud-kickback.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About a dozen executives at the company are expected to be arrested on Tuesday by the Manhattan district attorney on fraud, theft and bribery charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of allegations in fundamental Baptist churches across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article222576310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation into US fundamental Baptist churches found more than 400 sexual misconduct allegations. More than 160 pastors, ministers and Christian leaders have been accused of committing crimes against children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Threatens Vehicle Attacks Near U.S. Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-magazine-for-millennials-threatens-vehicle-attacks-near-u-s-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debut issue of The Youth of the Caliphate called for attacks in Australia; a month later, a jihadist conducted a deadly stabbing attack in Melbourne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONIC employees allegedly laced kid's meal with ecstasy...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/sonic-employees-accused-of-lacing-kids-meal-with-ecstasy/4871425/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say two Sonic employees and their manager were arrested after ecstasy was reportedly found in a child's meal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, rebels discussing term limits for party leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/10/pelosi-party-leader-term-limits-1054789</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several members of the anti-Pelosi group discussed the potential deal on a conference call Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's visit to Baltimore called off...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-trump-visit-cancelled-20181210-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A planned visit by President Donald Trump to Baltimore on Wednesday has been called off and a discussion of the administration’s urban revitalization policies will take place at the White House instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic Pamphlets With KKK Logos Distributed Across Pittsburgh...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/12/09/pittsburgh-anti-semitic-materials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Pittsburgh are investigating hate-filled material that is being distributed in city neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers leap to sign John Kelly to $15 million tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6479553/Publishers-leap-chance-John-Kelly-tell-book-deal-time-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top publishers said they 'would kill' to publish John Kelly's tell-all book about his time as Trump's Chief of Staff. One editor said they reached out to him before the formal announcement was made.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Voyager 2 Leaves Solar System, Enters Interstellar Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/voyager-2-probe-moves-into-interstellar-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;11 billion miles from Earth, NASA's Voyager 2 spacecraft has moved into interstellar space, joining Voyager 1 in the realm between the stars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of Honduras, El Salvador, Domincan Republic want to leave; USA top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/158-million-migrants-want-to-move-to-the-us-worlds-top-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is the top pick – by far – for migrants seeking a new home despite reports that President Trump’s policies are scaring people away and making countries like Canada and some in Europe the preferred choice, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ayers walks away from White House...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/09/politics/ayers-white-house-chief-of-staff/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Ayers, the leading candidate to replace John Kelly as President Donald Trump's chief of staff, announced Sunday he will not be taking the job, reviving discussions about who will succeed the retired Marine general when he leaves at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli troops raid office of Palestinian news agency...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181210162908-cagcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/RAID (TV, PIX):Israeli troops raid office of Palestinian news agency - Wafa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese court bans sale of most iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/apple-falls-after-qualcomm-injunction-in-china-bans-most-iphone-sales.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese court ordered a ban on most iPhone sales in the country as part of two preliminary injunctions. Qualcomm sought the injunctions, alleging Apple violated two of its patents. Apple denies any patent violation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY DELAY!</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181210154633-ygpjh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 9-UK's May pulls vote on her divorce deal, thrusting Brexit into the unknown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/wall-street-faces-stomach-churning-swings-as-economic-uncertainty-grows/18053902/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a trade war broke out between the world’s two largest economies in June, investors barely blinked. After the Federal Reserve raised interest rates — often a reason for investors to sell stocks — the markets kept climbing. As some of the world’s largest economies began to slow down, U.S. markets largely shrugged it off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY DELAY!</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/may-pulls-parliamentary-vote-on-her-brexit-deal-idUSKBN1O90X1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May on Monday abruptly pulled a parliamentary vot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOLD:  Pharrell Williams mocked for excessively thanking AMERICAN EXPRESS...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/12/10/pharrell-williams-mocked-for-excessively-thanking-american-express/?_ga=2.243566861.96299170.1544457139-1073313886.1542905213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is an amazing concert, but how many times is he contractually obligated to thank Amex?” a spy asked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM PULLS BREXIT VOTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fa2ff4d861a24db9a1fa717d9fdc9adb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — The Latest on the debate over Britain's impending departure from the European Union (all times local): 5:15 p.m. British opposition leader Jeremy Corbyn has challenged Prime Minster Theresa May's decision to delay a vote on Brexit in the House of Commons, arguing that her government is in "complete disarray." Labour lawmakers shouted "Resign! Resign!' as May wrapped up her remarks Monday, adding further insult to the humiliation of failing to deliver on her signature piece of legislation, the Brexit divorce deal from the European Union. Corbyn described the situation as unprecedented and serious. He says "the government has lost control of events and is in complete disarray." Even members of May's own party were quick to further criticize the way she's handled the negotiations. Conservative Party lawmaker Jacob Rees-Mogg sharply rejected May's "undeliverable deal," saying it risked paving the way for a Labour Party government led by Corbyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court gives victory to PLANNED PARENTHOOD in Medicaid case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-leaves-legal-victory-place-planned-parenthood-n945946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dispute did not involve abortion, but rather a legal battle over whether states could block Medicaid patients' access to other health services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'John of God' hit with sex abuse claims...</title>
      <link>https://www1.folha.uol.com.br/internacional/en/brazil/2018/12/twelve-women-accuse-medium-john-of-god-of-sexual-abuse.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.folha.uol.com.br&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twelve women have come forward with allegations of sexual abuse against world-famous Brazilian medium and spiritual healer João de Deus (John of God). According to the victims, he abused them when they sought spiritual healing in the House of Dom Inácio de Loyola, in Abadiânia (GO), where thousands of people from all over the world go searching for spiritual treatments and counseling to every week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve Women Accuse...</title>
      <link>https://www1.folha.uol.com.br/internacional/en/brazil/2018/12/abuse-allegations-against-john-of-god-shock-small-goias-town.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.folha.uol.com.br&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Silence. The word, repeated exhaustively as an order in pictures and posters hanging on walls at Casa Dom Inácio de Loyola, in Abadiânia (GO) describes what part of the small town's 15,000 residents have been going through since the press reported several allegations of sexual abuse involving João de Deus (John of God), one of Brazil's most famous psychics.On the streets, few people talk freely about the scandal, since the town's economy relies heavily on the activities of Casa Dom Inácio, João de Deus spiritual healing center, open since 1976. They say they are afraid of retaliation and also because the medium hasn't talked about it yet.On Saturday (8th), 13 women told newspaper O Globo and TV Globo's late night talk show "Conversa com Bial" that the psychic had been sexually abused them during spiritual healing sessions in his private quarters inside Casa Dom Inácio, where more than a thousand people pass every week, from Wednesdays to Fridays.The news reports changed Abadiânia's routine. On Sunday (9th) morning, tourists and residents were feeling unsettled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Summons U.S. Ambassador Over HUAWEI...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-09/china-foreign-ministry-summons-u-s-ambassador-over-huawei</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Roger Ailes documentary earns less than $13K at boxoffice...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/420507-roger-ailes-documentary-earns-less-than-13k-at-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new documentary on former Fox News CEO and Chairman Roger Ailes earned just $12,431 on Friday and Saturday after its release, according to ComScore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's Turn in Hot Seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-ceo-faces-hot-seat-in-washington-1544446801 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai is expected to face questions at a Congressional hearing on a range of topics, including the company’s handling of user data and its development of a search engine that would comply with China’s strict internet censors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking two languages may help aging brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Speaking-two-languages-may-help-the-aging-brain-13453980.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even when you're fluent in two languages, it can be a challenge to switch back and forth smoothly between them. It's common to mangle a split verb in Spanish, use the wrong preposition in English or lose sight of the connection between the beginning and end of a long German sentence. So does mastering a second language hone our multitasking skills or merely muddle us up? This debate has been pitting linguists and psychologists against one another since the 1920s, when many experts thought that bilingual children were fated to suffer cognitive impairments later in life. But the science has marched on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Jews feel under threat, think of emigrating: EU survey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-eu-antisemitism/european-jews-feel-under-threat-think-of-emigrating-eu-survey-idUSKBN1O91RA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than one in three European Jews have considered emigrating over the past fi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human SOUL' to be scanned?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/747335/powerful-mri-scanner-china-human-soul-consciousness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW TUMBLES AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/09/dow-futures-drop-200-points-as-sell-off-is-set-to-continue-in-new-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded lower in a volatile session as investors feared an intensifying trade war between the United States and China.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
