<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POPE STAYS SILENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/under-attack-pope-calls-silence-prayer-140408631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Monday said "silence and prayer" were the answer to those seeking "scandal and division", amid a barrage of attacks from ultra-conservative Catholics. "With people who lack goodwill, with people who seek only scandal, who seek only division, who seek only destruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Death of local news...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/793309/death-local-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The watchdogs of America's local and state governments are disappearing. Can they be saved?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding cuts blamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-45398084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire wrecked Brazil's main museum and one of the region's largest natural history collections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER: TROP STORM TAKES AIM AT GULF</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2018-09-03-tropical-storm-gordon-forecast-florida-gulf-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gordon has developed near southern Florida and will quickly move to near the Gulf Coast by later Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article217756285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm raining all over South Florida’s Labor Day weekend is now officially Tropical Storm Gordon, the National Hurricane Center announced Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar court sentences REUTERS reporters to 7 years in jail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd0f856e7eaa46ffb744d1909c29d9f1/Myanmar-court-sentences-Reuters-reporters-to-7-years-in-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YANGON, Myanmar (AP) — A Myanmar court sentenced two Reuters journalists to seven years in prison Monday for illegal possession of official documents, a ruling met with internatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day 2040: What Happens When Robots Do All the Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/labor-day-2040-what-happens-when-robots-do-all-the-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Holiday Weekend From Hell: Humans Still Drove Cars and Flew The Planes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian rial hits record low...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180903122646-a680o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ECONOMY/RIAL (URGENT):Iranian rial hits record low at 128,000 to the dollar- Bonbast website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes High as States Gear Up to Pick Govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stakes-are-high-as-states-gear-up-to-pick-governors-1535976001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 36 contested races for governor this election year have outsized significance because many of the new crop of state leaders will have some say over the redrawing of legislative and congressional maps in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strange disappearance' of WIKILEAKS consultant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/strange-disappearance-of-wikileaks-consultant-in-norway/a-45328433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks has raised concern after Arjen Kamphuis, an associate of founder Julian Assange, went missing in Norway. The cybersecurity expert was last seen in northern Norway on August 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right poised for big wins in Sweden election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180903-far-right-poised-big-wins-sweden-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte apologizes for cursing Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/philippines--duterte-apologises-for-cursing-obama-10679184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM: Philippine leader Rodrigo Duterte has apologised to former US president Barack Obama for calling him a "son of a whore" in 2016, which ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firefighters battle suicidal thoughts after the blaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180903-us-firefighters-battle-suicidal-thoughts-after-blaze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to save relics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf1a4eff4ae04901afe1264a643d7a27/Firefighters-try-to-save-relics-as-fire-engulfs-Rio-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — A huge fire engulfed Brazil's 200-year-old National Museum in Rio de Janeiro, lighting up the night sky with towering flames as firefighters and museum worke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Struggle Puts Heat on Older White Incumbents...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/09/03/democratic-power-struggle-puts-heat-on-older-white-incumbents#gs.TuS9FA0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Power Struggle Puts Heat on Older White Incumbents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputy shoots man who fired gun after told no tickets available for Ice Cube concert...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/sd-me-shooting-delmar-20180902-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sheriff's deputy shot a man who fired a weapon Sunday outside a gate leading into a scheduled Ice Cube concert at the Del Mar Racetrack. The man's condition wasn't known.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women caned in Malaysia for attempting to have lesbian sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/women-caned-in-malaysia-for-attempting-to-have-lesbian-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rare punishment was carried out in a courtroom and witnessed by up to 100 people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Incalculable' loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/fire-engulfs-brazil-national-museum-rio</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Museo Nacional houses artefacts from Egypt, Greco-Roman art and some of the first fossils found in Brazil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresco that survived Pompeii destroyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/huge-fire-engulfs-brazils-200-13184185?5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio’s Museu Nacional houses a collection of more than 20 million items ranging from archaeological findings to historical memorabilia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIO ROCKED...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6125217/Giant-flames-tear-National-Museum-Rio-Janeiro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far nobody has been reported injured during the fire as it began after the museum had closed for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200-year-old National Museum hit by massive fire...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180903001032-p13t9/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-FIRE/MUSEUM:Rio's 200-year old National Museum hit by massive fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired during Del Mar race during televised event...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7161252/del-mar-shooting-horse-race-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOTS were fired at Del Mar race course in California during a live televised competition – as crowds gathered for an Ice Cube concert. Shocking footage caught the moment commentators screame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seoul to check public toilets to tackle 'spy-cam porn' crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/seoul-to-check-public-toilets-daily-to-tackle-spy-cam-porn-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move follows protests by record numbers of women calling for more action to tackle rise of voyeurism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Fence Jumper Nabbed...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/secret-service-person-arrested-climbing-white-house-security-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has been arrested for climbing over a White House security barrier Sunday night, according to authorities. Secret Service says the incident happened at around 8:10 p.m. in the area of 15th Street NW and Alexander Hamilton Place. Secret Service a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab-grown brain bits open windows to mind -- and ethical dilemmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/lab-grown-brain-bits-open-windows-to-the-mind--and-a-maze-of-ethical-dilemmas/2018/09/02/9a76efee-a25b-11e8-83d2-70203b8d7b44_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human ‘minibrains’ are far from conscious, but scientists say it’s time to talk about ethics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer attacked by own police dog -- shoots it to escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article217744755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officer Brian Carter of the Columbus, Ohio, police division shot Benzi, his K9 partner, after the Belgian Malinois attacked him during a training session, police say. The dog was later euthanized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Films Make Roaring Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/silent-films-make-roaring-return-with-help-from-younger-audiences-1535907601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The silent-film era peaked almost a century ago and lost steam with the advent of the talkies. But now the films are making a comeback in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey drops Israel appearance after pressure...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/music/la-et-ms-lana-del-rey-postpones-israel-concert-20180902-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop singer Lana Del Rey calls the move a postponement in hopes that one day all fans in the region can attend her shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Nebraska diocese rocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nebraska-catholic-diocese-rocked-old-abuse-allegations-161106949.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than a decade, a conservative Catholic diocese in Nebraska was the only church in the U.S. that refused to participate in annual reviews of sexual misconduct that were a key reform enacted in the wake of the 2002 Boston clergy abuse scandal. As a new wave of abuse scandals rock the Roman Catholic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/refresh/AL072018_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/234741_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm watch issued for central Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/florida-us-gulf-coast-on-alert-for-budding-tropical-depression/70005956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has gender reassignment surgery to become a woman -- at 81!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7159732/oldest-person-in-britain-to-have-reassignment-surgery-shares-her-joy-at-becoming-a-woman-aged-81-thanks-to-the-nhs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TRANSGENDER woman has spoken of her joy at becoming the oldest person in Britain to have surgery. Ruth Rose, 85, had a reassignment op four years ago after her doctor told her she could be consid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Russia against plans to hike pension age...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/02/thousands-protest-in-russia-against-plans-to-hike-retirement-age</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has called the reform a financial necessity as Communist party leader brands move ‘cannibalistic’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri's Senate race is nation's top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/govt-and-politics/how-big-is-missouri-s-senate-race-it-s-the/article_6513cd7d-0b32-5462-a624-76be5f548d88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chuck Schumer-related PAC is spending heavily for McCaskill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Mayor Eric Garcetti spreads wealth, influence around USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.postbulletin.com/news/politics/la-mayor-eric-garcetti-spreads-wealth-influence-around-the-us/article_3031597a-46de-5da6-bc72-1666566fb59c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Trav Robertson, chairman of the South Carolina Democratic Party, likes to tell people about Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti’s generosity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK FACES AUTUMN CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6123641/David-Davis-vows-vote-against-Mays-Chequers-Brexit-plan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two interventions from Michel Barnier and David Davis underline the challenge Mrs May faces in getting any kind of deal based on her Chequers proposals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin's tight governor's race puts Walker on defensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsins-tight-governors-race-puts-walker-defensive-161742018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Wisconsin's tight race for governor is putting Republican Gov. Scott Walker on the defensive about his record on education, roads and health care, while his Democratic challenger faces accusations he mismanaged his duties as the state schools chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY laid to rest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/week-bipartisan-tribute-mccain-laid-rest-213954718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nearly weeklong celebration of the life of US senator John McCain -- war hero, maverick, two-time presidential candidate and outspoken critic of Donald Trump -- came to a solemn and subdued end on Sunday as he was laid to rest at the US Naval Academy in Annapolis, Maryland. McCain, who died August</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian city remembers Jews on Holocaust anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ukrainian-city-honors-jews-holocaust-anniversary-094027226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — The Ukrainian city of Lviv, once a major center of Jewish life in Eastern Europe, is commemorating the 75th anniversary of the annihilation of the city's Jewish population by Nazi Germany and honoring those working today to preserve what they can of that vanished world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aretha Franklin funeral eulogy slammed; Pastor stands firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pastor-stands-firm-aretha-franklins-funeral-criticism-165138203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — A fiery, old-school pastor who is under fire for saying black America is losing "its soul" at Aretha Franklin's funeral stands firm by his words with the hope critics can understand his perspective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO HAS A DREAM</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/orourke-bets-national-attention-lifts-him-texas-race-151300471--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If elections were decided by viral videos and fawning media profiles, Democrat Beto O'Rourke would win Texas' Senate race in a landslide. National magazines are suggesting he could be a Democratic vice-presidential pick in 2020 — or even a White House contender, ala a young Barack Obama. Sure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard did not consider Warren as Native American...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2018/09/01/did-claiming-native-american-heritage-actually-help-elizabeth-warren-get-ahead-but-complicated/wUZZcrKKEOUv5Spnb7IO0K/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exhaustive review of newly released records and interviews with dozens of faculty members bolsters Warren’s assertion that her claim to Native American heritage did not help her win jobs at prestigious law schools, even though there is evidence Harvard took advantage of it after she was hired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW STREAMING:  A Renaissance for Documentaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-renaissance-for-documentaries-1535895000 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer sleepers like “RBG,” “Won’t You Be My Neighbor” and “Three Identical Strangers” have many filmmakers saying there’s never been a better time to make documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's double trouble: Political heat from Trump and left...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/sep/02/big-techs-double-trouble-bipartisan-criticism-may-signal-a-reckoning-ahead </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s timing of attacks on Google, Facebook and Twitter could not have been better, as the three come under scrutiny in hearings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women cheer as man-free music festival kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/florida-s-toxic-red-tide-stretches-residents-report-health-problems-n905336'&gt;Florida residents report health problems as toxic red tide stretches on...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Mueller subpoena president? Move carries risks for both sides...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/404598-will-mueller-subpoena-trump-move-carries-risks-for-both-sides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The months-long dance between President Trump’s lawyers and Robert Mueller over a voluntary presidential interview has yet to bear fruit, raising the question of whether the special counsel will subpoena the preside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster drills held across Japan to prepare for massive quake...</title>
      <link>http://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0004702766 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;the-japan-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishops Divided...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-bishops-are-divided-in-a-way-rarely-seen-in-public-1535893201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crisis engulfing the Catholic Church has exposed deep rifts in the U.S. church. The latest trigger is a letter by an archbishop accusing Catholic officials, including Pope Francis, of covering up sexual abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director flaunts 'Weinstein Is Innocent' T-shirt on Venice... </title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/italian-director-flaunts-weinstein-is-innocent-shirt-on-venice-film-festival-red-carpet </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Italian filmmaker Luciano Silighini Garagnani displayed the disgusting shirt for all to see at the red carpet premiere of ‘Suspiria’ on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABBAS: TRUMP OFFERED US PEACE PLAN BASED ON CONFEDERATION WITH JORDAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Abbas-Trump-offered-us-peace-plan-based-on-confederation-with-Jordan-566330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I want a three-party confederation with Jordan and Israel and I am asking Israel to accept such a proposal," Abbas was quoted as saying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis urges action -- on plastic...</title>
      <link>https://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2018/09/pope_franciss_plastic_emergency.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.americanthinker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church is in the middle of a massive pedophilia, pederasty and coverup crisis. And now the pope tells us plastic trash in the ocean is the 'emergency.' Somehow, we're the bad guys again...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS tries to distance themselves for Charlie Rose...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/cbs-news-charlie-rose-sexual-harassment-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Truly Juvenile'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/rogerlsimon/trump-bash-at-mccain-franklin-funerals-truly-juvenile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Bash at McCain/Franklin Funerals Truly Juvenile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican Whistleblower Begs Journalists to Investigate Vatican's 'Cache of Documents'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/vigano-to-journalists-investigate-vaticans-cache-of-documents-showing-clerical-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still in hiding, Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò checks in with an Italian journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls grow for 'extraordinary synod'... </title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/vatican/2018/09/02/calls-grow-for-extraordinary-synod-in-response-to-abuse-crisis/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cruxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is an “extraordinary synod” a key piece to the puzzle for finding lasting solutions to the clerical abuse crisis which has engulfed the Church for the past generation?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
