<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden DOJ Will Keep Defending Trump in Jean Carroll Rape Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/biden-doj-will-keep-defending-trump-on-rape-defamation-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump used the Justice Department to defend him in a defamation case that accuses him of rape, and the Biden administration will continue defending him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MINISTER OF CHAOS:  Boris Johnson knows exactly what he's doing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/07/boris-johnson-minister-of-chaos/619010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson knows exactly what he’s doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gates's Epic Divorce Saga Enters Next Phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/bill-and-melinda-gates-divorce-saga-next-phase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blowup of a billionaire duo’s 27-year marriage was always going to be rife with drama. Now come the private investigators, rumors of affairs, and former employees chafing at NDAs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDIO:  Phone call reveals how Giuliani pressured Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/rudy-giuliani-ukraine-call-investigate-biden/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never-before-heard audio, obtained exclusively by CNN, shows how former President Donald Trump's longtime adviser Rudy Giuliani relentlessly pressured and coaxed the Ukrainian government in 2019 to investigate baseless conspiracies about then-candidate Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX turned down Gaetz for a job...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607194243-43225</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CONGRESS/GAETZ (PIX):Newsmax turned down embattled Republican Matt Gaetz for a job -spokesperson</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy chief cites risk of cyberattacks crippling power grid...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/energy-chief-cites-risk-cyberattacks-crippling-power-grid-78117554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Energy Secretary Jennifer Granholm is urging more public-private cooperation on cyber defenses, and she says U.S. adversaries already are capable of using cyber intrusions to shut down the power grid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How am I losing to a mental retard?'</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/trumps-deranged-theory-might-have-helped-him-lose-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president was obsessed with the idea that Democrats would strip the primary win from Joe Biden and nominate Hillary Clinton or Michelle Obama instead, reporter Michael Bender writes in an upcoming book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome Gets First Pizza Vending Machine. Will Romans Bite?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/07/rome-gets-its-first-pizza-vending-machine-will-romans-bite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME — Romans eat pizza all the time. They have pizza a taglio, cut with scissors to the desired size</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full volume: White House briefing room back to crammed again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-voting-rights-government-and-politics-08fc7329fe679b5c52bf47f49338d353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House briefing room on Monday might have been a fire marshal's nightmare. For the first time in 449 days, reporters could cram into every seat for the daily briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want To Have Sex With A Celeb? Sign An NDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/hallielieberman/celebrity-gossip-sex-scandal-ndas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I thought [the NDA] was really creepy. If he's asking for that, like how much more weird could it get?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Mom and Hornet's Nest...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/amy-chua-jed-rubenfeld-yale-law.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two decades, Amy Chua and Jed Rubenfeld were Yale Law power brokers. A new generation wants to see them exiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality TV news could be casualty of streaming wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/op-ed-quality-tv-news-could-be-a-casualty-of-the-streaming-wars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Rogers, the first president of NBC Cable, lays out the quandary for the TV news business in light of cord-cutting and increased competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK warns of inflation 'time bomb'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/07/deutsche-bank-warns-of-global-time-bomb-coming-due-to-rising-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation may look like it will go away but is more likely to persist and lead to a crisis in the years ahead, according to Deutsche Bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone refuels fighter jet in midair for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/boeing-drone-refuels-us-navy-fighter-jet-midair-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy F/A-18 Super Hornet and an unmanned aircraft were connected by a hose as the drone transferred jet fuel to the aircraft in the skies over the Midwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to Be Covered by Global Tax Deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report-international/amazon-set-to-be-covered-by-global-tax-deal-despite-thin-margins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global policy makers are crafting their international tax plan to make sure Amazon.com Inc. is included, even though the U.S. company’s profit margin is below the 10% proposed threshold that would give other countries rights to collect revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big win for Merkel's party confounds pundits, pollsters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/the-strategic-vote-in-saxony-anhalt-big-win-for-merkel-cdu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor’s CDU romped home in state of Saxony-Anhalt despite polls suggesting close race with far right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Turning Water-Scarcity Crisis into Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/06/china-is-turning-its-water-scarcity-crisis-into-a-weapon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antagonizing neighbors, imposing top-down solutions, and not actually solving the underlying problem — as China in other areas, so with water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise line reverses course on requiring jabs for passengers...</title>
      <link>https://local12.com/news/coronavirus/one-cruise-line-has-already-reversed-course-on-requiring-vaccinations-for-passengers-royal-caribbean-ron-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;local12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (CNN/CNN Newsource/WKRC) - The cruise industry is getting ready to set sail once again but a political storm brewing on land &amp;ndash; one between Florida Governor Ron DeSantis and the Centers for Disease Control &amp;ndash; suggests it will be anything but smooth sailing. Right now, most cruise lines are advertising new summer sailings with vaccination requirements. But Royal Caribbean abruptly changed course on Friday. Only its ships departing from Seattle and the Bahamas on or before Aug.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian neo-Nazis plotted to bomb NATO base...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/italian-neo-nazis-were-plotting-to-bomb-nato-base-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carabinieri raided the homes of 12 alleged members of an extremist group on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Steps up Efforts to Sow Discord Inside USA...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6071615/iran-disinformation-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian state actors are intensifying their disinformation campaign on social media to spread discord and anti-Semitic tropes inside the U.S., two U.S. intelligence officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabbed in park hours before announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-stabbed-in-central-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed on the east side of Central Park late Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY MASK WARS MAY NEVER END...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-the-mask-culture-wars-may-never-end-163722944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks have been divisive from the start, and even though the pandemic appears to be nearing its end in much of the United States, mask-related divisions remain as wide as ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT REOPENING SHOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/new-york-city-pplans-a-central-park-mega-concert-to-celebrate-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lineup hasn't been announced for the Aug. 21 event, but producer Clive Davis, who has worked with numerous big names, says he's aiming for eight "iconic" stars for the event, which will be televised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planned Parenthood loses lawsuit over Texas 'Sanctuary City for the Unborn'...</title>
      <link>https://thetexan.news/planned-parenthood-lawsuit-against-lubbock-abortion-ban-dismissed-by-u-s-district-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thetexan.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Plaintiffs admit that this Court cannot force the city to revoke or amend its ordinance," Judge Hendrix wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious video...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/07/suspicious-floyd-mayweather-logan-paul-video-emerges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exhibition boxing match between Logan Paul and Floyd Mayweather on Sunday night was a farce for many reasons – but a video clip from the fight suggests it may have gone as far as to be fixed. W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and O'Reilly to embark on MAGA Arena Tour... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/7/donald-trump-conduct-history-tour-his-presidency-t/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump announced Monday that he will go on a “history tour” to discuss his presidency for paying customers at arenas in Florida and Texas in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAS HE WEARING A DIAPER?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3030920/americans-convinced-donald-trump-diaper-bulge-north-carolina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE were speculating online that former president Donald Trump was wearing a diaper after they spotted a bulge in his suit trousers during his speech to Republicans in North Carolina. Trump addr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHENEY: Republicans Voted Against Impeaching Out of Fear For Personal Safety...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/liz-cheney-gop-members-of-congress-told-her-they-voted-not-to-impeach-trump-due-to-personal-security-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney revealed to David Axelrod that multiple GOP members of Congress told her they did not vote to impeach Trump due to concerns about their safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Last Time He'll Step In Ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/boxing/news/floyd-mayweather-vs-logan-paul-fight-results-highlights-money-impresses-as-exhibition-goes-the-distance/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retired pound-for-pound great wasn't able to finish his much larger opponent, but he was crisp throughout the eight-round affair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves Alzheimer's drug despite 'lack of evidence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fda-alzheimers-drug-biogen-2a729516-4c7e-46f1-8d1f-a3e716a7e13e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA ignored the advice of its independent expert panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury at Mo'Nique After She Slams Black Women for Wearing 'Bonnets and Slippers' in Public...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/06/04/monique-unapologetic-for-comments-about-black-women-and-bonnets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mo'Nique says she's "unapologetic" for an Instagram post telling Black women to fix themselves up before they go out in public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico President's Grip on Congress Slips, Showing Limits of His Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/07/mexico-presidents-grip-on-congress-slips-showing-limits-of-his-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY — Mexico’s leftist ruling coalition was on track to lose its absolute majority in Congress following midterm elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes won't hear challenge to male-only military draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/supreme-court-military-draft/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday declined to hear a constitutional challenge to the male-only registration requirement for the draft filed by a group called the National Coalition for Men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels says attorney in contact with prosecutors investigating Trump Org...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/557110-stormy-daniels-my-attorney-is-in-contact-with-new-york-investigators-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels says her lawyer has been in touch with prosecutors in New York City who are investigating former President Trump's company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticks on 'quest' for blood at CA beaches. Lyme disease rising risk?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ticks-quest-blood-californias-beaches-120016167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyme disease-carrying ticks usually found in woodlands and fields are spreading along California's beaches, carried by an unknown host.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative talk host once backed election recount. Now warning Republicans against it...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/conservative-talk-radio-host-once-130014093.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Broomhead, a talk radio host in Phoenix, used to support a local audit of the 2020 election. Now he's urging fellow Republicans to reconsider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jails emptied in pandemic. Should they stay that way?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-5f212e27598df815243ef90a7aea4dc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t long after Matthew Reed shoplifted a $63 set of sheets from a Target in upstate New York that the coronavirus pandemic brought the world to a standstill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul v Mayweather ends in boos...</title>
      <link>hhttps://www.msn.com/en-gb/sport/boxing/logan-paul-v-floyd-mayweather-ends-in-boos-as-each-fighter-makes-millions/ar-AAKM7UX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans have 'untapped' ability to regenerate body parts, scientists claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9660023/Humans-untapped-ability-regenerate-body-parts-just-like-salamanders-scientists-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studying axolotls helped experts from MDI Biological Laboratory in Bar Harbor, Maine, to conclude humans have an 'untapped' ability to regenerate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON off hook AGAIN?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/06/global-g7-deal-may-let-amazon-off-hook-on-tax-say-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: communique from ministers suggests deal only applies to ‘profit exceeding a 10% margin’, which could rule out Amazon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan fury at Floyd fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/boxing/article-9659389/Furious-boxing-fans-claim-Logan-Pauls-exhibition-bout-against-Floyd-Mayweather-FIXED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayweather dominated the contest at the Hard Rock Stadium in Miami but was surprisingly unable to stop Paul, with the rookie surviving the full eight rounds of their exhibition bout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G7 historic deal on global tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/05/g-7-nations-reach-historic-deal-on-global-tax-reform.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most powerful economies have been at odds over taxation for some time. The goal is to make sure companies are paying taxes to the proper regions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation of seabirds wiped out by drone. Now, scientists fear for future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/generation-seabirds-wiped-drone-o-110013203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 3,000 elegant terns fled the Bolsa Chica Ecological Reserve after the May 12 crash, in the largest egg abandonment scientists who work there can recall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to change ad practices in landmark antitrust deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607103602-q5x39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-GOOGLE/ANTITRUST (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Google to change global advertising practices in landmark antitrust deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-tax-reform-technology-government-and-politics-business-12736e0426f0898a1a3bc187e3c4dfc1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The Group of Seven wealthy democracies agreed Saturday to support a global minimum corporate tax of at least 15% to deter multinational companies from avoiding taxes by stashing profits in low-rate countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gluten-Free Generation: Children With Celiac Disease Doubles in 25 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gluten-free-children-celiac-disaese-doubled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with celiac disease produce antibodies to gluten, a protein found in wheat, barley and rye, ingredients which are commonly used to make a variety of tasty foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital patient dies after security guard performs surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210607-hospital-patient-dies-after-security-guard-performs-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospital patient dies after security guard performs surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president keeps Congress but loses shine in mid-term vote...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210607061347-y28qh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-ELECTION/ (PIX, TV):Mexican president keeps Congress but loses shine in mid-term vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Turkish mafia boss dishes dirt, becomes YOUTUBE phenomenon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-health-coronavirus-pandemic-6868c1563a1152712bd2b2191445da95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — From alleged drug trafficking and a murder cover-up to weapons transfers to Islamic militants, a convicted crime ringleader has been dishing the dirt on members of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s ruling party through a series of tell-all videos that have captivated the nation and turned him into an unlikely social media phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sedition Hunters' Turn Capitol Insurrection Into Ultimate Online Manhunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/features/2021-capitol-riot-sedition-hunters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amateur sleuths have turned the Washington D.C. insurrection on Jan. 6 into the ultimate online manhunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul v Mayweather ends in boos...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jun/07/logan-paul-vs-floyd-mayweather-boxing-fight-result-earnings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight between one of the greatest boxers in history and one of the best YouTube personalities in his family ended in predictable fashion</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
