<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Global Tax Overhaul Gains Steam as G20 Backs New Levies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/562309-g-20-finance-heads-endorse-global-tax-overhaul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finance officials in the Group of 20 (G-20) on Saturday endorsed “key components” of a framework for an international tax overhaul that is a top priority of the Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel preparing for civil war in West Bank?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/561845-is-israel-preparing-for-the-inevitable-civil-war-in-the-west-bank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International attention is focused on fighting in Gaza, but Hamas is looking ahead to opportunities to take over the West Bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On This Farm, Cows Are Coequals...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/10/on-this-german-farm-cows-are-in-charge-or-at-least-coequals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUTJADINGEN, Germany — Tom will lay his head in the lap of anyone who sits down to rub his neck,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers deplaned...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3256589/fort-lauderdale-airport-evacuated-passengers-deplaned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT Lauderdale Airport is being evacuated and passengers told to deplane over a “security investigation” amid “bomb threat” fears. Areas of Terminals 2 and 3 at Fort Lauder…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/fl-ne-ftl-airport-terminal-evacuated-20210710-covfs3n7pjavvaqrqi24hinhh4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A security investigation has caused the evacuation of Terminals 2 and 3 at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport, officials said Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Terminals at Fort-Lauderdale-Hollywood Airport evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/local/broward/officials-evacuate-terminals-at-fort-lauderdale-hollywood-intl-airport-as-they-investigate-security-related-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE-HOLLYWOOD INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT, FLA. (WSVN) - Officials have evacuated terminals at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport as they investigate a security-related incident.Portions of Terminals 2...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod Waters Getting Very, Very Sharky...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/07/new-way-prevent-great-white-shark-attacks/619405/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are toying with a new option to prevent great-white-shark attacks: predicting when they might strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arms Race for Weather Lovers Has Begun...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/07/fox-news-weather-channel/619408/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New streaming services from Fox and the Weather Channel are betting big on the idea that an armchair meteorologist lives inside each of us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Exercising Twice A Week For 10 Mins Slashes Alzheimer's Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/exercise-10-minutes-twice-week-prevents-alzheimers-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with memory issues could prevent the onset of Alzheimer's disease by exercising more than once a week, suggests a recent study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking heart and bank: Romance scammers thriving...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/07/10/in-focus-how-dating-scammers-are-thriving-during-the-pandemic-14801217/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I actually said to him that he sounded like a scammer because he’d asked for money and his reply was, "Do you actually hear yourself right now!"'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: The Ascension of Bernie Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/10/the-ascension-of-bernie-sanders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURLINGTON, Vt. — I want to talk to Bernie about Balenciaga. And Britney. And Dua Lipa, Sha’Carri Richardson and Joe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tears, politics, money: School boards become battle zones...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-school-boards-e41350b7d9e3662d279c2dad287f7009</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAPID CITY, S.D. (AP) — Local school boards around the country are increasingly becoming cauldrons of anger and political division, boiling with disputes over such issues as COVID-19 mask rules, the treatment of transgender students and how to teach the history of racism and slavery in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Marijuana Martyr' fought 40-year sentence for selling weed. Now he can legally smoke joint...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/virginia-s-marijuana-martyr-fought-a-40-year-sentence-for-selling-pot-now-he-can-legally-smoke-a-joint/ar-AALZHcA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1974, Roger T. Davis was sentenced to 40 years in prison for marijuana possession and intent to sell – a case that went all the way to the Supreme Court and transformed Davis into Virginia’s Marijuana Martyr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA CASES RISING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-40e168838274a8908ebccedc4822c0b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. (AP) — Florida health officials reported an increase in COVID-19 cases and a higher positive test rate over the past week. The number of virus cases in Florida rose by about 8,000 compared with the week before, for a total of 23,747 new cases, the state Department of Health reported Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review closes courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-health-courts-miami-f2934f1febdb5e82eabe3be2bac0b026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The Miami-Dade County Courthouse will begin undergoing repairs immediately after a review, prompted by the deadly collapse of a nearby condominium building, found that safety concerns exist within the courthouse, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Sees China Offensive Space Tech 'On the March'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/pentagon-sees-china-e2-80-99s-offensive-space-technology-e2-80-98on-the-march-e2-80-99/ar-AALZOHh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China is making sizable, long-term investments in weapons designed to jam or destroy satellites as the nation seeks to rapidly narrow the gap in space technology with the U.S., according to the top intelligence official for the Pentagon’s Indo-Pacific command. China is pushing to develop antisatellite weapons with capabilities from “dazzling to jamming, to kinetic kill-from-the-ground, from space -- all that, they’re on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA rebuffs troops request...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210710012601-ou03n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-PRESIDENT/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-U.S rebuffs Haiti troops request after president's assassination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Paid for Montreal Mansion? Senator or People?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/10/who-paid-for-that-mansion-a-senator-or-the-haitian-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTREAL — He is one of the few lawmakers left in Haiti, a close ally of the assassinated president who</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People craving adrenaline fueling 'major increase' in demand for extreme sports...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/people-craving-adrenaline-are-fueling-a-major-increase-in-demand-for-extreme-sports-after-a-year-at-home/ar-AALZyOj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extreme, a leading adventure sports company, told Insider that it's seen a "major increase" in interest for extreme sports around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion hits Tehran on heels of cyberattack on railway grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.israelhayom.com/2021/07/10/explosion-hits-northern-tehran-on-heels-of-cyberattack-on-railway-grid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.israelhayom.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reservoirs drying up...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Reservoirs-are-drying-up-as-consequences-of-the-16304219.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reservoir levels are dropping throughout the West, as the drought tightens its grip on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rent prices soaring as Americans flock back to cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/rent-prices-are-soaring-as-americans-flock-back-to-cities/ar-AALZFye</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large rent increases and bidding wars on rentals are the new norm in some parts of America as re-opening comes with big price hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRANSON TAKES DAREDEVIL ACT TO THE EDGE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/branson-blasts-off-mach-3-to-zero-g-in-a-natty-blue-spacesuit/ar-AALZaEp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Branson plans to fly to the edge of space in his Virgin Galactic rocket plane on Sunday, finally fulfilling a goal he set for himself when the company was founded more than 15 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What CA warning system got wrong - and right - about 6.0 quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/what-shakealert-warning-system-got-wrong-and-right-about-this-weeks-6-0-quake-in/article_3185c037-ea1f-5444-8d0a-a1dc7fdc7727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's new ShakeAlert earthquake warning system got three big things wrong about this week’s Antelope Valley temblor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert E. Lee statue removed in Charlottesville...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/charlottesville-robert-e-lee-statue-removed-2efbc5e13b74e2545a0f6642e2384308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. (AP) — A Confederate monument that helped spark a violent white supremacist rally in Charlottesville, Virginia, has been hoisted off its stone pedestal. Work to remove the statue of Gen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA HOTTEST JUNE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3254400/us-records-hottest-june-ever-heatwaves-another-coming-west/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Western US is preparing for blistering, dangerous heat next week as the heat wave continues that set record high temperatures and left at least 500 dead. Last month earned the title of the hott…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley hits 130&amp;#8457;, within 4 degrees of world record!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/temperatures-in-death-valley-las-vegas-could-tie-records-in-heat-wave/976676</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature soared to 130 degrees on the first day of excessive heat that will grip the world's hottest place, while Las Vegas could tie its all-time record high temperature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING:  APPLE in Early Talks With NFL on Sunday Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/media/apple-early-talks-stream-nfl-sunday-ticket-games-rcna1380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple executives have held preliminary discussions with NFL leadership about acquiring the rights for the league’s Sunday Ticket package for Apple TV+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Top 50 Podcasts in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/here-are-the-top-50-podcasts-in-america-this-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, we take a look at which podcasts are top charted on Spotify and Apple respectively. On Spotify, The Joe Rogan Experience is the top-rated podcast, followed by the Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard, Distractable, Crime Junkie, and Call Her Daddy. Joe Rogan’s massively popular show doesn’t top the charts at Apple — it’s […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 25,000 bees in Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-bee-keeper-removes-25000-bees-from-times-square</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive swarm of bees invaded Times Square earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE?  
Residents Of Miami Beach Condo Towers Forced To Evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/09/evacuated-residents-crestview-towers-north-miami-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the North Miami Beach condo Crestview Towers, who were forced to evacuate over concerns about the building's structural integrity, are being allowed to return to retrieve essential items on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian Nun Drama Wows Critics in Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/paul-verhoevens-lesbian-nun-drama-benedetta-wows-critics-cannes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Verhoeven's lesbian nun drama "Benedetta" just premiered at the 2021 Cannes Film Festival to positive reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trooper uses Heimlich to save driver choking on bag of pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article252679483.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m sorry,” the driver told a trooper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racy Convent Sex...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/lesbian-sex-nuns-movie-paul-verhoeven-benedetta-cannes-1235016161/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Racy sex in a convent? Explicit dreams about Jesus Christ? A coming-of-age lesbian love story? Paul Verhoeven’s “Benedetta” featured all that and more, leaving its premiere audien…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL DELTA CLOSE SCHOOLS?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cdc-pushes-for-school-reopening-amid-concerns-over-delta-variant-184207598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Students benefit from in-person learning, and safely returning to in-person instruction in the fall 2021 is a priority,” says the new guidance issued Friday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Tom Cruise snubbed Scientology?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/15549073/tom-cruise-drifted-away-scientology-mission-impossible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPIRALLING budgets and delays have sparked major woes for studio chiefs as the latest Mission Impossible film continues to grind along painfully slowly. But it’s the major lifestyle changes of its …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security boss fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/09/biden-fires-social-security-boss-a-trump-appointee-who-refused-to-resign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said the Social Security commissioner, Andrew Saul, "undermined and politicized" the agency's benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large explosion heard in Tehran...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/large-explosion-heard-in-tehran-report-673388</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'urban terrorists' planning attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9774361/Haiti-pleads-send-troops-amid-fears-terrorists-planning-attack-infrastracture.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haiti's Minister of Elections Mathias Pierre warned that the masterminds of the assassination could continue their attack by targeting the nation's critical infrastructure in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite CDC Guidance, CA Students Will Still Be Required To Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/09/cdc-fully-vaxed-students-teachers-california-keeping-school-mask-guidance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While new CDC recommendations state that fully vaccinated teachers and students won't need to wear masks in school this upcoming academic year, California students will be keeping their masks on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Quietly Funding Hunt for Alien Megastructures...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbq7z/nasa-is-quietly-funding-a-hunt-for-alien-megastructures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detecting 'technosignatures' such as hypothetical Dyson spheres in space could lead us to extraterrestrial life, and now NASA is funding the search.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Bezos ex-wife 'undemocratic figure -- oligarch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/economy/mackenzie-scott-billionaire-philanthropy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Bill Gates in disgrace, oligarchy's apologists have been pushing Scott as a replacement. But is Jeff Bezos's ex-wife really an improvement?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US military forces to help stabilize country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/haitian-authorities-have-asked-us-military-forces-to-help-stabilize-the-country/ar-AALYt25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haitian officials have asked for help protecting Haiti's port, airport, and gas supply following the assassination of President Jovenel Moïse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers breach Iran rail network, disrupt service...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/severe-disruptions-in-irans-railway-network-cyber-attacks-suspected-673376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trains were delayed by apparent cyberattacks as hackers posted the phone number of the country's supreme leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God Bless Abortions' banner hung on Christ of the Ozarks statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.arkansasonline.com/news/2021/jul/09/god-bless-abortions-banner-hung-overnight-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arkansasonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of protest artists claim they strung a "God Bless Abortions" banner on the Christ of the Ozarks statue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon plunges into darkness amid record power outages...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/world/mena/lebano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORTNITE slammed as players can destroy building 'looking like Islamic holy site'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/fortnite-slammed-players-can-destroy-24485836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage has gone viral of a Fortnite scene where a character carrying a scythe walks around a complex looking like the Great Mosque of Mecca, complete with the Kaaba-like structure in the centre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fault system poses big dangers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/not-san-andreas-fault-system-152407347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sierra Nevada area at the epicenter of Thursday's magnitude 6.0 earthquake is capable of a destructive temblor and is seismically active.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 'optimistic' after pressing Putin to crack down on cyberattacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-optimistic-after-call-pressing-putin-crack-down-russian-based-n1273559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The call came after a group of Russian hackers infected hundreds of organizations around the world over the Fourth of July weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson surrenders on assault warrant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-new-hampshire-marilyn-manson-8eb3bd54c1e3c116e6dc5b4d73bd1e8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Rocker Marilyn Manson surrendered to police in Los Angeles last week in connection with a 2019 arrest warrant out of New Hampshire where he allegedly assaulted a videographer at a concert, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Extreme Heat Wave In West Threatens All-Time Highs; 130s In Death Valley?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/heat-wave-western-states-all-time-highs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the third time since the beginning of June, a life-threatening heat wave is underway in the western U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans living with HIV have same life expectancy as those without...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/longevity/562283-americans-living-with-hiv-have-the-same-life-expectancy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suicide rates, however, remain high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How South is paying price for Europe's 'green' energy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2021/07/us/american-south-biomass-energy-invs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the European Union's drive to curb carbon emissions led to pollution and community disruption in the American South</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What impending rubber 'apocalypse' means for economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/09/what-the-impending-rubber-apocalypse-means-for-the-us-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
