<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STRENGTH: HK PROTESTERS DEFY POLICE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/defiant-hong-kong-protesters-vow-huge-rally-despite-220012829.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sea of democracy activists flooded the streets of Hong Kong Sunday during torrential rain in a peaceful show to city leaders that their movement still pulls wide public support, despite mounting violence and increasingly stark warnings from Beijing. Hundreds of thousands of protesters carrying umbrellas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG HEART TRANSPLANTS HOPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9745464/pig-heart-transplant-human-surgeon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIG hearts could be used for human transplants within just three YEARS, according to the surgeon who performed the first op in Britain 40 years ago. Sir Terence English said his protege from the UK…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv's Kosher Sex store seeks to give intimacy a spiritual revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-the-daughter-of-america-s-rabbi-just-opened-a-sex-shop-and-it-s-kosher-1.7683156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEY'RE BACK!  ISIS claims bombing at Kabul wedding that killed 63...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b5ceb0cfb33d4d73aaaadf5eee19fe9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The suicide bomber stood in the middle of the dancing, clapping crowd as hundreds of Afghan children and adults celebrated a wedding in a joyous release from Kabul's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kudlow dismisses fears of looming recession...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ffff50df5ad479e89156f31ab9d6044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERKELEY HEIGHTS, N.J. (AP) — President Donald Trump's top economic adviser is playing down fears of a looming recession after last week's sharp drop in the financial markets and predicting the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING WAITS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190818153055-vj4yj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONGKONG-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Hong Kong protesters throng streets peacefully in pouring rain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland's ruling party condemns gay pride marches as election nears...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190818134014-q24uh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland's ruling party has used LGBT rights as a key campaign issue, depicting them as a dangerous Western idea that undermines traditional Catholic values</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy to build world's largest robot warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9747088/us-navy-robot-warship-unmanned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Navy wants to build a fleet of ten robot warships over the next five years. The huge ships referred to as Large Unmanned Surface Vehicle (LUSV) would function as scouts for the main battle f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 earthquakes in 5 days hit one Kansas county...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/kansas/article234125492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client says therapist's 'cuddling' session turned sexual...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/17/cuddling-session-massage-therapist-turned-sexual-client-says/2042376001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Phoenix woman's complaint says a "cuddling" session with a massage therapist turned sexual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom Time for Bunker Business, Doomsday Capitalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-boom-time-for-the-bunker-business-and-doomsday-capitalists/ar-AAFL1ND</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purported madam now focus in sex abuse cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e339d24fd74c45d295a8554604d2f435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — She's been called Jeffrey Epstein's madam, the woman who recruited girls for his sexual appetites, and at times his social planner and household organizer in places ranging from New...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRENGTH: HK PROTESTERS DEFY POLICE</title>
      <link>https://scroll.in/latest/934299/hong-kong-tens-of-thousands-defy-police-ban-and-brave-the-rain-to-march-in-a-show-of-strength</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scroll.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for China’s legislature condemned statements from US senators and Congress members supporting the pro-democracy protestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian nuclear plant turns off unit after safety system error...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190818101030-661kv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-NUCLEAR/STATION:Russian nuclear plant turns off unit after safety system error</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left-wing journalist says he was victim of 'premeditated assault'..</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/18/owen-jones-guardian-journalist-says-he-was-victim-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-known left-wing journalist says he was pushed to the ground and kicked in the head in what he described as a “blatant premeditated assault.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Tlaib Pushes Bill Maher Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/rashida-tlaib-suggests-boycott-of-bill-mahers-show-for-hosts-position-on-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Rashida Tlaib, D-Mich., suggested Saturday that viewers boycott comedian Bill Maher’s HBO talk show after he devoted a segment of Friday's program to bashing the anti-Israel Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran changes name of seized tanker in defiance of US warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1167105/iran-oil-tanker-gibraltar-grace-1-name-change-adrian-darya</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEFIANT Iranian shipping chiefs have renamed the Grace 1 supertanker as it prepares to leave Gibraltar despite a US warrant to seize the vessel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Photo of gal pal photoshopped?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7367943/The-tantalising-mystery-Ghislaine-Maxwells-burger-bar-makeover.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conspiracy theorists have leapt on apparent discrepancies in the images of the 57-year-old eating at In-N-Out Burger in Hollywood, pointing to a seemingly photoshopped poster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French police suicide rate climbs; Govt flummoxed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa2ac2c871a349ecbdb98313b644634b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Three riot police officers, a police commander, a police academy teacher — all are among eight French police officers who have killed themselves recently. That makes 64 so far this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked UK memos warn of food, drug shortages in Brexit chaos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1499de77308e4c798a7b4059e61f80f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Secret British government documents have warned of serious disruptions across the country in the event that the U.K. leaves the European Union without a trade deal on Oct. 31,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White nationalist arrested for threatening to shoot up Ohio Jewish center...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/ohio-white-nationalist-anti-semite-arrested-threatening-shoot/story?id=65040200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio man has been arrested for making threats toward a local Jewish community center in New Middletown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NK, China generals huddle in Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/18/north-korea-china-generals-meet-beijing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting came as North Korean leader Kim Jong Un supervised another test-firing of an unspecified new weapon, seen as an attempt to pressure Washington and Seoul over nuclear negotiations and joint military exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore deputy police commissioner, wife robbed at gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/18/daniel-murphy-baltimore-deputy-police-commissioner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say one of Baltimore’s newest deputy police commissioners and his wife were robbed at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In blue Seattle, Trump supporters starting to come out of hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/politics/in-blue-seattle-trump-supporters-are-starting-to-come-out-of-hiding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who used to worry about backlash for supporting Donald Trump are "coming out of the woodwork" here. Trump has more than 1,200 donations from inside the city, and statewide has nearly three times more named donors than the six...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ditch the Switch? Call to Go on Permanent Daylight Saving Time Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcdfw.com/news/national-international/Permanent-Daylight-Saving-Time-550145631.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcdfw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days after our chronically sleep-deprived country “springs forward,” costing us an hour of rest, disoriented Americans face a slightly greater risk of heart attack and stroke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How red light cameras undermine rule of law...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/457790-red-light-cameras-undermine-rule-of-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Eco-warriors' Prince Harry, Meghan under fire for private jet use...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9744378/meghan-markle-prince-harry-private-jet-french-riviera-ibiza/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ECO-WARRIOR royals Harry and Meghan left a huge carbon footprint when they took a private jet to the South of France two days after their flight to Ibiza. The trip to Nice created seven times more …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water cannon trucks on standby as protesters take over streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/politics/article/3022772/anti-government-protesters-hong-kong-flock-victoria-park</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organisers of biggest demonstrations against the extradition bill have been banned from holding associated march, but given all-clear to stage static protest within Victoria Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland 'ground zero' for protests between right, left-wing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/423e0ee1018942a59e218a800b30b59f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Hundreds of far-right protesters and anti-fascist counter-demonstrators swarmed downtown Portland, Oregon, on Saturday for a long-hyped rally that attracted President Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  French waiter 'shot dead over slow sandwich'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/french-waiter-shot-dead-over-slow-sandwich-11788114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a witness, the gunman lost his temper "as his sandwich wasn't prepared quickly enough".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beats replace bombs: Young Iraqis revel at summer festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/beats-replace-bombs-young-iraqis-revel-summer-festival-114622267.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neon red, yellow and white stage lights helped transform the basketball court in the People&amp;#39;s Stadium in central Baghdad into a club for the &amp;quot;Summer Festival&amp;quot;, the first celebration of its kind in the city. Restaurants are again abuzz with families and coffee shops full of young people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG HEART TRANSPLANTS HOPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/08/17/pig-hearts-could-used-human-transplants-within-three-years-gene/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pig hearts adapted for human use could be available to patients within three years, the surgeon who pioneered heart transplantation in the UK has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weapons seized...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/far-right-rally-portland-met-anti-fascist-protesters-n1043646</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump tweeted about the demonstration, saying there is consideration to labeling Antifa an "organization of terror."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland gears for dueling rallies amid fears of violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.kptv.com/news/large-crowds-of-demonstrators-march-in-portland-police-make-multiple/article_19eea86c-c11d-11e9-967f-ef34795aed80.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, OR (KPTV) - Large crowds of demonstrators gathered in Portland on Saturday, as had been expected for weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake evidence so realistic 'innocent people will go to jail'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/deepfake-evidence-realistic-innocent-people-18938712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deepfake content is getting 'really good, really fast' warns Shamir Allibhai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew pictured inside Epstein mansion of depravity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7367511/Prince-Andrew-pictured-inside-paedophile-Jeffrey-Epsteins-63million-mansion-depravity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke was spotted peering around the door of the billionaire's Manhattan home in December 2010 on a day where a procession of young women were seen entering the property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions heat up in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/hong-kong-protests-australia-university-students-one-china-11817492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY: Hundreds of pro-Beijing demonstrators marched through Sydney on Saturday (Aug 17) in response to a growing number of rallies in support of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing robots home eases loneliness... </title>
      <link>https://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0005903089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;the-japan-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Saijo in Ehime Prefecture faces the Seto Inland Sea to the north and Mt. Ishizuchi, the tallest mountain in western Japan, to the south. Here, 87-year-old Setsuko Saeki has lived with a robot for a year in her spacious house at the foot of a mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival rallies as Hong Kong's divisions deepen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rival-rallies-hong-kongs-divisions-deepen-100523296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten weeks of demonstrations have plunged the international finance hub into crisis, with communist-ruled mainland China taking an increasingly hardline tone, including labelling the more violent protester actions "terrorist-like". Democracy activists are billing the weekend rallies as a way</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL KNEELS BEFORE PRESEASON LOSS, RIPS JAY-Z DEAL AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://nationalfootballpost.com/reid-kneels-before-preseason-loss-rips-jay-z-deal-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalfootballpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special treatment in Florida jail was far more lenient than anyone knew...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-jeffrey-epstein-jail-records-release-20190817-qvinwbnpobfb3c7lox7qnzmrni-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At one point in 2009, Epstein was given permission to leave Palm Beach County Jail seven days a week, for up to 16 hours a day — including two hours per day at the Palm Beach mansion where he previously sexually abused dozens of minor girls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's speech at SHELL plant drew thousands of workers paid extra to be there...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/business/powersource/2019/08/16/Trump-speech-union-crowd-Shell-ethane-plant-natural-gas-beaver-county-pennsylvania-attendance-pay-overtime/stories/201908160113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen unions work at the Shell site, the largest construction project in Pennsylvania</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Chips Away at Biden's Strength as One Who Beats Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warren-chips-away-bidens-strength-080000360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden’s strongest selling point -- that he’s the most likely to beat Donald Trump -- is losing some of its edge, as Elizabeth Warren vaults into second place because a growing number of Democrats think she can win the general election.In a new Economist/YouGov poll, 65% of Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-person protests in Moscow for free elections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moscow-set-fresh-protests-month-rallies-021230553.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition activists held one-person protests in Moscow Saturday to demand free elections, as the wave of the Russian capital's larger demonstrations took a breather this weekend. In a move to circumvent restrictions by the authorities, activists took turns to hold up protest signs as such</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To save money, American patients and surgeons meet in Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/to-save-money-american-patients-and-surgeons-meet-in-cancun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patient is from Mississippi. The surgeon is from Wisconsin. They meet in a Mexican resort for knee replacement surgery. Because the care costs so much less than in the U.S, the patient’s health…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Oil Plant Attacked by Drones...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/saudi-oil-plant-attacked-drones-125237255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Drones attacked oil and gas facilities at the Shaybah field in southeast Saudi Arabia but failed to disrupt production, the kingdom’s Oil Minister Khalid Al-Falih said.Saudi Arabian Oil Co., or Aramco as the company is known, extinguished a small fire at a natural gas liquids plant at</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
