<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS KEEP SOARING; MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gains in the stock market came after a better-than-expected reading on jobless claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue Of Jesus Beheaded Outside Church...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/st-charles-chapel-waltham-jesus-statue-beheaded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So we’re hoping that if someone did this intentionally, they can come get help and they won’t do it again to another church."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC pitches free vaccines for tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/broadway-theaters-resume-ticket-sales-for-100-fall-return-but-how-many-will-fill/3039919/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City is getting creative when it comes to vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli tech ensures you keep your distance; attached to clothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/this-israeli-tech-could-prevent-mass-quarantines-using-proximity-scanning-667411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small enough to be attached to clothing, the Canario Pro buzzes to inform wearers that they are within two meters of someone – and tracks them to minimize the need to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis signs Florida election bill into law amid new controversy...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/gop-gov-desantis-signs-florida-election-bill-law/story?id=77530271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis created new controversy around Florida's already controversial new election law Thursday, giving exclusive access to the signing ceremony to Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What lies ahead for Chris Ruddy?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/What-lies-ahead-for-Chris-Ruddy-16156348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night last month at Mar-a-Lago, Chris Ruddy positioned himself in a familiar spot:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Lapid faces daunting path to anti-Netanyahu govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210506-israel-s-lapid-faces-daunting-path-to-anti-netanyahu-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Lapid faces daunting path to anti-Netanyahu govt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media shut out of DeSantis elections bill signing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/552085-media-shut-out-of-desantis-elections-bill-signing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Local reporters were barred on Thursday from witnessing Florida Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Musk Is Actually Going to Do This Mars Thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/05/elon-musk-spacex-starship-launch/618781/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From his private Cape Canaveral, the billionaire is manifesting a world where interplanetary travel feels real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage Coaches Helping Hollywood Take on Powerful Jerks...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-features/rage-coaches-are-helping-hollywood-take-on-powerful-jerks-1234947508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Coach Lacey Leone McLaughlin was advising a leader in the entertainment industry recently who had come up in the business working exhausting hours for relentless bosses. It had been an ag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Sequel Pave Way for Theater Return?</title>
      <link>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2566965/a-quiet-place-part-ii-final-trailer-emily-blunt-john-krasinkis-movie-theater</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cinemablend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The saga of A Quiet Place continues in a fast and loud new trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Hunt for WASH POST Next Top Editor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-hunt-washington-post-next-084946890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastThe Washington Post is in the closing stages of the hunt for its new top editor, and looks set to finalize a decision in the coming weeks.The Daily Beast spoke with seven knowledgeable people inside and outside the paper, including several with direct insight into the selection process. Over the past few weeks, these industry insiders said, a consensus has emerged that the internal favorite to replace long-time executive editor Marty Baron is Post national editor Steve Ginsberg, whose name has been floated as a potential successor in various outlets over the past year. Others believe the job could still go to New York Times assistant managing editor Marc Lacey, who insiders claimed is viewed as the strongest external candidate.Both of those candidates have strong credentials but come with some drawbacks.Ginsberg is broadly well-liked in the Washington Post newsroom, insiders said, at a time when there has been increasingly public tensions between many staffers and the paper’s management. But he is not seen as a major player in the broader media business and selecting Ginsberg, who is white, would buck the trend of powerful news outlets like CBS News, ABC News, MSNBC, and the Los Angeles Times making diverse hires for their top positions.Lacey is a prominent Black journalist held in very high regard at the Times. A member of two Pulitzer Prize-winning teams, the former Times national editor and foreign correspondent would represent the kind of splashy big-name (and diverse) hire that insiders said Post publisher Fred Ryan may be interested in. However, Lacey is further down the managerial line at the Times and, insiders suggested, his hire would potentially irk some editors at the Post who may be viewed as more qualified than him.Other names like interim editor Cameron Barr, National Geographic editor Susan Goldberg, and New York Times deputy managing editor Carolyn Ryan have been floated as potential successors in previous reporting. Media insiders have also noted that the paper’s process around this hiring has been unpredictable and intensely guarded.Neither Ginsberg nor Lacey responded to requests for comment. A Washington Post spokeswoman labeled this story “wild speculation” but declined to address specific parts of the reporting.Inside the Battle to Run CBS NewsSince Baron announced his departure early last year, the Post has cast a wide net in the hunt for his successor. At one point, the search included now-former ESPN executive Kevin Merida, who reportedly removed himself from the race and was named as the Los Angeles Times’ new top editor earlier this week. Multiple people familiar with the situation told The Daily Beast that Post staffers had privately expressed frustration that Merida, who is Black, was not courted more heavily for the job amid an industry-wide push for more diverse leadership.Another name that had been touted for the gig was New York Times media columnist and former BuzzFeed editor-in-chief Ben Smith, though sources said discussions never reached a serious level on either side. (Smith is currently writing a book about digital media in the blogging heyday of the late aughts, The Daily Beast has learned, including accounts from Gawker founder Nick Denton and BuzzFeed CEO Jonah Peretti.)To the chagrin of some staffers, much of the newsroom—including some relatively senior leaders—have been kept in the dark on the hiring process.Multiple people familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast that unlike other major news outlets like ABC News, which put together a group of staffers to find a new network president earlier this year, there has been no official search committee for Baron’s replacement. Insiders at the paper said that Ryan, the publisher, has largely conducted the search himself, with some assistance from Wayne Connell, the Post’s human resources vice president.Ultimately, Ryan’s decision could also have major implications for another newsroom that is also poised to begin its search for a new editor in the coming months. New York Times editor Dean Baquet is set to turn 65 later this year, the age when top Times masthead editors are typically expected to step down. Lacey, who is among the candidates primed to replace Baquet, would almost certainly increase his chances of getting the executive editor job should he turn down a possible offer to run the Post.Meanwhile, Baron has not been involved in his own succession. One person familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast that the former executive editor’s interest in the Post at this point is almost entirely limited to a book he is currently writing about his time at the newspaper’s helm.Earlier this year, the Post’s employee union sent a letter to the publisher seeking some input in the hiring process and noting that members hoped Ryan would hire a new top editor specifically committed to publishing work about underrepresented communities and the local D.C. area, fostering a more positive work environment, and tackling some lingering, thorny questions about social media policies.Ryan said in response that while some of the requests were “consistent with our vision for this position,” he would not agree to hold an employee town hall on the matter. “Given the confidential and sensitive nature of the executive editor search, however, we do not plan to broadly address the search process with employees,” he wrote in a reply email.Washington Post Braces for Top Editor Marty Baron’s RetirementThe next editor will have to gear up for contract negotiations with a larger, more emboldened staff union under the NewsGuild, which represents a number of media unions including ones at The New York Times and The Daily Beast. People with knowledge of the situation told The Daily Beast that the union—which, unlike other newsroom unions, is voluntary, but includes editorial and many non-editorial commercial staff—has increased membership substantially over the past several years from around 30 percent of staff to nearly 60 percent.Selecting Baron’s successor will prove to be one of the biggest decisions Ryan has made since becoming the Post’s publisher in 2014. People familiar with the situation said that Ryan was envious of Baron’s close relationship with the paper’s owner, Jeff Bezos, and tried to edge Baron out of some meetings with the Amazon founder. A Washington Post spokeswoman hit back, calling the allegations “categorically false.”In many ways, the next top editor will inherit an easier job than the one Baron stepped into. Bezos purchased the paper in 2013, providing a financial lifeline that allowed the paper to expand and invest in ambitious projects that have reversed the paper’s fortunes. The size of the newsroom nearly doubled under Baron, boosting web traffic and digital subscriptions, and opening up more diverse revenue streams including a successful content software licensing business.But the next newsroom leader will also have to contend with growing unrest in the newsroom’s ranks about the handling of sensitive newsroom issues. Staff were up in arms earlier this year after the paper’s leadership prohibited reporter Felicia Sonmez from covering stories related to sexual assault, essentially arguing that she was biased because of her own experience as a survivor (the paper reversed the decision after it became public and sparked outrage online).Others were upset about the recent decision to host Republican Sen. Josh Hawley for a live discussion, noting his key role in denying the legitimacy of the 2020 presidential election.That Tuesday afternoon chat became contentious when Hawley complained the paper was trying to “censor, cancel, and silence me here.” But in a now-viral moment, reporter Cat Zakrzewski fired back: “Senator, we’re hosting you here.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raid exposes Giuliani and signals widening criminal search, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/06/rudy-giuliani-doj-raid-trump-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-profile nature of search highlights inquiry’s seriousness and suggests officials may have new Ukraine-related leads to follow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER massive brawl breaks out at Miami Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9547293/Flight-Club-massive-brawl-breaks-Miami-International-Airport-face-mask.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos shared Wednesday shows a man fighting with two women - said to be from Chicago - after one of the women refused to wear a mask. The brawl is said to have begun after they were deplaned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did agents raid home of wrong woman over Jan. 6 riot? Maybe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/riots-technology-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-0a0f555f20c4d942fb9d3a515d391144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — “We’re looking for Nancy Pelosi’s laptop,” FBI agents told Marilyn Hueper after briefly handcuffing her. Hueper shot back: “That still doesn’t explain why you’re in my home...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner, speaking from her plane hangar, says friends fleeing CA because of homeless people...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/caitlyn-jenner-speaking-from-her-plane-hangar-says-friends-are-fleeing-california-because-of-homeless-people/ar-BB1gq4lE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner’s attempt to court social conservatives in her recall-election campaign for California governor has sometimes put her in a tenuous spot, particularly as one of the most visible transgender women in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX series signals racial breakthrough in Italian TV...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/beyonce-knowles-europe-entertainment-race-and-ethnicity-business-638014ca4dcdcd4f8d84f5f33b26c71d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The Netflix series “Zero,” which premiered globally last month, is the first Italian TV production to feature a predominantly Black cast, a bright spot in an otherwise bleak Italian television landscape where the persistent use of racist language and imagery is sparking new protests...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York's Luxury-Rent Rebound Leaves London Homes in Doldrums...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/new-york-s-luxury-rent-rebound-leaves-london-homes-in-doldrums/ar-BB1gpN8j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s luxury-home market is showing early signs of recovery, storming ahead of rival financial hub London and other global cities with a sudden rebound in rental growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand weightlifter set to be first trans Olympian...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210506-new-zealand-weightlifter-set-to-be-first-transgender-olympian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand weightlifter set to be first transgender Olympian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Jet South to Caribbean Beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/where-can-you-fly-right-now-americans-jet-to-caribbean-with-other-places-shut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where Can You Fly Right Now? Americans Jet South to Caribbean Beaches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Vaccine Patent Shock Roils Pharma as Talks Move to WTO...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/u-back-waiver-vaccine-ip-194403661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S.’s sudden support for a waiver of patent protections for Covid-19 vaccines headed to the World Trade Organization, setting the stage for potentially thorny negotiations over sharing the proprietary know-how needed to boost global supplies of the life-saving shots.“In terms of how soon the WTO can deliver -- that literally depends on the WTO members, collectively, being able to deliver,” U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai said in an interview Wednesday. “I am the first one to admit that what we are leaning into is a process that is not going to be easy.”With the European Union and China signaling a willingness to take part in the debate after the Biden administration’s shock announcement, pharmaceutical executives reacted with anger and their stock prices tumbled worldwide.BioNTech SE’s depository receipts dropped as much as 19% in Germany while shares in Pfizer Inc. were down 2.5% in U.S. premarket trading as of 7:10 a.m. in New York, after closing little changed. Together, the companies sell the messenger RNA shot that was one of the first to win regulatory endorsement.“This change in longstanding American policy will not save lives,” said Stephen Ubl, the president and CEO of PhRMA, the biopharma industry’s lobbying group. “This decision does nothing to address the real challenges to getting more shots in arms, including last-mile distribution and limited availability of raw materials.”CureVac NV of Germany, which is developing another mRNA vaccine, fell as much as 17%, while Asian vaccine stocks including Shanghai Fosun Pharmaceutical Group Co. and CanSino Biologics Inc. also slumped.“The EU is ready to discuss any proposal that addresses the crisis in an effective and pragmatic manner,” European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen told a virtual conference in Florence, Italy on Thursday. “And that’s why we are ready to discuss how the U.S. proposal for a waiver on IP protection for Covid vaccines could help achieve that objective.”The U.S. and Europe have been strong supporters of IP protections at the WTO over the years, particularly as a way to enforce problems like Chinese patent infringement. As the pandemic leads to some of the world’s more monumental and lucrative scientific discoveries, defenders of IP rights are warming to exceptions on ethical grounds when it comes to vaccines even though the drug companies argue it’ll do more harm than good.The WTO’s General Council meets again on Thursday, though any final waiver of intellectual-property protections may take weeks to hammer out in the face of opposition from the pharmaceutical industry. Tai added that she sees momentum from WTO Director-General Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala “to take this opportunity and see what is the WTO capable of.”In a statement, Okonjo-Iweala called it the “moral and economic issue of our time.”The Biden administration will encourage other countries to join its position, Tai said. “We are for the waiver at the WTO, we are for what the proponents of the waiver are trying to accomplish, which is better access, more manufacturing capability, more shots in arms,” she said.Drugmakers argue that the plan is ineffective and that few countries have the capacity to produce more vaccines even if they knew the formulas. Also, there’s limited global supply of the materials needed, and building new factories with the necessary technology to produce the vaccines could take years, they say.Nathalie Moll, director general of the European Federation of Pharmaceutical Industries and Associations, said the Biden administration’s decision “puts the hard-won progress in fighting this terrible disease in jeopardy.”“While we wholeheartedly agree with the goal of protecting citizens around the world through vaccines, waiving patents will make winning the fight against the coronavirus even harder,” Moll said.India and South Africa, two nations struggling to contain fresh outbreaks of Covid-19, have been urging WTO members to temporarily suspend rules on IP rights, arguing that it would be the most efficient and equitable way to address vaccine shortages in poor countries.”We will be exercising our convening power at the WTO to bring members together to work towards resolving the different viewpoints to bridge the gap so that the WTO can be relevant, the WTO can be a force for good,” Tai said.The U.S. wasn’t the only country with initial reservations. The EU, U.K., Japan, Switzerland, Brazil and Norway have also resisted earlier proposals. However, supporters of the waiver argue that U.S. leadership on the issue could help sway other holdouts. The timing for approval of the waiver depends on how soon member states can find agreement.Norway’s foreign ministry on Thursday praised the U.S.’s decision to “commit itself to finding a solution that is less far-reaching than the proposal that was originally on the table, and on which there was great disagreement. This could be a limited and targeted measure to avoid patents being a possible bottleneck.”WTO chief Okonjo-Iweala said proponents of the waiver were planning to revise a proposal initially submitted in October 2020 and asked for a meeting open to all WTO members in the second half of May, before the next formal gathering on the issue slated for early June.As the U.S. inoculations advanced and outbreaks diminished in recent weeks, the White House came under pressure from progressive Democrats and public-health advocates to take a stance while India in particular suffers from surging deaths and infections.Tai also met with top executives of vaccine-producing companies and held calls with members of Congress and other stakeholders in civil society and public health. In April, she called on the pharma companies to make sacrifices.“The desperate needs that our people face in the current pandemic provide these companies with an opportunity to be the heroes they claim to be -- and can be,” she said at a virtual conference at the WTO.(Updates markets)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General: China's Africa outreach poses threat from Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-africa-china-business-government-and-politics-24f774a952eaabcb38d2b25380b61a62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The top U.S general for Africa is warning that a growing threat from China may come not just from the waters of the Pacific but from the Atlantic as well...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling Chinese rocket to crash to Earth Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/may/06/chinese-rocket-falling-crash-to-earth-saturday-china-space-station-long-march-5b-us-space-command</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communist party newspaper claims Long March 5B should easily burn up in atmosphere but expert warns pieces will reach Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Being touched by robot makes people happier...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/touched-by-robot-people-happier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are hoping that one day robots may be able to fulfill the roles of therapists, personal trainers, and even life coaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA thought Don would get back on FACEBOOK. Now, they're scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/05/trump-facebook-suspension-gop-485464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s suspension remains in place. And GOP operatives worry what that might mean for him and the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly revealed Mars glacier could support human exploration...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/study-newly-revealed-mars-glacier-160700751.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mars is slowly revealing its secrets, and a new study of its terrain done 170 million miles away here on Earth has unveiled an anomalous glacier on a flat plain, akin to those found in Antarctica — and it could someday support humans. Glaciers and other ice have been confirmed on the Mars since 2008, as NASA chronicled at the time, and had been detected back in the 1970s by the Viking probe. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India sees record deaths, new cases in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-05-india-covid-deaths-cases-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India saw record new jumps in COVID-19 cases and deaths on Thursday, dashing tentative hopes that a catastrophic recent surge that has stretched hospitals to the limit might be easing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic has made some rethink daily shower...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/06/see-fewer-people-take-fewer-showers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin Harper, an administrative assistant at a preschool in Martha’s Vineyard, grew up showering every day. “It’s what you did,”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia, Strained by Pandemic and Economic Hardship, Explodes in Protest...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/05/colombia-strained-by-pandemic-and-economic-hardship-explodes-in-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia — A teenager shot to death after kicking a police officer. A young man bleeding out on the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 years since 1st American in space: Tourists lining up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-lifestyle-travel-apollo-11-moon-landing-business-cbe5e6b34422af6a80ae92fe084981be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — Sixty years after Alan Shepard became the first American in space, everyday people are on the verge of following in his cosmic footsteps. Jeff Bezos’ Blue Origin used Wednesday's anniversary to kick off an auction for a seat on the company's first crew spaceflight — a short Shepard-like hop launched by a rocket named New Shepard...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Trump crosshairs, Cheney says Republicans 'at turning point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-republicans-step-up-push-oust-key-trump-critic-liz-cheney-2021-05-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Representative Liz Cheney warned on Wednesday that her Republican Party is "at a turning point" as it prepares to try to remove her from leadership for rejecting former President Donald Trump's false claims the election was stolen from him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIVES OUT FOR CHENEY</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/06/cheney-wyoming-2022-primary-485508</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's political operation is engaged in recruiting for Liz Cheney's 2022 primary as the House GOP prepares to oust her from leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decries 'Cult of Personality'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/liz-cheney-decries-trump-cult-of-personality-in-washington-post-op-ed-the-republican-party-is-at-a-turning-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WY) defended herself and doubled down on her criticism of President Donald Trump, saying he threatened to do "long-term damage" to the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA hospitalizations lowest since pandemic start...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/health/in-dramatic-shift-california-covid-19-hospitalizations-are-lowest-since-pandemics-start/article_f6b4da1d-808c-5b09-b8ea-4502b18484cd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — In another dramatic sign of how rapidly California is recovering from COVID-19, the state recorded its lowest hospitalization rate since the first few weeks of the pandemic,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors find covid spurs diabetes...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/clash-of-2-pandemics-doctors-find-that-covid-19-spurs-diabetes/article_c9b11da9-069e-58f5-928f-ecdabcf54310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Ziyad Al-Aly’s research team told him how often diabetes appeared to strike COVID-19 survivors, he thought the data must be wrong, so he asked his five colleagues to crunch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls out McCarthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/05/politics/liz-cheney-op-ed-washington-post-gop-turning-point/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new op-ed for The Washington Post, Rep. Liz Cheney says the Republican Party is at a "turning point" and must decide whether to accept or reject Donald Trump's lies about the 2020 election, which she says provoked the violence on January 6 and could provoke violence again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA backs waiving patent protections for vaccines, citing global health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/us-backs-covid-vaccine-intellectual-property-waivers-to-expand-access-to-shots-worldwide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration announced Wednesday that it supports waiving intellectual property protections for Covid-19 vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END? Netanyahu rule threatened...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-f0545951d0b433bc64c1542f9be55eb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — For the past 12 years, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has dominated Israeli politics, vanquishing a stream of challengers as he maintained his tight grip on power. But after a bruising two-year cycle of political deadlock, Netanyahu is facing the toughest challenge of his record-setting rule and could soon find himself pushed into the opposition...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddie Gallagher Now Claims SEALs Intended to Kill Unarmed ISIS Fighter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/eddie-gallagher-now-claims-seals-intended-to-kill-unarmed-isis-fighter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We killed that guy... Our intention was to kill him. Everybody was on board,” he said during a recent podcast interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FBI breaking into corporate computers...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/05/04/the-fbi-is-breaking-into-corporate-computers-to-remove-malicious-code_partner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI’s latest cybersecurity moves bring the government into new territory — inside privately owned computers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada confirms first death linked to ASTRAZENECA vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/canadas-alberta-confirms-first-death-linked-astrazeneca-vaccine-2021-05-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canadian province of Alberta reported its first death of a patient from a rare blood clot condition after receiving the AstraZeneca (AZN.L) COVID-19 vaccine, its chief medical officer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAVRE: Gut tells me Rodgers done with PACKERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/31394130/brett-favre-says-not-optimistic-aaron-rodgers-play-green-bay-packers-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brett Favre said on ESPN Wisconsin radio's Wilde &amp; Tausch on Wednesday that he's not optimistic that Aaron Rodgers and the Packers will be able to work things out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds fine unruly, maskless airplane passengers as violent incidents increase...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/05/politics/unruly-airplane-passengers/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are planning to fine two unmasked and unruly passengers accused of hitting and grabbing flight attendants amid a rash of disruptive and sometimes violent incidents on board planes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA:  Booster shot generates promising response to variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/covid-booster-shot-moderna-says-vaccine-generates-promising-immune-response-against-variants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna said its booster dose increased neutralizing antibody responses against the original virus as well as B.1.351 and P.1 variants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPP Out Of Funds For Most Small Businesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/paycheck-protection-program-out-of-funds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just $8 billion remains in the program, earmarked for companies headed by women or minorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Dem Party Chair Resigns After Calling Tim Scott 'Oreo'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/05/05/texas-democratic-party-leader-resigns-gary-o-connor-sen-tim-scot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I am deeply and sincerely sorry,” Lamar County Democratic Party Chairman Gary O'Connor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Struck, Killed By Drunk Driver -- Just After Leaving AA Meeting!</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/man-hit-killed-drunk-driver-alcoholics-anonymous-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Modesto man devoted to living a better life was hit and killed by an alleged drunk driver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  CDC's Guidance 'Insane'...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/05/04/cdc-summer-camp-guidance-masks-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Masking kids at camp outdoors is simply virtue signaling."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translator denies being person who split up Bill and Melinda Gates...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/05/translator-denies-splitting-up-bill-and-melinda-gates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zhe “Shelly” Wang, who works for the Bill &amp; Melinda Gates Foundation, has denied wild social media rumors that she was involved in their divorce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Prices Up Steeply From Same Time Last Year...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/04/grocery-prices-up-steeply-from-same-time-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your grocery list could be eating away at your budget, without you noticing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC projects 'sharp decline' in summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/cdc-projects-a-surge-in-us-covid-cases-through-may-due-to-bpoint1point1point7-variant-before-a-sharp-decline-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Covid cases are expected to increase this month, hospitalizations and deaths will likely remain low nationally, the U.S. agency said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Seagal gifts Maduro samurai sword...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210505161808-4tulk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-MADURO/SEAGAL (PIX, TV):Venezuela's Maduro receives samurai sword gift from actor Steven Seagal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal staffers offered free yoga class led by Sophie Grégoire Trudeau...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/eyes-roll-as-stressed-liberal-staffers-offered-free-virtual-yoga-class-led-by-sophie-gregoire-trudeau</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In boring Biden era, NYTIMES growth coming from NON-NEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/new-york-times-subscription-gains-non-news-products-0690d5ea-9d7f-4225-97ce-9822200da996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Times now has nearly 8 million paid subscribers — far ahead of even its closest news competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle accused of plagiarizing book...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/05/05/markle-accused-of-plagiarizing-2018-kids-book-but-defended-by-author/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online critics are accusing Meghan Markle of ripping-off of another author with her new children’s book. The author of the original work disagrees that Markle copied the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPID GETS A SHOT...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/rivlin-to-meet-lapid-bennett-as-consultations-begin-667245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yamina leader Naftali Bennett: Wide emergency government to be formed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Amy Coney Barrett has changed Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/05/politics/barrett-supreme-court-kavanaugh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Amy Coney Barrett has aligned most often with Clarence Thomas and Neil Gorsuch in her first months on the bench. Yet as the court enters the final weeks of its annual session, Barrett is also separating herself from brethren on the right with a lower key, attention-deflecting manner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Told Their Therapists Everything. Hackers Leaked It All...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/vastaamo-psychotherapy-patients-hack-data-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mental health startup built its business on easy-to-use technology. Patients joined in droves. Then came a catastrophic data breach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  'Proud Boys' saw wave of contributions from Chinese before Capitol attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/05/04/proud-boys-chinese-americans-community-support-donations/7343111002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Proud Boys enjoy support from some Chinese Americans and the broader Chinese diaspora, attracted by the group's claim to be fighting communism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The art detective who hunts stolen Picassos and lost Matisses...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2021/may/05/pitbulls-art-detective-christopher-marinello-mobsters-stolen-picassos-lost-matisses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Marinello has spent three decades finding missing masterpieces, recovering half a billion dollars’ worth of art. He talks about threats from mobsters, tricky negotiations – and bungling thieves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Iran releases horrifying video of U.S. Capitol blowing up...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2824464/iran-video-blow-up-us-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HORRIFYING fake footage of the US Capitol being blown up was released by Iran as Joe Biden comes under increasing pressure to take action from a GOP senator. The video leaked on state-controlled Ir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre new trend of eating ROTTEN meat to get high...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/2827943/trend-eat-raw-rotten-meat-get-high-explosive-incontinence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE are forcing down chunks of rotten, raw meat in a bid to get high in the latest bizarre social media trend. Coronavirus lockdowns have driven some people to attempt strange challenges but doc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sleeping 6-7 Hours Best For Heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sleeping-six-to-seven-hours-best-for-heart-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that people who manage less -- or more -- than 6-7 hours of sleep each night are more prone to cardiovascular disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area market so hot houses selling $1M over asking price...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/realestate/article/2021-05-east-bay-real-estate-overbids-hot-market-16151227.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Especially in the East Bay, this type of sale isn’t an anomaly anymore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN opens up ticket sales for suborbital sightseeing trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/blue-origin-begin-space-tourism-ticket-sales-wednesday-2021-05-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin, billionaire Jeff Bezos' rocket company, said on Wednesday it is targeting July 20 for its first suborbital sightseeing trip on its New Shepard spacecraft, a landmark moment in a competition to usher in a new era of private commercial space travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STICKS TO BELIEFS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/05/cheney-isnt-fighting-mccarthy-push-to-replace-her-in-leadership-485430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian Caught Up In Ancient Roman Statue Smuggling Row...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/kim-kardashian-caught-up-in-ancient-roman-statue-smuggling-row-2428113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Kardashian found herself caught up in an unlikely international art smuggling row Tuesday involving an ancient Roman sculpture that was imported to California under her name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN HERD?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/herd-immunity-us-san-francisco-offers-reasons-optimism-rcna815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco's low case numbers and high vaccination rates are signaling to experts that the city may have already reached herd immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another top Republican backs ousting...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/another-top-republican-publicly-backs-ousting-cheney-gop-conference-chair-n1266376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Whip Steve Scalise is calling for New York Rep. Elise Stefanik to take over the leadership role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He faked virus certificate to fly to Argentina, officials say. He was infected all along...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-faked-a-coronavirus-certificate-to-fly-to-argentina-officials-say-he-was-infected-all-along/ar-BB1gnGg4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santiago Solans Portillo had traveled to Miami to get vaccinated, but likely exposed more than 200 people to the virus on his flight back to Buenos Aires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Tribe to Buy Palms Casino in Vegas for $650 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/california-tribe-to-buy-palms-casino-in-vegas-for-24650-million/ar-BB1gm4AI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Manuel Band of Mission Indians agreed to buy the Palms Casino Resort in Las Vegas from Red Rock Resorts Inc. for $650 million, the biggest purchase by a Native-Indian tribe in the U.S. gambling capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy trashes her on hot mic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/listen-kevin-mccarthy-caught-on-fox-news-hot-mic-bashing-liz-cheney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McCarthy — prior to hitting the air on Fox News Tuesday morning — spoke candidly on his feelings about Cheney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of expensive koi mysteriously die in Florida neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/05/01/mysterious-situation-in-coconut-grove-as-thousands-of-expensive-fish-suddenly-die-outside-several-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The common denominator is that all the ponds source their water from wells connected to the aquifer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind WARNER BROS. Search for Black Superman...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/black-superman-ta-nehisi-coates-warner-bros-movie-1234947599/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While promoting his Amazon Prime film Tom Clancy’s Without Remorse in late April, Michael B. Jordan put a Kryptonite pin in any rumors that he might suit up as Warner Bros.’ next Superman. “I’m fla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She told followers she was 'Mother God.' Her mummified body was found wrapped in Christmas lights...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/She-told-followers-she-was-Mother-God-Her-16152659.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amy Carlson's body was mummified in a sleeping bag and wrapped in a cloth adorned with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM fuels rise in black-market sales of maids into Persian Gulf servitude...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Instagram-fuels-rise-in-black-market-sales-of-16152644.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates - The advent of Instagram in recent years has helped create...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210505-israel-president-eyes-new-candidate-to-form-government-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel president eyes new candidate to form government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana paying bonuses to people willing to work...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/montana-to-end-extra-unemployment-pay-due-to-worker-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana, facing a shortage of workers, will now give bonuses to people who start working instead of extra unemployment pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite green light, Broadway to stay dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/despite-green-light-broadway-to-remain-dark-until-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor is giving the go-ahead to performance venues to reopen later this month. But the reality is that the lights won't go up on Broadway until the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pentagon tracking out of control Chinese rocket expected to crash into Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/the-pentagon-is-tracking-an-out-of-control-chinese-rocket-expected-to-crash-into-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese Long March 5B rocket is expected to reenter Earth's atmosphere around May 8. No one knows where. But don't panic!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELETON recalling all treadmills after injuries, death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/peloton-recalling-all-treadmills-after-reports-of-injuries-one-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a major reversal, Peloton announced Wednesday voluntary recalls of both its Tread+ and Tread treadmill machines over safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK: TRUMP STAYS BANNED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/facebook-will-keep-trump-ban-in-place.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's oversight board effectively punted the decision on the length of the suspension back to the social media company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butt Implants Up, Botox and Hair Transplants Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-05/cosmetic-surgery-2020-data-butt-implants-up-botox-and-hair-transplants-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair transplants, not so much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious brain disease baffles doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-56910393</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of people in New Brunswick are showing symptoms of the devastating new condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia raided across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/ndrangheta-mafia-raided-across-europe-01620204012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy led a Europe-wide police operation Wednesday against the 'Ndrangheta organised crime group, seizing cocaine and millions of euros in assets in early morning raids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untold Story of How Bezos Beat Tabloids...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-4ecfbfe6-4640-428e-9c78-e9a609b4f76b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Stone has all the details in his new book "Amazon Unbound."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to more babies than expected -- 9...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/africa/2021/05/a-woman-from-mali-gives-birth-to-9-babies-in-morocco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Malian woman has given birth to nine babies after only expecting seven, Mali’s Ministry of Health said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani allies press Trump to help foot his growing legal bills...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/551787-giuliani-allies-press-trump-team-to-help-foot-his-growing-legal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani’s allies are reportedly pressing former President Trump’s team to help the embattled lawyer pay for his growing legal bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Global tax deal 'urgently needed'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/551793-imf-warns-global-tax-deal-urgently-needed-to-avoid-potential-trade-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The International Monetary Fund (IMF) warned Tuesday that a global tax deal is “urgently needed” in order to avoid a potential trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure increases for USA to send covid vaccines to Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/551810-pressure-increases-for-us-to-send-vaccines-to-latin-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising rates of COVID-19 infections in Brazil and other countries in Latin America are posing a risk to the U.S. in its own battle to overcome the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney defends: She 'refuses to lie'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/551761-romney-defends-cheney-she-refuses-to-lie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Mitt Romney (R-Utah) is coming to the defense of Rep. Liz Cheney (R-Wyo.) amid a high-profile feud with House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) that is sparking fresh questions about her future in GOP leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to flex clemency powers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/551842-biden-set-to-flex-clemency-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House officials are signaling that President Biden is prepared to flex his clemency powers as officials wade through a large backlog of requests behind the scenes, according to advocates with whom the White House has consulted on criminal justice reform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Equity Mess...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/05/02/the-equity-mess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite their professed goals, Democrats' pandemic policies have widened disparities between races, classes, and genders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman missing for 6 months found living in tent in Utah, eating moss and grass...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/04/woman-missing-since-2020-found-living-utah-canyon-eating-grass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who went missing nearly six months ago was found living in a tent in a national forest in Utah, subsisting on a diet including grass and moss -- after a drone that was searching for her crashed nearby, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists see path for virus to invade brain...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-see-path-coronavirus-invade-130011296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An up-close view of how the coronavirus infects cells in the brain and spinal cord helps explain the neurological symptoms of some COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA RECALL CIRCUS: 1,000-pound bear and Hollywood-worthy campaign video...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/day-california-recall-1-000-002151477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Republican opponent posed for photos with a bear and another sought to leverage her celebrity status on national television. These events woke up what has so far been a quiet march toward a historic election to recall Gov. Gavin Newsom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chauvin Attorney Files Motion For New Trial On Grounds Of Juror Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/04/derek-chauvins-attorney-files-motion-for-new-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Eric Nelson has filed a motion for a new trial for former Minneapolis police officer Derek Chauvin, who was convicted of murdering George Floyd last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Intensifies With Supply Shortages Multiplying...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inflation-risk-intensifies-supply-shortages-210000287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Discover what’s driving the global economy and what it means for policy makers, businesses, investors and you with The New Economy Daily. Sign up hereSigns of inflation are picking up, with a mounting number of consumer-facing companies warning in recent days that supply shortages and logistical logjams may force them to raise prices.Tight inventories of materials as varied as semiconductors, steel, lumber and cotton are showing up in survey data, with manufacturers in Europe and the U.S. this week flagging record backlogs and higher input prices as they scramble to replenish stockpiles and keep up with accelerating consumer demand.As commodities become increasingly expensive, whether faster inflation proves transitory -- or not -- is the biggest question for policy makers and markets. Rising prices and the potential for a response from central banks topped the list of concerns for money managers surveyed by Bank of America Corp.Many economists and central bankers, from the Federal Reserve on down, maintain that price gains are temporary and will be curbed by forces such as virus worries and unemployment. Investors remain skeptical, with businesses including Nestle SA and Colgate-Palmolive Co. already announcing they’ll need to raise prices.U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, a former Fed chair, entered the debate on Tuesday when she ruffled markets with the observation that rates will likely rise as government spending ramps up. She later clarified she was neither predicting nor recommending an increase.The Bloomberg Commodity Spot Index, which tracks 23 raw materials, has risen to its highest level in almost a decade. That has pushed a gauge of global manufacturing output prices to its highest point since 2009, and U.S. producer prices to levels not seen since 2008, according to data from JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. and IHS Markit. JPMorgan analysts also estimate non-food and energy import prices in the biggest economies rose almost 4% in the first quarter, the most in three years.“Risk clearly leans to the upside in the current environment,” said John Mothersole, pricing and purchasing research director at IHS Markit. “The surge in commodity prices over the past year now guarantees higher goods-price inflation this summer.”The IHS Markit analysis across oil, chemicals, steel, copper, zinc, lumber, pulp and rubber expects the price boosts to fade closer to the end of the year. Meanwhile, strategists at Blackrock Investment Institute wrote Monday that they see U.S. consumer-price increases averaging just under 3% from 2025-2030, though that pace is “still under-priced by markets.”The case for higher-for-longer inflation into 2022 often rests on the trillions of dollars being pumped into infrastructure projects globally in a low-interest rate atmosphere, most notably in the U.S. That has supercharged a rally across raw materials, as major economies recover from the pandemic amid growing signs of shortage across several markets.Some businesses have found they can’t afford to wait for “temporary” increases to pass. That means consumers can expect to deal with higher costs for a range of daily items, including garbage bags and children’s clothes.“Straight price increases will continue to be an important element as we look at the back half of the year,” Colgate-Palmolive Chief Executive Officer Noel Wallace said late last month when the company announced earnings. “I anticipate that you’ll see more price increases across the sector, given the headwinds that everyone has faced in this space.”Higher cotton prices from Chinese producers are pushing clothes-maker Carter’s Inc. to consider how much of the increase it can pass along.“We’re beginning to see signs of inflation in product input costs, particularly those related to fabric,” Chief Executive Officer Michael Casey said on an April 30 earnings call. The company will offer “fewer promotions” this year, he said, amid a return of resilient shoppers buoyed by stimulus payments.Corn, too, is on the growing list of commodities seeing price boosts. Futures surged this week above $7 a bushel for the first time in more than eight years on the Chicago Board of Trade, alongside increases for soybeans and wheat.The underlying materials shortage has spooked Greg Sharenow, who manages a portfolio focused on energy and commodities at Pacific Investment Management Co.The premium on near-term deliveries over future deliveries for commodities tracked by the Bloomberg Commodity Index has jumped to the highest in more than 15 years, signaling immediate physical shortages across different markets, Sharenow said. He sees the price surge this time as more organic, rather than the kind of anticipatory demand seen from 2005 to 2008.Edward Robinson, deputy managing director and chief economist at Singapore’s central bank, said in a speech last week that he’s watching Chinese producer prices closely as an “important upside risk” to his baseline call that inflation should stay in check, helped by labor-market slack.A surge in copper is crippling some Chinese manufacturers, who have idled units, delayed deliveries and even defaulted on bank loans, data from a Shanghai Metals Market survey show. That’s already rippled through the production chain, delaying projects by power grids and property developers.Lumber has been in the spotlight as red-hot housing markets, especially in advanced economies, are driving up costs for the commodity.Fed Chairman Jerome Powell said last week the central bank was watching that market closely, even though he doesn’t currently have financial stability concerns around housing. Still, the sector has been emblematic of the K-shaped recovery, with cost surges pricing out middle-income buyers while homeowners reap gains.Markets have responded more calmly of late to the Fed’s mantra, with bond yields little changed after Powell last week doubled down on his inflation read and still-easy policy stance. The inflation run across so many materials, though, could break that patience, as pressure builds on businesses and officials to ward off price increases for consumers.“One always has to be careful not to overplay a few anecdotes, and project that onto the broader economy,” Douglas Porter, chief economist at BMO Capital Markets, said in a May 1 report. “But as the anecdotes accumulate, they eventually become data.”Porter pointed to a sampling of 10 recent datasets, including U.S. employment costs, Canadian wages and still-soaring shipping costs.“As rising inflation risks suggest,” he said, “when you run things hot, you risk getting burned.”(Updates with additional detail on corn prices in second paragraph after cotton price chart.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Were Promised Socialist Paradise, and Ended Up in 'Hell'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/05/they-were-promised-a-socialist-paradise-and-ended-up-in-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL — On a bright August morning in 1960, after two days of sailing from Japan, hundreds of passengers rushed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury will employ measures to avoid unprecedented default on national debt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-national-debt-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-a95665cfc7fbd8504fc91fdb2a6eb861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Treasury Department says it will employ measures to avoid an unprecedented default on the national debt this summer, but officials say those measures could be exhausted “much more quickly” than normal given the unusual circumstances of the global pandemic...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
