<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar court sentences REUTERS reporters to 7 years in jail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd0f856e7eaa46ffb744d1909c29d9f1/Myanmar-court-sentences-Reuters-reporters-to-7-years-in-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YANGON, Myanmar (AP) — A Myanmar court sentenced two Reuters journalists to seven years in prison Monday for illegal possession of official documents, a ruling met with internatio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day 2040: What Happens When Robots Do All the Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/labor-day-2040-what-happens-when-robots-do-all-the-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Holiday Weekend From Hell: Humans Still Drove Cars and Flew The Planes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian rial hits record low...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180903122646-a680o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-ECONOMY/RIAL (URGENT):Iranian rial hits record low at 128,000 to the dollar- Bonbast website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes High as States Gear Up to Pick Govs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stakes-are-high-as-states-gear-up-to-pick-governors-1535976001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 36 contested races for governor this election year have outsized significance because many of the new crop of state leaders will have some say over the redrawing of legislative and congressional maps in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Strange disappearance' of WIKILEAKS consultant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/strange-disappearance-of-wikileaks-consultant-in-norway/a-45328433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks has raised concern after Arjen Kamphuis, an associate of founder Julian Assange, went missing in Norway. The cybersecurity expert was last seen in northern Norway on August 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right poised for big wins in Sweden election...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180903-far-right-poised-big-wins-sweden-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte apologizes for cursing Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/philippines--duterte-apologises-for-cursing-obama-10679184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM: Philippine leader Rodrigo Duterte has apologised to former US president Barack Obama for calling him a "son of a whore" in 2016, which ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firefighters battle suicidal thoughts after the blaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180903-us-firefighters-battle-suicidal-thoughts-after-blaze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race to save relics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf1a4eff4ae04901afe1264a643d7a27/Firefighters-try-to-save-relics-as-fire-engulfs-Rio-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — A huge fire engulfed Brazil's 200-year-old National Museum in Rio de Janeiro, lighting up the night sky with towering flames as firefighters and museum worke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Struggle Puts Heat on Older White Incumbents...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/09/03/democratic-power-struggle-puts-heat-on-older-white-incumbents#gs.TuS9FA0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Power Struggle Puts Heat on Older White Incumbents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputy shoots man who fired gun after told no tickets available for Ice Cube concert...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/sd-me-shooting-delmar-20180902-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sheriff's deputy shot a man who fired a weapon Sunday outside a gate leading into a scheduled Ice Cube concert at the Del Mar Racetrack. The man's condition wasn't known.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women caned in Malaysia for attempting to have lesbian sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/women-caned-in-malaysia-for-attempting-to-have-lesbian-sex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rare punishment was carried out in a courtroom and witnessed by up to 100 people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Incalculable' loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/fire-engulfs-brazil-national-museum-rio</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Museo Nacional houses artefacts from Egypt, Greco-Roman art and some of the first fossils found in Brazil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresco that survived Pompeii destroyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/huge-fire-engulfs-brazils-200-13184185?5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio’s Museu Nacional houses a collection of more than 20 million items ranging from archaeological findings to historical memorabilia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIO ROCKED...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6125217/Giant-flames-tear-National-Museum-Rio-Janeiro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far nobody has been reported injured during the fire as it began after the museum had closed for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200-year-old National Museum hit by massive fire...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180903001032-p13t9/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-FIRE/MUSEUM:Rio's 200-year old National Museum hit by massive fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired during Del Mar race during televised event...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7161252/del-mar-shooting-horse-race-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOTS were fired at Del Mar race course in California during a live televised competition – as crowds gathered for an Ice Cube concert. Shocking footage caught the moment commentators screame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seoul to check public toilets to tackle 'spy-cam porn' crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/03/seoul-to-check-public-toilets-daily-to-tackle-spy-cam-porn-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move follows protests by record numbers of women calling for more action to tackle rise of voyeurism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Fence Jumper Nabbed...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/secret-service-person-arrested-climbing-white-house-security-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has been arrested for climbing over a White House security barrier Sunday night, according to authorities. Secret Service says the incident happened at around 8:10 p.m. in the area of 15th Street NW and Alexander Hamilton Place. Secret Service a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab-grown brain bits open windows to mind -- and ethical dilemmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/lab-grown-brain-bits-open-windows-to-the-mind--and-a-maze-of-ethical-dilemmas/2018/09/02/9a76efee-a25b-11e8-83d2-70203b8d7b44_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human ‘minibrains’ are far from conscious, but scientists say it’s time to talk about ethics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer attacked by own police dog -- shoots it to escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article217744755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officer Brian Carter of the Columbus, Ohio, police division shot Benzi, his K9 partner, after the Belgian Malinois attacked him during a training session, police say. The dog was later euthanized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Films Make Roaring Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/silent-films-make-roaring-return-with-help-from-younger-audiences-1535907601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The silent-film era peaked almost a century ago and lost steam with the advent of the talkies. But now the films are making a comeback in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lana Del Rey drops Israel appearance after pressure...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/music/la-et-ms-lana-del-rey-postpones-israel-concert-20180902-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop singer Lana Del Rey calls the move a postponement in hopes that one day all fans in the region can attend her shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Nebraska diocese rocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nebraska-catholic-diocese-rocked-old-abuse-allegations-161106949.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than a decade, a conservative Catholic diocese in Nebraska was the only church in the U.S. that refused to participate in annual reviews of sexual misconduct that were a key reform enacted in the wake of the 2002 Boston clergy abuse scandal. As a new wave of abuse scandals rock the Roman Catholic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT07/refresh/AL072018_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/234741_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm watch issued for central Gulf Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/florida-us-gulf-coast-on-alert-for-budding-tropical-depression/70005956</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has gender reassignment surgery to become a woman -- at 81!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7159732/oldest-person-in-britain-to-have-reassignment-surgery-shares-her-joy-at-becoming-a-woman-aged-81-thanks-to-the-nhs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TRANSGENDER woman has spoken of her joy at becoming the oldest person in Britain to have surgery. Ruth Rose, 85, had a reassignment op four years ago after her doctor told her she could be consid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands protest in Russia against plans to hike pension age...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/sep/02/thousands-protest-in-russia-against-plans-to-hike-retirement-age</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has called the reform a financial necessity as Communist party leader brands move ‘cannibalistic’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri's Senate race is nation's top target...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/govt-and-politics/how-big-is-missouri-s-senate-race-it-s-the/article_6513cd7d-0b32-5462-a624-76be5f548d88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chuck Schumer-related PAC is spending heavily for McCaskill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Mayor Eric Garcetti spreads wealth, influence around USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.postbulletin.com/news/politics/la-mayor-eric-garcetti-spreads-wealth-influence-around-the-us/article_3031597a-46de-5da6-bc72-1666566fb59c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Trav Robertson, chairman of the South Carolina Democratic Party, likes to tell people about Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti’s generosity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK FACES AUTUMN CHAOS...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6123641/David-Davis-vows-vote-against-Mays-Chequers-Brexit-plan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two interventions from Michel Barnier and David Davis underline the challenge Mrs May faces in getting any kind of deal based on her Chequers proposals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin's tight governor's race puts Walker on defensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsins-tight-governors-race-puts-walker-defensive-161742018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — Wisconsin's tight race for governor is putting Republican Gov. Scott Walker on the defensive about his record on education, roads and health care, while his Democratic challenger faces accusations he mismanaged his duties as the state schools chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY laid to rest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/week-bipartisan-tribute-mccain-laid-rest-213954718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nearly weeklong celebration of the life of US senator John McCain -- war hero, maverick, two-time presidential candidate and outspoken critic of Donald Trump -- came to a solemn and subdued end on Sunday as he was laid to rest at the US Naval Academy in Annapolis, Maryland. McCain, who died August</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian city remembers Jews on Holocaust anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ukrainian-city-honors-jews-holocaust-anniversary-094027226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LVIV, Ukraine (AP) — The Ukrainian city of Lviv, once a major center of Jewish life in Eastern Europe, is commemorating the 75th anniversary of the annihilation of the city's Jewish population by Nazi Germany and honoring those working today to preserve what they can of that vanished world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aretha Franklin funeral eulogy slammed; Pastor stands firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pastor-stands-firm-aretha-franklins-funeral-criticism-165138203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — A fiery, old-school pastor who is under fire for saying black America is losing "its soul" at Aretha Franklin's funeral stands firm by his words with the hope critics can understand his perspective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO HAS A DREAM</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/orourke-bets-national-attention-lifts-him-texas-race-151300471--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If elections were decided by viral videos and fawning media profiles, Democrat Beto O'Rourke would win Texas' Senate race in a landslide. National magazines are suggesting he could be a Democratic vice-presidential pick in 2020 — or even a White House contender, ala a young Barack Obama. Sure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard did not consider Warren as Native American...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2018/09/01/did-claiming-native-american-heritage-actually-help-elizabeth-warren-get-ahead-but-complicated/wUZZcrKKEOUv5Spnb7IO0K/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exhaustive review of newly released records and interviews with dozens of faculty members bolsters Warren’s assertion that her claim to Native American heritage did not help her win jobs at prestigious law schools, even though there is evidence Harvard took advantage of it after she was hired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW STREAMING:  A Renaissance for Documentaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-renaissance-for-documentaries-1535895000 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer sleepers like “RBG,” “Won’t You Be My Neighbor” and “Three Identical Strangers” have many filmmakers saying there’s never been a better time to make documentaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's double trouble: Political heat from Trump and left...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/sep/02/big-techs-double-trouble-bipartisan-criticism-may-signal-a-reckoning-ahead </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s timing of attacks on Google, Facebook and Twitter could not have been better, as the three come under scrutiny in hearings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women cheer as man-free music festival kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/florida-s-toxic-red-tide-stretches-residents-report-health-problems-n905336'&gt;Florida residents report health problems as toxic red tide stretches on...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Mueller subpoena president? Move carries risks for both sides...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/404598-will-mueller-subpoena-trump-move-carries-risks-for-both-sides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The months-long dance between President Trump’s lawyers and Robert Mueller over a voluntary presidential interview has yet to bear fruit, raising the question of whether the special counsel will subpoena the preside</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster drills held across Japan to prepare for massive quake...</title>
      <link>http://the-japan-news.com/news/article/0004702766 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;the-japan-news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishops Divided...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-bishops-are-divided-in-a-way-rarely-seen-in-public-1535893201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crisis engulfing the Catholic Church has exposed deep rifts in the U.S. church. The latest trigger is a letter by an archbishop accusing Catholic officials, including Pope Francis, of covering up sexual abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director flaunts 'Weinstein Is Innocent' T-shirt on Venice... </title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/italian-director-flaunts-weinstein-is-innocent-shirt-on-venice-film-festival-red-carpet </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Italian filmmaker Luciano Silighini Garagnani displayed the disgusting shirt for all to see at the red carpet premiere of ‘Suspiria’ on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABBAS: TRUMP OFFERED US PEACE PLAN BASED ON CONFEDERATION WITH JORDAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Abbas-Trump-offered-us-peace-plan-based-on-confederation-with-Jordan-566330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I want a three-party confederation with Jordan and Israel and I am asking Israel to accept such a proposal," Abbas was quoted as saying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis urges action -- on plastic...</title>
      <link>https://www.americanthinker.com/blog/2018/09/pope_franciss_plastic_emergency.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.americanthinker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church is in the middle of a massive pedophilia, pederasty and coverup crisis. And now the pope tells us plastic trash in the ocean is the 'emergency.' Somehow, we're the bad guys again...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS tries to distance themselves for Charlie Rose...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/cbs-news-charlie-rose-sexual-harassment-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Truly Juvenile'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/rogerlsimon/trump-bash-at-mccain-franklin-funerals-truly-juvenile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Bash at McCain/Franklin Funerals Truly Juvenile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican Whistleblower Begs Journalists to Investigate Vatican's 'Cache of Documents'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/vigano-to-journalists-investigate-vaticans-cache-of-documents-showing-clerical-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still in hiding, Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò checks in with an Italian journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls grow for 'extraordinary synod'... </title>
      <link>https://cruxnow.com/vatican/2018/09/02/calls-grow-for-extraordinary-synod-in-response-to-abuse-crisis/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cruxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is an “extraordinary synod” a key piece to the puzzle for finding lasting solutions to the clerical abuse crisis which has engulfed the Church for the past generation?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Yanks 'PARTS UNKNOWN' Episodes Featuring Asia Argento...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/juliareinstein/asia-argento-parts-unknown-cnn-jimmy-bennett-bourdain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision follows news that Argento paid a financial settlement to young actor Jimmy Bennett, who accused her of sexual assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unearths one of oldest villages ever found in Nile Delta...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af5f4c369dcc4bb18677511e92609592/Egypt-says-village-found-in-Nile-Delta-predated-pharaohs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) — Egypt said Sunday that archeologists have unearthed one of the oldest villages ever found in the Nile Delta, with remains dating back to before the pharaohs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to Kill?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-09-01/there-plan-south-africa-take-white-farms-and-kill-white-farmers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycott Of IN-N-OUT Backfires Spectacularly...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-31/california-liberals-draw-line-refuse-boycott-n-out-after-democratic-official-goes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U2 cancels Berlin show after Bono loses voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/u2-cancels-berlin-show-bono-loses-voice-072149826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irish rock group U2 was forced to cut short a concert in Berlin before thousands of fans after performing only a few songs when lead singer Bono lost his voice. It was the second and last concert by the group in the German capital as part of its "Experience + Innocence" tour. After the first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan calls USA 'wild wolves', vows to abandon dollar in trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkey-calls-us-wild-wolves-vows-abandon-dollar-102644099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Turkey and Russia are reeling from punitive economic measures imposed by Washington. "America behaves like wild wolves. Don't believe them," Erdogan told a business forum during a visit to Kyrgyzstan, in comments translated into Kyrgyz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police reports detail O'Rourke's '98 drunken-driving arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/police-reports-detail-orourkes-98-drunken-driving-arrest-145042700--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Police documents from a decades-old drunken-driving arrest of Democratic Senate candidate Beto O'Rourke provide a more complete picture of an incident that the congressman has long acknowledged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan braces for 'very strong' typhoon...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/japan-braces-very-strong-typhoon-065230096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typhoon Jebi, packing winds of up to 252 kilometres (156 miles) an hour, is expected to make landfall on the country's main island on Tuesday, according to Japan's Meteorological Agency. "Maintaining its very strong power, the typhoon is forecast to approach western and eastern Japan,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former chief rabbi warns of 'existential threat' to UK Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/former-chief-rabbi-warns-existential-threat-uk-jews-105708893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain's former chief rabbi has warned that Jewish people are thinking about leaving the country because of anti-Semitism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum under fire; Corruption attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/floridas-democratic-gubernatorial-candidate-under-attack-123123793--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Gillum is picking up endorsements, money and plenty of national attention in the aftermath of his suprising upset victory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Queen Story Hour sparks protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/drag-queen-story-hour-sparks-protests-conservative-towns-130205923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Once upon a time, in 2015, a writer in San Francisco named Michelle Tea got the idea for "Drag Queen Story Hour": men in full drag reading children's books to kids and parents in programs aimed at providing "positive and unabashedly queer role models."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's 'Silk Road' project runs into debt jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinas-silk-road-project-runs-debt-jam-042500476.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's massive and expanding "Belt and Road" trade infrastructure project is running into speed bumps as some countries begin to grumble about being buried under Chinese debt. First announced in 2013 by President Xi Jinping, the initiative also known as the "new Silk Road" envisions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pepper spray discharges during flight to Hawaii, 15 treated...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/15-aboard-hawaii-flight-treated-pepper-spray-goes-002751836.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — A can of pepper spray went off inside a plane headed from Oakland, California, to Maui on Friday, requiring emergency help for several people aboard, Hawaiian Airlines said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says 'Canada Will Be Out' Without 'Fair Deal' on Nafta...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-says-canada-will-be-out-without-fair-deal-on-nafta-1535816122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said Canada would be left out of a new North American Free Trade Agreement if a “fair deal for the U.S.” isn’t reached—and warned Congress he would terminate the deal entirely if lawmakers “interfere.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Billionaire Arrested in Minnesota on Suspicion of Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/billionaire-head-of-chinas-jd-com-arrested-in-minnesota-1535885060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police record shows Liu Qiangdong was arrested in Minnesota on suspicion of sexual misconduct but released the next day, after what the e-commerce giant said was a false accusation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ FIGHT OF HIS LIFE?</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/beto-o-rourke-dreams-of-one-texas-ted-cruz-sees-another-clearly-/17809047/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONGVIEW, Texas — Beto O’Rourke was racing left again, insisting he knew what he was doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women cheer as man-free music festival kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180901/women-cheer-as-swedish-man-free-music-festival-opens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matilda Hagerman laughs with her friends as she queues at a man-free music festival, which kicked off in Sweden  on Friday in protest against a wave of sexual assaults at festivals in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica white farmers warn as more land grabs loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/31/white-farmers-warn-new-zimbabwe-calls-grow-land-expropriation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any aspiring farmer would envy Nick Serfontein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burning Man: The Orb...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/burningman/article/Bjarke-Ingels-Jakob-Lange-the-ORB-Burning-Man-13197472.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are calling it a giant bulb of garlic. Others say it's the world's biggest disco ball. But really, the official name of the 100-foot-diameter reflective sphere is "the ORB."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials, worried about outbreak, investigate HIV cluster in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/homeless/health-officials-investigating-cluster-of-hiv-infections-in-north-seattle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diagnoses are among 19 HIV cases reported so far this year among heterosexuals in King County. For all of last year, that number was seven, according to the health agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival adds security but won't fence off fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/life/arts/burning-man/2018/08/31/burning-man-adding-volunteer-security-around-fires/1171094002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after a man died after running into the flames of the Man burn, organizers say they won't add fencing around large fires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Safe zone'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/01/world/europe/sweden-statement-festival-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Statement festival in Gothenburg, Sweden, is billed as the world’s first music festival exclusively for women and transgender and nonbinary people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City tells police to ignore sex in public...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/travel-updates/mexican-city-tells-police-to-look-the-other-way-when-it-comes-to-sex-in-public/news-story/a101c623bc111887fea24aefcfc6113c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO’s second-largest city has made it harder to police sexual activity in places like parks, alleys, entertainment venues and cars by ordering cops to look the other way most of the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV star gassed, robbed in holiday villa in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/celebrity-life/richard-hammond-and-his-wife-were-gassed-and-robbed-in-holiday-villa-in-france/news-story/2bf5ca1a54e698032bb82f3a3cdc69ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV star Richard Hammond and his wife were gassed before they were robbed in their holiday villa in the South of France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside terrifying world of modern exorcisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/inside-terrifying-world-modern-exorcisms-13172802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new BBC documentary looks at the popularity of exorcisms in Buenos Aires with Padre Manuel Acuna who has performed thousands of the religious rituals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOS: Obama, Bush, Meghan McCain Take Shots at Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-obama-bush-meghan-mccain-swipe-at-trump-during-john-mccain-funeral-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS misconduct bombshell 'only beginning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/only-the-beginning-daily-beast-has-a-lot-more-reporting-to-come-on-nbc-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine commander sacked over LGBT slur...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2018/08/30/26-meu-battalion-commander-fired-during-deployment-over-equal-opportunity-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2/6 commander was abruptly fired in May in the middle of a deployment with the 26 MEU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Surprise Album 'Epic Fail'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/why-eminem-s-surprise-album-kamikaze-is-an-epic-fail-1139101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record is the work of an aging artist trying, and failing, to remain relevant by acting out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatriotic...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180901-neil-armstrong-film-accused-being-unpatriotic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aretha funeral bishop apologizes for 'groping' Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180901-aretha-franklin-funeral-bishop-apologizes-groping-grande</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi plot to turn Qatar into island with huge canal...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1011376/saudi-arabia-qatar-canal-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SENIOR Saudi official today appeared to confirm local media reports the kingdom is considering digging a canal to separate the Qatari peninsula from the mainland and turn it into an island, amid a year-long dispute between the neighbours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a race'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/09/01/race-cruz-allies-will-spend-plenty-put-brakes-betokeep-texas-senate-seat-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON--With Beto O'Rourke fighting Ted Cruz to a draw in polls and topping him in cash, and his party itching to nab a Senate seat and end...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI to 'bring dead back to life' with human replicas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/726877/AI-bring-dead-back-life-human-replicas-3D-technology-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series of explosions reported at Syria airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/09/01/middleeast/syria-explosion-al-mazzeh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Syrian state media says the series of explosions was caused by an electrical fault at an ammunition depot in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Self-Driving Car in Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/2018/08/31/apple-discloses-minor-crash-involving-self-driving-test-vehicle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. disclosed in a filing with the California Department of Motor Vehicles that one of its autonomous test vehicles was involved in a crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day Sees Americans Grilling More Steaks on Strong Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/31/americans-are-grilling-more-steaks-for-labor-day-as-economy-hums#gs.YgWPfLw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans Are Grilling More Steaks for Labor Day With the Economy Humming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over 'FIRST MAN' Signals Controversial Award Season...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/31/-first-man-outcry-portends-controversial-award-season-for-films#gs.=QOU_Lk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not even September yet, and likely Oscar contenders are already stirring up controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC CRAZY: Woman smashes bus window, hits man with car...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2018/08/video-woman-smashes-greyhound-bus-window-rams-driver-in-dc/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic video released by D.C. police shows a woman smashing the windows of a Greyhound bus with a car jack, and then ramming and attempting to run down the bus driver in an apparent act of road rage…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Winter Storm Warning of Season Issued in USA...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/winter/news/2018-09-01-first-winter-storm-warning-of-season-in-us-issued-alaska</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be the beginning of meteorological fall, but winter is right around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High School Football Team Cancels Season After Outscored 102-0 In First Two Games...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/08/29/healdsburg-high-football-team-calls-it-quits-after-crushing-shutout-losses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a pair of lopsided losses to start off the year, the Healdsburg High School football team has decided to turn in its uniforms and cancel the rest of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARETHA'S TOO!</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/vicious-anti-trump-diatribes-mar-aretha-franklins-memorial-service-orange-apparition-leech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;Continuing a sickening Democratic tradition of politicizing public memorial services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected MS-13 member breaks into sleeping girl's room, rapes her...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/01/perv-breaks-into-sleeping-11-year-old-girls-bedroom-then-rapes-her-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A purported member of the MS-13 gang broke into the bedroom of a sleeping 11-year-old Brooklyn girl and raped her in her bed, cops said Saturday as the suspect was taken into custody. The horrific …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microwaves 'main suspect' in attack on US diplomats in Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/01/microwaves-are-main-suspect-in-attack-on-us-diplomats-in-cuba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American diplomats and family members who mysteriously fell ill while stationed at the US embassy in Havana may have been zapped by microwaves that can cause brain injuries, according to a frig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada considers 'right to disconnect' outside work...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/liberals-eye-closer-look-at-right-to-disconnect-in-labour-rule-revamp-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some employees choose to stay connected because they don’t work a traditional workday. At least one employer group called any government action a ‘legislative over-step’ the repor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport Installs First Unmanned Control Tower...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/08/31/unmanned-airport-control-tower-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-of-a-kind virtual air traffic control tower was recently installed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German foreign minister says country too lazy to fight racism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cc4abf14eb6b4ef88d8bbfe9aab1d4b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHEMNITZ, Germany (AP) — Germany's foreign minister told his fellow countrymen Sunday they're too lazy when it comes to battling racism and fighting for democracy.        "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 hurt, 2 missing after boats collide on Colorado River...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a67d421a794f48b19615cafc4429095f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOABI REGIONAL PARK, Calif. (AP) — Two recreational boats collided head-on Saturday in a stretch of the Colorado River marking the California border with Arizona that was crowded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BASH AT MCCAIN FUNERAL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c3b8c91dfc34f42868eb2ccb09b675a/McCain-tributes-echo-with-criticism-of-Trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — John McCain's daughter and two former presidents led a public rebuke of President Donald Trump's divisive politics at the late senator's memorial service Saturda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary helped up steps...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-two-people-help-hillary-up-stairs-at-aretha-franklin-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton still needs help with stairs. The Clintons were in Detroit today for Aretha Franklin’s funeral, and after viewing the open casket, the two made their way to different parts of the stage. As Hillary approached the stairs, two people grabbed each of her arms to help her ascend the handful of steps. Watch: …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICO's must-read briefing on what's driving the day in Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female prison staffer admits romancing inmate -- while working for Patricia Arquette...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-metro-illicit-romance-clinton-correctional-facility-20180901-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prison worker Denise Prell, 39, has admitted to romancing an inmate at Clinton Correctional Facility at the same as she was working as an assistant to actress Patricia Arquette in a TV series about the 2015 Shawshank Redemption-style prison escape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NY DAILY NEWS] CONFIDENTIAL</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/confidential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read celebrity gossip around New York and Hollywood from the New York Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caught in political echo chamber? Listening to opposition can make partisanship worse...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-twitter-partisan-politics-20180831-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Living in a political echo chamber where you only encounter the views of people who agree with you is hardly conducive to a healthy democracy. But it turns out that broadening our horizons by listening to opposing points of view on Twitter only makes the problem worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH DRUDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain's smallest baby at 12oz survives...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6123567/Britains-smallest-baby-weighed-COKE-survives-against-odds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theo Taylor was smaller than expected at a 19-week scan then stopped growing altogether and his parents were told to fear the worst. He was born at 26 weeks and five days in Newcastle upon Tyne.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The six-term Republican senator from Arizona, and two-time presidential candidate passed away last Saturday at the age of 81.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Giant cage protests tech ties with ICE...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/404630-activists-protest-palantirs-ice-contract-at-burning-man</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizers hope to catch the attention of tech workers who often flock to the Nevada festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Ready For Campaign Trail...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/404703-obama-readies-fall-campaign-push-but-some-dems-say-no-thanks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obama is set to dive into the midterm elections this week, but not all Democrats want the former president's help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/article/declarations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE NEWS</title>
      <link>http://news.google.com/nwshp?hl=en&amp;tab=wn&amp;q=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap produces a wide range of news contents and provides print, broadcast media as well as state and private institutions with real-time news products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
