<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>False alarms and hoax reports: Americans on edge after shootings...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/07/active-shooter-false-reports-put-america-edge-after-mass-shootings/1942249001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a string of mass shootings, multiple false reports of active shooters have spread around the country, highlighting fears in many Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA: Patients left to rot in feces at psychiatric hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9677636/inside-venezuelas-hellhole-psychiatric-hospital-where-patients-are-left-to-rot-in-cells-covered-in-faeces-and-cockroaches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE disturbing photographs taken in a Venezuelan hospital lay bare the suffering of vulnerable mentally ill people as the country implodes.  Hospital services across the stricken socialist South …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going under knife may damage memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/08/07/major-surgery-doubles-risk-substantial-brain-decline-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major surgery doubles the chance of experiencing a substantial decline in mental skills, such as reasoning, memory and language ability, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: X-37B Military Space Plane Mission Hits 700 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/x-37b-military-space-plane-otv5-700-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longest X-37B mission to date is 718 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Nelson Cancels Tour Due to 'Breathing Problem'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/willie-nelson-cancels-tour-breathing-problem-868950/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer won’t finish his summer run with Alison Krauss</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside student fight night where young men box unlicensed in front of glamorous women...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/inside-student-fight-night-young-14394995</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Boxing’s governing bodies are deeply concerned about the lack of control surrounding white-collar events - but for ungrads in Cardiff, it is the night of the term</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran jamming ship GPS to get them to wander into waters?</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/iran-is-jamming-ship-gps-navigation-systems-to-seize-them-2019-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ships report "GPS interference, bridge-to-bridge communications spoofing, and/or other communications jamming with little to no warning," US military says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man 'full of anger' goes on two-hour stabbing rampage in SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e44f7bd106f4fce8da21c2c11f334fc </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw anger...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/texas/article/Some-skeptical-as-Trump-prepares-to-visit-sites-14286057.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas (AP) - Aiming to play the traditional role of healer during national tragedy, President Donald Trump paid visits Wednesday to two cities reeling from mass shootings that left 31 dead and dozens more wounded. But his divisive words preceded him, large protests greeted him and biting political attacks soon followed.  The president and first lady Melania Trump flew to El Paso late in the day after visiting the Dayton hospital where many of the victims of Sunday's attack in that city were treated. The president was kept out of view of the reporters traveling with him, but White House Press Secretary Stephanie Grisham said the couple met with hospital staff and first responders and spent time with wounded survivors and their families.  Trump told them he was "with them," she said. "Everybody received him very warmly. Everybody was very, very excited to see him."  But outside Miami Valley Hospital, at least 200 protesters gathered, blaming Trump's incendiary rhetoric for inflaming political and racial tensions in the country and demanding action on gun control . Some said Trump was not welcome in their city. There were Trump supporters, as well.  Emotions are still raw in the aftermath of the early Sunday morning shooting rampage that left 10 dead, including the gunman, in the city's popular Oregon entertainment district. Critics contend Trump's own words have contributed to a combustible climate that has spawned violence in cities including El Paso, where another shooter killed 22 people over the weekend.  And the vitriol continued Wednesday. Trump spent part of his flight between Ohio and Texas airing his grievances on Twitter, berating Democratic lawmakers, a potential 2020 rival and the press. It was a remarkable split=screen appearance for TV viewers, with White House images of handshakes and selfies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Smollett will NOT be on final season of EMPIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7334701/Fox-Jussie-Smollett-wont-final-season-Empire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Jussie Smollett will not appear on the final and sixth season of Empire after allegedly fabricating a hate crime attack in Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR WARS STUMBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-06/disney-misses-profit-estimates-as-parks-slump-fox-film-flops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING CODE LEAK EXPOSES SECURITY FLAWS DEEP IN 787'S GUTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/boeing-787-code-leak-security-flaws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One researcher's discovery suggests troubling oversights in Boeing's cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Erectile Dysfunction Linked To Poor Work Productivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-erectile-dysfunction-linked-poor-work-productivity-lower-quality-of-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new international study conducted across eight countries finds that erectile dysfunction is associated with problems on the job and an overall decline in quality of life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS FIND HUGE WORLD OF HIDDEN GALAXIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/universe-galaxies-milky-way-hubble-nasa-discovery-breakthrough-latest-a9045951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugly spat...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7332199/Donald-Trump-vents-Twitter-Fake-News-ignoring-left-wing-leanings-Dayton-mass-shooter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Wednesday blasted two Democratic officials who held a press conference after Donald Trump's visit to Dayton, Ohio, saying 'it's disgusting' that they didn't acknowledge the 'rock star treatment' the president received while visiting survivors of Saturday night's mass shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China has $1 trillion trade war weapon. Will it ever use?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/07/business/trade-war-china-treasuries/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has a hugely powerful weapon it could use in the trade war — it is America's biggest creditor. But there are very good reasons why it's highly unlikely to dump US Treasuries to drive up interest rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead Planets Send 'Zombie Signals' That Can Be Heard On Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/dead-planets-send-out-zombie-signals-that-can-be-heard-on-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They've been destroyed by their suns but still sing a sad song. And one day it's going to happen here, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USATODAY EVACUATED; 'MISTAKEN' WEAPON REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/08/07/usa-today-headquarters-evacuated-after-report-man-gun/1944136001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newspaper's headquarters in suburban Virginia was evacuated; police said they were responding to reports of a man with a gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 12 Years as 'Digital Prophet,' David Shing Out Of VERIZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/digital/after-12-years-as-a-digital-prophet-david-shingy-is-moving-on-from-verizon-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ‘futurist’ cut one of the industry’s most recognizable figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: PRESIDENT FUELING 'CARNAGE'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4863d9f74f49478492751d4b3d45203a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House drafting order on tech industry 'censorship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/07/white-house-tech-censorship-1639051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government has only limited options to police alleged ideological bias in Silicon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico's new governor must resign after swearing-in ruled unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/puerto-rico-s-supreme-court-law-used-name-new-governor-n1039911</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The island's highest court ruled, in a decision which becomes official at 5 p.m. ET, that the process used by Gov. Pedro Rosselló to name his successor did not follow Puerto Rico's Constitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Endorses Background Checks, Rules Out Assault Weapons Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-endorses-background-checks-rules-out-assault-weapons-ban/ar-AAFtB4F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barcelona women win fight to swim topless after discrimination complaints...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/barcelona-topless-pools-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Barcelona confirm it's allowable for women to be topless in city-run pools after complaints that some swimming spots were discriminating against those wanting to shed their tops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMMYS to go hostless...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2bc05eb916a04dd29be97969149c6983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Castro outed own supporter to shame Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/joaquin-castro-outed-one-of-his-own-donors-in-bid-to-shame-trump-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Trump donors whose names and employers were posted in a highly controversial tweet by Democratic Rep. Joaquin Castro blasted the Texas congressman on Wednesday for what they described as a “ridiculous” stunt and, in interviews with Fox News, rejected his claim that they are “fueling a campaign of hate” against Hispanics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of 'Herculean' parrot found...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/evidence-of-herculean-parrot-found-in-new-zealand-11788026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON: The remains of a super-sized parrot that stood more than half the height of an average human and roamed the earth 19 million years ago ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: NYTIMES STOCK TUMBLES AS MUCH AS 20%...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/new-york-times-stock-price-q2-earnings-revenue-outlook-drops-2019-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy scrambles to shadow Russian ship through Channel...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/hms-forth-scrambled-to-shadow-russian-ship-through-channel-11779527</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Royal Navy says the patrol ship had just returned to UK waters from her first foreign port visit when it was deployed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE:  72,000 arrested in July...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/illegal-crossing-arrests-at-mexican-border-dropped-by-about-20-000-in-july-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people arrested for illegally crossing the U.S.-Mexico border declined by approximately 20,000 in July, the second monthly decline in a row following a steep increase this spring, according to three senior Homeland Security officials and a nongovernmental official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Bureau Seeks to Hire Non-Citizens Ahead of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2019-08-06/census-bureau-seeks-to-hire-non-us-citizens-ahead-of-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  FOXNEWS OVER CNN; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLE NEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to host 'online extremism' roundtable...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/07/white-house-to-meet-with-internet-companies-after-shootings-1451005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The roundtable discussion will take place Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE stands in global antitrust crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/07/apple-antitrust-europe-united-states-1449919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iPhone maker, not Facebook or Google, is rapidly becoming the test case for a&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Big Tech crackdown from Europe to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Murphy's First NETFLIX Show 'THE POLITICIAN' Takes On Trump-Era... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-ryan-murphys-politician-skewers-trump-era-entitlement-1229627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The Politician,' also starring Ben Platt, Zoey Deutch and Jessica Lange, eviscerates the absurd lengths the .001  percent will go to stay on top — and the writers even predicted the college cheating scandal: "It is about the ugliest thing someone of means can do."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans At MICROSOFT Hearing Your Skype Calls?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90387035/microsoft-may-be-listening-to-your-translated-skype-calls-just-like-every-other-tech-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Machines: 1; Privacy: 0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud noise causes chaos at Utah mall...</title>
      <link>https://www.deseretnews.com/article/900082978/west-valley-fair-mall-noise-gunshot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deseretnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Valley Fair Mall in West Valley City was evacuated Tuesday night after a sign fell and the noise led mall patrons to panic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian drone with 'brain' flies solo from Moscow to London...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/796819/russia-drone-brain-unmanned-missile-stealth-bomber-fly-solo-moscow-london</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TREASURY RATES COLLAPSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/07/us-treasury-bonds-china-sets-the-yuan-below-expectations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The August slide in the 10-year Treasury note yield accelerated to new 2016 lows after China announced a weaker benchmark for the yuan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fort Sumter restricts access...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/07966f7b70bb42aeb3bbfe03ca256fca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCUWEATHER Founder: No evidence heatwaves becoming more common because of 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-blogs/realimpactofweatherwithdrjoelnmyers/throwing-cold-water-on-extreme-heat-hype/70008963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewinsky Producing 'IMPEACHMENT' Drama at FX...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/bill-clinton-american-crime-story-impeachment-series-set-fx-monica-lewinsky-sarah-paulson-linda-tripp-1202662799/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FX said today that the third season of its award-winning limited series franchise American Crime Story will center on the sex scandal that rocked the Bill Clinton presidency. Sarah Paulson, after w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manifestos play vital role in clarifying motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2019/08/07/after-el-paso-vital-keep-shooter-manifestos-available-public-column/1931628001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How much information should be concealed about attackers? Their last words to society help us to understand them and their motivations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  30-year nears record low...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-bonds/treasuries-recession-fears-pummel-u-s-30-year-yields-to-near-record-low-idUSL2N2530O3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;year notes at 1 p.m.   * Rate cuts by Asian central bank spur more bond buyin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  DISNEY SHARES SLIDE AFTER BIG EARNINGS MISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/07/disney-shares-slump-after-earnings-disappoint.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company blames the disappointing results on the integration of Fox, increased streaming costs and weak theme parks attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angry Neighbors Demand City Do Something About House Painted Pink With Giant Emojis...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/08/06/angry-neighbors-demand-manhattan-beach-do-something-about-pink-emoji-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan Beach City Council got an earful from a handful of angry residents who want the owner of a pink house covered with two giant emojis to remove them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain welcome awaits president in Ohio, Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/daa18df66eaf4d99acebc36f86edd330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Red flag' plan has support in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bdb661de1fe14e58951102349d5d44be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland Braces for Another Round of Proud Boys, Antifa Fights...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/portland-braces-for-another-round-of-proud-boys-antifa-fights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Proud Boys and their far-right allies are headed to Portland, weeks after clashes at another Portland rally made national news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Cage on Acting, Philosophy, Searching for Holy Grail...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/nicolas-cage-explains-his-dinosaur-skill-fiasco-his-hunt-literal-holy-grail-1229919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oscar-winning actor also discusses why one of his least favorite films is 1986's 'Peggy Sue Got Married,' which his uncle directed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA live feed cuts as mysterious object appears near ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/796745/NASA-live-feed-cut-mystery-object-appear-ISS-space-station-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spending time with 'high status' people can increase own social standing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7332035/Spending-time-high-status-people-increase-social-standing-scientists-discover.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A University of Richmond anthropologist and colleagues studied the relationship between status and levels of cooperation among the men of the indigenous Bolivian Tsimane people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The crisis of American loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/857296/crisis-american-loneliness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey paints a bleak picture of modern America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is NF, the Eminem-soundalike who beat Chance the Rapper for No. 1 album?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/music/2019/08/06/who-nf-eminem-soundalike-who-beat-chance-rapper-no-1-album/1935006001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NF's "The Search" edged out Chance's highly-anticipated release "The Big Day" for the No. 1 album in America this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nate Parker 'AMERICAN SKIN' Added to Venice Film Fest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/nate-parkers-american-skin-added-to-venice-film-festival-slate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The L.A.-set drama is Parker's first feature since 2016's "The Birth of a Nation"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Cage on Acting, Philosophy, Searching for Holy Grail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2019/08/07/magazine/nicholas-cage-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I wanted to have the mystery of the old stars, always preserved in an enigmatic aura.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS COALESCE AROUND GUN CONTROL</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/red-flag-gun-control-bills-pick-up-momentum-with-gop-in-congress/ar-AAFqNjB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange County, in historic shift, now has more registered Dems than Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-08-07/orange-county-turns-blue-with-more-registered-democrats-than-republicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orange County, long a conservative bastion, is officially Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He went to jail as fake doctor. Now he's real one...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-fake-doctor-becomes-md-20190422-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When someone mistook him for a resident at UCLA Medical Center, he didn't correct them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALGREENS closing 200 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/06/walgreens-to-close-200-stores-in-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walgreens said the closures will affect about 3% of its U.S. footprint. The company operates roughly 10,000 drugstores nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN eyes all-black panel show...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/06/cnn-eyes-all-black-panel-show/?_ga=2.150539510.156191497.1565173026-1795275849.1565173026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The network hopes to hire regular CNN contributors April Ryan, Andrew Gillum, Angela Rye and Bakari Sellers as panelists for a brand-new show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORIOLES outfielder embarrassing misplay ends in concussion...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/07/dj-stewarts-embarrassing-misplay-ends-in-concussion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orioles outfielder DJ Stewart will likely end up on “SportsCenter’s” Not Top 10 with his misplaying of a fly ball Tuesday night, and he left Camden Yards with an injury in the pro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver attacked by shark rescued by fishing boat full of nurses...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/diver-attacked-shark-rescued-fishing-boat-full-nurses/story?id=64803039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spearfisherman who was attacked by a shark over in Florida the weekend was saved by a group of medical professionals who just happened to be in a boat nearby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Staring At Seagulls Could Save Lunch...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/self-conscious-seagulls-staring-may-save-your-lunch-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most people don't appreciate being stared at, especially by strangers. Well, according to a new study conducted at the University of Exeter, seagulls feel the same way about prying eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DEATH CAMPS FOR TRUMP SUPPORTERS' FLIERS IN NEW YORK...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/death-camps-for-trump-supporters-fliers-posted-in-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So much for the tolerant left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson calls white supremacy 'hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/857574/fox-news-tucker-carlson-claims-problem-white-supremacy-hoax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week after a man believed to have written a racist manifesto about a "Hispanic invasion of Texas" killed 22 people in El Paso, Texas, Fox News' Tucker Carlson claims the idea of America having a white supremacy problem is a "hoax." Carlson made this claim on his Tuesday show, saying that white supremacy is "right up there with Russia" in terms of problems the United States faces and is "actually not a real problem in America" at all. To back up this argument, Carlson said that every person who is a member of a white supremacist organization in the country could fit inside a single college football stadium. Of course, as CNN's Brian Stelter points out, this neglects the fact that "men like the suspect in El Paso aren't 'members' of an 'organization.'" "This is a hoax," Carlson claimed. "Just like the Russia hoax. It's a conspiracy theory used to divide the country and keep a hold on power. That's exactly what's going on." Carlson's comments immediately drew backlash, with CNN's Don Lemon playing the clip on his show shortly after, taking a long pause and then asking his guest, "Was that not the dumbest thing you've ever heard"? Conservative columnist Jonah Goldberg also hit back against Carlson and hoped his argument isn't picked up by President Trump ahead of his El Paso visit. Goldberg wrote, "If Trump apes these talking points, it'll be awful for the country and devastating for Trump's presidency." Trump on Wednesday morning tweeted a different quote from Carlson's show, suggesting he saw the white supremacy segment. Brendan Morrow Tucker Carlson: White supremacy is "actually not a real problem in America." Calling white supremacy and issue is "a hoax" and "a conspiracy theory used to divide the country" pic.twitter.com/ydzmJ0L7UI â€” Andrew Lawrence (@ndrew_lawrence) August 7, 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds flee; 22 injured...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/08/07/times-square-crowd-mistakes-backfiring-motorcycle-for-possible-mass-shooter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two dozen people were hurt when a backfiring motorcycle sent people running for their lives Tuesday in Times Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds flee; 20 injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Panic-in-Times-Square-as-Motorcycle-Backfire-Sends-Pedestrians-Running-524335611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People walking in Times Square were sent into a widespread panic Tuesday night after what sounded like multiple gunshots rang out in the crowded tourist destination — only later to be ruled as motorcycle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock futures losses accelerate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/07/stock-markets-wall-street-in-focus-amid-lingering-trade-war-concerns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures rolled over on Wednesday as the ongoing trade war sparked fears of a global economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to take on directly in speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-speech-donald-trump-white-supremacy-e2055f0d-c303-4036-8e57-660162979175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"[O]ur president has more in common with George Wallace than George Washington."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman's viral rant says she's infecting men with HIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/959ef0857cf842b698d637d695a9a0e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic in Times Square after motorcycle backfire mistaken for gunshots...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/07/panic-in-times-square-after-motorcycle-backfire-mistaken-for-gunshots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos erupted in Times Square on Tuesday night as people stormed from the area when a backfiring motorcycle was mistaken for gunshots. The false alarm took place at around 10 p.m. as a loud boom se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists say water in Hawaii crater heated by volcano...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-water-hawaii-volcano-crater-005039485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have discovered that a growing pond of water inside a Hawaii crater is being heated by Kilauea volcano. The U.S. Geological Survey said Tuesday that temperature readings taken over the weekend show that a growing pool of water in Kilauea volcano's Halemaumau crater, the former home of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain welcome awaits Trump in Ohio, Texas...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190807083816-l08cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHOOTING/ (PIX, TV):Uncertain welcome awaits Trump in Ohio and Texas after deadly mass shootings</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
