<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  UK editors call on ministers to protect freedom of information...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2021/feb/08/uk-editors-call-on-ministers-to-protect-freedom-of-information</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open letter raises concerns public is being obstructed when requesting information from official files</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Capitol Police fully investigate its own?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/02/08/will-capitol-police-fully-investigate-its-own/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the absence of a transparent Capitol Police internal affairs division and inspector general, questions of what can be done to ensure accountability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyers have their eyes on Jeffrey Epstein's infamous islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article249048485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The islands once owned by Jeffrey Epstein are caught in a tug-of-war between the estate, which says it is strapped for cash, and the attorney general of the Virgin Islands, who is making a move on all assets that once belonged to Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAN B:  Invoke 14th Amendment?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article249077830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Constitutional scholars have helped draft the censure resolution, engaging in late-night calls with Democratic congressional staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge permits release of Proud Boys leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/08/politics/proud-boys-capitol-riot/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge in Seattle on Monday decided that a Proud Boys leader on the West Coast, Ethan Nordean, should be released pending trial, even after federal prosecutors warned he could coordinate with the Proud Boys for another attack on the federal government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant DeSantis goes to game barefaced!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/537860-desantis-on-going-maskless-to-super-bowl-i-had-to-watch-the-bucs-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) addressed a photo circulating on the internet showing him at Sunday's Super Bowl in Tampa while not wearing a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate opens another Trump impeachment trial for divided nation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senate-readies-trump-impeachment-trial-120017190.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week's impeachment trial will shape Donald Trump's legacy but probably not resolve the sharp divide over how to view the former president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney emerges as anti-Trump leader...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/liz-cheney-emerges-republican-anti-194218527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Cheney, the lone congresswoman from the western US state of Wyoming and daughter of the former vice president, is done with Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITCOIN TOPS $47,000</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-surges-past-47-000-012426395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin hit a fresh record above $47,000 on Tuesday after Tesla Inc.’s announcement of a $1.5 billion investment in the largest cryptocurrency.The token rose as much as 6.3% to almost $47,493 in early Asian trading before paring some of the gains. Tesla’s disclosure Monday sent the price soaring.The company also said it would begin accepting the digital token as a form of payment for its electric cars. The developments amounted to the biggest endorsement of the controversial cryptocurrency by a mainstream firm. Elon Musk, Tesla’s founder and the world’s richest man, has for months been commenting about Bitcoin, buffeting its price.Tesla’s decision may be “a catalyst for other companies to go that route,” said Julius de Kempenaer, senior technical analyst at StockCharts.com, adding a new bull run is underway in the token.A rally was also evident in Bitcoin futures, suggesting shorts are throwing in the towel and signaling traders won’t fight the crypto advance. The wider Bloomberg Galaxy Crypto Index, which includes Bitcoin, Ether and three other tokens, jumped to a record.Japanese and South Korean cryptocurrency-exposed stocks rose, tracking a rally in their U.S. and European peers.Bitcoin’s journey to its latest summit came with big swings that continue to stoke controversy about its outlook. Predictions for its possible long-term price range from $400,000 and more to zero.Proponents cite backing from the likes of Musk and signs of interest from long-term investors as evidence of a durable rally. They also envisage a role for the token as a hedge for risks such as faster inflation, akin to gold.Others continue to see speculators at work and are reminded of the 2017 boom that turned to bust. The token is designed to have a fixed supply of 21 million coins, underpinned by a digital ledger distributed across computer networks.Bitcoin has more than quadrupled over the past year. Commentators have cited day traders, wealthy buyers, hedge funds, companies and even signs of interest from usually staid investors like insurers for the climb.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Director Says Covid Tests for ALL Flights Could Ease Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/world/the-americas/cdc-director-says-covid-tests-for-us-domestic-flights-could-ease-spread-1.1162440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discussions comes as 'variants of concern' spread nationwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FIGHT AGAINST VARIANTS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/with-astrazeneca-rollout-suspended-south-africa-scrambles-for-a-vaccine-plan-e2-80-94-a-e2-80-98preview-e2-80-99-of-new-fight-against-variants/ar-BB1dvHZK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A limited study indicated the Oxford-AstraZeneca vaccine was minimally protective against a new variant widespread in southern Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the rich got richer: REDDIT trading frenzy benefited Wall Street elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/how-the-rich-got-richer-reddit-trading-frenzy-benefited-wall-street-elite/ar-BB1dvfI7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of heralding a new wave of investor populism, the rise and fall of GameStop’s stock may end up reinforcing what professional investors have known for a long time: Wall Street is very good at making money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT RECORD HIGH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-futures-point-to-another-round-of-records-after-biggest-weekly-rise-since-november-11612786760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All four major stock indexes closed at records Monday, as investors piled into energy stocks and penciled in another round of aid spending out of Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive teen brawl erupts at trampoline park...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article249108050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens are seen punching, kicking, stomping and pulling hair at the family-friendly park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacked sex robots could be told to kill users...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/hacked-sex-robots-could-told-23463702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasingly sophisticated AI in robots intended for intimate use poses a "grave threat to humanity" should developers fail to safeguard against malicious hacks, legal experts are warning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES LOWEST SINCE OCTOBER!</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Etvqc-7U0AAr27X?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk-bond yields drop below 4% for the first time ever...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-junk-bond-yields-drop-231257469.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The average yield on U.S. junk bonds dropped below 4% for the first time ever as investors seeking a haven from ultra-low interest rates keep piling into an asset class historically known for its high yields.The measure for the Bloomberg Barclays U.S. Corporate High-Yield index dipped to 3.96% on Monday evening, making it six straight sessions of declines.Yield-hungry investors have been gobbling up junk bonds as an alternative to the meager income offered in less-risky bond markets. Demand for the debt has outweighed supply by so much that some money managers are even calling companies to press them to borrow instead of waiting for deals to come their way. A majority of new issues, even those rated in the riskiest CCC tier of junk, have been hugely oversubscribed.The lower yields should encourage more speculative-grade companies to tap the market after raising more than $7 billion last week. January was a record month for sales with $52 billion priced, and year-to-date volume stands at about $60 billion.Buyers have been snapping up CCC graded issues as yields for that slice of high yield also decline. They dropped to 6.21% on Monday, also a record low, and have outperformed the rest of the market for three consecutive months, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Notes rates in the single-B tier yield an average 4.30%, while those in the BB range yield 3.05%, the data show.Issuance conditions have been so conducive that some of the riskiest types of transactions come to market, such as bonds that are used to fund dividends to a company’s owners and so-called pay-in-kind bonds that allow a borrower to pay interest with more debt.Some see continued outperformance from the junkiest part of the market. CCCs, which have accounted for a significant chunk of recent supply, may be one of the best parts of credit this year, according to David Norris, head of U.S. credit at TwentyFour Asset Management. “This robust new issue pipeline of lower-quality credit is worth poring over as there are likely to be some good stories in here for investors with sufficient liquidity to get involved,” he said.(Updates with rating-bucket yields in fifth paragraph. A previous version of this story was corrected to note that the index declined for six straight sessions in second paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS PUSH MORE BAILOUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-15-dollar-minimum-wage-450d27c72ba701cb5aef3213cb4bcd8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats on Monday proposed an additional $1,400 in direct payments to individuals as Congress began piecing together a $1.9 trillion COVID-19 relief package that tracks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DANGEROUS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/local/pinellascounty/pinellas-oldsmar-water-system-computer-intrustion/67-512b2bab-9f94-44d7-841e-5169fdb0a0bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtsp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to a vigilant operator and several redundancies, officials say the heightened level of sodium hydroxide never caused a public threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKER TRIES TO POISON FL WATER SUPPLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88ab33/hacker-poison-florida-water-pinellas-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hacker tried to drastically increase sodium hydroxide levels in the water, Pinellas County, Florida, officials said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fraud-busting business -- found to be a fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/owner-of-fraud-business-found-to-also-be-fraud-sentenced-to-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida businessman whose fraud-busting business was exposed as a fraud itself was sentenced Monday to a year and a day in prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Around the globe, virus cancels spring travel for millions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-coronavirus-pandemic-china-germany-indiana-3acb00dcb30aa8b4d1f7858f857237f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — They are the annual journeys of late winter and early spring: Factory workers in China heading home for the Lunar New Year; American college students going on road trips...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Album sales surge for Morgan Wallen after racist comment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-race-and-ethnicity-morgan-wallen-music-radio-3641ae1b0ac656e4af6445f226ffc8eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLLE, Tenn. (AP) — Fans of Morgan Wallen are buying up the country star's latest album after a video showed him shouting a racial slur last week. Wallen’s sophomore record, “Dangerous:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIELSEN Fumbles Super Bowl Ratings; Networks &amp; NFL Livid...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/super-bowl-ratings-delayed-nielsen-cbs-buccaneers-tom-brady-1234690027/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a lot of history made at the Super Bowl last night for Tom Brady, the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and halftime show headliner The Weeknd, but Nielsen today are making some history of their own. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems Demand PARLER Hand Over List of Investors, Creditors...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/house-democrats-demand-parler-hand-over-list-of-investors-creditors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats are demanding that Parler turn over a list of its investors and creditors, citing a report that former President Donald Trump was offered a stake in the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA Officials Review Phone Call as Scrutiny Intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/georgia-officials-review-trump-phone-call-as-scrutiny-intensifies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — The office of Georgia’s secretary of state, Brad Raffensperger, on Monday started an investigation into former President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly Man Dead Shortly After Receiving NYC Jab...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/08/investigation-underway-after-elderly-man-died-shortly-after-receiving-covid-vaccine-at-javits-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man collapsed outside the Javits Center on Sunday morning as he was leaving, but it's too early in the investigation to link the vaccine to the patient's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT:  Manafort Can't Be Prosecuted in NY After Pardon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/manafort-cant-be-prosecuted-in-new-york-after-trump-pardon-court-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney’s attempt to prosecute former President Donald Trump’s 2016 campaign chairman was dealt a final blow when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: For Donald, Palins Fall Shows  Limits of Media Obsession...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/02/for-donald-trump-sarah-palins-fall-shows-the-limits-of-media-obsession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Alaska governor dominated coverage while she was seen as a GOP kingmaker and potential presidential candidate—until reality (or at least reality TV) set in. The spotlight on Trump, too, may dim without a social media megaphone and as new outrage makers, like Marjorie Taylor Greene, grab headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer, McConnell reach deal on Impeachment II...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/537876-schumer-mcconnell-reach-deal-on-trump-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate leadership announced on Monday that they have reached a deal on the framework for former President Trump's impeachment trial, which will start on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election turmoil splits WV city's evangelicals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-west-virignia-evangelicals-891cb9a4c4e377f1778f5915c4431145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BLUEFIELD, W.Va. (AP) — If you’re Christian in Bluefield — and most everyone is, in this small city tucked into the Blue Ridge Mountains — you have your choice. You can follow Pastor Doyle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Hygiene Theater Still a Huge Waste of Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/hygiene-theater-is-still-a-huge-waste-of-time/ar-BB1duqW6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too many people imagine the fight against COVID-19 as a land war to be waged with sudsy hand-to-hand combat against grimy surfaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and Fall of Bitcoin Billionaire Arthur Hayes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/02/the-rise-and-fall-of-bitcoin-billionaire-arthur-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BitMEX cofounder created a cryptocurrency exchange that has traded trillions. Now he’s wanted by U.S. authorities, and insiders wonder whether he and his partners are villains—or victims of a two-tiered justice system that favors big banks over brash outsiders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools plan for remote learning -- in fall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/schools-plan-remote-learning-fall-0db9806f1db5253846b3946f28af6a6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents of schoolchildren learning from home shouldn't necessarily count on reclaiming the dining room table any time soon. After seeing two academic years thrown off course by the pandemic,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to crack down on 'vaccine misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/facebook-says-it-will-crack-down-on-covid-vaccine-misinformation-3eadfa34-4f7d-46e1-b14b-5247424dbbf3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a partial reversal from Facebook's previous position on vaccine misinformation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managers: 'Most grievous constitutional crime ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-files-brief-reply-to-trump-answer-of-impeachment-article</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House impeachment managers accused former President Donald Trump of "the most grievous constitutional crime ever committed by a President" in their final brief before Trump's impeachment trial begins in earnest Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University To Play Black National Anthem Before Every Sport...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/02/08/gannon-university-black-national-anthem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ganon University is playing the Black national anthem before every home game of every sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variants raise worry reinfections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-new-variants-b4d472f3d61c62a57aa68c4aa7c85012</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evidence is mounting that having COVID-19 may not protect against getting infected again with some of the new variants. People also can get second infections with earlier versions of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents fired cannon to celebrate baby shower. Guest killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Expectant-parents-fired-a-cannon-to-celebrate-15932801.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan couple tied balloons to the mailbox and set out a chalkboard with a hand-drawn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Allegations From Inside CA's New Billion Dollar Testing Lab; Swabs Found In Restrooms...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/08/whistleblower-allegations-california-covid-testing-lab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lab techs sleeping while processing COVID samples for testing. COVID test swabs found in the restrooms. These are just two of the concerning allegations from whistleblowers about what's happening inside the state’s new billion-dollar COVID testing lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX congressman dies after covid battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/arlington/article249092395.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Ron Wright, known as a staunch conservative and member of the Freedom Caucus, died Sunday after a battle with COVID-19. He was 67.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church Of Scientology Spot Stuns Viewers; 'Dare To Think For Yourself'...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/sports/news/super-bowl-scientology-ad-fans-cant-believe-commercial-ran-during-big-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Kansas City Chiefs and the Tampa Bay Buccaneers battled it out on the field for the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China, Iran to hold joint naval drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/russia-china-and-iran-to-hold-joint-naval-drills-in-indian-ocean-soon-658242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrophotographer captures incredible footage of jet photobombing Sun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9236207/Photographer-captures-United-Airlines-plane-photobombing-Sun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California-based astrophotographer has captured 'one-in-a-million' footage of a United Airlines plane photobombing the Sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers blast 'political theater'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-impeachment-40ef81572403c82422464169e67554d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawyers for Donald Trump on Monday blasted the impeachment case against him as an act of “political theater” by Democrats, whom they accused of exploiting for their own party’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery disease which 'causes people to throw up blood' kills 'at least 15 victims'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mystery-disease-causes-people-throw-23463535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A health official claimed the strange disease emerged in the Chunya district in the Mbeye region of Tanzania and said experts were investigating – but she was later suspended. An outbreak has been ruled out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Capitol on Jan. 6, Vets Fought on Both Sides of Battle...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/at-the-capitol-on-jan-6-veterans-fought-on-both-sides-of-an-american-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As Samuel Hahn of the Metropolitan Police Department struggled to hold back rioters storming the Capitol on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish man strikes up 37-year friendship with swan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-turkey-friendships-animals-4f953fb187d21593775156f9e37964c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDIRNE, Turkey (AP) — An unusual friendship between a Turkish man and a swan he rescued has endured for decades. Retired postman Recep Mirzan found Garip, a female swan, 37 years ago in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His Biz Shunned, She Resigned, Everyone Sued: What Became of Trump Election Dead-Enders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/what-became-of-trumps-election-dead-enders-his-biz-is-shunned-she-resigned-and-everyone-is-being-sued</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the current ruin of Trump's hardcore election dead-enders came as a direct result of their decisions to become major players in Trump’s failed endeavor to cling to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen apologizes to Stormy Daniels for 'needless pain'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/537776-michael-cohen-apologizes-to-stormy-daniels-for-needless-pain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump's onetime fixer and personal attorney Michael Cohen has apologized to adult-film star Stormy Daniels for the pain he says he caused her while working for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy theories hang over county plans to buy voting machines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/conspiracy-theories-hang-over-a-trump-loving-county-e2-80-99s-plans-to-buy-dominion-voting-machines/ar-BB1duGgq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The situation in Stark County is a testament to how viral claims repeatedly debunked by courts and authorities have persisted, hanging over local decision-making and saddling officials with the daunting task of somehow rebuilding public trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As alcohol abuse rises, hospitals see wave of deadly liver disease...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/alcohol-abuse-rises-amid-pandemic-130030403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UCLA, USC and hospitals nationwide are treating more patients for alcoholic hepatitis, cirrhosis and other conditions amid COVID-19 shutdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Few say democracy working well...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-biden-cabinet-democracy-elections-only-on-ap-403434c2e728e42a955c72a652a59318</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Only a fragment of Americans believe democracy is thriving in the U.S., even as broad majorities agree that representative government is one of the country's bedrock principles,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE IS ON: First of three Mars missions ready to arrive...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/02/08/First-of-three-Mars-missions-ready-to-arrive/9341612466213/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new era of Mars exploration begins Monday with the expected arrival of the United Arab Emirates' Hope spacecraft in vicinity of the Red Planet -- the first of three such arrivals planned for February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unleashed Bezos will shift space venture into hyperdrive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/unleashed-jeff-bezos-seek-shift-120913932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freed from his daily obligations at Amazon.com Inc, Jeff Bezos is expected to turn up the heat on his space venture, Blue Origin, as it faces a pivotal year and fierce competition from Elon Musk's SpaceX, industry sources said. The 57-year-old Bezos, a lifelong space enthusiast and the world's second-richest person behind Musk, said last week he is stepping down as chief executive of the e-commerce company as he looks to focus on personal projects. Blue Origin has fallen far behind SpaceX on orbital transportation, and lost out to SpaceX and United Launch Alliance (ULA) on billions of dollars' worth of U.S. national security launch contracts which begin in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic line judges make Grand Slam debut...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannot-serious-electronic-line-judges-083755583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The days of tennis players arguing whether balls are in or out could be coming to a close, after the smooth introduction of electronic line judging at the Australian Open on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu walks out on his own corruption trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-netanyahu-walks-out-on-his-own-corruption-trial/ar-BB1duCPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli leader was summoned to court for the second phase of hearings, just weeks before elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Hastens Exit from Israel's Ultra-Orthodox Community...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/08/virus-hastens-exit-from-israels-ultra-orthodox-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — When the coronavirus pandemic swept through Israel, it upended Racheli Ohayon’s life in unexpected ways. The 21-year-old phone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of maskless Tampa fans flood streets, risking superspreader event...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/thousands-of-maskless-tampa-fans-flooded-the-streets-celebrating-the-super-bowl-win-while-risking-a-superspreader-event/ar-BB1duDel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hordes of football fans crammed into bars, clogged up streets and belted chants from their uncovered mouths in Tampa this weekend, defying pleas from public health experts to help stop the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like GAMESTOP, BED BATH &amp; BEYOND reduced to stock meme. But 42,000 people work there...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Like-GameStop-Bed-Bath-amp-Beyond-has-been-15932853.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching short sellers duke it out with Reddit- and Robinhood-inspired buyers over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY SCHOOLS THE CHILDREN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-new-england-patriots-football-7418cec28100392206508c6a1496cb39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — So much of it looked familiar — from the heartfelt rendering of the national anthem, to the silvery, star-studded halftime show, to Tom Brady standing there at the end with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial to open with sense of urgency, speed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-capitol-siege-trials-acquittals-40ef81572403c82422464169e67554d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Donald Trump's historic second impeachment trial is opening this week with a sense of urgency — by Democrats who want to hold the former president accountable for the violent...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
