<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The Day the Space Station Lurched...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/the-day-the-space-station-lurched/ar-AAMOj4W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent arrival at the International Space Station created a little too much excitement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influencer arrested after man assaulted, left with brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/influencer-hayes-grier-arrested-after-a-man-was-assaulted-and-left-with-brain-damage/ar-AAMO26u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influencer Hayes Grier was arrested in Charlotte, North Carolina, after a man was left with a broken eyeball socket, brain damage, and bruised ribs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will high-res image of monkey brain unlock secrets?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3143188/chinese-scientists-hope-unlock-secrets-human-brain-high-res</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found a way to get a full 3D image providing an unprecedented level of detail that could be used for research into neurological conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery nightly siren coming from Census HQ keeping residents awake...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/prince-georges-county/unidentified-noise-keeping-suitland-residents-up-at-night/2753920/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Suitland, Maryland, say an unidentified siren sounds off regularly through the night, making it difficult to sleep. They want to know where the noise is coming from and they want it to stop so they can get some sleep. “It sounds kind of like a combination of a tornado siren and a spaceship taking off, like the siren…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions at risk of eviction as moratorium expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210801-millions-of-americans-at-risk-of-eviction-as-moratorium-expires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pandemic-related U.S. government ban on residential evictions expired at midnight on Saturday, putting millions of American renters at risk of being forced from their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People experiencing hair loss months after Covid infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1470608/hair-loss-coronavirus-long-covid-symptoms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONG COVID sufferers can experience hair loss months after an infection, a doctor has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Aaliyah Drugged Before Fatal Plane Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-books-shock-claim-aaliyah-was-drugged-before-her-fatal-plane-crash/ar-AAMOdfr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This month marks the 20th anniversary of rising star Aaliyah’s death. The Princess of R&amp;B tragically died in a plane crash in the Bahamas after shooting the music video for “Rock the Boat,” a song that would become part of her final album. Still, two decades later, an air of mystery surrounds what went so tragically wrong on Aug. 25, 2001, when an hour-long flight from the beachy shores of the Abaco Islands to Miami claimed the lives of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of Paradise burning -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9848737/Thousands-flee-Dixie-Fire-California-races-Paradise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dixie Fire is currently burning as California's largest active blaze relocating thousands and burning nearly 241,000 acres, or about 375 square miles. The flames burned through Meadow Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine quick reaction force deployed twice in last 30 days to defend embassies...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/us-marine-force-deployed-twice-defend-embassies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Marine Security Augmentation Unit has deployed twice in the past 30 days to support and protect embassies in Africa and the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL star's pregnant wife says he tanked games for gambling profit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/01/evander-kane-tanked-games-for-gambling-profit-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose Sharks forward Evander Kane was called out by his pregnant wife on Instagram for being a gambling addict who’s even thrown his own games. The NHL is now intending to investigate the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON APPEARS TO SHOVE FAN...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/07/31/lebron-james-appears-shoves-fan-video-usher-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a video tweeted by @Stephreyy26_, LeBron James was at an Usher concert in Las Vegas when he appeared to shove a fan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mayor Partied Maskless Hours Before New Mask Rules...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/31/dc-mayor-muriel-bowser-mask-mandate-birthday-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor's maskless birthday party was also attended by comedian Dave Chappelle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bible-reading, 65-year-old woman became Wall Street's hottest stock picker...</title>
      <link>https://airmail.news/issues/2021-7-31/prophet-of-the-golden-bull</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;airmail.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's a Bible-reading, Trump-supporting, divorced mother with a $53 billion investment fund and a rabid band of followers who hang on her every word.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dressel Joins Exclusive Club With 5 Golds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/dressel-joins-exclusive-club-with-5-golds-at-tokyo-olympics/3190465/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caeleb Dressel has earned his fifth swimming gold medal of the Tokyo Olympics as part of Team USA’s winning 4x100m medley relay squad, putting him in elite company. Earlier in the day, the 24-year-old Dressel cruised to a relatively easy victory in the 50-meter freestyle, touching in an Olympic record of 21.07 seconds. With his fifth victory, Dressel joins Americans…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vax mandates will backfire. People will resist even more'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-vaccine-mandates-will-backfire-people-will-resist-even-more/ar-AAMN584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Persuading, not dictating, is how Biden can avoid a crisis of legitimacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JUNGLE' FLOP AT BOX?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/31/box-office-you-jungle-cruise-you-lose-200-million-disney-theme-park-ride-turned-movie-set-to-flop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can’t I remember being on the Jungle Cruise ride at Disneyland, but I know it’s popular. So why not make a movie about it? I’ll tell you why not: no one’s going. The $200 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin teases Senate run...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/31/sarah-palin-teases-2022-senate-run-in-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin said she may yet jump back into politics, teasing the possibility of a Senate run in 2022 against incumbent Lisa Murkowski.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee faces unprecedented choice of whether to call Republican lawmakers to testify...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-committee-faces-unprecedented-choice-of-whether-to-call-republican-lawmakers-to-testify/ar-AAMMF4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reports pressure drop in space station service module...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/russia-reports-pressure-drop-space-station-service-module-2021-07-31/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of Russia's Roscosmos space agency said on Saturday that pressure in a Russian service module on the International Space Station had dropped as a result of an air leak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti police identify former top judge as suspect in ex-president's killing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/565763-haiti-police-identify-former-top-judge-as-suspect-in-ex-presidents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haitian police are investigating what role a former Supreme Court judge may have played in the assassination of Haiti’s president following new developments announced on Friday, Reuters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ammunition shelves bare as gun sales continue to soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-gun-politics-86e61939eb4ae1230e110ed6d7576b70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — The COVID-19 pandemic, coupled with record sales of firearms, has fueled a shortage of ammunition in the United States that’s impacting law enforcement agencies, people seeking personal protection, recreational shooters and hunters -- and could deny new gun owners the practice they need to handle their weapons safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacon may disappear in California as pig rules take effect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-health-california-coronavirus-pandemic-5ebe70407fcd94ef712c16410f32c4b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Thanks to a reworked menu and long hours, Jeannie Kim managed to keep her San Francisco restaurant alive during the coronavirus pandemic. That makes it all the more frustrating that she fears her breakfast-focused diner could be ruined within months by new rules that could make one of her top menu items — bacon — hard to get in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Spreader Sex Houses to Nude Beach Fistfights, Vaxxed Partying Not All Cracked Up to Be...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/super-spreader-sex-houses-nude-102827164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ilan Deutsch/Paris Match via Getty ImagesAfter being woken up by the sound of a little dog below me humping his favorite teddy bear, I crawl down the ladder of a kid bunk bed and head downstairs to assess the damage of last night’s debauchery. Cigarette butts, empty wine bottles, and half eaten baguettes litter the kitchen and pool area of this mini French mansion my friend Jackie is currently dog sitting at. There’s puke around the toilet in the “cave” downstairs, a hot Frenchie sashaying throu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula 2022? Brazil poised for sensational political comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/30/lula-2022-brazil-poised-for-sensational-political-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With former president’s political rights restored, polls suggest he would thrash Jair Bolsonaro if he stands for election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS prepares for bloody showdown after littering streets with headless corpses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-jihadis-prepare-bloody-showdown-24653728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrorists affiliated to ISIS have wreaked havoc in Mozambique in recent years, leaving thousands dead. However, a new fighting force is now aiming to halt their advances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths rise 300%...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9846441/Deltas-deadly-surge-Daily-deaths-rise-nearly-300-891-number-new-cases-doubles-190k.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Thursday there were 321 deaths from COVID-19 reported. Twenty four hours later, the figure had risen to 891. The shocking surge suggests that the United States is feeling the full force of Delta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer hoped history books would help her Capitol riot clients grow. She was called traitor -- and worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-lawyer-hoped-history-books-would-help-her-capitol-riot-clients-grow-she-was-called-a-traitor-e2-80-94-and-worse/ar-AAMMoRF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shaner’s method seemed unconventional to the public, but not to her. She’s been giving her clients books for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden eagle populations struggling in West...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-business-science-health-utah-ca29dab560179148f4d2be8208093862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNOWVILLE, Utah (AP) — Dustin Maloney is in sagebrush country in remote northern Utah west of Snowville on a grueling hiking trip full of dust and heat and sweat. He’s got one eye looking for snakes and the other on the ground so he doesn’t lose his step and take a perilous fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE BRACED FOR PROTESTS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-256bbfd835e6388219390cacb536eaba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France braced for more protests on Saturday against the upcoming special virus passes that will be needed to enter restaurants, as police took up posts along Paris’ Champs-Elysees to guard against an invasion of the famed avenue by rowdy demonstrators.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
