<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Teachers shot 'execution style' during school shooting drill...</title>
      <link>https://www.theindychannel.com/news/politics/indiana-teachers-hit-with-pellets-during-active-shooter-training-ista-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theindychannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indiana teachers were hit with pellets during an active shooter training at a school, the Indiana State Teachers Association said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust lawsuit against mega hotel chains moves forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-leisure-antitrust/lawsuit-on-hotels-internet-advertising-tactics-moves-forward-idUSKCN1R22JT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Thursday rebuffed a request by hotel chains including Hyatt H...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical flaw lets hackers control lifesaving devices implanted inside patients...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2019/03/critical-flaw-lets-hackers-control-lifesaving-devices-implanted-inside-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Implanted devices from Medtronic can have their firmware rewritten, DHS warns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Amendment 'Sanctuary' Cities, Counties, States Spring Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-20/second-amendment-sanctuary-cities-counties-states-spring-across-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans in special election use as foe to run against...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/article228235684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERAL TO GRILL GOOGLE ON CHINA TIES</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/cultural-clash/2019/03/21/dunford-to-meet-with-google-for-debate-on-chinese-ties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon's top uniformed officer thinks tech companies need to be smarter with how they approach China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possessing, distributing footage cause for prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/21/new-zealand-vows-pragmatic-approach-to-policing-ba/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Police warned Thursday that social media companies will face consequences for failing to keep their platforms free of footage recorded during last week’s mass shootings at two mosques in Christchurch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears -- communicate like humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2019/03/sun-bears-play-mimic-faces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's smallest bears have a social skill set previously thought limited to apes and dogs, and there may be more species like them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz pleads with visitors: Stop disrespectful photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/auschwitz-museum-asks-visitors-not-to-balance-on-train-tracks/a-48006024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The museum called on visitors to behave more respectfully after finding photos of people balancing on the tracks at the former Nazi death camp. "There are better places to learn how to walk on a balance beam," it said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial expressions throw doubt on mankind superiority...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-03-world-smallest-facial-human-superiority.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's smallest bears can exactly mimic another bear's facial expressions, casting doubt on humans and other primates' supremacy at this subtle form of communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Bans Ads That Help Chinese Circumvent Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-21/be-evil-google-bans-vpn-ads-helping-chinese-circumvent-censorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard investigates student 'trauma' after prof agrees to represent Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/21/harvard-investigates-trauma-among-students-law-professor-agrees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard University has launched an investigation into law professor Ronald Sullivan after he agreed to represent Harvey Weinstein in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biker gangs guard  NZ mosques during Friday prayer...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/biker-gangs-stand-guard-outside-nz-mosques-during-first-friday-prayer-since-massacre-a4096341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bikers have vowed to stand guard outside New Zealand mosques as Muslims take part in their first Friday prayer following the Christchurch shootings. Gangs like The Mongrel Mob, King Cobra and The Black Power have promised to support and protect their local Muslim communities across the country, after 50 people were killed and 50 injured in the attack on March 15. Waikato Mongrel Mob president Sonny Fatu offered to shield the Jamia Masjid Mosque in Hamilton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA bans ROUNDUP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/LA-County-Halts-Use-of-Popular-Weed-Killer-on-County-Property-507399471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors Tuesday directed all departments to stop using a popular weed killer until more is known about its potential health and environmental effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidnapper made woman pose for selfies, read Bible...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/suspected-kidnapper-made-boston-woman-pose-selfies-read-bible-officials-n985791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman was found alive on Jan. 21 in Victor Peña's apartment, three days after she went missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters weigh personality vs. policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/to-nerd-out-or-rock-out-democratic-voters-weigh-personality-vs-policy-in-primary-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the campaign heats up, voters in early primary states are trying to figure out the best way to beat Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines practice seizing islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/us-marines-seize-small-island-to-train-for-a-possible-china-fight-2019-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Marines are dusting off the island-hopping strategy they used in the Pacific during World War II as they prepare for a high-end fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOKER:  President 'Literally' Could 'Cause People's Death'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/booker-trump-policies-literally-could-cause-peoples-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Cory Booker said Donald Trump's policies could "literally" cause people to die, called for "radical love" in politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating billboards turn Miami waterfront into Times Square...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article228192969.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Marine: Troops at Border 'Unacceptable Risk'...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/03/21/commandant-of-the-marines-says-deploying-troops-to-the-border-poses-unacceptable-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commandant of the Marines has warned the Pentagon that deployments to the southwest border and funding transfers under the president's emergency declaration, among other unexpected demands, have posed “unacceptable risk to Marine Corps combat readiness and solvency.” In two internal memos, Marine Corps Gen. Robert Neller said the “unplanned/unbudgeted” deployment along the border that President Trump ordered last fall, and shifts of other funds to support border security, had forced him to cancel or reduce planned military training in at least five countries, and delay urgent repairs at bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey birth a step to saving fertility of boys with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34fc33ade9aa4406a214e0fe2605ff9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Scientists are closing in on a way to help young boys undergoing cancer treatment preserve their future fertility — and the proof is the first monkey born from the experimental...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More whales under Golden Gate Bridge spark starvation worries...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/whales-sharks/article/gray-whale-in-sf-bay-golden-gate-whale-watching-13703705.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On their way from Mexico to Alaska, gray whales are making a pit-stop in San Francisco - and staying a while.  "Historically, one or two gray whales would temporarily pass underneath the Golden Gate Bridge during this time period. Last week alone, experts counted five entering the Bay," said the Marine Mammal Center in a recent press release.  Not only are more coming to town, they're also hanging out much longer than expected. One gray whale has been in and around the San Francisco Bay for more than a month now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last stronghold liberated...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/isis-has-officially-crumbled-and-last-stronghold-liberated-fox-news-has-learned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The caliphate has crumbled, and the final offensive is over. While the official announcement hasn’t yet been made – Fox News has been told that this village, the last ISIS stronghold, is liberated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADHD drugs lead to psychosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/adhd-drugs-can-lead-psychosis-some-according-new-study/dUyKiThflPYe0ySlMn9I1K/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADHD drugs can lead to psychosis in some according to new study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT: Military steps up preparations in case of no deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/brexit-military-steps-up-preparations-in-case-of-no-deal-11671941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation Redfold will direct some 3,500 military personnel who have been put on standby for a no-deal scenario.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to recognize Golan Heights as part of Israel...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6835799/Trump-says-U-S-recognize-Golan-Heights-Israel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumors of the potential move swirled in diplomatic circles this week as the American Israel Public Affairs Committee prepares for its annual meeting next week, where Netanyahu will speak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model with Down syndrome breaks stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/lifestyles/parenting/aisha-sultan/wildwood-model-with-down-syndrome-breaks-down-stereotypes/article_2cbb30a1-342e-5476-948a-d12599490a74.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lunchroom can get a little rowdy when the kindergarten through second-grade classes fill up the tables. Grace Strobel scans the room for little hands waving in the air. She</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More revelations to come in Trudeau scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-politics/ex-canadian-minister-says-more-revelations-to-come-in-scandal-surrounding-trudeau-idUSKCN1R21NG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Canadian cabinet minister, who had quit in protest over the government's ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Letterman: I stayed on TV too long...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/40180066e2cd44c5848c22ba4e2eae61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — David Letterman says he stuck around on network television about 10 years too long. He made that admission during an appearance Thursday on Ellen DeGeneres' talk show....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Left Up Video of New Zealand Shootings for an Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facebook-our-ai-tools-failed-to-catch-new-zealand-attack-video-11553156141?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook left a gruesome video of shootings at a New Zealand mosque up on its site for half an hour after a user brought it to the company’s attention, a previously unreported delay that highlights the social media company’s difficulty in controlling violent content on its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Ratings Sink to All-Time Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/empire-ratings-series-lows-jussie-smollett/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Empire" sunk to series lows on Wednesday, a week after an already-rough midseason return. It was the Fox drama's 2nd episode since Jussie Smollett's arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATION:  Our phones ARE listening to us...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/8678640/proof-phones-listening-to-us/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVE you ever been talking about a pair of trainers or holiday destination, and then suddenly seen an advert for that precise thing pop up on social media? Us too. As incredible as it sounds, it mi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 STRIKES:  Macron says no-deal Brexit if UK MPs reject accord AGAIN... </title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/454403-macron-no-deal-brexit-deal-reject/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK will have to leave the EU with “no deal” if the British MPs reject the EU-backed accord once again, the French President Emmanuel Macron has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TODAY'S EPISODE:  THE CONWAY SHOW!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/kellyanne-conway-calls-husbands-attacks-on-trump-unusual-thanks-president-for-defending-her-from-perceived-unfairness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kellyanne Conway weighed in Thursday on the bitter Twitter feud between her husband George and President Trump, calling her spouse's criticism of her boss "unusual" while thanking Trump for defending her from what “he thinks is unfairness.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Passwords Visible Internally...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-21/facebook-says-millions-of-passwords-were-visible-internally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE: TRUMP WORST KIND OF DUMB...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435059-george-conway-goes-on-early-morning-tweetstorm-against-trump-worst</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, lashed out at President Trump in a new series of tweets early Thursday, saying that he is a liar and "the worst kind of dumb."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro 'turned me into a pariah', says gay lawmaker who fled Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-turned-pariah-says-gay-lawmaker-fled-brazil-175945188.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's first openly gay lawmaker, Jean Wyllys, who fled his country over mounting death threats after the election of far-right President Jair Bolsonaro, fears he won't be returning home anytime soon. In recent months, he said: "I received death threats by telephone, on social media and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labrador Retriever Top Dog Breed For 28th Straight Year!</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/labrador-retriever-most-popular-dog-breed-28th-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labrador retrievers aren't letting go of their hold on U.S. dog lovers, but German shorthaired pointers are tugging on the top ranks of doggy popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May stares into the abyss...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190321141839-tntz7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-No deal beckons: EU presses May on Brexit deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration court backlog up 300%...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/immigration-court-backlog-up-300-system-on-brink-of-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Bar Association is warning of an “existential crisis” over the unprecedented surge in the number of immigration cases clogging up courts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Moves More Data to AMAZON Cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2019/03/another-defense-agency-migrates-data-amazon-cloud/155699/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Health Agency joins a growing list of defense agencies moving their data to the commercial cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Drops 3 Busloads of Illegals At Bus Station; Churches Scrambled to Provide Shelter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mrctv.org/blog/ice-reportedly-dropped-3-busloads-illegal-aliens-greyhound-station-churches-scrambled-provide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mrctv.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA wants to track data on scooter users...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/la-wants-to-track-data-on-scooter-users-is-it/article_ca99e38b-52f3-535b-8444-73411cf32a97.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The abrupt arrival of thousands of electric scooters in Los Angeles last year has already forced public, sometimes ugly, disagreements about how the city’s street and sidewalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan forces detain key aide to opposition leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dc2c5f751aa04454b79769d17748ee94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Masked security forces detained a key aide to Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido in a raid on his home early Thursday, arriving in a convoy of vehicles and breaking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigative division of ICE feels ostracized...</title>
      <link>https://pressfrom.info/us/news/us/-257742-investigative-division-of-ice-feels-ostracized.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pressfrom.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mammoth moves: frozen cells come to life, but only just  	 A team of scientists in Japan has successfully coaxed activity from 28,000-year-old cells from a frozen mammoth implanted into mouse c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER GETS READY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/093727be24b649f7adad971e0b48878d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said he believes special counsel Robert Mueller's report should be released to the public, even as he disparaged its very existence as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne Bashes Husband: 'Air Grievances in Private'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/kellyanne-conway-bashes-her-husband-on-fox-you-air-your-grievances-in-private/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX to blast people across Atlantic in 30 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6830075/SpaceX-blast-people-Atlantic-rocket-30-minutes-2030.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-haul flights in a rocket will soon wipe out plane travel on Earth, said UBS analysts. It may only take 29 minutes from London to New York and less than one hour to Sydney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/435073-ocasio-cortez-staff-received-risk-assessment-training-from-police-due-to-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's (D-N.Y.) staff has reportedly been trained on performing risk assessments due to the amount of death threats the congresswoman has received.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The naked populist: Baudet stuns Netherlands...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/naked-populist-thierry-baudet-stuns-netherlands-131930952.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former academic with a love of classical allusions and naked poolside Instagram photos, Thierry Baudet has stunned the Dutch political world with his victory in provincial elections. The latest in a line of flamboyant Dutch populists, 36-year-old Baudet and his Forum for Democracy party have been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wingsuit Stunt Lights Up LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/red-bull-wingsuit-stunt-downtown-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People in downtown Los Angeles saw what appeared to be a flaming fireball burning through the sky Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police put out PSA to calm residents...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/03/20/fireball-above-l-a-not-an-alien-invasion-just-a-film-shoot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Police Department would like residents to know that aliens are not invading. The LAPD says a fireball that dashed through the sky over downtown Wednesday evening was part of a movie production. The department tweeted a video of the fiery streak with the reassuring message that it wasn't a meteor or an alien invasion — "just a film shoot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers Call for Help With Debt at 1980s Levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/americas-farmers-call-help-debts-climb-1980s-levels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US figure skater accused of deliberately slashing rival at world championships...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/21/us-figure-skater-accused-deliberately-slashing-rival-world-championships/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American figure skater has been accused of colliding into a 16-year-old Korean rival in the final warm-up session ahead of the opening of the World Figure Skating Championships in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden advisers debate Stacey Abrams as out-of-the-gate VP choice...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2020-presidential-election-joe-biden-stacey-abrams-vp-54472f8f-5bb2-4d1f-bc7c-0544a09ebba5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They want to show the former V.P. "isn't just another old white guy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New populist star emerges from Dutch local elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/602a05ea46894b2a859fa9c6595a9da7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Netherlands has woken up to a new star of right-wing populism, as the party of a Latin-quoting, philosophy-reading lawmaker surged past anti-Islam firebrand Geert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Military to be deployed for next round of Yellow Vest protests...</title>
      <link>http://en.rfi.fr/france/20190320-military-be-deployed-saturdays-french-yellow-vests-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.rfi.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government is to deploy its military anti-terror force as reinforcement during Act 19 of Saturday Yellow Vest protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastest-shrinking cities in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2019/03/21/population-decline-us-cities-losing-most-residents/39199277/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a fifth of all states reported a population decline in the last two years. In many metro areas, it has been a long-term trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise in migrants at sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/With-more-focus-on-the-southern-border-US-13705397.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO - The Trump administration's focus on the southern border has closed some gaps in immigration enforcement but expanded a challenging problem, law enforcement officials here said Wednesday: undocumented immigrants sneaking into California by sea.  The migrants enter in various ways, including on personal watercraft and small, open-top motorboats known as pangas that often arrive under cover of darkness, said Jeremy Thompson, Customs and Border Protection's director of marine operations in San Diego.  On Sunday, the 87-foot Coast Guard patrol boat USCGC Petrel stopped a vessel with 12 migrants from Mexico aboard near California's southern maritime border. On Tuesday, a Customs and Border Protection team on a high-speed coastal interceptor vessel stopped another group, disabling a boat with gunfire after it failed to stop, and detaining eight more migrants, Thompson said.  Chief Patrol Agent Rodney Scott, who oversees CBP operations in San Diego, said that he expects smugglers to adjust their tactics as U.S. officials alter theirs, and he believes that the United States is taking away most of the "low-risk ways" to get into the country.  "We've been busy out here," Scott said. "Once the rhetoric started with the wall, it definitely picked up in the maritime."  The intercepts are carried out by both the Coast Guard and CBP, which has an Air and Marine Operations branch. They coordinate plans through a Joint Harbor Operations Center at Coast Guard Air Station San Diego, where personnel scan computer screens that display images from dozens of cameras, watching the coastline for watercraft that look out of place.  Across Southern California, 1,022 migrants were intercepted at sea in the fiscal year ending Sept. 30, Coast Guard officials have said. That was up from 213...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots enable BEES and FISH to talk to each other...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2019-03-robots-enable-bees-fish.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through an imaginative experiment, researchers were able to get two extremely different animal species located far apart to interact with each other and reach a shared decision with the help of robots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Millennials care more about date's politics than good sex...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/20/millennials-care-more-about-dates-politics-than-good-sex-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody’s sleeping with the enemy these days. “If I see somebody who’s like, ‘I’m moderate or conservative,’ I keep swiping,” Bronx resident Nadine Anglesey tells The Post. The 33-year-old art…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest Accused Of Groping Woman During Last Rites...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/03/20/catholic-priest-accused-groping-texas-woman-last-rites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman reported Rev. Gerold Langsch first anointed her chest with holy water, then began to apply lotion, massaging a breast, pinching a nipple and asking "Does that feel good?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Inside Unlikely Rise...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/longform/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-profile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez represents a vision of the Democratic Party's future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand to Impose Sweeping Gun Ban After Mosque Killings...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-zealand-to-ban-military-style-semiautomatic-weapons-and-assault-rifles-11553134883 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern said she would ban all military-style semiautomatic weapons and assault rifles in the wake of the Christchurch mosque massacre that left 50 people dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Ancient Societies Hit Million People, Vengeful Gods Appeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/65039-punishing-gods-rise-with-complex-societies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belief in a punishing, moralizing god follows the rise of complex societies, new research shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternal shell: Sacred turtle embalmed in Hanoi...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/eternal-shell--sacred-turtle-embalmed-in-hanoi-11366274</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sacred giant turtle that died in Hanoi's storied Hoan Kiem lake has been given a new lease on life by city authorities who have embalmed the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tax Reform Causing Freakouts in Rich New York Area Towns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/trump-tax-reform-causing-freakouts-in-rich-new-york-area-towns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Tax Reform Hits Home in Wealthy New York Suburbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canned air and water-spraying drones: Smog remedies...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-03-canned-air-water-spraying-drones-smog.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As millions of people in Asia choke under polluted skies, authorities have turned to water-dispersing drones and outdoor air purifiers to improve air quality, while companies have tried to cash in by selling everything from canned air to lung-purifying teas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary Birth: Twin Inside Twin...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2019/03/20/news/a-twin-inside-a-twin-in-colombia-an-extraordinary-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON pressuring brands: Lower prices or no advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/20/amazon-aggressively-suspending-ads-of-unprofitable-products-as-focus-on-the-bottom-line-grows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has been more aggressively enforcing its policy of suspending ads if the product being promoted doesn't make money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telecoms start blocking websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-03-19/after-blocking-zerohedge-and-others-nz-telcos-demand-big-tech-censorship-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts hundreds of drilling projects over 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2019/mar/20/judge-halts-drilling-climate-change-trump-administration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rebuke of the Trump administration’s ‘energy-first’ agenda, a judge rules greenhouse gas emissions must be considered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Red flag' plan to stop Trump: 1M more Florida voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2019/03/20/gillums-red-flag-plan-to-stop-trump-1m-new-florida-voters-927053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Tallahassee mayor said increased voter registration is crucial to the Democratic Party’s ability to survive and thrive in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT LEVEL OF CENSORSHIP IS HERE: THE BANNING OF URLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/the-final-level-of-censorship-is-here-the-banning-of-urls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Blocking Zero Hedge And Others, NZ Telcos Demand Big-Tech Censorship Surge To</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU hits GOOGLE with $1.7 billion fine for blocking ad rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90322678/google-hit-with-another-eu-antitrust-fine-the-grand-total-now-comes-to-e8-2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EU just gave the search giant another multibillion-euro fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kale now one of  most pesticide-contaminated vegetables...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/20/kale-is-now-one-of-the-most-pesticide-contaminated-vegetables.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kale joins the "Dirty Dozen" list this year. The list of fruits and vegetables with the most pesticide contamination also includes strawberries, spinach, nectarines, apples, grapes, peaches, cherries, pears, tomatoes, celery and potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth forecast cut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fed-rate-hikes-none-in-2019-federal-reserve-projects-no-rate-hikes-slower-growth-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central bank stands pat on interest rates and signals there may be no more hikes in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 Migrants Apprehended in Five Minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/03/20/400-migrants-apprehended-within-five-minutes-in-el-paso-sector/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents apprehended two large groups of Central American migrants after they illegally crossed the border from Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carter gets new title: Oldest living former president...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/jimmy-carter-gets-new-title-oldest-living-former-president/68TFzP9SMDjrVuqcUt3PkK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 94 years, 172 days the 39th president passes George H.W. Bush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol says detention centers are full; Starts releasing...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/nation/article_b47a4ead-d1f4-541b-9167-c80121d65c04.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Border Patrol released 50 recently apprehended migrants here Tuesday, the first of several hundred border-crossers who officials say will soon be freed because there is no room to hold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BATTLES GHOST OF MCCAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9cfac2db09c4aa884e9f17e5fcdf346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Casting aside rare censure from Republican lawmakers, President Donald Trump aimed new blasts of invective at the late John McCain Wednesday, even claiming credit for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Jury Finds ROUNDUP Causes Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-jury-finds-roundup-weed-killer-caused-cancer/story?id=61809259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial's second phase started on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>32 dogs trapped in 'hoarding' house saved from freezing waters... </title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2019/03/20/dogs-saved-freezing-waters-after-hoarding-house-gets-flooded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flooding hit much of the Midwest this week, particularly in Nebraska and Iowa, and morning temperatures in the area plunged into the low 30s.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
