<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'KILL ME'</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/ricky-gervais-attacks-woke-hollywood-and-shreds-apple-disney-and-amazon-in-savage-golden-globes-monologue-2020-01-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It didn’t take long for the notorious pot-stirrer and five-time host to draw gasps at the 77th annual Golden Globes on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GET DRUNK, TAKE YOUR DRUGS'</title>
      <link>https://www.eonline.com/ap/news/1108373/ricky-gervais-truly-didn-t-care-as-he-hosted-the-2020-golden-globes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aside from a scathing monologue, Ricky Gervais mostly stayed in the sidelines as he hosted the 2020 Golden Globes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Gets Wiped Out...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/77-golden-globe-awards-show-review-ricky-gervais-1917-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-succession-fleabag-1202821358/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of the start of Harvey Weinstein’s rape trial, there were literally no bombshells tonight on the Golden Globes. Bombshell star Charlize Theron lost out on a Best Actress – Dr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GET DRUNK, TAKE YOUR DRUGS'</title>
      <link>https://drudgereport.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'KNOW NOTHING OF REAL WORLD'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ricky-gervais-golden-globes-monologue-mocks-hollywoods-jeffrey-epstein-ties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back for the fifth time, Ricky Gervais opened the 2020 Golden Globes by roasting the hell out of the Hollywood crowd in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICKY TELLS HOLLYWOOD 'F OFF'</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/ricky-gervais-golden-globes-monologue-gets-political-1266308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During his monologue, the 'Office' creator also took shots at Felicity Huffman and Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBES 2020... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9146ceebd39493cc6c0fe3a8ff587d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on on the 77th annual Golden Globe Awards honoring achievements in television and film and being presented Sunday at the Beverly Hilton in Beverly Hills,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubles down on striking cultural sites...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d3385ab6c29c3da3ab9b081bae53884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump insisted Sunday that Iranian cultural sites were fair game for the U.S. military, dismissing concerns within his own administration that doing so would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA POLL:  Sanders, Biden, Buttigieg Tied...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/iowa-poll-shows-sanders-biden-buttigieg-tied-campaign-update/ar-BBYDlYE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL PRICE SPIKES</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-continue-to-rise-us-stock-futures-retreat-as-mideast-tensions-remain-high-2020-01-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices rose more than 1% in late Sunday trading, continuing their surge in the wake of last week’s killing of Iranian Gen. Qassem Soleimani in a U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2020-golden-globes-winners-full-list-updating-live-1265577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime's 'The Loudest Voice' and Hulu's 'Ramy' picked up early wins on Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens sanctions ON IRAQ 'like they've never seen before'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/06/trump-threatens-to-slap-sanctions-on-iraq-like-theyve-never-seen-before.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His remarks come after the Iraqi parliament passed a resolution calling for the government to expel foreign troops from the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS Officially Moving On From Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/cowboys-part-ways-coach-garrett-missing-nfl-playoffs-002340374--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dallas Cowboys made it official Sunday, confirming they are parting ways with head coach Jason Garrett a week after their NFL season ended short of the playoffs. Team owner Jerry Jones confirmed the widely expected news in an official statement. &amp;quot;We are extremely grateful to Jason Garrett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Cyber Attack on Billionaire Adelson Provides Lesson...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-cyber-attack-billionaire-adelson-170413240.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the U.S. awaits possible retribution over a recent airstrike that killed a top general, there’s at least one American businessman who can attest, in detail, to what happened after he provoked Iran.In October 2013, Sheldon Adelson, the casino magnate and prominent supporter of conservative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Climbs to Highest Level Since 2013...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gold-climbs-highest-level-since-230920306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Gold surged to the highest level in more than six years as rising tensions in the Middle East stoked demand for haven assets. Palladium also extended gains to an all-time high.Iran’s government said it would no longer abide by any limits on its enrichment of uranium following the killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE QUESTIONS RAISED IN CONTROVERSIAL DEATH OF JEFFREY EPSTEIN; GUARD WHO FOUND HIM HAS YET TO BE INTERVIEWED BY INVESTIGATORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/did-jeffrey-epstein-kill-himself-60-minutes-investigates-2020-01-05/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein was a convicted sex offender and a wealthy financier with powerful friends. 60 Minutes examines the circumstances surrounding his death in a Manhattan federal jail cell. Warning: This report contains graphic images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Bloomberg pops to third place in Dem race...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/476689-bloomberg-rises-to-third-place-alongside-warren-in-national-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg saw a 6-point bump in the latest Hill-HarrisX survey of the Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More rockets hit near US embassy in Baghdad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/least-two-rockets-hit-near-us-embassy-baghdad-000726339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baghdad (AFP) - Two rockets hit near the US embassy in Iraq's capital Sunday, witnesses told AFP, hours after the ambassador was summoned over a US strike that killed top Iraqi and Iranian commanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv a target...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-ex-guards-chief-vows-turn-tel-aviv-212430978.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former head of Iran's Revolutionary Guards threatened on Sunday to turn the Israeli cities of Haifa and Tel Aviv "to dust" if the US attacks targets in Iran. "If America takes any measures after our military response, we will turn Tel Aviv and Haifa to dust," Mohsen Rezai,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Activates Terrorism Alert Network... </title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/homeland-security-issues-terrorism-alert-after-soleimani-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security issued a new terrorism alert Saturday evening following the assassination this week of top Iranian military leader Qassem Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS Officially Moving On From Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/01/05/jason-garrett-no-longer-cowboys-head-coach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a week of will they or won't they, the Dallas Cowboys have made their final decision and are officially moving on from head coach Jason Garrett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES On High Alert...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/golden-globes-security-iran-tensions-soleimani-death-donald-trump-nbc-1202820982/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Donald Trump’s drone strike on Iran’s top general Qasem Soleimani just days ago, safety concerns and security are high at today’s Golden Globes, very high. “We are …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On short notice, fast-response force flies to Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9b7169d2cf472b8f643ecd69b47730a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT BRAGG, N.C. (AP) — Being a U.S. soldier in a fast-response force sometimes means being sent halfway across the world within a day, leaving no time to say goodbye to those staying behind....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFERS $80 MILLION FOR TRUMP'S HEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2020/01/huge-breaking-news-iranian-regime-offers-80-million-for-president-donald-trumps-head-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/politics/2020/01/04/britain-sends-warships-persian-gulf-protect-citizens-wake-qassim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Royal Navy was on Saturday night deployed in the Persian Gulf to &amp;quot;take all necessary steps to protect our ships and citizens&amp;quot; in the wake of Donald Trump's decision to assassinate Iran's top general Qassim Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani mixed White House role, personal cybersecurity business...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/Rudy-Giuliani-mixed-White-House-role-personal-14949921.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani’s mixing of his business interests, closeness with President Trump and involvement in government actions involving Ukraine is the subject of much attention as the impeachment case against the president moves toward the Senate. But a Chronicle investigation has found that Giuliani’s blurring of White House and personal business didn’t start with Ukraine. It began in 2017 when Giuliani was named as a White House adviser in an area where he had limited experience but was trying to build a clientele: cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi parliament passes resolution to end foreign troop presence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200105141444-bjkfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/PARLIAMENT-RESOLUTION (URGENT):Iraqi parliament passes resolution to end foreign troop presence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi parliament meets to discuss withdrawal of US troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/world/mena/iraqi-parliament-meets-to-discuss-withdrawal-of-us-troops-1.960145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq's parliament held an extraordinary session on Sunday with Prime Minister Adel Abdul Mahdi in attendance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters thought she was talking to Greta Thunberg. It was actually trolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Rep-Maxine-Waters-thought-she-was-talking-to-14950261.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The call starts innocently enough: Rep. Maxine Waters, D-Calif., warmly greets the voices on the line, whom a staffer identifies as Greta Thunberg and her father, Svante. They share a laugh about Waters's nickname, "Auntie Maxine." The congresswoman praises her young caller for her climate change activism.  "You have made quite a big, big, big, big thunder on this issue. I am really, really very proud of you and the work that you're doing," Waters is heard saying.  The congresswoman and her staff thought they had connected with Thunberg, the 17-year-old Swedish climate activist who was recently named Time magazine's "Person of the Year." In reality, two 30-something Russians, Vladimir "Vovan" Kuznetsov and Alexei "Lexus" Stolyarov, were on the other end of the line. The duo describe themselves as comedians and pranksters, but they are widely suspected of having ties to the Russian government.  Audio from the call with Waters was posted to the pair's YouTube page on Thursday, along with a cartoon animating the approximately 10-minute interaction as part of their comedy video series called "Stars Save the Earth."  It's unclear when exactly the call took place. Waters' office did not respond to questions seeking details about how the call was arranged or whether her office has screening or security protocols for phone calls. Waters waved off the incident on Saturday, telling The Washington Post in an email statement:  "This was just another stupid prank by the same Russian operatives who have targeted many U.S. elected officials, including Rep. Adam B. Schiff, Sen. Lindsey O. Graham, Sen. Mitch McConnell, and late-Senator John McCain, and international heads of state such as Emmanuel Macron. The end."  But security experts warn that what's being passed off as prank-call mischief is really Russian misinformation meant to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens to attack White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7853703/Iran-threatens-attack-White-House-crushing-powerful-retaliation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran has threatened to attack the White House in response to President Donald Trump's threat to strike 52 Iranian targets. 'We have the power,' said Iranian MP Abolfazl Abutorabi,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 dead, 60 injured in massive crash on PA Turnpike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b2bfea36577246521f22967102993de8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENSBURG, Pa. (AP) — At least five people were killed and dozens were injured in a crash early Sunday involving multiple vehicles on the Pennsylvania Turnpike, a transportation official said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu, in apparent stumble, calls Israel 'nuclear power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-netanyahu-nuclear-idUSKBN1Z40CS?taid=5e11d33648fe97000144aa9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an apparent slip of the tongue on Sunday, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small cracks in Republican unity on trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/politics/small-cracks-have-appeared-in-gop-unity-on-impeachment-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pbs.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For now, Republicans are holding the line behind Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell’s position that they should start the trial and hear arguments from House prosecutors and Trump’s defense team before deciding what to do. But small cracks in GOP unity have appeared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escalating U.S.-Iran tensions scramble politics of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/escalating-us-iran-tensions-scramble-the-politics-of-trumps-impeachment/ar-BBYB4bv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain 'must be ready' for looming war...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/britain-must-ready-looming-iran-21217332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Admiral Lord West said it would be “very difficult” for Britain to stay out of a fresh conflict in the Middle East amid tensions between Iran and the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condemns Trump as 'terrorist in suit'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200105092357-uhs3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 1-Iran condemns Trump as 'terrorist in a suit' after attack threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady says retirement 'pretty unlikely'; Free agent for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28424771/tom-brady-says-retirement-pretty-unlikely-patriots-exit-playoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots quarterback Tom Brady said it was "pretty unlikely" that he would retire this offseason, before adding it was "hopefully unlikely" after the team's 20-13 loss to the visiting Titans on Saturday night in the wild-card round of the AFC playoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death to America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/us-iran-soleimani-tensions-live-intl-01-05-20/h_6a85a53149579c7cedb252b3b616085a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US is sending thousands of additional troops to the Middle East as tensions grow following the killing of Iran's top general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military confirms terror attack on US base in Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/us-military-confirms-terror-attack-us-base-kenya/story?id=68075337</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military acknowledges terror attack on U.S. base in Kenya</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soleimani body taken on unprecedented public mournings tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/5/qassem-soleimani-body-tours-iran-public-mournings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This marks the first time Iran honored a single man with a multi-city ceremony. Not even Khomeini received such a processional with his death in 1989.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows charred koala, kangaroo remains; Billion animals feared dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10673494/australia-fires-billion-animals-feared-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEARTBREAKING footage shows the charred remains of dead koalas and kangaroos – as experts fear the devastating Australian wildfires have killed a BILLION animals. A horrific video shows the c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  DOUBTS AT PENTAGON...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/nationworld/ct-nw-nyt-trump-decision-to-kill-soleimani-20200105-we7fksvu25farhbbb2wkwv3zfm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon officials often offer improbable options to presidents to make other possibilities appear more palatable. https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/04/us/politics/trump-suleimani.html</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suburb soars to 120&amp;#176;... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7852649/8-000-koalas-perish-bushfires-sweeping-Australia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of dead koalas is equal to a third of their population in New South Wales. Ecologists say the animal may have to be reclassified as an endangered species as it disappears from areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARR: Trump ordered the strike, and came down to dinner cool, collected...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2020/01/03/howie-carr-president-trump-ordered-the-strike-and-came-down-to-dinner-cool-collected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was just another evening at Mar a Lago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ERA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/sports/patriots/2020/01/04/derrick-henry-tennessee-run-over-eliminate-punchless-patriots/201YEIyFeKDMtDQtCPPInM/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bruising back finished with 182 yards on 34 carries, and New England was held without a point in the second half.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
