<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bannon thought Donald had dementia?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2373046/bannon-trump-dementia-plot-oust-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STEVE Bannon secretly plotted to remove Donald Trump from office claiming he had dementia – and believed HE could personally succeed him as president, a bombshell new book claims. In a memoir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rained debris at least a mile wide!</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/United-flight-returns-to-airport-after-engine-15966746.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kieran Cain was at the playground with his two children when he heard what sounded like...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama on flight from Denver to Honolulu...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/news/local/airplane-parts-fall-broomfield/73-298bbbf8-637a-42a5-8bd0-5ca9b03c0f19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been no injuries, but parts have fallen in at least three locations, Broomfield Police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach Covid Compliance Team Investigating DeSantis Event For Maskless Crowd...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/02/19/palm-beach-covid-compliance-team-investigating-desantis-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach County's COVID Compliance Team is investigating an event Governor Ron DeSantis held at a West Palm Beach hotel Friday morning for violating the county's masking and social distancing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud Explosion...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/20/united-airlines-flight-328-passenger-plane-shuddering-explosion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Vena was traveling to Hawaii for a getaway when the unthinkable happened. The engine on his plane apparently failed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort gets 1.1 million signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Newsom-recall-effort-moves-closer-toward-making-15965131.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Almost 1.1 million signatures have been submitted in support of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA ramping up: To hire 6,000 new airport screeners...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/tsa-hiring-summer-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration is working to hire more than 6,000 airport security screening officers ahead of the traditionally busy summer travel season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds OK'd Export of Millions of Masks as U.S. Workers Cried for More...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/feds-okd-export-of-millions-of-n95-masks-as-u-s-workers-cried-for-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hours before President Joe Biden was inaugurated, the Federal Emergency Management Agency allowed a Texas mask maker to ship the high-quality masks overseas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM GOVS SEE STARS DIMMED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-california-8351591b02e965a250f8b04139f7f37d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. (AP) — At the outset of the coronavirus pandemic, two Democratic governors on opposite ends of the country were hailed as heroes for their leadership in a crisis. Now they're leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS THAWS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-austin-power-outages-tennessee-weather-e79196af45d3af529eda1af8f8293db7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Warmer temperatures spread across the southern United States on Saturday, bringing some relief to a winter weary region that faces a challenging clean-up and expensive repairs from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions without water...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2373375/biden-declares-texas-major-disaster-after-winter-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE winter storm death toll continues to mount as millions of Americans are thrust into third-world conditions amid widespread power outages and contaminated tap water. At least 69 people have died…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stakes high' as QAnon emerges in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20210220-stakes-are-high-as-qanon-conspiracy-phenomenon-emerges-in-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After rising to the fore in the US during the most fraught presidential campaign the country has seen for decades, the QAnon phenomenon has emerged in France – prompting President Emmanuel Macron’s g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates Battle 'Inhumane' Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-power-outage-jails-prisons-winter-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The toilet and water had been off for 24 hours. The sinks are dirty. It's just nasty. It's just not right — it's like we're not even human," one inmate told CBS News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic makes prostitution taboo in Nevada's legal brothels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-prostitution-las-vegas-c0647f194e2c7bf76743d671843cac4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Before the coronavirus pandemic, tourist-dependent Nevada had a notorious attraction: It was the only place in America where someone could legally pay for sex. These days,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In exchange for captive, Israel buys $1m of Russian doses...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-said-to-purchase-russian-covid-vaccine-for-syria-in-exchange-for-captive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asharq Al-Awsat report says 'secret clause' has Israel funding purchase of Sputnik V doses for Assad regime as part of deal to return woman who crossed border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faulconer the Next [Scrawny] Schwarzenegger?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/coronavirus/is-kevin-faulconer-californias-next-scrawny-schwarzenegger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under normal circumstances, a California conservative like Kevin Faulconer would stand little chance of toppling Governor Gavin Newsom (D.), the polished product of San Francisco's powerful political machine. But after nearly 12 months of harsh lockdowns and shuttered schools, the state's political landscape is anything but normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths in Bedrooms, Vehicles and Backyards...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/19/extreme-cold-killed-texans-in-their-bedrooms-vehicles-and-backyards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO — Carrol Anderson spent much of his life in Southeast Texas, where the most feared natural disasters spin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly virus could be next 'big one'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/health-problems/brainswelling-nipah-virus-75-times-more-deadly-than-coronavirus-may-be-next-pandemic-scientists-warn-of-the-big-one/news-story/5363e34783bd54c926434c738edd5e12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brain-swelling disease 75 times more deadly than coronavirus could mutate to become the next pandemic killing millions, scientists have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Fact-Checker Has Disappeared From Air Post-Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/what-ever-happened-to-daniel-dale-cnn-fact-checker-has-disappeared-from-air-post-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN fact-checker Daniel Dale was one of the busiest people in the cable news business for several years, but he has almost completely disappeared from the network's programming over the past month or so. What happened?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Cats destroy your love life...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/culture/article/cat-people-love-life-worse-15949215.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's your permission to blame a crappy Valentine's on your feline friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepens Chinese belief they're 'on right path'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-weather-crisis-deepens-chinese-111205544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's foreign ministry said on Friday that seeing the plight of Americans suffering in a severe winter storm that hit the state of Texas this week reinforced a belief among Chinese citizens that their country is "on the right path". Foreign ministry spokeswoman Hua Chunying made the comments in response to a question from a state media journalist on calls by western countries for an investigation into alleged human rights abuses in its western Xinjiang region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim's 'grip on NKorea never stronger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14109473/kim-jong-un-north-korea-covid-meth-starving-dirt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korean defections are now at “virtually zero” with Kim Jong-un’s grip never stronger due to a combination of Covid and crystal meth smuggling, The Sun can reveal. The pandemic has made it alm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurt by Lockdowns, CA Small Businesses Push to Recall Gov...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/19/hurt-by-lockdowns-californias-small-businesses-push-to-recall-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Alexandra and Daniela Del Gaudio had never been to a political rally before, let alone one to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingenuity helicopter phones home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/20/world/mars-ingenuity-helicopter-update-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ingenuity helicopter, sidekick and traveling companion to NASA's Perseverance rover, has checked in with a good report and is "operating as expected," according to the agency. It will be the first helicopter to fly on another planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX attacks Joe's dogs for being dirty...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/539710-newsmax-guest-mocks-bidens-senior-dog-champ-unlike-a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax host Greg Kelly took aim at President Biden’s dog Champ on Friday, mocking his appearance during a segment of his show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New legislation would protect drivers who hit protestors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-legislature-oklahoma-city-oklahoma-legislation-238201499e0d4a960ef49b92f25dbb31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — When massive demonstrations against racial injustice erupted across the nation last summer, protesters used an increasingly common tactic to draw attention to their cause:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern Baptists divided over politics, race, LGBTQ policy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-donald-trump-baptist-southern-baptist-convention-sexual-abuse-by-clergy-1b4bce88b58067f341e6e8eef259307f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divisions over race, politics, gender and LGBTQ issues are roiling America’s largest Protestant denomination, the Southern Baptist Convention, ahead of a meeting of its executive committee next...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Era of Black Holes Is Here...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/02/black-hole-collisions-gravitational-waves/618095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers have discovered a black-hole treasure trove that is changing our view of the cosmos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Navy sailors who disarm mines and bombs, learning never stops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailypress.com/military/dp-nw-navy-eod-20210220-rsijyde335frfpm52mg2ogfcuu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailypress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy's explosive ordnance disposal groups take on an expanded role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden declares major disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/20/biden-declares-major-disaster-in-texas-as-state-struggles-with-fallout-from-power-outages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has approved a major disaster declaration for Texas as the state grapples with widespread power outages and water shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dangerous Lives of Cuban Surfers Fighting for Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dangerous-lives-cuban-surfers-fighting-042602294.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HandoutOur 1958 Toyota Land Cruiser, a car that borders on modern in Cuba, rolled to a stop on the outskirts of the famed Guantanamo Bay naval base. Cuban military men in fatigues approached the rear door where our group, consisting of myself, my filming partners Seth, Marco, and Tyler, and two Cuban surfers named Frank and Yaya, were packed in like sardines with our legs all jammed in a formation we dubbed “the zipper.” While the guardsmen probed around our vehicle, intently eyeing the stack of surfboards strapped precariously to our roof, I found myself thinking of a line from one of the interviews we’d conducted days earlier with Yaya:“It doesn’t matter if it’s old or new, the mark or the brand, when we have a surfboard in our hands it is a treasure.”Over the first three months we’d spent filming Havana Libre, the meaning of this line took on several forms as we began to slowly evolve our understanding of the complicated context in which Cuban surf exists, and this stop was the manifestation of a reality that we’d often imagined but didn’t entirely comprehend. After all, surfing in Cuba was not exactly… legal. The circumstance that enabled us to embark on creating a film about this diehard and underground surf community was the sudden thawing of a hostile Cold War-era relationship between Cuba and the United States. It was the first time in roughly 60 years. Like many, our interest was sparked by the nostalgic images of tropical antiquity and the opportunity to seemingly step into the past, but what captivated us was the pursuit by a younger generation to escape the time capsule and chase their dreams. Inside Frank Gonzalez’s home in west Havana, the first thing I noticed was the faded green walls peeking from the bedrooms that were papered with wrinkled covers from old surf magazines and stickers of American skateboard brands. It was such a familiar collage from my own childhood, but I soon came to learn how much value every image held. When Yaya says surfboards are treasure, her sentiment goes far beyond the board itself. It extends to every morsel of information from the outside world; every image and opportunity to grow more connected to the broader surfing world beyond the blockade. We first heard her line as a commentary about how much passion they had for surfing, but over time it began to represent every obstacle they have to overcome simply to be able to surf.In one of his interviews, Frank commented, “We try to stay as far away from politics as we can, but eventually it always traps you.”The film we set out to make had very little political ambition, but like everything in Cuba, eventually we too were trapped by it. Political tendrils are embedded in the DNA of every Cuban story, and there is no way to tell an honest anthology of surf culture on the island without including politics to some degree. In essence, the blockade is the foundation of their disposition.There is no surf shop in Cuba. The closest thing to resembling one is Frank’s makeshift workshop where he has a collection of assorted chunks of foam and handmade tools, bartered carbon fiber and scraps of fiberglass from boatyards, and other ingredients to make and repair boards that have taken him years to amass. His craft was developed by dissecting every photograph that found its way into Cuba through the bag of some tourist. He’d analyze what the shape of the board should look like, how people positioned their hands to dive under waves, and how it looked as surfers shifted their balance to carve. Without internet access, each piece was vital for taking the next steps forward.This scarcity in material makes the barrier to entry very high. As Frank says, “If you want to be a Cuban surfer, you have to really want it.” On top of the scarcity of material is an equal scarcity of general knowledge. Your average Cuban most likely doesn’t know that a sport called surfing even exists. When traces of surfing did finally reach Cuba, its timing happened to coincide closely with the fall of the Soviet Union, Cuba’s lifeline at the time, and yielded the country’s biggest economic crisis. The ensuing exodus of tens of thousands of Cubans via shoddily built rafts deepened the conflict between Cuba and the United States and transformed the ocean into a highly policed and dangerous place for Cubans to enter. Handout It is important to understand this history because, while there was no signpost explicitly saying “surfing is illegal,” it is the reason that it has been forced to exist in the shadows. For decades, water activities were prohibited and surfers risked incrimination for fear that they were fleeing to America. And this brings us back to Guantanamo, where we sat with bated breath hoping that the soldier reprimanding us doesn’t notice the blinking red light of a recording GoPro that he’d unknowingly repositioned, framing a perfect portrait of himself. One of the men informed us we’d entered into a high-security zone due to our proximity to the American base, and that several days prior they detained a man who had triggered a series of alarms trying to escape on a windsurfing board. It was in this moment that we sort of realized the gravity of our surroundings, and the reality of what it means to be a surfer in Cuba. Throughout the interrogation, their attention kept resting back on our cargo on the roof, and, despite all our camera gear and computers, we were all hoping for the same thing.“Please don’t take their boards…”After about an hour we were told we could carry on with our voyage. They said they’d be monitoring us and under no circumstances were we allowed to enter the water anywhere along the coast, nor were we allowed to take our cameras out at any point. We pulled off the road just after our stop and after almost a thousand miles of coastal exploration, we could see a river mouth in the distance, opening into the bay with a beautiful peeling wave breaking down the presumably land-mined shores of the base. We took a moment to soak it in, and then hit the road looking for something new. HAVANA LIBRE is world premiering as the opening night virtual film at the upcoming Big Sky Documentary Film Festival in Missoula, Montana, on Feb. 19Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC tax agency subpoenaed in Trump criminal probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-investigation-subpoena-excl/exclusive-new-york-city-tax-agency-subpoenaed-in-trump-criminal-probe-idUSKBN2AK037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan District Attorney’s Office has subpoenaed a New York City property tax agency as part of a criminal investigation into Donald Trump’s company, the agency confirmed on Friday, suggesting prosecutors are examining the former president’s efforts to reduce his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSE: Taiwan scrambles air force again after Chinese exercises...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210220140812-2cf3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (PIX):Taiwan scrambles air force again after Chinese exercises in South China Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN ERASING 'FORMER GUY'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-inauguration-joe-biden-donald-trump-biden-cabinet-iran-nuclear-b7838bf96681674211b2b2b3a421385e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When Joe Biden walked into the Oval Office for the first time as president a month ago, his pens were ready. Already. Lining a fine wooden box, they bore the presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia reports world's first case of human infection with H5N8 bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-birdflu-russia/russia-reports-worlds-first-case-of-human-infection-with-h5n8-bird-flu-idUSKBN2AK0DU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has registered the first case of a strain of bird flu virus named A(H5N8) being passed to humans from birds and has reported the matter to the World Health Organization (WHO), Anna Popova, head of consumer health watchdog Rospotrebnadzor, said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech industry looking to replace smartphone -- all eyes on APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/20/apple-facebook-microsoft-battle-to-replace-smartphone-with-ar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry watchers and participants think that Apple has a good chance to validated and revolutionize augmented reality like it did with smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS 'getting closer' to precious oil reserves as terrorists launch savage attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-getting-closer-precious-oil-23532757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorists have amassed a fighting force and taken on Government forces in the southern African country, leading to brutal massacres and the arrival of foreign mercenaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More men suffering from infertility than ever before...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/20/why-more-men-are-suffering-from-infertility-than-ever-before/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sperm counts in Western countries have dropped by more than 50 percent since the 1970s. At the same time, men’s problems with conceiving are going up: Erectile dysfunction is increasing and testost…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year After Crash, Pandemic Losers Are New Winners...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/a-year-after-covid-crash-pandemic-losers-are-the-new-winners/ar-BB1dQHmV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after Covid-19 reordered world markets, sparking a brutal selloff for many stocks and creating new lockdown darlings, the prospect of vaccine-led reflation is turning the tide for the pandemic’s main laggards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Dangerous Network of Backstreet Castrators, Cutters, Eunuch-Makers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-dangerous-global-network-of-backstreet-castrators-cutters-and-eunuch-makers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast got an unprecedented look at the world of backstreet castrations where people desperate to have genitalia altered or removed undergo risky, illicit operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Russian court, Navalny caged and angry but far from silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-a-Russian-court-Alexei-Navalny-is-caged-and-15965827.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny took time in court this past week to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Will 15 Million Listeners Go Now?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/20/where-will-rush-limbaughs-15-million-listeners-go-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So who now takes the place of Rush Limbaugh as the media ringmaster of the right? The answer, most likely,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Ford on Wearing Same Ripped Jeans and Allowing Self to 'Be Unproductive'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/20/tom-ford-on-wearing-the-same-ripped-jeans-and-allowing-himself-to-be-unproductive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until last week, Tom Ford — designer, film director and chairman of the Council of Fashion Designers of America —</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
