<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CDC:   'Avoid cruise travel, regardless of vaccination status'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/30/us-cdc-says-people-should-avoid-cruise-travel-regardless-of-vaccination-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confederate monuments likely going to Black history museum...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/virginia/2021/12/confederate-monuments-will-likely-go-to-black-history-museum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia and Richmond officials on Thursday announced a tentative agreement to transfer ownership of the city’s now mostly removed Confederate monuments to the Black History Museum and Cultural Center of Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600 cars in line at Missouri testing site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-st-louis-missouri-ba73ddfff6449515b335a4386c43ab22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — The latest COVID-19 surge in Missouri has residents scrambling to get tested, but having difficulty finding a place to do it. Urgent care centers, pharmacies and other places offering COVID-19 tests are struggling to keep up with demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered tiger fatally shot at Florida zoo after biting man's arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/30/tiger-fatally-shot-florida-naples-zoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, who worked for an external cleaning service at the Naples Zoo, ‘put his arm through the fencing’ of the enclosure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets WORLD record; Risks grinding to HALT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10355849/US-hits-record-nearly-500-000-Covid-cases-24-hours-Experts-says-viral-blizzard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States' is the midst of its largest Covid surge yet, as the Omicron variant continues to ravage much of the nation. The country recorded nearly 500,000 cases in a single day on Wednesday, the most by any country in the world at any point during the pandemic, and experts predict it will only get worse in the coming weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd ex-CNN staffer probed for alleged crimes involving minors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/30/second-ex-cnn-staffer-under-investigation-for-alleged-crimes-involving-minors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Fairfax County, Virginia, have launched a criminal probe into Rick Saleeby, a former senior producer on Jake Tapper’s “The Lead.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SHE SING?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4361606/ghislaine-maxwell-conviction-bad-news-prince-andrew-naming-names/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew’s lawyers were locked in emergency talks last night amid fears his pal Ghislaine Maxwell could “name names” following her guilty verdict, a report says. Maxwell now …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES 65 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10332169/Underage-orgies-possible-pregnancy-key-moments-Ghislaine-Maxwells-sensational-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell has been found guilty of sex trafficking charges, and speculation is now mounting that she may 'flip' and testify against others in a bid to reduce her sentence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 10 richest people added $402 billion to fortunes in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/30/how-much-money-the-10-richest-people-in-the-world-made-in-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heading into 2022, the 10 wealthiest individuals in the world are all worth more than $100 billion, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Cancel 1,000 Flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-airlines-cancel-over-1-000-flights-on-day-before-new-year-s-eve-1.1701504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Airline cancellations are already piling up in the U.S., with more than 1,000 flights scrubbed the day before New Year’s Eve as coronavirus cases climbed and heavy snow brewed in the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOPHISTICATED PREDATOR'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/29/ghislaine-maxwell-convicted-of-sex-trafficking-victims-for-jeffrey-epstein/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell was convicted of five of the six charges against her at her sex-trafficking trial Wednesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Barely Known Politicians About to Take '22 by Storm?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/barely-known-politicians-2022-storm-100041528.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyAs 2022 arrives and the midterm elections get closer, so a new batch of political hopefuls is emerging.With individuals from all parts of the political spectrum hoping to break through to voters, primary fields are becoming crowded and difficult to parse out. But here are seven standout candidates who are building ground in their respective races—and who could become key players for both parties next year. 1228245081 Charles Booker speak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUILTY GHISLAINE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-alison-j-nathan-new-york-city-new-york-63a71a2825eab41184a79e37bb967e90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell was convicted of luring teenage girls to be sexually abused by the American millionaire Jeffrey Epstein. The guilty verdict capped a monthlong trial featuring sordid accounts of the sexual exploitation of girls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixth quake in four days rocks SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/weather/article256936267.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earthquakes can happen in clusters, according to seismologists. Here’s what you need to know about the latest quake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First they ran short of PPE, then ventilators. Now, hospital staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/first-they-ran-short-of-ppe-then-ventilators-now-the-shortage-is-hospital-staff/ar-AAShdmZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T cells come to rescue as studies show they buck omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/t-cells-come-to-the-rescue-as-studies-show-they-buck-omicron/article_d997503d-5856-5153-a793-0fb9a0b82a94.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unsung arm of the immune system appears to protect against severe disease with the omicron variant even when antibodies wane, helping to explain why a record wave of infections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA recalls half million cars over crash fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech-old/4364415/tesla-recalls-nearly-half-a-million-cars-safety-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON MUSK’S Tesla needs to recall almost half a million cars due to safety issues. The car brand wants to recall 475,000 of its Model 3 and Model S electric vehicles. Musk’s car brand i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin hold call as Ukraine tension smolders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-vladimir-putin-europe-ukraine-eastern-europe-1cb20563ff8dd31ce9dfa93757295eb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Presidents Joe Biden and Vladimir Putin are set to discuss the Russian troop buildup near Ukraine during their second call in recent weeks amid little progress toward ending the smoldering crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Threatens to 'Dish Dirt' on Trump for Pushing Vax...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alex-jones-threatens-to-dish-dirt-on-donald-trump-for-pushing-covid-19-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The one-time presidential pal has been taking massive swings at Trump over his endorsement and subsequent push of the jab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit Tops List Of Neediest Cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/detroit-neediest-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite its reputation for glitz and glamor, the study ranks Los Angeles, California as the 6th neediest city in the nation!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC admits shouldn't have interviewed Dershowitz...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1008486/bbc-admits-it-shouldnt-have-interviewed-alan-dershowitz-as-an-impartial-analyst-on-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger bites arm of man reaching into enclosure at Florida zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/tiger-bites-arm-of-man-reaching-into-enclosure-at-florida-zoo-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Malayan tiger Eko, which was acquired from Seattle's Woodland Park Zoo, was killed after the animal bit a man at a Florida zoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locked down in China's Xi'an amid  outbreak, residents subsist on deliveries of vegetables...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/locked-down-in-chinas-xian-amid-coronavirus-outbreak-residents-subsist-on-deliveries-of-vegetables/ar-AASgiiQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising gas price projections complicate Biden horizons...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/587643-rising-gas-price-projections-complicate-bidens-horizons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts expect U.S. gasoline prices to rise as high as $4 per gallon by this summer, putting a pinch on drivers and exacerbating problems for President Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Into the Metaverse!</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/30/everybody-into-the-metaverse-virtual-reality-beckons-big-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The metaverse, one of the most buzzy terms of the tech industry, could be many things. It could be a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says launched rocket into space...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/space-launches-business-europe-vienna-tehran-328de0d544eb750117c902883d162771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran on Thursday announced it launched a satellite carrier rocket bearing three devices into space, though it's unclear whether any of the objects entered orbit around the Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Tests Positive Mid-Flight, Isolates for 5 Hours in Bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/woman-tests-positive-for-covid-19-mid-flight-isolates-for-5-hours-in-bathroom/3472159/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Michigan schoolteacher who tested positive for COVID-19 in the middle of a flight to Iceland a few days before Christmas says she ended up voluntarily isolated in the plane’s cramped bathroom for the last five hours of the trip to Reykjavik.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron at 37: Where he stands among all-time greats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/lebron-james-at-37-breaking-down-where-he-stands-among-nbas-all-time-greats/ar-AASh77f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infections Will Rise So Dramatically 'Will Be Hard to Keep Life Operating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/infectious-disease-expert-cases-will-rise-so-dramatically-in-coming-weeks-it-will-be-hard-to-keep-everyday-life-operating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Michael Osterholm warned that a sharp spike in Covid infections in the next three to four weeks will make it hard to keep everyday life operationg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tributes from Dems' liberal flank reveal soft spot for 'fighter' Reid...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Tributes-from-Democrats-liberal-flank-reveal-a-16737202.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the 1960s, and Harry Reid was decades away from becoming one of the top Democrats...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin set for another call amid strains on Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-to-hold-another-call-with-Putin-on-Thursday-16736371.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden plans to speak with Russian President Vladimir Putin on Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls mount for other enablers to face charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-epstein-enablers-ghislaine-maxwell-verdict-reactions-20211230-aqagvv3hwrgrxd773inrs5e5tu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the month-long trial, the jury heard of the powerful figures who Maxwell and Epstein considered friends. Former presidents Donald Trump and Bill Clinton, as well as Prince Andrew, flew as passengers on the same private planes Epstein and Maxwell used to traffic minors for sexual abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some govts easing rules for isolation, citing dangers of economic and health-care strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/some-governments-are-easing-rules-for-isolation-citing-dangers-of-economic-and-health-care-strains-from-omicron-spread/ar-AASfNaA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell meets with ABC journalist; TV interview?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10352835/Ghislaine-Maxwell-jurors-face-working-New-Year-weekend-Omicron-threatens-case.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Alison Nathan is becoming increasingly concerned that the rapid spread of the coronavirus could strike jurors and force them to end their deliberations without a decision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese lockdown rule-breakers publicly shamed and paraded through streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10352249/Chinese-lockdown-rule-breakers-publicly-shamed-ensure-Covid-rules-obeyed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four masked suspects in hazmat suits - carrying placards displaying their photos and names - were paraded Tuesday in front of a large crowd in Guangxi region's Jingxi city in southern China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel Hires Austria's Disgraced Former Chancellor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/billionaire-peter-thiel-hires-austria-s-disgraced-former-chancellor-1.1701438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Peter Thiel’s investment firm is tapping former Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz to become a global strategist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed man with 'hit list' including Biden, Fauci arrested in Iowa on way to White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/587675-armed-man-with-hit-list-including-biden-fauci-arrested-in-iowa-on-way-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Iowa have arrested a man who was found during a traffic stop to be carrying a rifle and a "hit list" that included President Biden and Anthony Fauci, the nation's top infectious diseases expert,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business manager to Kardashians found dead; Boyfriend charged with murder, torture...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/business-manager-kardashians-found-dead-225325545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Kukawski was found dead in her car in Simi Valley last week. Authorities say her boyfriend, Jason Barker, tortured and killed her at their Sherman Oaks home, then dumped her body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Faces Year-End Technical Test After December Swoon...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-faces-end-technical-test-061959077.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin is continuing its December retreat and testing a key technical level that over the past two years has tended to act as a floor for the world’s largest cryptocurrency.Most Read from BloombergGhislaine Maxwell Found Guilty in Win for Epstein VictimsMercedes Swept Up in China Internet Furor Over Models’ EyesApple Aims to Prevent Defections to Meta With Rare $180,000 Bonuses for Top TalentThe Senator Who Could Rescue Biden’s AgendaCovid With Omicron Isn’t ‘Same Disease,’ Oxfor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous trucker logs first no-human road test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-arizona-department-of-transportation-arizona-tucson-2a53f9728635c13f38c7e3c4223700ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A semitruck completed an 80-mile route in Arizona with no human on board and no human intervention during the trip using technology developed by TuSimple, the company said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's live-streaming influencers in crosshairs of 'common prosperity' drive...</title>
      <link>/https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/China-s-live-streaming-influencers-are-in-the-16737857.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese brain control warfare work revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/dec/29/pla-brain-control-warfare-work-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Commerce Department imposed sanctions on Chinese technology companies and announced last week revealed that China’s military is engaged in dangerous work related to “brain control” warfare research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN AT THE BEACH...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?516942-1/president-biden-lady-jill-biden-rehoboth-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEAK COVID NOW!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-c69d1521b6411b6b78aae85d95165f5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — More than a year after the vaccine was rolled out, new cases of COVID-19 in the U.S. have soared to their highest level on record at over 265,000 per day on average, a surge driven largely by the highly contagious omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No way back for Prince Andrew the outcast royal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10333041/No-way-Prince-Andrew-outcast-royal-Ghislaine-Maxwell-verdict-changes-little-prince.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duke of York's lawyers will try to have the civil lawsuit brought by Virginia Roberts Giuffre thrown out of court. Royal observers say that even victory would not be enough to remove the stigma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreams of New Pill Panacea Dashed...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/dreams-covid-pill-panacea-dashed-095531014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyThe U.S. Food and Drug Administration has granted emergency-use authorization to two prescription COVID pills that patients with mild-to-moderate infections can take at home and that, to varying degrees, can prevent the worst outcomes. Serious illness. Hospitalization. Death.Doctors were counting on the new pills, from New Jersey pharma Merck and Pfizer in New York, to help keep people out of hospitals as the Delta and Omicron lineages of the SARS-CoV-2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flap ensues as trans 'JEOPARDY!' champ hailed as 'top female earner'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/dec/29/flap-ensues-trans-jeopardy-champ-amy-schneider-hai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Jeopardy!’ contestant Amy Schneider was born a man, but she’s being toasted as the highest-earning woman in the show’s history, much to the chagrin of those decrying the accolade as an example of stolen female glory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia rocked by 7.2 mag quake in Indonesia... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/northern-territory/northern-australia-rocked-by-magnitude72-earthquake-in-indonesia/news-story/ecaf1b7e4071d53c5abc7782cbf8a1ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darwin has been rocked by an earthquake that hit the Barat Daya Islands in Indonesia, with residents reporting feeling the tremor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business manager to Kardashians killed, boyfriend charged...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-business-los-angeles-nicki-minaj-arts-and-entertainment-7eab979c5603d4f8c3112f1772e7a936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A Los Angeles business manager whose clients had included Nicki Minaj and the Kardashians was killed, and her boyfriend was charged with murder, authorities said Wednesday. Police found Angela Kukawski, 55, dead in her car in Simi Valley northwest of Los Angeles on Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska 'Icemageddon' warning follows heat record...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-59820999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coldest US state faces weather extremes after heavy snowfall and torrential rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala asking Wall Street CEOs, business leaders for advice...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/29/kamala-harris-asking-wall-street-ceos-for-advice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris has frequently sought guidance from well-known Wall Street executives and business leaders as the Biden administration contends with a series of policy challenges at ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber brothel claims customers surged during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech-old/4358272/cyber-brothel-rise-in-customers-pandemic-sex-dolls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ‘world’s first’ cyber brothel says it’s seen a surge in clientele during the pandemic. The cyber sex experts think the increase in popularity is due to people feeling sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Director: Human behavior played into shortening quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/cdc-director-human-behavior-shortened-isolation-period-covid-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky acknowledged Wednesday that human behavior played into the latest quarantine guidelines for people with COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow orders foreigners fingerprinted, tested for STDS, drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-59820777</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business groups criticise a new law requiring mandatory fingerprinting, drug tests and STD checks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium reverses cultural rules: Show must go on!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-belgium-europe-7f456143b53500a93db216d5fd5f17d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Belgium reversed some of its COVID-19  restrictions Wednesday, allowing for the reopening of cinemas, theaters and concert halls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget TINDER. Chinese City Building Dating Database for Singles...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akvkwe/chinese-city-building-dating-database-for-singles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If they think that youngsters are going to forgo partying in favor of a virtual matchmaking party, they are so wrong.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis star rages after testing positive for '250th time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/sport/tennis/french-tennis-star-benoit-paire-rages-after-testing-positive-to-covid19-for-250th-time/news-story/3b346b6521c9c2a07da3e3c606a8ed6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French tennis player Benoit Paire has revealed he has tested positive for Covid-19 ahead of next month’s Australian Open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meet a Jew': Germany's New Scheme to Convince Country Jews Are People...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/human-interest/2021/12/meet-a-jew-germany-anti-semitism-crime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With violence against Jews on the rise, maybe the answer is radically simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  NO HUGS, NO KISSING...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2021-12-29/fauci-warns-against-hugging-and-kissing-in-new-years-eve-celebrations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fauci urged Americans not to celebrate the new year at large parties ‘with all the bells and whistles’ but blessed smaller, at-home gatherings among vaccinated individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spent final months demanding Biden reveal govt UFO secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4358526/harry-reid-nevada-senator-area-51-biden-ufo-secrets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Senate majority leader Harry Reid was at the center of efforts to transform the UFO debate into a serious political issue. For decades, discussions about unidentified aerial phenomena were o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen hospitalized after allergic reaction to FACEBOOK virtual reality headset...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4358216/allergic-reaction-virtual-reality-headset/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MUM has told how her son’s Christmas was ruined after he suffered an allergic reaction to a Facebook virtual reality headset. Lewis Gray, 13, was rushed to hospital after trying out his new…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine begins to court media...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article256912802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury that is deciding Ghislaine Maxwell’s fate could be ringing in the new year in a New York courthouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA CASES SMASH RECORD; DESANTIS VANISHES...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article256917562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida reported 46,923 COVID-19 cases and no new deaths Tuesday, according to Wednesday’s report to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, based on Miami Herald calculations of CDC data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials lead shift away from religion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/29/millennials-lead-shift-away-from-organized-religion-as-pandemic-tests-faith.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not uncommon for people to seek God during times of hardship. However, the opposite appears to have happened during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach smash and grab...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/27/1-million-worth-of-birkin-bags-robbed-in-palm-beach-smash-and-grab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight of the French handbag maker’s Birkin bags and five Kellys were stolen from Only Authentics on Dec. 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to speak with Putin on Thursday at Russian leader's request...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/29/politics/biden-putin-call/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will hold a call with Russian President Vladimir Putin on Thursday afternoon "to discuss a range of topics, including upcoming diplomatic engagements with Russia," National Security Council spokesperson Emily Horne told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines call mandate 'purge'; All religious exemption bids denied...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/29/marines-havent-approved-any-religious-exemptions-for-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News reported Wednesday that 169 Marines have been discharged for refusing to comply with the vaccine mandate, and more than 3,000 religious exemption requests have been denied.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
