<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>OJ GETS ONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2236253/oj-simpson-trolled-getting-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OJ Simpson was brutally trolled online after he shared a photo of himself getting a Covid vaccine while wearing a “The Juice” mask. Twitter users had jokes and complaints, with many bri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUMPING THE LINE:  Guantanamo inmates to get Covid jab, including alleged 9/11 mastermind...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2235958/911-mastermind-guantanamo-bay-inmates-covid-vaccine-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ALLEGED terrorist behind 9/11 and other detainees at Guantanamo Bay will get Covid-19 vaccines as soon as next week – before most Americans. Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, the supposed principal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems building elaborate, emotionally charged Impeachment case against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-democrats-building-elaborate-emotionally-charged-case-against-trump/ar-BB1ddVdf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House managers are scouring for new video evidence and police witnesses, even as the Senate tries to limit former president Donald Trump’s impeachment trial to a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercuts Optimism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/covid-mutations-undercut-optimism-even-as-more-vaccines-get-near/ar-BB1ddUW7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world could be on the verge of having two more vaccines to fight the Covid-19 pandemic, but virus variants popping up worldwide are forcing companies that make the shots to develop boosters for a disease that could remain active for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUBBLE TROUBLE: DOW BELOW 30,000</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/stock-futures-decline-as-volatile-wall-street-week-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heightened speculative trading by retail investors continued to unnerve the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED STILL BAILING OUT</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-daly-pushes-back-against-234022779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. central bank should not prematurely withdraw pandemic support for the U.S. economy just because some people are getting rich in the stock market, said San Francisco Federal Reserve Bank President Mary Daly.“We’re building this bridge, which is barely having many communities hang on, and the stock market is running pretty good and many people who already have money are getting more money,” she said Friday during a virtual discussion hosted by the Stanford Graduate School of Business.“I am not willing to pull that bridge away and injure, in my judgment, the livelihoods of people -- because they don’t have jobs, they don’t have income, they don’t have wage growth -- simply to ensure that some people who already have stock market wealth don’t get more.”Daly, who votes on monetary policy this year, was asked to comment on the frenzy around GameStop Corp.’s meteoric stock-price rise. Some people have blamed the central bank’s ultra-easy policy for fanning a bubble in financial markets, but policy makers have shown no inclination so far to step back.The Fed held interest rates near zero at its meeting this week and repeated an assurance it would continue its massive monetary assistance for some time to come. Fed Chair Jerome Powell, who was also asked about excessive market speculation, sidestepped several attempts to get him to comment directly on GameStop, saying instead that financial-stability vulnerabilities overall are “moderate.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guantanamo inmates  to get Covid jab as early as NEXT WEEK including alleged 9/11 mastermind...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2235958/911-mastermind-guantanamo-bay-inmates-covid-vaccine-americans/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ALLEGED terrorist behind 9/11 and other detainees at Guantanamo Bay will get Covid-19 vaccines as soon as next week – before most Americans. Khalid Sheikh Mohammed, the supposed principal …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even with pardon, Bannon not off hook...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Even-with-Trump-s-pardon-Stephen-Bannon-is-not-15909197.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his last day in office, President Donald Trump issued pardons to 74 people and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Actions by Proud Boy at Capitol show 'planning, determination, and coordination'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Two-more-accused-in-chase-of-Officer-Eugene-15908418.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A police riot shield used to break a window, then a door kicked open from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii wants tourists. Tourists want Hawaii. But rules are complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Hawaii-wants-tourists-Tourists-want-Hawaii-But-15909101.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Derrick has run an online guide to Hawaii travel for nearly 20 years, so he's used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washingtonians navigate new normal: Razor-tipped wire fences and armed soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/washingtonians-navigate-new-normal-razor-tipped-wire-fences-and-armed-soldiers/ar-BB1ddgcE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After rioters attacked the Capitol, D.C. residents adapt to the imposing security measures that have taken over their home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America 'flying blind' to mutations racing across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/why-america-is-e2-80-98flying-blind-e2-80-99-to-the-coronavirus-mutations-racing-across-the-globe/ar-BB1ddwSU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America currently has so little of the genetic sequencing needed to detect mutated versions of coronavirus - like those first discovered in Britain and South Africa - that such variants are likely proliferating quickly, undetected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines push back on potential testing for domestic flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/covid-testing-airlines-push-back-on-testing-for-domestic-flights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC said it's "actively looking" at mandating Covid tests for domestic flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia moves to isolate Navalny allies, shut part of central Moscow ahead of protests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129192431-t917q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-COURT (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-Russia moves to isolate Navalny allies, shut part of central Moscow ahead of protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper publisher sues FACEBOOKGOOGLE over advertising monopoly...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-media-newspapers-west-virginia-huntington-02c267f9ee9474f20b4c9afc24523485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A West Virginia news publisher has filed an antitrust suit against Google and Facebook, who together receive roughly half of all digital ad dollars in the U.S. and are facing antitrust charges...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges dropped against activist who exposed Iowa hog deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-iowa-city-iowa-trials-subpoenas-50332a3905f4913d108865d27ee5d21d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IOWA CITY, Iowa (AP) — Prosecutors have dropped trespassing charges against an activist who helped secretly record Iowa’s largest pork producer using heat to kill thousands of hogs last year as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France tightens borders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-france-restaurants-9a3b99454b98ce6d1379fc781fa52f90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France says it's closing its borders to people arriving from outside the European Union starting Sunday to try to stop the growing spread of new variants of the virus and avoid a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rod Stewart reaches plea deal after punching Palm Beach hotel guard...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-rod-stewart-breakers-battery-case-20210129-4juq3rhhlnehzpldtuyh3yhslu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The encounter happened when children in Rod Stewart’s entourage were apparently refused access to a private kid’s party area about 11 p.m. Dec. 31, 2019, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostility between congressional Republicans and Dems reaches new lows amid growing fears of violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Hostility-between-congressional-Republicans-and-15907014.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Open hostility broke out among Republicans and Democrats in Congress on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late-night freezer failure in Seattle sends recipients scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/late-night-freezer-failure-in-seattle-sends-hundreds-scrambling-to-get-a-fast-expiring-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a freezer failed at a nearby medical center Thursday night, nurses, firefighters and volunteers scurried throughout the hospital in a mad-dash scramble to use as many doses of Moderna COVID-19 vaccine as possible before they expired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS ON STREET:  Regulators take notice as REDDIT stock onslaught continues...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/regulators-notice-reddit-stock-onslaught-173331074.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Friday said its regulators were keeping an eye on the whipsawing share prices of some Wall Street stocks that had been targeted by a social media-driven campaign intended to make wealthy hedge funds suffer."The commission is closely monitoring and evaluating the extreme price volatility of certain stocks' trading prices over the past several days," the SEC said in a statement, one day after some platforms restricted trading in GameStop, AMC Entertainment and other stocks caught up in the surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 65, behind anti-Biden graffiti spree, cops say...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/connecticut/elderly-graffiti-artist-203817</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 65-year-old Connecticut woman--likely one of the country’s oldest graffiti artists--is facing a criminal rap in connection with a spate of anti-Joe Biden tagging, police report. Investigators charg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: AZ Republican chair rejects audit of party elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/elections/2021/01/29/arizona-gop-chair-kelli-ward-rejects-call-audit-party-elections/4310030001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You certainly don’t allow a challenger who lost an election to demand something that they don’t have the right to," state GOP Chair Kelli Ward said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Far-Right Recruits: Teenage Gamers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the74million.org/article/where-hate-is-normalized-how-white-extremists-use-online-gaming-communities-popular-among-teens-to-recruit-culture-warriors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the74million.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alt-right groups use online gaming communities popular among teens to recruit culture warriors Five days after extremists used the fringe video gaming platform Dlive to livestream a mob attack on the U.S. Capitol, a youthful white nationalist logged onto the site and offered his take about the future of a movement he helped create. In […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge piece of Highway 1 south of Big Sur falls into ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Highway-1-weather-storm-closed-Rat-Creek-Big-Sur-15908140.php?IPID=SFGate-HP-CP-Spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caltrans said Friday emergency repairs are underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Investors Instantly Make $16 Billion On 'Squeeze'...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/sectors/gme-stock-gamestop-investors-instantly-make-16-billion-gamestop-stock-squeeze/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran school renaming debacle 'historic travesty'...</title>
      <link>https://missionlocal.org/2021/01/the-san-francisco-school-districts-renaming-debacle-has-been-a-historic-travesty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;missionlocal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are complex times. Even the question “How are you doing?” is complex. But this is not complex: In a 6-1 vote late Tuesday night, the San Francisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to quarantine travelers, suspend flights south...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cananda-coronavirus-travel-21d1685b076a62025326b0eb4441cd9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Prime Minister Justin Trudeau on Friday announced stricter restrictions on travelers in response to new, likely more contagious variants of the novel coronavirus — including making...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA state bar opens 'impaired or incapacitated' inquiry into Lin Wood...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jan/29/state-bar-georgia-opens-lin-wood-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organization that licenses lawyers in Georgia has opened an inquiry into conservative attorney Lin Wood, who gained national attention since the general election for persistent, unfounded claims of widespread voter fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Perfect storm' of fatigue, crowded housing turned LA into epicenter...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-perfect-storm-of-pandemic-fatigue-crowded-housing-and-a-new-variant-turned-la-into-a-coronavirus-epicenter/ar-BB1ddBAR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA's average daily coronavirus deaths quadrupled from December to January, while hospitalizations rose from around 2,500 per day to 7,500 per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 troops to be deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/29/politics/pentagon-vaccination-agreement/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon and the Federal Emergency Management Agency are negotiating the final terms of an agreement that could see the military provide around 450,000 Covid-19 vaccinations a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor dining again allowed -- but without TV...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/business/outdoor-dining-restrictions-lifted-in-la-county;-tv-broadcasts-not-allowed/10129618/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The county's revised Health Officer Order also reinstates previous restrictions on outdoor dining, requiring servers to wear masks and face shields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As 'Zoom boom' brings wealthy to Santa Fe, locals get priced out...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/29/santa-fe-new-mexico-zoom-boom-housing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mexico city faces a crisis as Covid ravages the tourism-based economy and newcomers crowd the housing market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo callously addresses nursing home report: 'Who cares!'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/29/gov-cuomo-blames-politics-amid-covid-19-nursing-home-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Who cares [where they died]? They died!” That’s how New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo callously responded Friday to questions about a damning state attorney general report …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Isn't Buying Leon Black's Epstein Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/01/wall-street-isnt-buying-leon-blacks-epstein-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dechert’s report on the Apollo cofounder’s decades-long dealings with the late convicted sex offender, including payments of $158 million, is raising eyebrows—and more questions—on Wall Street. One lawyer dismissed it as a “whitewash.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pot Use In Teens Linked To Lower IQ In Adulthood...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/teen-marijuana-use-drops-iq-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that regular pot smokers suffer a decline of two IQ points over time compared to those who did not use cannabis as an adolescent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD still severely limiting trading...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/robinhood-is-still-severely-limiting-trading-gamestop-holders-can-only-buy-one-additional-share.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood customers can buy one share and up to five options contracts of GameStop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Ramsey's empire 'best place to work in America'? Say no and you're out...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/money/2021/01/29/is-dave-ramseys-empire-best-place-work-america/4281535001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Dave Ramsey has boasted that his company is the best place to work in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Endorsed Political Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/01/marjorie-taylor-greene-endorsed-political-violence-video-guns-elections-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Republican said in a broadcast with a gun activist that defending freedom could require “the price of blood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rep. moving office away 'for my team's safety'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/democratic-rep-moving-office-away-marjorie-taylor-greene-my-team-n1256185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Cori Bush says Greene and her staff “berated” her in a hallway. It’s unclear when the incident occurred or what was said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelmed, America's largest cemetery refrigerates bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/29/us/cemetery-delays-california-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Covid-19-related deaths since the holidays have so challenged its capacity that grieving families are having to wait a month for funeral services -- and the cemetery has had to order refrigeration units to hold the bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain bans flights from Dubai -- as influencers, TV stars rush to get home...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/coronavirus/ga-health-officials-wont-say-where-the-uk-variant-strain-has-surfaced/RKS27V3GPNGP3JMG5NPS6RFZKQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia has six confirmed cases of the variant coronavirus strain from U.K., but the Georgia Department of Public Health won't disclose where in the state those cases are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the NRA's Strategy to Escape Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/courts/inside-the-nras-strategy-to-escape-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association's bankruptcy in Texas may throw a wrench into New York attorney general Letitia James's (D.) push to shut down the group and seize its assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline pilots making in-flight errors say they're 'rusty' because of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airline-pilots-making-flight-errors-130044410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pilots have attributed mistakes to being out of practice because the COVID-19 pandemic, which slashed air travel demand, had kept them away from flying for a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR FORCE Fleet Oldest, Smallest in its History...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davedeptula/2021/01/28/air-force-dont-buy-old-combat-aircraft/?sh=2e5e57873409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force’s business case must be driven by what it costs to achieve a mission objective, or “cost-per-effect,” rather than the lowest lifecycle cost of individual aircraft absent operational realities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Fort Bliss soldiers ill after ingesting substance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-texas-68e5712382b902b14c93925ad3cc4a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT BLISS, Texas (AP) — Eleven soldiers were sickened — including two who were in critical condition — after ingesting an unauthorized substance during a field training exercise at Fort Bliss in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Pipe bombs at RNC, DNC were planted night before riot'...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/01/fbi-pipe-bombs-at-rnc-dnc-were-planted-night-before-riot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI said the investigation had revealed new information about when the pipe bombs were planted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: May start dosing children by summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-united-nations-health-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-50c1f79fca97a6c2e46f7eaf8fd7afc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci says the Biden administration hopes to begin vaccinating younger children by late spring or early summer. The government’s top public health expert says...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurrection aftermath: Staffers struggle with trauma, guilt and fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/01/28/insurrection-aftermath-staffers-struggle-with-trauma-guilt-and-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the aftermath of the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol, staffers are looking for ways to cope in a highly decentralized workplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: ABCNEWS president announces departure, joining exodus from newsrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/abc-news-president-announces-departure-joining-exodus-from-us-newsrooms/ar-BB1dbKkv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Goldston will leave ABC News at the end of March and will help find a successor in the meantime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires' tax for virus relief takes effect in Argentina...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/millionaires-tax-for-virus-relief-takes-effect-in-argentina/ar-BB1ddkqC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-off tax on Argentina's richest people to help pay for medical supplies and relief for small businesses battered by the global coronavirus pandemic entered into force on Friday. The proceeds will be used to buy medical supplies, aid small and medium enterprises, fund social aid, and to provide natural gas to people off the energy grid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge gaps in data make it impossible to know who got shots...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/huge-gaps-in-vaccine-data-make-it-next-to-impossible-to-know-who-got-the-shots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details about race, ethnicity and occupation are often missing as data collected nationally is scattered across scores of digital systems that don’t connect. And the CDC doesn’t require vaccinators…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Orthodox unrest threatens Netanyahu reelection hopes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-pandemics-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-benjamin-netanyahu-2e87c8f56dc64ed6876a623ef9f7f352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — As he seeks reelection, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has turned to a straightforward strategy: Count on the rock-solid support of his ultra-Orthodox political allies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief calls for regulating social media companies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-media-social-media-antonio-guterres-united-nations-b6ed291f3008f935eeda5c1ae4b16d78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — The United Nations chief called Thursday for global rules to regulate powerful social media companies like Twitter and Facebook. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow cultivating Trump as asset for 40 years, says former KGB spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/29/trump-russia-asset-claims-former-kgb-spy-new-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The KGB ‘played the game as if they were immensely impressed by his personality’, Yuri Shvets, a key source for a new book, tells the Guardian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug treatment clinic owner accused of drug trafficking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/drug-treatment-clinic-owner-accused-of-drug-trafficking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operator of a Kansas drug treatment clinic has been indicted in Kansas City, Missouri, on federal charges of drug trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AI-powered sex robot declares herself 'more than a machine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-learning-ai-proclaims-23408140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Nova, created by sex robot manufacturer RealDoll, was quizzed on religion, psychology, and ethics – and was able to provide detailed answers to nearly every question</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Parisians, taxis are ticket to freedom...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129105906-4m1vq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-CURFEW-TAXI (TV):For locked-down Parisians, taxis are a ticket to freedom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to quarantine all travelers in hotels --  at their own expense!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-justin-trudeau-canada-coronavirus-pandemic-21d1685b076a62025326b0eb4441cd9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — An official familiar with the matter says Prime Minister Justin Trudeau will announce stricter restrictions on travelers response to new, likely more contagious variants of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man caught directing flight traffic with radio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-berlin-f56833f73c7ecfa34a5ed5e6461669bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A man has been arrested in Berlin on allegations he made radio contact with air traffic, including police helicopters, and gave fake flight orders while impersonating an aviation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Covid map hidden by Trump reveals worst hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2231507/covid-map-hidden-by-trump-published-virus-hotspots-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID data which Democrats claim was “hidden” by the Trump administration has been published for the first time, revealing the worst virus hotspots. Donald Trump had allegedly told stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Says Bug Will Last Forever, Isolation Leads Nowhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bolsonaro-says-covid-will-last-forever-isolation-leads-nowhere/ar-BB1dbKac?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT FENZY PUMPS UP DOGECOIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/dogecoin-cryptocurrency-rises-over-400percent-after-reddit-group-talks-it-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogecoin added about $7.17 billion to its market capitalization in 24 hours, thanks to the SatoshiStreetBets Reddit group talking it up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus consequence: World without cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/consumers-abandon-cash-altogether-because-of-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of the coronavirus pandemic, Americans are finally embracing touch-free payments. And they may never go back to paper currency again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210129-france-s-le-pen-at-record-high-in-polls-proposes-hijab-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/sec-reviewing-recent-trading-volatility-amid-gamestop-frenzy-vows-to-protect-retail-investors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC said it will work to protect investors by reviewing the recent volatility that has fueled a meteoric rise in stocks like GameStop and AMC Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Antipope of Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/01/29/trump-antipope-president-mar-a-lago-463238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a medieval religious schism can teach us about Donald Trump’s unprecedented and radically antagonistic approach to the ex-presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury house listings grow as wealthy flee tax-heavy states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/luxury-house-listings-grow-as-wealthy-flee-high-tax-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world’s most expensive homes, Villa Firenze, comes on the market as a growing number of high-priced homes are up for sale, especially as celebrities and wealthy individuals are fleeing high-tax states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-zero rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129130354-m7zs0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-YAKUTSK (PIX):Some Russians gear up for sub-zero rally for Kremlin critic Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China derecognizes British National Overseas passport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-beijing-hong-kong-immigration-china-9eff79173444f227c67c838fd86a45aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China said Friday it will no longer recognize the British National Overseas passport as a valid travel document or form of identification amid a bitter feud with London over a plan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELESTE: Modern soul hero comes good on the hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/en_asia/reviews/album/celeste-not-your-muse-review-2867890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She topped every tipster's poll as once to watch for 2020 and the London star has proved herself a generational talent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow cultivating Trump as asset for 40 years, says former KGB spy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-cultivating-trump-asset-40-122505054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuri Shvets told the Guardian that the KGB had identified Trump as a potential asset as far back as the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamlet absorbs charges of  unknowing role in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-columbus-media-social-media-ohio-b033c3b44e9a260a26dc10172dc7e7cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODSTOCK, Ohio (AP) — In this don't blink-or-you'll-miss-it, one-stoplight town, dozens of residents still fly “Trump 2020” and “Make America Great Again” flags. But it's a now-shuttered...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
