<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Left-Wing Mob Descends on  Homeland Secretary's Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/22/protesters-descend-kirstjen-nielsens-home-no-justi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of protesters gathered outside Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen’s Virginia home Friday morning, chanting “no justice, no sleep” and blaring audio of migrant children crying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainwreck Interview on CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tom-arnolds-cnn-interview-is-a-mind-boggling-trainwreck-i-am-not-f-ing-around/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX's top spokesman fired over use of racial term...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/jonathan-friedland-exits-netflix-1122675</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In lengthy internal memo, CEO Reed Hastings addressed letting go top communications executive Jonathan Friedland: "His descriptive use of the N-word on at least two occasions at work showed unacceptably low racial awareness and sensitivity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX's top spokesman fired over use of racial term...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netflixs-top-spokesman-fired-over-racial-term-232824349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix CEO Reed Hastings says he fired the company's top spokesman over use of the N-word. The spokesman, Jonathan Friedland, confirmed in tweets that he was leaving the company, saying he was insensitive in speaking with his team about words that offend in comedy. In a memo to employees, published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushes back against border separation uproar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08eda57806d844618ccfd657e286cf15/Trump-pushes-back-against-border-separation-uproar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump tried to cast doubt Friday on wrenching tales of migrant children separated from their families at the border, dismissing "phony stories o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 people use California assisted death law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07070506167549edacffd30ad6b3f126/Nearly-400-people-used-California-assisted-death-law-in-2017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California health officials reported Friday that 374 terminally ill people took drugs to end their lives in 2017, the first full year after a law made th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone woman digs for family lost under Guatemalan volcanic rubble...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/lone-woman-digs-family-lost-under-guatemalan-volcanic-163412270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Carlos Jasso and Sofia Menchu SAN MIGUEL LOS LOTES, Guatemala (Reuters) - Eleven days after the Fuego volcano rained down on the Guatemalan village of San Miguel Los Lotes, a backhoe ripped the roof off one of the homes buried by ash, revealing a corpse in the still-hot dust. "It's my sister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVER 'CORRECTION'</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/white-house-accuses-democrats-media-exploiting-toddler-photo-175002249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photograph, taken by photographer John Moore at the scene of a border detention this month, became a powerful image in the media coverage of the separation of families at the U.S.-Mexican border. Dozens of newspapers and magazines including Time and the Washington Post published the image. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE:  Few client communications found so far in documents...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/few-client-communications-found-far-michael-cohen-documents-235132326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Brendan Pierson NEW YORK (Reuters) - A review of documents seized from U.S. President Donald Trump's longtime personal lawyer Michael Cohen has so far turned up only a handful of communications between Cohen and his clients, a federal judge said in a written order on Friday. Out of nearly 300,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Turkey opposition candidate challenges Erdogan again in giant rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkey-opposition-candidate-challenges-erdogan-again-giant-rally-194712684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have the courage, confront me," Muharrem Ince, a fiery lawmaker from the secular Republican People's Party (CHP), told hundreds of thousands of people in Ankara. "Look, that's my last proposal to you ... If you want, I can even cancel my Istanbul rally for you. The Ankara campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania does it her way...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/much-ado-melania-us-first-lady-does-her-171043126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after moving into the White House with her young son to rejoin her husband, Melania Trump -- this most enigmatic of presidential wives -- demonstrated once more this week she is anything but the typical US first lady. As the United States grapples with a political crisis sparked by the forcible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela urged to stop spread of measles, diphtheria...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-urged-stop-spread-measles-diphtheria-222825380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pan American Health Organization on Friday painted a bleak picture of Venezuela's healthcare system, calling for urgent action to stop the transmission of measles and diphtheria amid an intensifying crisis that has seen an exodus of doctors. The Americas were declared measles-free in 2016, but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLIANO: Liberate men with satin and corsets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/liberate-men-satin-corsets-fashion-icon-galliano-180745412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Galliano set out Friday to redefine 21st-century masculinity with corsets, sensual satins and vinyl trousers to "liberate" men from their sartorial shackles. The British designer's new collection for Maison Margiela at Paris men's fashion week not only blurred the lines between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another court defeat for jailed Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/22/paul-manafort-money-laundering-charge-664793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manafort's defense team argued that the tens of millions of dollars he's accused of laundering didn't qualify as the proceeds of criminal activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK's Relentless Drive to Track Every Detail of Users' Lives...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/creepy-patents-show-facebooks-relentless-drive-to-track-every-detail-of-users-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook wants to weaponize our phones to spy on us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers accused of dealing meth out of WENDY'S...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/wendys-workers-in-meth-bust-652093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 22--A quartet of fast-food workers sold methamphetamine from a Wendy’s in Georgia, according to police who raided the eatery and busted the employees on narcotics charges. Investigators allege</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels Heading to Border to Help the Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/stormy-daniels-says-shes-headed-to-the-border-next-week-as-soon-as-she-figures-her-best-course-of-action/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX SHARES HIT FRESH HIGHS ON DISNEY DEAL DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/disney-willing-to-divest-more-fox-assets-for-deal-clearance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney said it was willing to divest Twenty-First Century Fox assets that generated up to $1 billion to get a regulatory nod for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-gun protester David Hogg -- protected by armed guards?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/anti-gun-protester-david-hogg-struts-through-nyc-with-armed-guards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Hogg is a VIP now. The 18-year-old attended the Parkland, Florida school where a student murdered 17 people in February, then made himself famous with relentless calls for gun control in the wake of the tragedy. Now he’s got a book deal, and publicists — and armed guards. Sean Di Somma snapped some pictures …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEX PREZ CANDIDATE: FLOOD THE USA!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/22/mexican-candidate-immigration-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal immigration ... what's that?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Fake News With $300 NYT T-Shirt?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/kzkjpx/the-new-york-times-invites-you-to-fight-fake-news-with-this-dollar300-t-shirt-vgtrn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Gray Lady teamed up with a Japanese streetwear company to sell you woke merch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcetti says L.A. can resume overnight sidewalk sleeping ban...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-sidewalk-sleeping-20180622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven years ago, L.A. officials agreed to stop arresting people who bedded down for the night on streets and sidewalks. Now Mayor Eric Garcetti says the city has built enough housing to meet the terms of a legal settlement, clearing the way for the city to enforce the disputed law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Male DC journalists don't tweet with women...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/6/22/17489516/male-politics-reporters-only-tweet-other-men-nikki-usher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals why female journalists are so much less influential on Twitter than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TIME Stands By Cover After 'Correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/time-magazine-stands-by-cover-after-photo-correction-captures-stakes-of-this-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Testimonies...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/22/trump-rips-media-for-ignoring-angel-families-permanently-separated-by-illegal-immigrant-crime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday blasted what he described as a media double standard, as he honored families whose loved ones were killed by illegal immigrants and accused the press of ignoring them to focus on the plight of migrants caught crossing the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Ad Tech Interest Gets Madison Ave. Thumps Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-ts-interest-in-ad-tech-gets-thumbs-up-on-madison-avenue-1529692570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of AT&amp;T’s talks to acquire advertising tech firm AppNexus was welcomed by marketers, who are eager to have more options in the online ad sector beyond the dominant players Google and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAcTc-hFhYQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President meets with 'Angel Families'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/22/trump-meet-families-loved-ones-killed-illegals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the outcry over illegal immigrant children separated from their families, President Trump is meeting at the White House Friday with “Angel Families” — U.S. citizens whose loved ones were killed by illegal immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parmesan Thefts Grate on Cheesemakers; 'Fort Knox' security measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/who-stole-my-cheese-parmesan-thefts-grate-on-italian-cheesemakers-1529682856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parmigiano-Reggiano thieves are driving producers to drastic measures, from installing alarm systems to a storing wheels in a bank’s secure warehouse; “This is Fort Knox for cheese.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Pride parades used to mean protests. Now an excuse for straight kids to party...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/LGBT-issues/2018/06/22/pride-parades-excuse-straight-kids-party/712068002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pride parades were born from radical protests. Recently, however, they've become the latest excuse for straight kids to party. Not everyone is happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugmakers target growing male clientele with 'Brotox'...</title>
      <link>http://nationalpost.com/news/canada/not-just-for-women-cosmetic-targets-men-in-new-brotox-campaign-reports-gradual-increase-in-male-clients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April, the drugmaker rolled out print, television and social media ads during baseball games and the Stanley Cup finals in attempt to lure male customers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex crimes alleged at Hawaii home for naked parties...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38482865/child-sex-crimes-prostitution-alleged-at-nuuanu-home-for-naked-parties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom House in upper Nuuanu advertises for parties like Naked Yoga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For second year, Bernie earns $1,000,000+...</title>
      <link>https://vtdigger.org/2018/06/22/second-year-sanders-earns-1m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;vtdigger.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Parents grab baby after priest SLAPS it during baptism...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5875197/French-Catholic-priest-89-suspended-slapping-baby-baptisim-ceremony-Champeaux.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of Father Jacques Lacroix, 89, slapping the baby boy at a church in Champeaux, near Paris, France was posted on Twitter yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterpiece Mystery: Da Vinci 'earliest' work found after 600 years?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6597726/leonardo-da-vinci-first-ever-painting-discovered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEONARDO da Vinci’s first painting may have been unearthed by eagle-eyed sleuths who claim to have found a fascinating detail unnoticed for 600 years. Using infrared analysis, Italian experts…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver streaming HULU before fatal self-driving crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-uber-selfdriving-crash/uber-driver-was-streaming-hulu-show-just-before-self-driving-car-crash-police-report-idUSKBN1JI0LB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Tempe, Arizona said evidence showed the "safety" driver behind the wheel of a self-driving Uber was distracted and streaming a television show on her phone right up until about the time of a fatal accident in March, deeming the crash that rocked the nascent industry "entirely avoidable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus-size models may fuel obesity epidemic, researchers claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/06/22/plus-size-clothing-overweight-models-may-fuel-obesity-epidemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The normalisation of 'plus-size' clothing and overweight models could be fuelling the obesity epidemic because it leads people to underestimate their own weight, a new study has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates engineered mosquitos kill each other using SEX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6597909/bill-gates-mosquitos-kill-themselves-during-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICROSOFT founder Bill Gates is pouring £3million into a project to create killer mosquitoes that destroy each other through sex. It’s a bold bid to curb malaria, a deadly disease typically t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big brands drop social 'influencers' over fake follower fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/22/wane-social-media-influencers-big-brands-drop-stars-fears-fake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appeal of social media &amp;ldquo;influencers&amp;rdquo; to advertise products may be slipping, as Unilever called for &amp;ldquo;urgent action&amp;rdquo; to address the problem of fake followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON: END OF PELOSI REIGN?</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2018/06/22/is-the-nancy-pelosi-era-coming-to-a-close-at-least-20-democrats-running-for-the-house-oppose-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trend may have caught fire following Conor Lamb's razor-thin in a special election in Pennsylvania this March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says warrant necessary for phone location data...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/supreme-court-says-warrant-necessary-for-phone-location-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US justices say law enforcement needs a warrant to follow your digital footprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Erdogan faces biggest election challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkeys-master-campaigner-erdogan-faces-biggest-election-challenge-131243223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dominating Turkish politics for a decade and a half, President Tayyip Erdogan now faces his biggest electoral challenge, from a combative former teacher who has revitalised a dispirited opposition in less than two months. Turkey holds presidential and parliamentary elections on Sunday that are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation of Americans Entering Old Age Least Prepared in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-generation-of-americans-is-entering-old-age-the-least-prepared-in-decades-1529676033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low incomes, paltry savings, high debt burdens, broken family structures, failed insurance—the U.S. is upending decades of progress in securing life’s final chapter. According to a Wall Street Journal tally, more than 40% of households headed by people aged 55 through 70 lack sufficient resources to maintain their living standards in retirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: For Love of God, Will Someone Put 'JURASSIC' Out of Its Misery?</title>
      <link>http://observer.com/2018/06/jurassic-world-fallen-kingdom-movie-review-please-just-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As brainless summer-escapism movies go, this one can’t go fast enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hair extensions fly during wild brawl between women inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5872533/Shocking-moment-hair-extensions-flying-wild-brawl-four-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair extensions went flying during a wild brawl inside a Walmart in Ohio. A shocking video shows the moment four women exchanged blows shortly after walking through the doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Hunting Serial Tip Jar Thief -- Who Flees In MERCEDES...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/police-hunt-for-tip-jar-thief-who-escapes-in-a-mercedes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grand total of loot taken from both businesses? Only $35.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France faces suit over no-sex rule for blood donations by gay men...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/france-faces-suit-over-no-sex-rule-blood-130322962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Frenchman has filed a discrimination suit at Europe's top rights court over a rule that requires gay men to refrain from having sex for a year before they donate blood, his lawyer said Friday. Laurent Drelon, 48, has been prohibited from giving blood several times since he first tried to do so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery extinct ape discovered in ancient tomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/22/mystery-extinct-ape-discovered-ancient-chinese-imperial-tomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An entirely new species of ape has been discovered buried in an ancient tomb in central China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC strikes deal on production levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/opec-ministers-strike-deal-on-oil-production-levels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPEC ministers meeting in Vienna have agreed on oil production levels for their countries and crude-producing nations cooperating with the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine protects heart?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/caffeine-protect-heart-helping-make-energy-mouse-study/story?id=56026309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research builds on human studies that showed coffee has health benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing news costs companies $43.6 million -- every minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/disturbing-news-costs-u-s-companies-43-6-million-every-minute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers reading and dwelling on stories like those of immigrant children taken from parents harm productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals back self-styled top pimp...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/age-trump-evangelicals-back-self-styled-top-u-113200418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He styles himself as America's best-known pimp, a strip-club owner who runs multiple brothels and looks set to win a seat as a Republican in the Nevada legislature with the blessing of many conservative Christian voters. Meet Dennis Hof, whose political rise reflects fundamental changes in electoral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He 'has all the tapes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-mugs-trump-critic-tom-arnold-n885611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold is hunting for 'incriminating' tapes of Trump as part of a show for Vice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOM ARNOLD: Cohen and I are teaming up to take Trump down...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/393598-tom-arnold-cohen-and-i-are-teaming-up-to-take-trump-down </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Tom Arnold said Friday that he and President Trump’s former, longtime personal lawyer are teaming up to “take down” the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: First summer in 20 years no comedy grosses $100 million...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/movies/la-ca-mn-comedy-box-office-struggles-20180622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studio comedies used to be a reliable staple of summer moviegoing. But, even as many proclaim we're in a golden age of comedy, lately the genre has been stumbling badly at the box office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Cities see spike in cheating spouses...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/22/cities-most-ashley-madison-accounts-cheating-husbands/720864002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheating husbands and wives might be most common in Seattle, Washington, according to a report from infidelity website Ashley Madison.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
