<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NFL star had meds taken away  before killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2666277/nfl-phillip-adams-meds-cut-off-killing-spree/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EX-NFL star Phillip Adams had reportedly just had his meds taken away by his doctor victim before going on a killing spree that left five dead. Adams fatally shot Dr Robert Lesslie, 70, his wife, B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought he was in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2021/04/08/tiger-woods-crash-report-reveals-clues-his-condition-day/7151217002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods thought he was in Florida when interviewed by a deputy at a Los Angeles County hospital right after his crash in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heart Failure, Stroke Cases On Rise In Men Under 40...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/heart-failure-stroke-men-under-40/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research also discovered a link between higher rates of cardiovascular disease and obesity or low fitness levels as a teenager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: DISNEY makes pick for next ABCNEWS president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/disney-makes-its-pick-next-abc-news-president-n1263584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Godwin, the executive vice president of CBS News, looks set to become the first Black woman to lead a broadcast news division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: NASA prepares for first helicopter flight on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/09/nasa-helicopter-mars-479768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's plan to launch the Ingenuity on Sunday has been decades in the making, says Robert Hogg, the deputy surface mission manager for the Mars 2020 program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant Devastating Brazil Spreading in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9453651/Brazil-coronavirus-variant-second-common-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now at least 434 cases of Brazil's P1 variant, which is capable of reinfecting COVID-19 survivors, in the U.S., according to Centers for Disease Control and Prevention tracking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Pelosi's war with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/2021/04/09/bracing-battle-inside-nancy-pelosis-war-donald-trump/7053833002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The election she thought would be the end of her career became the beginning of its most consequential chapter: Defying a 'scary' president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's biggest boom since 1946?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/global-economy-boom-growth-100e317f-2c0e-4465-8c18-2b13c2c1353d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The years-long economic boom is likely to be a global phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA hitting vaccine wall?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-coronavirus-vaccines-republicans-rural-states-34755cbf-384e-4539-bb45-68a775581f6f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people who are eager for a vaccine is shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top court orders probe of Bolsonaro pandemic steps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-brazil-judiciary-coronavirus-pandemic-sao-paulo-31decb098c1058ca0862b1894270ca90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO (AP) — A Brazilian Supreme Court justice ordered the Senate on Thursday to investigate the government's handling of the coronavirus crisis and the full court ruled that churches can be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US warships to deploy in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-usa-turkey/turkey-says-u-s-warships-to-deploy-in-black-sea-until-may-4-idUSKBN2BW1HV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has informed Turkey that two of its warships will pass through Turkish straits to be deployed in the Black Sea until May 4, Ankara said on Friday, as Russia has bulked up its military forces on Ukraine's eastern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans next...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/09/elon-musks-neuralink-shows-video-of-monkey-using-mind-to-play-pong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neuralink, the brain machine interface company founded by Tesla CEO Elon Musk, has published a video of a monkey playing the video game Pong with its mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Attacks DUNKIN' Clerk With Tip Jar When Asked To Cover Face...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/dunkin-employee-attacked-tip-jar-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dunkin’ store served up a chaotic scene recently when police said a customer attacked a worker after being asked to put on a face mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Americans Infected With Variant Devastating Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/brazilian-p1-coronavirus-variant-has-infected-hundreds-of-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The P1 variant that was first identified in Brazil is now the second most prevalent in the United States, with at least 434 people having been infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How monkeys made more friends after their island was devastated by hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/offbeat/puerto-rico-exeter-pennsylvania-hurricane-maria-exeter-university-b1828619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rhesus macaques living in Cayo Santiago also became more tolerant of each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Warns Risk of Broader Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/kremlin-says-ukraine-s-actions-raise-risk-of-broader-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin Warns of Risk of Broader War in Ukraine Conflict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE PHILIP DEAD AT WINDSOR CASTLE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14207808/prince-philip-dead-duke-edinburgh-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Philip has died aged 99, Buckingham Palace announced today. The Duke of Edinburgh, who had been married to the Queen for 73 years and described as her constant strength, passed away “p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Migration: Moving to Cities While Others Flee...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/09/reverse-migration-moving-to-cities-while-others-flee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly Shoul and Alex White spent years trying to get out of their house in York, Pa., only to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Your Illegal Drugs Pure? New Zealand Will Check for You...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/09/are-your-illegal-drugs-pure-new-zealand-will-check-them-for-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand — New Zealand has enshrined into law a one-year experiment allowing drug users to have illegal substances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New footage captures 'pyramid UFOs swarming Navy destroyer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/astonishing-new-footage-captures-pyramid-23882803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amazing video and collection of photos of a "spherical" craft swarming a US Navy destroyer were allegedly part of a classified briefing conducted to "de-stigmatise the UAP problem"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch monkey with Musk's brain chip play video games with mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/elon-musks-neuralink-reveals-monkey-playing-pong-with-brain-implant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Neuralink video shows nine-year-old Macaque playing the classic video game... using a brain-implant device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will take plea deal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/matt-gaetz-associate-to-take-plea-deal-in-sex-trafficking-case-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg, an associate of embattled GOP Congressman Matt Gaetz, is expected to take a plea deal in his own sex-trafficking case — and cooperate with federal authorities, according to re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST:  Gaetz Paid Accused Sex Trafficker, Who Then Venmo'd Teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gaetz-paid-accused-sex-trafficker-who-then-venmod-teen?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56%  Say Pandemic Ruined Their Sex Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/2020-pandemic-stress-ruined-sex-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;56 percent experienced performance anxiety or concerns their sexual performance might not meet their partners wants, needs, or expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK VAN DYKE AT 95:  I DON'T KNOW HOW I DID IT!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/04/08/exclusive-dick-van-dyke-95-on-his-kennedy-center-honor-i-never-thought-id-live-this-long-i-dont-know-how-i-did-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick van Dyke — of the towering performers of our lives — is thrilled and surprised to receive a Kennedy Center honor this June. He’s only 95. (It should have been 20 years ago at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Bar Slammed After Requiring Proof Of Vaccination...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/denver-bar-max-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bar Max in Denver is now open after being closed for much of the pandemic. Patrons can enjoy a cocktail inside only if they provide proof of vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY passes CA to become highest taxed state!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ny-lawmakers-reach-212-billion-economic-deal-to-boost-economy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo and state lawmakers reached a new budget deal in Albany to the tune of $212 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's tax crackdown on tech giants: Firms face tougher measures under global plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9451921/Joe-Bidens-tax-crackdown-tech-giants.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US President plans to force companies to pay more tax in the countries they operate in, leaked documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caribbean island orders mandatory evacuations amid volcano eruption fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/08/st-vincent-evacuation-volcano-la-soufriere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caribbean island says there is a ‘substantial prospect of disaster’ after several days of increased seismic activity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas beat their chests to size each other up, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/apr/08/gorilla-beat-chest-signal-size-avoid-fight-with-rival-researchers-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chest-beating behaviour in male gorillas allows them to signal their size and avoid fights with larger rivals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Blood from Young Slow Aging? Silicon Valley Bet Billions It Will...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/2021/04/16/can-blood-young-people-slow-aging-silicon-valley-has-bet-billions-it-will-1581447.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biotech startups are trying to hack the process of aging and, in the process, stave off the most devastating diseases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC RICH FACE 52% TAX RATE</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-york-city-rich-face-52-percent-combined-top-income-tax-rate-highest-in-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of New York's top earners may have to pay roughly half their salaries to city, state and federal governments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Purges Desantis Video Over Claims Children Don't Need to Wear Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/youtube-purges-florida-governor-video-over-claims-children-dont-need-to-wear-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube deleted a video in which Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis and a few medical experts questioned the effectiveness of children wearing masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE sales hit record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/08/rolls-royce-hits-new-sales-record-in-the-first-quarter-as-the-wealthy-demand-luxury-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The luxury auto company delivered 1,380 cars in the first quarter, up 62% from the same time last year as the pandemic started hurting sales and manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro doubles down despite mass death...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210408221628-iz0oi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Brazil sets new daily COVID-19 death record as hospital supplies run low</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim view of global future offered in intelligence report...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-environment-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-health-cbcafe70b4724a7605d56d40fa294027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. intelligence officials are painting a dark picture of the world's future, writing in a report released Thursday that the coronavirus pandemic has deepened economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NFL player kills 5, then self...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/phillip-adams-kills-5-then-himself-south-carolina-aaf71f2618f139ab3781592634c8e37c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCK HILL, S.C. (AP) — Former NFL player Phillip Adams fatally shot five people, including a prominent doctor, his wife and their two grandchildren before killing himself early...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries worldwide hit new records for virus cases, deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/countries-worldwide-hit-new-records-coronavirus-cases-deaths-29b18a267fbe972766403f8de0fee415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambulances filled with breathless patients lined up in Brazil as nations around the world set new records Thursday for COVID-19 deaths and new coronavirus infections. The disease surged even in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON SET FOR VICTORY IN UNION ELECTION... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amazoncom-inc-alabama-birmingham-fadc4bad21f8eef32cd8f5a3afbd33ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vote counting in the union push at an Amazon warehouse in Bessemer, Alabama, is underway but a winner may not be determined until Friday. By Thursday evening, the count was tilting heavily...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of Americans want THE ROCK to run for president!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/poll-nearly-50-of-americans-want-dwayne-the-rock-johnson-to-run-for-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll suggests that many Americans would like to see both Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson and Matthew McConaughey run for public office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin puts 100,000 troops on Ukraine border...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/russia-ukraine-days-war-vladimir-23880564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russia-Ukraine crisis could be days from exploding into war with a source saying UK commanders are on "high alert" and monitoring the situation "with growing concern"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthiest look for exits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/08/new-yorks-wealthiest-look-for-exits-as-state-readies-hefty-tax-increase-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's business leaders are looking for exits as their taxes are set to be raised in the states upcoming budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE BUILDS TO END REMOTE LEARNING...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/stop-abusing-our-children-and-open-the-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Open. The. Schools. It’s been more than a year since schools closed for the COVID-19 virus. Across the country and across the world, schools have opened up, full-time, for students. But those of us…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain herd on Monday?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-britain-pass-covid-herd-184428044.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain will pass the threshold for herd immunity on Monday, according to dynamic modelling by University College London (UCL), placing more pressure on the Government to move faster in releasing restrictions. According to the UCL results, published this week, the number of people who have protection against the virus either through vaccination or previous infection will hit 73.4 per cent on April 12 – enough to tip the country into herd immunity. The number is in stark contrast to the modelling released by Imperial College this week, which suggested there was just 34 per cent protection by the end of March. Last week, antibody testing by the Office for National Statistics (ONS) suggested that, in the week ending March 14, around 54 per cent of people in England already had antibodies to the virus, and slightly less in the devolved nations. Since then, a further 7.1 million people have received a first dose of vaccine and nearly 100,000 have tested positive for the virus, with many more acquiring a silent, asymptomatic infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lost golden city of Luxor' discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/history/article/lost-golden-city-luxor-discovered-archaeologists-egypt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 3,400-year-old royal city was built by Amenhotep III, abandoned by his heretic son, Akhenaten, and contains stunningly preserved remains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Radio Blasts From Space Just Got Whole Lot Weirder...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7bjb8/mysterious-radio-blasts-from-space-just-got-a-whole-lot-weirder-somehow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists discovered that so-called "giant radio pulses" coincide with X-rays, suggesting they are hundreds of times more energetic than previously thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC director says racism 'serious public health threat'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/547251-cdc-director-says-racism-is-serious-public-health-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Thursday declared racism a "serious public health threat," becoming the largest federal agency to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATHER:  'Football messed him up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/e2-80-98i-think-the-football-messed-him-up-e2-80-99-phillip-adams-e2-80-99-dad-blames-nfl-for-mass-shooting-suicide/ar-BB1frDGN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after former Jets cornerback Phillip Adams allegedly killed five people, then himself, his dad said his years in the NFL changed him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner moves closer to California recall run...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/caitlyn-jenner-california-governor-run-480232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality TV star and transgender rights activist has brought aboard a team of seasoned GOP strategists for a possible campaign for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$60 million per week to shelter!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-administration-spending-60-million-per-week-to-shelter-unaccompanied-minors/ar-BB1frIhG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services has announced at least 10 temporary sites to shelter thousands of teens and children at convention centers, oil worker camps and military bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida sues CDC to allow cruises to resume...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/08/florida-sues-cdc-to-allow-cruises-to-resume-us-sailings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's governor said the state will sue the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, demanding cruise ships be allowed to resume sailing immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day Parade on National Mall Canceled...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/fourth-of-july/2021/04/national-park-service-no-independence-day-parade-on-national-mall-in-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Park Service has announced that it will skip this year’s Independence Day Parade on the National Mall, citing logistics and planning limitations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left-wing prosecutors face reckoning as murders spike nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/homicide-surge-progressives-district-attorneys-479966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in murders across the country is testing their resolve — and their electability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Reporter Robbed Of Camera In San Fran For 2nd Time In 2 Months!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/kpix-5-reporter-guard-pepper-sprayed-attempted-robbery-san-francisco-golden-gate-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the second time in two months, a KPIX 5 journalist was the victim of a crime while on the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturers embrace robots, perfect pandemic worker...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/manufacturers-embrace-robots-perfect-pandemic-worker-n1263434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After social distancing measures forced layoffs in labor-intensive factories, manufacturers turned to automation, despite the high cost. Now, they aren't going back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA considering sending warships to Black Sea amid Russia-Ukraine tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/08/politics/ukraine-us-black-sea/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is considering sending warships into the Black Sea in the next few weeks in a show of support for Ukraine amid Russia's increased military presence on Ukraine's eastern border, a US defense official told CNN Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Researchers Testing Nuke Blast Defense Against Earth-Threatening Asteroids...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/lawrence-livermore-earth-threatening-asteroids-nuclear-defense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds like a scene from a Hollywood sci-fi thriller, but researchers from Lawrence Livermore National lab have joined with an Air Force team of technologists to test if a nuclear blast could be used to deflect a earth-threatening asteroid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key figure likely cooperating with feds...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/08/key-figure-in-matt-gaetz-probe-likely-cooperating-with-federal-prosecutors-480289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We believe this case is going to be a plea," federal prosecutor Roger Handberg said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbage Cans Set On Fire At Transit Stations Across NYC...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/sources-garbage-cans-set-on-fire-at-transit-stations-across-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell CBS2 the fires appear to have been intentionally set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reigning Mrs. World arrested over onstage melee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/reigning-mrs-world-caroline-jurie-arrested-sri-lanka-e686337f8ce16add45937eb0035ff8d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLOMBO, Sri Lanka (AP) — Police in Sri Lanka on Thursday arrested the reigning Mrs. World for pulling the crown off the head of the winner of a Mrs. Sri Lanka beauty pageant and allegedly causing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Executive Actions Could Turn Millions Into Felons...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/guns/biden-gun-exec-orders-could-turn-millions-into-felons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden issued sweeping executive actions to restrict access to popular firearms on Thursday, measures that could turn millions of Americans into felons overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Party of 5,000 Off-Roaders Leads to Absolute Chaos in AZ National Forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/news/40104/illegal-party-of-5000-off-roaders-leads-to-absolute-chaos-in-arizona-national-forest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven vehicular accidents were reported by authorities with violations including DUIs and illegal use of fireworks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden targets 'ghost guns', 'red flag' laws in new gun control measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/biden-target-ghost-guns-red-flag-laws-new-gun-control-n1263438</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president wants to curb the spread of homemade firearms that lack traceable serial numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Britain's richest men stabbed to death inside mansion...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-one-britains-richest-men-23878440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sir Richard Lexington Sutton, an 83-year-old Baronet, was attacked inside his £2m home in north Dorset, on Wednesday night with a woman in her 60s also suffering knife injuries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant encounters up 71% as Biden grapples with border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/04/08/migrants-border-were-up-march-biden-grapples-immigration/7130399002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection encountered 18,890 unaccompanied children at the southern border in March, a 100% increase from February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will give undocumenteds $15,600 stimulus cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2661358/new-york-illegal-immigrants-15600-stimulus-payments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York state has approved a fund that will award a one-time $15,600 stimulus payment to illegal workers. The $2.2billion program for “excluded workers” will provide payments for hundr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Villagers gather to 'wake the dead' in bizarre ritual; Dousing corpse in water...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/villagers-gather-wake-dead-bizarre-23877289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING, DISTRESSING CONTENT: The bizarre footage shows dozens of villagers surrounding the corpse of a recently deceased man before chanting, pounding on his chest and covering him in water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic cold blast takes Alaska back to winter; -30&amp;#8457 in Fairbanks!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/all-time-april-low-could-fall-in-alaskan-city/929260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shift in the jet stream will send Arctic air pouring into Alaska, threatening to send temperatures as low as 30 below zero F, which could rival a record last set in 1911.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  America's bipolar summer...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/976080/americas-bipolar-summer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'A time to mourn and a time to dance'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Population Growth Slowest Since 1918...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/us-population-growth-lowest-since-1918-negative-economic-impact-demographics-2020-1-1028810617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J SHOT FACES MORE SCRUTINY</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/covid-vaccine-clinic-johnson-dicks-sporting-goods-park-adverse-side-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID vaccination clinic at Dick's Sporting Goods Park was put on hold after 11 patients experienced adverse side effects after receiving the shot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
