<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>World Press Freedom Day events raise alarm on fake news...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9591968b2a804c009a04da9edc8dc6f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — A rising tide of fake news and disinformation is dominating World Press Freedom Day discussions taking place this week in Ethiopia, which is hosting the event after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll finds hunger for change to US system of govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6e8132f2c131477eb4b9ff67f02c7921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After more than two years of the Donald Trump presidency, Andrea Petrusky is ready for some fundamental changes in the way the United States government works. "Right now we're being shown...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass evacuations as monster cyclone heads for India...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/mass-evacuations-monster-cyclone-targets-india-071647709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 800,000 people in eastern India have been evacuated from the path of an incoming major cyclone packing winds gusting up to 200 kilometres (125 miles) per hour and torrential rains, officials said Thursday. The Indian weather service said Extremely Severe Cyclonic Storm Fani was expected to make</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel comes to halt to commemorate Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-comes-halt-commemorate-holocaust-083053833.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israelis stopped their cars and stood still, often with heads bowed, for two minutes Thursday for the country's annual commemoration of the six million Jewish victims of the Nazi Holocaust. Sirens rang out nationwide during the commemoration, while pedestrians and drivers in Jerusalem, the bustling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG DOES MAYOR...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5581815/mayor-pete-buttigiegs-unlikely-untested-unprecedented-presidential-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Pete Buttigieg addressed supporters off a back porch in Marshalltown, Iowa, the Devil was whispering his name. “Pete,” the Devil hissed into a microphone....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie never had this before: Campaign machine that's crushing it...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/politics/la-na-pol-bernie-sanders-campaign-machine-20190501-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders now has the campaign infrastructure he lacked when he first ran for president, and it's the envy of the Washington establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese database tracking cellphone usage, car location, electricity consumption...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Chinese-database-is-tracking-cellphone-usage-car-13812775.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities in Xinjiang are building a comprehensive database that tracks the precise locations of its citizens, their mobile app usage, their religious habits and even their electricity and gasoline consumption as part of a technology-driven crackdown that has interred an estimated 1 million Muslim citizens, according to an analysis of Chinese government software by a U.S. rights group.  In the last two years, a growing body of testimony by former Xinjiang residents and a trove of government procurement documents, directives and state media reports have painted a picture of oppression in the region, where Chinese authorities have relied on far-reaching electronic surveillance to help dictate its mass internment program.  New York-based Human Rights Watch said Thursday it gained a new level of insight into precisely what information the Chinese government collects by examining a mobile app that Xinjiang officials use to input data into a database called the Integrated Joint Operations Platform.  The IJOP system, which keeps track of practically the entire Xinjiang population, alerts authorities when a person unexpectedly crosses virtual "fences" by driving past a certain checkpoint or checking into a hotel, according to the rights group. It tracks citizens' smartphones, their national identification cards and GPS devices on their vehicles, which have been widely installed under new government regulations.  After denying their existence for a year, Chinese authorities have recently argued that Xinjiang's network of detention centers are built for educating and de-radicalizing a Muslim population that became increasingly influenced by extremist Islamic ideology.  International rights groups and Western countries say the limited extremist threat does not warrant the vast scale of the internments, a suffocating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Older Americans Aren't Retiring...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-02/older-americans-aren-t-retiring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gets powerful new rival in Letitia James...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/441709-trump-gets-powerful-new-rival-in-letitia-james</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has a new and powerful rival in Letitia James, the first woman and the first African American to serve as New York’s attorney general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes Adds Tarantino to Competition Lineup...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cannes-adds-quentin-tarantinos-once-a-time-hollywood-1203730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The addition will bring Brad Pitt, Leonardo DiCaprio and Margot Robbie to the red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American military prepping for Guaido takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/us-military-prepping-for-guaido-takeover-in-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commander of U.S. forces in Latin America told Congress Wednesday that the military is developing plans to be immediately ready for any contingency if Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaidó ousts dictator Nicolás Maduro from power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Shapiro Target of Death Threats; FBI Makes Arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/05/01/ben-shapiro-death-threats-man-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative talk show host Ben Shapiro target of death threats and FBI makes arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MODFATHER: Man who invented metal mohawks, genital implants...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sun-men/8982430/meet-modfather-extreme-body-piercings-genitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEET the body modification artist dubbed the “Modfather” who has invented extreme body implants and – some even fit in your genitals. Steve Haworth, based in Arizona in the US, has been haile…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO info not for general public, Navy says...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/UFO-information-not-expected-to-go-to-general-13810876.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy has drafted a procedure to investigate and catalogue reports of unidentified flying objects coming in from its pilots. But the service doesn't expect to make the information public, citing privileged and classified reporting that is typically included in such files.  Joe Gradisher, a spokesman for the office of the deputy chief of naval operations for information warfare, said in a statement that the Navy expects to keep the information it gathers private for a number of reasons.  "Military aviation safety organizations always retain reporting of hazards to aviation as privileged information in order to preserve the free and honest prioritization and discussion of safety among aircrew," Gradisher said. "Furthermore, any report generated as a result of these investigations will, by necessity, include classified information on military operations."  He added, "Therefore, no release of information to the general public is expected."  The Navy's recent decision to draft formal guidelines for pilots to document encounters with unexplained aerial phenomena comes after the revelation in late 2017 that the Pentagon ran a secret "UFO" office that spent $22 million over five years to collect and analyze "anomalous aerospace threats." Funding for the office, known as the Advanced Aerospace Threat Identification Program, or AATIP, officially ended in 2012, though operations continued.  Among other things, the program resulted in the release of footage from the cockpit cameras of military aircraft, which appeared to document oval-shape vessels that resemble flying Tic Tacs.  Reports of curious sightings from military aircraft aren't new. During World War II, Allied military pilots witnessed unexplained objects and fireballs that they dubbed "foo fighters." A number of official government investigations looked into such...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' fans exposed to measles at midnight premiere, LA officials say...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article229916659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ ALDRIN: Time to plot  migration to Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Buzz-Aldrin-It-s-time-to-focus-on-the-great-13811434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Vice President Mike Pence announced that we are headed back to the moon. I am with him, in spirit and aspiration. Having been there, I can say it is high time we returned. When Neil Armstrong, Michael Collins and I went to the moon 50 years ago this July, we did so with a mission. Apollo 11 aimed to prove America's can-do commitment to space exploration, as well as its national security and technological superiority. We did all that. We also "Came in Peace for all Mankind." More of that is needed now.  Today, many nations have eyes for the moon, from China and Russia to friends in Europe and Middle East. That is all good. The United States should cooperate - and offer itself as a willing team leader - in exploring every aspect of the moon, from its geology and topography to its hydrology and cosmic history. In doing so, we can take "low-Earth orbit" cooperation to the moon, openly, eagerly and collegially.  Meanwhile, another looming orb - the red one - should become a serious focus of U.S. attention. Mars is waiting to be discovered, not by clever robots and rovers - though I support NASA's unmanned missions - but by living, breathing, walking, talking, caring and daring men and women.  To make that happen, members of Congress, the Trump administration and the American public must care enough to make human exploration missions to Mars a national priority. To be clear, I do not mean spending billions of taxpayer dollars on a few hijinks or joy rides, allowing those who return to write books, tweet photos and talk of the novelty. I mean something very different.  The United States' eyes - and our unified commitment - should focus on opening the door, in our time, to the great migration of humankind to Mars. Books aplenty have been written about how to do this, and they have inspired government and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot lounges approved in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5vegas.com/news/marijuana-lounges-approved-by-las-vegas-city-council/article_6559f19c-6c56-11e9-a57f-cffdf90fa3f6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5vegas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas is the first Nevada city to approve marijuana consumption lounges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's a Good Boy? Wolves, not dogs, apparently...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/whos-good-boy-wolves-not-dogs-apparently-211249743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of touchscreen experiments carried out by the Wolf Science Center in Vienna, Austria, found that wolves make for more selfless pack mates than dogs who were also raised in groups. The study's authors say the findings suggest domestic dogs inherited their cooperative tendencies from their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS:  System Off Florida May Be 2019's First Named Atlantic Storm...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/system-off-florida-may-become-183127544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patch of low pressure swirling over the northwest Bahamas has a 20 percent chance over the next five days of becoming the first tropical storm of 2019, the National Hurricane Center in Miami said. “May storms are not all that uncommon,” said Jim Rouiller, chief meteorologist at Energy Weather Group</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest proxy battle with Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/trump-venezuela-russia-1296784</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The face-off is a potentially explosive confrontation between President Donald Trump and Vladimir Putin as the president heads into his re-election bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR CANCELS ON HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/barr-testimony-house-democrats-1296377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney general is boycotting the hearing amid a fight with Democrats over the ground rules for his testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/441723-rift-opens-between-mueller-and-barr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr has described special counsel Robert Mueller as a friend. But their relationship is showing some strain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' moviegoers in Orange County measles exposure warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2019/04/30/orange-county-confirms-1st-measles-case-of-2019-possible-exposure-sites-include-amc-theatres-in-fullerton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Placentia woman who contracted the virus is under voluntary isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small retailers who sold through AMAZON face tax time bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/opinion/editorials/la-ed-amazon-marketplace-taxes-20190501-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California agency wants back taxes from small out-of-state businesses that sold products through Amazon. It's unfair retailers avoided the sales tax burden, but they played by the rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second known portrait of Leonardo da Vinci uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/art/news/leonardo-da-vinci-portrait-picture-new-exhibition-buckingham-palace-a8895771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARTOONIST BLAMES 'JEWISH PROPAGANDA MACHINE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/01/media/new-york-times-anti-semitic-cartoon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen New York Times staffers described a short-staffed international publication; an opinion section prone to self-inflicted wounds; and an ongoing debate about the newspaper's biases and blind spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Derby Favorite 'Omaha Beach' Scratched From Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.wlky.com/article/morning-line-favorite-omaha-beach-scratches-out-of-kentucky-derby/27337342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wlky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kentucky Derby favorite Omaha Beach has scratched, according to its trainer Richard Mandella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronaldo denies being mystery buyer of $19M BUGATTI supercar...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/05/01/cristiano-ronaldo-bugatti-supercar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The car tops out at 260 MILES PER HOUR!!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveler tells TSA bag full of moose poop is for politicians...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/news/nation-world/national/article229864959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe light on policy, heavy on emotion...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/01/joe-biden-2020-1296862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former veep shows signs of rust in Iowa, but his supporters don’t mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER SAYS TRYING TO 'BLACKMAIL'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/uncategorized/nadler-blasts-terrified-barr-for-cancelling-house-appearance-hes-trying-to-blackmail-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortly after Attorney General William Barr announced that he would not appear in front of the House Judiciary Committee on Thursday morning as planned, Rep. Jerry Nadler suggested that the Attorney General was simply too chicken to appear in front of a skilled attorney to answer questions and that is why he was not planning to show up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House seeking NSA surveillance power permanent renewal?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Permanent-renewal-of-NSA-law-possible-13809653.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Trump administration has signaled in recent weeks that it may seek the permanent renewal of a surveillance law that has, among other things, enabled the National Security Agency to gather and analyze Americans' phone records as part of terrorism investigations, according to five U.S. officials familiar with the matter.  The White House, these officials said, was prepared to issue a public statement calling on Congress to reauthorize in full Section 215 of the Patriot Act, which in the past has been the focus of heated debate over the acceptable bounds of government surveillance. The plan to issue a statement was put on hold, officials said, but it illustrates nonetheless where the administration stands on the contested issue of national security authority.  The officials spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss an issue that remains deeply sensitive.  A White House spokeswoman declined to comment or explain why the statement was not issued, saying only that the matter is still under deliberation.  Section 215 was last revised in 2015 as part of the USA Freedom Act after a former NSA contractor, Edward Snowden, exposed how the government was collecting vast quantities of Americans' phone logs to be able to scan them for clues to terrorist plots. This "metadata" denoted the calls' time, date and duration, and who called whom, but did not include the conversations' content. The ensuing uproar led Congress to impose restraints, and last year, the NSA reportedly suspended the program because of technical issues that put Americans' privacy at risk.  The statute expires in mid-December, and the reported suspension of the phone records program had raised questions about whether the Trump administration would seek to renew it. National security officials widely expect the administration to call for Congress...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside iconic Hollywood hotel full of titillating celeb tales...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6971983/Inside-famed-Chateau-Marmont-actors-Anthony-Perkins-Tab-Hunter-began-secret-affair.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's Chateau Marmont is legendary for the antics celebrities have gotten into at the iconic hotel, writes author Shawn Levy in his book, The Castle on Sunset, out May 7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTEMPT?</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/House-Democrats-consider-holding-Barr-in-contempt-13810687.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democrats on the House Judiciary Committee are discussing holding Attorney General William Barr in contempt of Congress for ignoring a subpoena and threatening to skip a scheduled, according to several lawmakers and officials familiar with the plan.  During a pair of closed-door meetings Tuesday evening and Wednesday morning, the committee decided that it would probably make a push for a Barr contempt citation if he refuses to testify Thursday or ignores their subpoena for the full, unredacted report by special counsel Robert Mueller III.  Lawmakers and officials, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to freely discuss private deliberations, cautioned that no final decision has been made. Barr was supposed to hand over the full Mueller report by 10 a.m. Wednesday.  Additionally, Barr on Friday threatened to skipa Judiciary Committee hearing over objections to the format in which a counsel would question him alongside lawmakers. As of 4 p.m. Wednesday, the committee has yet to receive an answer about whether he is coming, panel officials said.  "We are now seeing the attorney general engage in obstruction of a congressional subpoena," said Rep. David Cicilline, D-R.I., a member of the committee. "Congress has a number of tools at its disposal, obviously beginning with holding him in contempt."  Discussions about contempt for Barr follow the disclosure that Mueller challenged the attorney general's handling of the report on Russia interference in the 2016 election. The news that Mueller felt Barr misconstrued his findings reverberated in the House, with Democrats accusing Barr of perjuring himself in testimony to Congress.  In back-to-back congressional hearings in early April, Barr claimed to have no knowledge of Mueller's concerns with his four-page summary of the report's findings. But Mueller's March 27...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: US HOPES FOR VENEZUELA CHANGE FIZZLE -- AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/efee26c91e0d418fa04da5f981c7d737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For the third time this year, the big moment in Venezuela has turned into a bust. Trump administration officials had expected that Wednesday might turn out to be the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship quarantined after measles case confirmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/2019/05/cruise-ship-quarantined-in-st-lucia-after-measles-case-confirmed-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News reports the ship has been quarantined since Monday (April 29).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing cat returns home 475 days after missing in mudslide...</title>
      <link>https://www.keyt.com/news/santa-barbara-s-county/missing-cat-returns-home-475-days-after-it-went-missing-in-the-montecito-mudslide/1073956466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.keyt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Montecito family is overjoyed after being reunited with their beloved cat that was missing for 475 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules museum can keep Nazi-looted Pissarro painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/us-judge-rules-spanish-museum-can-keep-nazi-looted-pissarro-painting/a-48566221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US court has ruled a Spanish museum legally purchased a prized French Impressionist painting looted by Nazis. The judge criticized Spain for not following its "moral commitments" to return the Camille Pissarro work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death squads' add new, terrifying layer...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/05/01/maduros-death-squads-add-new-terrifying-layer-intimidation-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first difference I noticed was the FAES.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR: 'BIT SNITTY'</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-barr/barr-defends-clearing-trump-on-obstruction-chides-snitty-mueller-letter-idUSKCN1S73HF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under pressure from Democrats, Attorney General William Barr on Wednesday defend...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Elite on Edge as Prosecutors Pursue Admissions Scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/las-elite-on-edge-as-prosecutors-pursue-more-parents-in-admissions-scandal/ar-AAAM29V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California population growth slowest in state history...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-population-growth-20190501-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state's population growth rate in 2018 was the slowest in state history as births declined and an upward trend in deaths continued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT updating 'unconscious bias' trainings...</title>
      <link>https://www.jta.org/quick-reads/new-york-times-to-discipline-editor-who-oked-anti-semitic-cartoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jta.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are updating our unconscious bias training" to include "direct focus on anti-Semitism," the New York Times publisher said the note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin signs controversial, isolating 'sovereign internet' law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190501-putin-signs-controversial-internet-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin signs controversial internet law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dems Question, Then Fundraise Off Testimony...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/441677-harris-fundraises-off-barr-testimony-americans-deserve-truth-and-integrity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopefuls Sens. Kamala Harris (Calif.) and Cory Booker (N.J.) sent out fundraising blasts Wednesday afternoon following their questioning of Attorney General William Barr on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist says MAGGOT SAUSAGES may feed overpopulated world...</title>
      <link>https://montrealgazette.com/news/world/aussie-scientist-maggot-sausage-is-a-meat-alternative/wcm/5ed74031-b9e4-4314-b060-fccfd2287b64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;montrealgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people already debate the types of meat found in sausages, but this idea may make your stomach churn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rise tests  plan of casting foes as socialists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/42fd2ad31a1a450980e841db142eec09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump may want to cast his potential Democratic rivals as a band of angry socialists, but Joe Biden is not cooperating with Trump's reelection strategy, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR: 'BIT SNITTY'</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/live/2019/may/01/william-barr-testimony-mueller-report-donald-trump-live-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live as Trump’s attorney general testifies after Mueller criticized his summary of the Trump-Russia investigation report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba denies military support...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6980721/Trump-national-security-adviser-says-Russia-not-interfering-Western-Hemisphere.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton told White House reporters Wednesday morning that Trump is returning to the Monroe Doctrine and will be exerting its influence to stabilize Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect ACT scores soaring...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2019/05/01/act-sat-scholarships-college-admissions-scores-test-prep/3566998002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of perfect ACT scores nationwide has more than doubled since 2015 and is six times higher today than it was eight years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamptons Residents Angered By Indian Nation's Massive Electronic Billboards...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/04/30/shinnecock-indian-nation-billboards-southampton-the-hamptons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An assault on the East End, that's how Southampton officials describe what the Shinnecocks are quickly building at the gateway to the Hamptons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL teachers can now carry guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article229906419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic attacks spike, killing most Jews in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldextra.com/news/world/anti-semitic-attacks-spike-killing-most-jews-in-decades/article_e546d35f-c4ea-5ec8-a2ae-686de3cf9ffd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israeli researchers reported Wednesday that violent attacks against Jews spiked significantly last year, with the largest reported number of Jews killed in anti-Semitic acts in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG says he DID NOT exonerate President...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/barr-testimony-mueller-report/h_47600d094b183e8048088dd5456b2ca1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr said he did not exonerate President Trump and said that the American people can decide for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information war escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/01/media/media-venezuela-information-war/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Venezuelan government and opposition clash on the streets of Caracas another battle is underway: an information war fought over social media and TV networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT eliminating passwords...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/01/microsoft-ciso-bret-arsenault-wants-to-eliminate-passwords.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft's Bret Arsenault, who serves as its top cybersecurity executive, discussed the top issues facing his company and its clients, and offers advice for smaller firms on how they can get better at eliminating the simplest, most devastating attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Huddles With Hillary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/441632-buttigieg-meets-with-hillary-clinton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg sat down with Hillary Clinton on Tuesday, sources tell The Hill. Buttigieg, the mayor of South Bend, Ind., who has been recently surging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man guilty in plane bomb plot involving meat grinder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/01/australian-man-found-guilty-in-plane-bomb-plot-involving-meat-grinder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE — An Australian court on Wednesday found a man guilty of plotting to blow up an Etihad Airways flight out of Sydney at the behest of the Islamic State militant group by hiding a bomb in t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It was MY baby!'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6981035/Bill-Barr-faces-senators-following-revelation-Mueller-told-TWICE-release-report-summaries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barr clashed with Senate Democrats in his first appearance on Capitol Hill since the release of the special counsel's report, insisting that 'it was my decision how and when to make it public.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicions grow as Baltimore mayor's leave drags on...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/politics/bs-md-ci-pugh-leave-month-20190430-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mayor Catherine Pugh's leave of absence passes the one-month mark, day-to-day city government operations go on as always but the future remains cloudy. In a city with great needs, and a strong-mayor form of government, clarity at the top ranks of City Hall is needed, many say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly ex-poet laureate faces uproar for skinhead past...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national/philadelphia-poet-laureate-faces-uproar-for-skinhead-past/SRP0OB5KMxSCfdXTqJLRJP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia's second poet laureate, who focused on taking poetry to neighborhoods and the city's yo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House wants $4.5 billion -- but NOT for wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/trump-seeks-billions-emergency-border-funds-not-his-wall-n1000706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior administration official said the money would be for "the immediate humanitarian crisis."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA could soon lose ability to 'sniff' ChineseRussian subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/digital-show-dailies/navy-league/2019/05/01/us-could-lose-a-key-weapon-for-tracking-chinese-and-russian-subs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the one supplier disappearing, Pentagon is preparing to spend cash to find alternatives for sonobuoy production. But the clock has started to run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private payrolls surge by 275,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/01/private-payrolls-surge-by-275000-in-april-blowing-past-estimates-and-the-biggest-gain-since-july.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gain was led by the services sector, which saw jobs increase by the most in more than two years for the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine becomes 1st state to ban single-use foam containers...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/national/2019/05/maine-becomes-1st-state-to-ban-single-use-foam-containers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine has become the first state to ban single-use food and drink containers made from polystyrene foam, commonly known as Styrofoam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN VIEWERSHIP COLLAPSE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/441557-cnn-sees-ratings-swoon-in-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN's prime-time ratings dropped a whopping 26 percent in April compared to last year, according to Nielsen Media Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear Gas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/70f5125f80b34ed0b5b6d9cb1dc3da23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The Latest on the political crisis in Venezuela (all times local): 11:30 a.m. State security forces are using tear gas to disperse protesters opposed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House wants $4.5 billion in emergency funds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/37fef1378820455a9beb44d408eb152e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House is asking Congress for an additional $4.5 billion in emergency spending for border security. That's according to two people familiar with the request who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 'WOODSTOCK 50' Festival Collapsed over Massive Crowd Shrinkage...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/05/01/woodstock-50-music-festival-canceled-investors-accommodating-guests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woodstock 50's main investor pulled out because it wasn't anticipating making room for overnight guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia 'secretly installs nukes in Venezuela'... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8977662/russia-nuke-missiles-venezuela-cuban-missile-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has secretly installed nuclear missiles in Venezuela a US politician has sensationally claimed  – in a chilling echo of the Cuban Missile Crisis. Republican congressman Mario Diaz-Bala…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fines? Jail time? All options on table for enforcing subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/fines-jail-time-democrats-leave-options-table-enforcing-subpoenas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats have several options to enforce their subpoena power over the administration, including what is known as inherent contempt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Might Give Homeless People Right to Camp ANYWHERE...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/04/29/this-city-might-give-homeless-people-the-right-to-camp-anywhere</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a half-million people live on the street in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norman Lear Rips NETFLIX: 'Death By Data'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/norman-lear-rita-moreno-one-day-at-a-time-cancellation-1205229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two icons weigh in on how their sitcom reboot became a victim of the streaming algorithm: "There’s a lesson here."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Jinping: Socialism 'Essence of Patriotism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/04/30/xi-jinping-socialism-is-essence-of-patriotism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping tells Chinese youth that patriotism, nationalism, and socialism are inseparable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro vows to resist 'Gringo Empire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/05/01/venezuela-maduro-speech-guaido-uprising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicolás Maduro denied that he had lost control of the military and vowed to use all his power to crush legitimate President Juan Guaidó.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL: Sharp increase in Congo Ebola deaths as medical teams hit by attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/sharp-increase-in-congo-ebola-deaths-as-medical-teams-hit/article_f42efc86-deee-5029-8136-eb5a09123312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINSHASA, Congo — Ebola cases and deaths in eastern Congo have risen sharply in the past week, authorities said Tuesday, placing the blame on recurrent attacks on treatment centers and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military stops releasing Afghanistan war information...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/253f6e2504ad4c72aed8a2d0499a673e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Amid a battlefield stalemate in Afghanistan , the U.S. military has stopped releasing information often cited to measure progress in America's longest war, calling it of little...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL GRILL!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff8a0eed70d0451584a941eab7a5d15c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Attorney General William Barr defended his handling of special counsel Robert Mueller's Russia report on Wednesday amid new revelations that Mueller expressed frustration to Barr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pour out of manhole in busy El Paso intersection...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-illegals-pour-out-of-manhole-in-busy-el-paso-intersection-flee-into-darkness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The invasion across the southern border is now occurring from the ground up. Literally. New video shows several illegal aliens pouring out of a manhole in a busy El Paso, Texas intersection. Watch: Illegal immigrants popping up through a manhole in a busy intersection in El Paso, Texas pic.twitter.com/aOJBdr9vmf — Wojciech Pawelczyk 🇵🇱 (@PolishPatriotTM) May …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agreement reached to have Mueller testify before Congress... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190501134145-z0yg8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/MUELLER (URGENT):Agreement reached to have Mueller testify on Russia probe - lawmaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushed AG Twice to Release Summaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/01/us/politics/mueller-letters-barr.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert S. Mueller III wrote that “there is now public confusion about critical aspects of the results of our investigation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professed ignorance prompts calls for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Barr-s-professed-ignorance-prompts-calls-for-his-13809829.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In back-to-back congressional hearings on April 9 and 10, Attorney General William Barr disclaimed knowledge of the thinking of special counsel Robert Mueller and members of his team of prosecutors investigating Russian interference in the 2016 election.  "No, I don't," Barr said, when asked by Rep. Charlie Crist, D-Fla., whether he knew what was behind reports that members of Mueller's team were frustrated by the attorney general's summary of their top-level conclusions.  "I don't know," he said the next day, when asked by Sen. Chris Van Hollen, D-Md., whether Mueller supported his finding that there was not sufficient evidence to conclude that President Donald Trump had obstructed justice.  These statements resurfaced Tuesday following the revelation that Mueller had sent a letter to Barr two weeks earlier objecting to the attorney general's characterization of the probe.  Suggesting that Mueller's letter - only portions of which have been made public - belied the sworn testimony of the attorney general, Van Hollen recirculated a clip of his back-and-forth with Barr and declared, "He must resign."  In an interview with The Washington Post, the Maryland Democrat said he believed Barr's answer was "completely misleading because he was well aware of the fact that Bob Mueller had raised questions with the substance of the conclusions stated in the attorney general's letter."  The Justice Department didn't immediately return a request for comment on Van Hollen's accusation.  In the March 27 letter, Mueller protested that Barr's four-page memo "did not fully capture the context, nature, and substance" of his work, according to a copy reviewed by The Post. In a subsequent phone conversation between Mueller and Barr - longtime colleagues whose differences of opinion about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skies darken as millions of locusts invade Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1121121/saudi-arabia-news-locust-swarm-najran-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SWARM of locusts seemingly darken the skies and added a thick layer of insects to trees as they invaded Najran in Saudia Arabia at the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside secret world of CIA's social media team...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/441480-inside-the-secret-world-of-the-cias-social-media-team</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A government agency known for its secrecy is making a splash in a very public forum: Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Flushed Kin's Cremated Remains...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/ashes-get-flushed-482091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 30--After his mother kicked him out of her Pennsylvania residence, a 33-year-old man flushed his grandparents’ ashes down the home's toilet, a bizarre retaliatory move for which he is facing cr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifetime supply of California tap water could increase cancer risk...</title>
      <link>http://www.ktvu.com/news/ktvu-local-news/study-a-lifetime-supply-of-california-tap-water-could-increase-cancer-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study published Tuesday claims that drinking California tap water over the course of a lifetime could potentially increase your risk of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may have to stop borrowing later this year: Treasury...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-treasury-refunding/u-s-may-have-to-stop-borrowing-later-this-year-treasury-idUSKCN1S73U4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government will have to stop borrowing money between July and December ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER CHALLENGED BARR SPIN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mueller-complained-that-barrs-letter-did-not-capture-context-of-trump-probe/ar-AAAKJB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS to start DNA testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/30/politics/homeland-security-dna-testing-immigration/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest mummies NOT in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/worlds-oldest-mummies-chile/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
