<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STD INFECTIONS SPREAD TO 1 MILLION -- DAILY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/wake-up-call-1-million-new-std-infections-daily</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1 million new cases of sexually transmitted diseases pop up across the world every day, a figure that shows health officials have made little progress in curbing infections over the course of about five years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Exchange for Movies?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/members/2019/06/05/ryan-kavanaugh-proxima-media-stock-exchange-for-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Missing link' in human evolution found after 30,000-year-old remains dug up...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9233938/missing-link-ancient-siberians-native-americans-evolution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWLY discovered ancient teeth dating back 31,000 years are evidence of a new ethnic group in human history – and could change everything we know about the first American settlers. Living in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI WANTS TRUMP IN PRISON</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/05/pelosi-impeachment-1355435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She also clashed with Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerry Nadler, who pressed her to begin impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extinct Volcano Wakes; Could Unleash 'Pompeii-Size' Destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/russia-extinct-volcano-woken-pompeii-eruption-1442479</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clooney secret battle to protect family from ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/inside-amal-george-clooneys-secret-16268250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International human rights lawyer Amal Clooney is battling ISIS in the courtroom - and George Clooney is pulling out all the stops to keep their twins safe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto urged to abandon 'smart city' project...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/jun/06/toronto-smart-city-google-project-privacy-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project with Google’s Sidewalk Labs comes under increasing scrutiny amid concerns over privacy and data harvesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alliance for 21st century...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/As-allies-remember-D-Day-Putin-and-Xi-look-ahead-13948643.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, Western allies are gathering in Britain and France to commemorate the largest seaborne invasion in history. But far from the English Channel, another significant gathering is taking place that aims to cement a new alliance for this century.  Leaders from countries including the United States, Britain and France met Wednesday in Portsmouth, England, on the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings, the Allied invasion of Normandy during World War II. On Thursday, those leaders headed to Normandy to commemorate the assault on Nazi-occupied France in June 1944.  Representatives of the countries that formed that World War II alliance were slated to be in attendance, as well as envoys from Germany.  The leaders of Russia and China, two countries that made their own sacrifices to the Allied war effort, will not be present, however. They are meeting on their own, beyond the eastern edge of Europe.  Russian President Vladimir Putin welcomed Chinese President Xi Jinping to Moscow on Wednesday for the start of his three-day visit to Russia. An event on Wednesday marked the 70 years of diplomatic relations between Moscow and Beijing, and both sides claim the relationship is better than ever. Putin "is my best and bosom friend," Xi told Russian state news agency Tass ahead of his visit.  The two international gatherings stand in stark contrast: old and new, East and West, democratic and autocratic. But these differences weren't always so obvious. The Russian president first attended D-Day ceremonies in 2004. Although Moscow was not directly involved in the invasion, Soviet soldiers played the most significant role in defeating Nazi Germany, on the Eastern Front, and paid a deadly cost for it.  Putin's later presence at D-Day commemorations in 2014 was tense and came amid attempts by world leaders to isolate Moscow after its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Least 20 Cadets Involved in Major West Point Crash; Military Describes 'Chaotic' Situation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/West-Point-New-York-Major-Car-Crash-Orange-County-Emergency-510906491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major emergency response is underway after a crash involving at least 20 cadets near the U.S. Military Academy in New York's Orange County early Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Flippers Cashing Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-home-flippers-are-cashing-out-before-profits-get-slimmer-1.1269342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed out? Your dog may feel it too, study suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cd654537064a40adb97fe7bd1c63ba3e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot baristas latest automation push...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ccb243ac19c64c0cbf22cd9c8dd99e5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Video Shows Employees Brutally Beating Dairy Cows At Indiana Farm...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/06/05/disturbing-undercover-video-shows-animal-cruelty-fair-oaks-farms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tribute to immortals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9233542/dday-anniversary-piper-beach-normandy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world today paid tribute to the “ultimate sacrifice” made by the soldiers who stormed the beaches of Normandy on D-Day 75 years ago. Some of the last surviving heroes from the Allied invasion o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Chipping Away at Bernie Support...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/i-have-a-plan-warren-gains-on-sanders-with-policy-focus-1.1269417</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi praises 'best friend' Putin during Russia visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48537663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr Xi has also unveiled two pandas for the Moscow Zoo as part of his three-day visit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dora Maar shakes off Picasso's shadow in new Paris show...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dora-maar-shakes-off-picassos-shadow-paris-show-113723786.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She has gone down in his history as the muse who was almost Picasso's match, but a new show in Paris tries to drag Dora Maar out from under his shadow. The huge retrospective at the Pompidou Centre -- which will transfer to London's Tate Modern in November -- portrays Maar as a leading surrealist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ice pirate' to steal 3,000-foot iceberg; Tow across ocean, melt down to drink...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9234307/iceberg-tow-antarctica-melt-drink-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COLD, BOLD plot to hijack an iceberg and tow it from Antarctica to South Africa could take place this year. “Ice pirate” Nicholas Sloane wants to cart a 125million-ton ‘berg acr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Have Revered Crocodiles of Island Nation Suddenly Started Killing People?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/06/world/asia/east-timor-crocodile-attacks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two scientists traveled to East Timor to help solve a national murder mystery. The culprits, they say, might be migrants from Australia with a taste for blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-Day 75...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/567d5642eef242119ff75aeda3a2371c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA:  I PREFERRED LIFE BEFORE PHONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/05/magazine/madonna-madame-x.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The original queen of pop on aging, inspiration and why she refuses to cede control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico blocks new caravan of Central American migrants... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/caravan-1-200-migrants-enters-mexico-192344686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuxtla Gutiérrez (Mexico) (AFP) - Authorities blocked a new caravan of Central American migrants Wednesday after they entered Mexico bound for the United States, as the government scrambled to dodge President Donald Trump's threat to impose tariffs over undocumented immigration. Soldiers and police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Paso Immigration Center Dangerously Overcrowded...</title>
      <link>https://www.elpasotimes.com/story/news/immigration/2019/05/31/el-paso-migrant-processing-center-overcrowded-dhs-border-patrol-ice/1300160001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.elpasotimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Department of Homeland Security inspection found 900 detainees at the 125-migrant capacity Paso Del Norte International Bridge Processing Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military personnel ordered to paint border barriers?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/447215-us-military-personnel-ordered-to-paint-border-barriers-to-improve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United States military personnel deployed near the U.S.-Mexico border have reportedly been assigned to paint certain barrier structures to strengthen their “aesthetic appearance.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feud over abortion adds to questions about Joe's vulnerabilities... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dem-rivals-rebuke-biden-not-184058345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is under fire from his Democratic presidential rivals and women's rights advocates for his defense of a decades-old prohibition on federal money paying for abortions. Most Democratic White House hopefuls reflect their party's latest platform calling for the outright repeal of the Hyde</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text messages reveal anguish of underage NXIVM 'sex slave'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-cult-text-messages-girl-nxivm-20190605-4e65rjhhzfhppojogkmme47k5u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twisted texts between Keith Raniere and the underage ‘sex slave’ at the heart of trafficking and conspiracy charges against the NXIVM “cult” leader reveal a level of control prosecutors said he used to keep his conquests in line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Poisonous thorns': The times Abraham Lincoln got really mad at CHICAGO TRIB...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/poisonous-thorns-the-times-abraham-lincoln-got-mad-like-really/article_1594e55a-d0be-5113-a441-e84796e36e61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Abraham Lincoln was mad. Really mad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN +4 IN TEXAS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/images/polling/tx/tx06052019_tgye56.pdf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY:  3 Americans die at same Dominican Republic resort just days apart...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/5354804/u-s-tourists-dead-dominican-republic-resort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In all three cases, the cause of death was listed as respiratory failure and pulmonary edema, a condition caused by excess fluid in the lungs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads revoked from Steven Crowder channel...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/6/5/18654196/steven-crowder-demonetized-carlos-maza-youtube-homophobic-language-ads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘A pattern of egregious actions has harmed the broader community,’ a spokesperson said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic number of illegals flood southern border...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/record-number-undocumented-immigrants-flooded-southern-border-may-n1014186</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are in a full-blown emergency, and I cannot say this stronger: The system is broken," said acting CBP Commissioner John Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firework display explosion near Roswell airport; Numerous injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.koat.com/article/firework-display-set-up-results-in-explosion-near-roswell-airport/27758335</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Mexico State police are reporting a explosion with possible fatalities at the Roswell Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Suit for Stroke Victims Gets FDA Nod...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/small-cap-rewalk-triples-on-fda-nod-for-robotic-suit-for-stroke</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robotic Suit for Stroke Gets FDA Nod, Rocketing ReWalk Stock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of NYC ice cream trucks seized over ticket scam...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/05/dozens-of-nyc-ice-cream-trucks-seized-over-multimillion-dollar-ticket-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freeze! More than 40 ice-cream trucks were seized by the city in Long Island City Wednesday over a multimillion-dollar ticket-avoidance scam. The trucks, most of which brandish the New York Ice Cre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbors On Edge As Man Displays Giant Swastika On Front Yard...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/06/04/neighbors-on-edge-as-el-sobrante-man-displays-giant-swastika-on-front-yard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A community in Contra Costa County is on edge after a man displayed a giant cement swastika on his front yard. He denied it was a swastika, calling it a "Tibetan symbol."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>+12 IN NC...</title>
      <link>https://emersonpolling.reportablenews.com/pr/north-carolina-2020-biden-with-early-lead-on-trump-and-democratic-primary-field</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;emersonpolling.reportablenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON delivering by drones 'in months'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91506a8d547a4c48be3cc7c6e357bc1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record setting 55,000 children caught at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/5/more-55000-children-caught-border-may/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government set another grim record in May with more than 55,000 children nabbed by Border Patrol agents along the southwest border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat passengers held captive by drunken, armed captain...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/news/20190604/police-sarasota-boat-passengers-held-captive-by-drunken-armed-captain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Bailey, 36, was charged with boating under the influence and resisting arrest for actions that occurred during a charter fishing trip Saturday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press freedom in 'downward spiral' across world...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190605-press-freedom-orban-hungary-russia-china-india-modi-usa-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press freedom is declining around the world, with democratic governments joining authoritarian regimes in seeking to suppress independent journalism, a human rights watchdog said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers Launches $50M Venture Capital Fund...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kurtbadenhausen/2019/06/05/aaron-rodgers-launches-50-million-venture-capital-fund-with-roth-capital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-time NFL MVP Aaron Rodgers is a general partner in a new venture and growth capital fund that banks on the influence of investors from the world of sports, entertainment and business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL mulls 'chemical castration' requirement for child sex offenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2019/06/alabama-gov-kay-ivey-reviewing-chemical-castration-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Legislature passed a bill requiring sex offenders whose victims are children to receive medication that reduces or blocks testosterone as a condition of parole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE BANNING 'HATEFUL' VIDEOS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/youtube-ban-hateful-supremacist-videos-170733974.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube announced Wednesday it would ban videos promoting or glorifying racism and discrimination as well as those denying well-documented violent events, like the Holocaust or the Sandy Hook elementary school shooting. The announcement by the Google-owned video-sharing platform was the latest of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK on trial for 'censorship' in Poland...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-trial-censorship-poland-173914861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Polish court held a first hearing Wednesday in a case brought against Facebook by a historian who claims the tech giant engaged in "censorship" by suspending accounts that had posted about a nationalist rally in Warsaw. The case comes as major tech firms like Facebook and Twitter have been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President ending fetal tissue research by federal scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/5/trump-ending-fetal-tissue-research-by-federal-scie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration said Wednesday it is ending medical research by government scientists using human fetal tissue, a victory for abortion foes that comes despite impassioned pleas from scientists that some health problems can’t be studied any other way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE BANNING 'EXTREME VIEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/05/business/youtube-remove-extremist-videos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision by YouTube, which is owned by Google, is the latest action by a Silicon Valley company to stem the spread of hate speech and disinformation on their sites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Health Supplements Harming Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbur.org/commonhealth/2019/06/05/weight-loss-muscle-building-energy-supplements-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbur.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hundreds of reports of hospitalization, ER visits and even death among young people are likely just "the tip of the iceberg," a researcher says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland decriminalizes magic mushrooms, other psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/06/05/oakland-california-legalizes-magic-mushrooms-and-peyote/1347888001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oakland, Californiaâ€™s city council on Tuesday voted unanimously to decriminalize hallucinogenic fungi, otherwise known as â€œmagic mushrooms.â€�</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Senate races likely to determine control of chamber...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/eight-senate-races-likely-to-determine-control-of-the-chamber</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight for the Senate starts off with only a handful of seats at risk. And that’s being generous,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio doctor charged with 25 counts of murder, accused of prescribing excessive doses of painkillers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/ohio-doctor-charged-25-counts-murder-accused-prescribing-excessive-doses-n970026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patient deaths involving William Husel, 43, have exposed a stunning case of medical oversight and alleged medical malpractice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds buying MILLIONS of diapers for border crossers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/06/04/border-agency-buying-2-2-million-diapers-to-help-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DHS is buying 2.2 million diapers to help deliver many economic migrants and their children into Americans' worksites and neighborhoods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The Case for Wearing AirPods All the Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/06/airpods-apple-street-harassment/590989/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inconspicuous buds might make friendly interactions awkward, but they can also provide protection in dangerous situations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New HBO show to push envelope of teen sex, drugs, male nudity...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/euphoria-review-1215681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boundary-pushing, real and exceptionally realized, HBO's new drama starring Zendaya tracks sex, drugs and rap in the life of modern teens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL SHOCK:  MORE WORRIED ABOUT 'FAKE NEWS' THAN TERROR</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/americans-fake-news-problem-terrorism-da565b6c-6ab3-42a1-ae08-3400d68ab99c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's undermining Americans' trust in key institutions, like government and the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicaid Paid For Sex Offenders' Erectile Dysfunction Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://wcbs880.radio.com/articles/ap-news/medicaid-paid-new-york-sex-offenders-erectile-dysfunction-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcbs880.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's publicly funded Medicaid program paid more than $63,000 for erectile dysfunction drugs and other sexual treatments for sex offenders, despite laws banning such expenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLEGROUND TEST FOR TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/tracking-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a daily basis, Morning Consult is surveying over 5,000 registered voters across the United States on President Trump. Each month, we’ll update this page with the latest survey data, providing a clear picture of Trump’s approval and re-election prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CULTURE WARS: Maine legislators OK assisted suicide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3676ac9875e74c11b10f95299d171dd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
