<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA restarts diplomatic activity inside Ukraine, pledges more aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-restarts-diplomatic-activity-inside-ukraine-and-pledges-more-aid/ar-AAWACG1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming ground battle crucial phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/looming-ground-battle-is-crucial-phase-in-ukraine-us-officials-say/ar-AAWzFe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everything halted': Shanghai shutdowns worsening shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/everything-is-halted-shanghai-shutdowns-are-worsening-shortages/ar-AAWBCt6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formula One Miami Brings Racing, Legal Trouble, $100,000 Tables at Clubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/formula-1-miami-preview-race-cars-a-lawsuit-and-100-000-tables-at-clubs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Formula One Miami Brings Racing, Legal Trouble,Â and $100,000 Tables at Clubs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI:  Migrants in TX increasingly subject to kidnapping, extortion, other abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2022/04/25/migrants-in-texas-increasingly-subject-to-kidnapping-extortion-other-abuse-fbi-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO — Migrants are increasingly becoming victims of kidnapping, extortion, ransoms and physical abuse in this border region, targeted by local gangs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Dorsey's bizarre lifestyle revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4168298/jack-dorsey-fast-silent-meditation-retreat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWITTER co-founder Jack Dorsey eats only one meal per day and once spent his birthday at a silent retreat where you can’t use technology or make eye contact. Dorsey officially resigned as CEO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN:  Humanity stuck in 'spiral of self-destruction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.terradaily.com/afp/220425220120.fmepvf0g.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.terradaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK TAKES TWITTER</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/twitter-accepts-elon-musks-buyout-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement ends a weekslong saga Musk kicked off when he offered to buy the company at $54.20 per share, his "best and final."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sends artillery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-ships-artillery-ukraine-destroy-210936888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The push by the United States to send artillery to Ukraine aims to degrade Russian forces -- not only on the immediate battlefield but over the longer term, according to US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin and military experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of WWIII...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-us-officials-meet-zelensky-042325957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia on Monday warned the Ukraine conflict risked escalating into a third world war and accused Kyiv of playing at peace talks a day after visiting US officials said Ukrainian forces could beat back Moscow's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans forced to travel out of state, wait weeks for abortions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texans-forced-travel-state-wait-202719893.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a small Louisiana clinic, a five-hour drive from her home in the neighboring state of Texas, Shayla waits for her long-sought appointment to receive an abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing expands mass testing as lockdown fears grow ...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beijing-expands-mass-testing-lockdown-020157185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing on Tuesday launched mass coronavirus testing for nearly all its 21 million residents, as fears grew that the Chinese capital may be placed under a strict lockdown like Shanghai.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi puts ideology before economy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/xi-puts-ideology-economy-market-113317064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China’s worst equity selloff since early 2020 reflects a growing concern about President Xi Jinping: He can’t afford the political costs of shifting from a Covid Zero strategy that is pummeling the economy. Most Read from Bloomberg‘Weak Sauce’: Elon Musk’s 2018 Feud With Saudi Fund RevealedAnger in Japan as Ukraine Links Emperor Hirohito to Adolf HitlerUkraine Latest: U.S. Vows to Step Up Weapons for KyivMusk Nears $43 Billion Deal for Twitter as Soon as MondayStocks Decline Ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp finishes 4 days on stand; Filed lawsuit to 'fight back'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/johnny-depp-amber-heard-trial-defamtation-domestic-abuse-1235009173/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2nd UPDATE, 12:25 PM Johnny Depp ended his testimony in his $50 million defamation trial against Amber Heard on Monday with a declaration that he is the victim of domestic abuse, not her. “Yes,” th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG BIRD!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elon-musk-twitter-takeover-2d0eb4e0511fe0e296fd6974a851a252</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk reached an agreement to buy Twitter for roughly $44 billion on Monday, promising a more lenient touch to policing content on the social media platform where he — the world's richest person — promotes his interests, attacks critics and opines on a wide range of issues to more than 83 million followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS TROLLS CHINA TIES</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/jeff-bezos-trolls-elon-musk-over-twitter-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a battle of the world's richest men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. restarts diplomatic activity inside Ukraine and pledges more aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-restarts-diplomatic-activity-inside-ukraine-and-pledges-more-aid/ar-AAWACG1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming ground battle is crucial phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/looming-ground-battle-is-crucial-phase-in-ukraine-us-officials-say/ar-AAWzFe0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER workers fear future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/twitter-workers-face-a-reality-they-e2-80-99ve-long-feared-elon-musk-as-owner/ar-AAWAD7C?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he won't rejoin. Some advisers don't believe him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-he-won-e2-80-99t-rejoin-twitter-some-advisers-don-e2-80-99t-believe-him/ar-AAWAAt9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems approach a midterm message, but struggle to deliver it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-approach-a-midterm-message-but-struggle-to-deliver-it/ar-AAWzqlM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphic audio recordings shock courtroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/entertainment/celebrity-life/graphic-audio-recordings-shock-courtroom-at-johnny-depp-amber-heard-trial/news-story/e96cffb3ef280da5a4b21b41bdaba1ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audio recordings of Johnny Depp and Amber Heard’s explosive fights were played in court today as the third week of the doomed couple’s defamation trial kicked off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene raised prospect of 'Marshall law'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Greene-in-text-to-Meadows-raised-topic-of-17125092.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene, R-Ga., told then-White House Chief of Staff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  'Exhilarated' McConnell said Jan. 6 'discredited' Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/e2-80-98exhilarated-e2-80-99-mcconnell-said-jan-6-e2-80-98discredited-e2-80-99-trump-book-says/ar-AAWAqTi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House manager recalls finding finger tip on floor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnny-depp-house-manager-recalls-203217533.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp’s House Manager Ben King said he heard “hysterical sobbing, crying” as he entered the house where Mr Depp and Amber Heard were staying in Australia on Sunday 8 March 2015. Mr King said Ms Heard was “hysterical” and that she was “crying a lot ... uncontrollably”. The defamation trial between Mr Depp and Ms Heard began on Monday 11 April in Fairfax, Virginia following Mr Depp’s lawsuit against his ex-wife in March 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Obesity 'Rewires' Immune System...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/obesity-rewires-immune-system-eczema-allergies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obesity, sometimes classified as a chronic inflammatory state, alters the immune system in many ways, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin seen telling cops how he accidentally killed in newly released video...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10752327/New-photos-Alec-Baldwin-set-Rust-minutes-accidentally-shooting-Halyna-Hutchins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin was filming a scene in a church set when he drew the gun and accidentally shot Hutchins, a mother and experienced cinematographer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Wallace unsure of what's next...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/25/chris-wallace-breaks-silence-on-cnn-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Wallace revealed his future role at the left-leaning network is unclear once the platform is shuttered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen plots parliament win...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-france-elections-presidential-macron-a94360ac6dc6fc1b0015b82a57789ba5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French far-right leader Marine Le Pen gathered her party’s troops on Monday, not to mourn her loss a day earlier in the French presidential election but to plot how to orchestrate a victory in June's parliamentary vote and capture a majority of seats in the National Assembly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Police Do Marketing for Surveillance Tech Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93b4b5/when-police-do-marketing-for-surveillance-tech-companiess</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drone company called Skydio has managed to get autonomous drones into dozens of police departments by turning cops into their biggest fans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AUTHENTICATING ALL HUMANS'</title>
      <link>https://wsvn.com/news/elon-musk-to-buy-twitter-in-44-billion-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsvn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(CNN) — Twitter said Monday it has agreed to sell itself to Elon Musk, who will take the company private in a deal valued at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aussies warned to 'prepare for war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/innovation/military/peter-dutton-says-australia-should-be-prepared-for-war/news-story/7ba64018bda3b940be2fe6f1a8954029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Dutton has dialled up his rhetoric about the threat of China and Russia, warning Australia should be prepared for war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect storm of nuclear anxieties, inflation threat, crime wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/dem-pollster-issues-frantic-warning-on-midterms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America today is facing real, undeniable problems, and most of them are strongly associated with the Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke-capable missiles seen loaded onto submarines heading to Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-filmed-loading-nuclear-missiles-26790733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has threatened the world with nuclear war on several occasions during its long, drawn out invasion of Ukraine, and is now seemingly ready to put words into action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's 'only oil pipeline to EU' in flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1600623/russia-news-druzhba-oil-pipeline-fire-ukraine-eu-energy-germany-austria-hungary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FIRE that broke out at oil storage facilities near the Ukraine border could impact the "only pipeline sending Russian oil into Europe," an expert has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As US retreats, Saudi Arabia and Iran are trying to mend fences...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/25/middleeast/saudi-iran-talks-resume-mime-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Gulf Arab states lose faith in the United States' commitment to their security, two Middle East archrivals are taking matters into their own hands. On Monday, Iran revealed that it held a fifth round of talks with Saudi Arabia late last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inept 'People's Convoy' chased out of Bay Area by egg-throwing kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Peoples-Convoy-chased-out-of-Bay-Area-17122881.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One livestreamer for the convoy begrudgingly conceded victory to the Bay Area youth....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Treating With Antibiotics Leading To Creation Of New Superbugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-antibiotics-superbugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drug resistant infections which develop while a patient is in the hospital are soaring during COVID, and these infections are affecting those with and without the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills always watching with thousands of cameras. And city isn't done...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/beverly-hills-is-always-watching-you-with-thousands-of-cameras-and-the-city-isnt-done/ar-AAWzgOW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House seeks more power to counter use of drones in US...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-federal-aviation-administration-congress-90c34d902cacb04d0d7369356d9706c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration is calling on Congress to expand authority for federal and local governments to take action to counter the nefarious use in the U.S. of drones, which are becoming a growing security concern and nuisance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,319 Meadows texts revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/25/politics/mark-meadows-texts-2319/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN has obtained 2,319 text messages that former President Donald Trump's White House chief of staff Mark Meadows sent and received between Election Day 2020 and President Joe Biden's January 20, 2021 inauguration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can meat be grown in space?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-61116018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An experiment to find out has just finished on the International Space Station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of NYC teachers accused of faking vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-new-york-education-city-cebf3151b9c5f9f9f358b6e868c9c66d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Several dozen New York City teachers and other school employees who officials said submitted fraudulent proof of COVID-19 vaccination were placed on leave as of Monday. The United Federation of Teachers is challenging the disciplinary action, which it says violates its collective bargaining agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY judge holds Trump in contempt for failing to comply with subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/judge-holds-donald-trump-in-contempt-for-failing-to-comply-with-ny-subpoena.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump will have to pay $10,000 a day as a result of the contempt order, until he produces documents sought by New York Attorney General Letitia James.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of parents still financially support their adult children...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/half-of-parents-still-financially-support-adult-children-study-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On average, parents who financially support grown children give them $1,000 a month for expenses like food, rent, cell phones and car insurance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Michael Cohen Downloads on Trump Cognitive Test Boast!</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wOSgjZ3nhfE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's former fixer and attorney Michael Cohen reacts to his former boss's disastrous and humiliating rally in Ohio.Donate to MeidasTouch: https://se...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victory without triumph...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10750437/French-media-decry-Macrons-victory-without-triumph-Le-Pen-celebrates-best-result-far-right.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel Macron's latest victory over his far-right rival was narrower than their last face-off in 2017, when he won over 66 per cent of the vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MOGUL MUSK</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2022-04-25/elon-musk-s-twitter-and-what-it-means-for-donald-trump-tweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEAL TODAY?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-twitter-set-accept-musks-114217898.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) -Twitter Inc is poised to agree a sale to Elon Musk for around $43 billion in cash, the price the CEO of Tesla has called his "best and final" offer for the social media company, people familiar with the matter said. Twitter may announce the $54.20-per-share deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders, the sources said, adding it was still possible the deal could collapse at the last minute. Musk, the world's richest person according to Forbes, is negotiating to buy Twitter in a personal capacity and Tesla is not involved in the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp in starring role at defamation trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amber-heard-johnny-depp-entertainment-arts-and-lawsuits-d1009ce6bab302d61d0e44c6398589f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAIRFAX, Va. (AP) — Jurors in Johnny Depp's libel lawsuit against his ex-wife, actress Amber Heard, on Monday heard audio recordings in which he referred to the violence that could ensue if their arguments were allowed to escalate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass Testing Amid 'Grim' Situation...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/china-covid-cases-beijing-lockdown-covid-spike-in-beijing-prompts-mass-testsing-panic-buying-2916949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears of a hard Covid lockdown sparked panic buying in Beijing as long queues formed on Monday in a large central district for mass testing ordered by the Chinese authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear of lockdown sparks panic buying in Bejing following Covid outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/access-asia/20220425-fear-of-lockdown-sparks-panic-buying-in-bejing-following-covid-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing residents snapped up food and other supplies as the city's biggest district began mass COVID-19 testing of all residents on Monday, prompting fears of a Shanghai-style lockdown after dozens o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Praying Football Coach Tests Religious Rights at Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-football-religion-prayer-washington-7490d215c8b1ead529299ac92114dbab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court will tackle a dispute between public school officials and a former high school football coach who wanted to kneel and pray on the field after games. The case before the justices on Monday involves Joseph Kennedy, a former football coach at Bremerton High School in Bremerton, Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrage of assault, racism, rape jokes: Nightmare trip into metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2022/apr/25/a-barrage-of-assault-racism-and-jokes-my-nightmare-trip-into-the-metaverse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new documentary sees a reporter don a VR headset and head into the world that’s supposed to be our future. Within 10 minutes, she had witnessed the most disturbing sights of her life – in a space seven-year-olds can access</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks dip as April sell-off continues, economic slowdown fears loom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/24/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are looking ahead to a packed week of corporate earnings, including reports from Amazon, Apple and Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Good' Cholesterol Vital To Liver Protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/good-cholesterol-hdl-liver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers reveal that a form of good cholesterol, known as HDL3, protects against liver inflammation by blocking inflammatory signals from gut bacteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You may be recovering from your workouts all wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.universalpersonality.com/you-may-be-recovering-from-your-workouts-all-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.universalpersonality.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Placeholder while article actions load You’re on the last set of squats at the gym at the end of a long week, and your legs feel like lead. You’re proud of your progress, but your muscles have gone on strike, and you’d like to make them feel better. You might think: Time to take it […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air stunt goes badly wrong as pilots try to swap planes 12,000ft up...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5194939/plane-swap-wrong-red-bull-spirals-out-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING footage shows the moment a Red Bull plane plunged to the ground after a stunt went wrong. Daredevil pilots and cousins Luke Aikins and Andy Farrington tried to complete a plane swap near E…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal today?</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/technology/twitter-on-track-to-reach-deal-with-elon-musk-as-soon-as-monday/articleshow/91075205.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter may announce the $43 billion deal later on Monday once its board has met to recommend the transaction to Twitter shareholders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Voters Haven't Been Afraid Like This in Long Time...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/25/american-voters-havent-been-afraid-like-this-in-a-long-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare convergence, America’s voters are not merely unhappy with their political leadership, but awash in fears about economic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden prime target if Republicans win Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-2022-midterm-elections-biden-europe-elise-stefanik-0e782fc6486c2c625194622ae244e4ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Intelligence officials had gathered to brief select members of Congress on future threats to U.S. elections when a key lawmaker in the room, No. 3 House Republican Elise Stefanik of New York, tried to move the discussion to a new topic: Hunter Biden’s laptop .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers flare over emotion-sensing AI...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mood-emotion-sensing-ai-tempers-flare-a01efe11-362d-4fab-9d86-cee64ff839f1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology's already being put to use, but critics say it's inaccurate and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
