<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>App At-Home Test For Brain Diseases Via 'Eye Selfies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/app-test-brain-diseases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of California-San Diego have developed a new app that uses eye recordings to assess cognitive health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!   NYC raises covid alert level as new cases surpass threshold...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/nyc-raises-covid-alert-level-as-new-cases-surpass-key-threshold-what-to-know/3671167/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC COVID cases surpassed a critical threshold, prompting health officials to raise the city’s alert level to medium on Monday. Here’s what that means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The many controversies surrounding Madison Cawthorn...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-many-controversies-surrounding-madison-cawthorn/ar-AAWPtaX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flawed math behind Elon Musk's TWITTER deal?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/the-flawed-math-behind-elon-musk-e2-80-99s-twitter-deal/ar-AAWPSy9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian tycoon who defected says Putin 'must be hanged'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-gas-tycoon-who-defected-26846616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Igor Volobuyev fled Russia just days into the war and now feels the need to "repent" after two decades of support for the Kremlin - and he wants to see the president pay with his life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman investigating dog attack  -- killed by pack of dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/dogs-kill-alabama-woman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested an Alabama dog owner after a pack of dogs attacked and killed a state employee investigating an earlier attack by the same dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare tornado touches down in Puerto Rico, jolts residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/tornado-in-arecibo-puerto-rico-jolts-residents/1181198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Severe weather erupted across the island on Sunday, causing damage and prompting weather officials to give the twister -- the first to hit Puerto Rico in about three years -- an EF1 rating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dead' woman bangs on coffin to say she's alive during funeral!</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/05/02/dead-woman-bangs-on-coffin-to-say-shes-alive-during-funeral-in-peru-16571399/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning: You may find the content of this story distressing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dismay and dissent within FOX?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/30/what-to-know-about-tucker-carlsons-rise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Night after night on Fox, Tucker Carlson weaponizes his viewers’ fears and grievances to create what may be the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How He Became Trump's Heir Apparent...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/30/how-tucker-carlson-reshaped-fox-news-and-became-trumps-heir/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson had a problem. After years in the cable wilderness, he had made a triumphant return to prime time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demands apology...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/lapid-denounces-russian-fms-unforgivable-claim-that-hitler-had-jewish-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett blasts Lavrov's 'lies' as FM summons envoy for 'clarification'; Lavrov had defended 'denazification' of Zelensky-run Ukraine by saying 'some of worst antisemites are Jews'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindell gets banned from TWITTER, again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-technology-business-social-media-donald-trump-3bdebae1fc19af4fc8643a587de01324</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell was banned from Twitter for a second time after attempting to use a new account to access the social media platform. Lindell set up a new account Sunday on Twitter under @MikeJLindell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA cases rising. New wave?</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/news/again-california-coronavirus-cases-rising-120057040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases have risen by nearly 30% in California over the last week. Hospitalizations are up, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM MYSTERY: HOW TO BRIGHTEN MOOD</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/02/democrats-mystery-how-to-brighten-a-presidency-and-a-national-mood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEWOOD, Ohio — At a Whole Foods in one moderate Cleveland suburb, shoppers recently worried about war, inflation, a “scary”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is China preparing to invade Taiwan?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10774819/Beijing-looks-save-3-2tln-foreign-reserves-sanctions-event-military-conflict.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West's harsh economic sanctions on Russia prompted an emergency meeting in China, with the Ministry of Finance stating that Xi's administration had been put on high alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St stumbles into new month following April slide...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/05/01/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures were mixed in early morning trading on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can pee help feed world?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220502-can-pee-help-feed-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Go pee on the rhubarb!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greyhound racing nearing its end after long slide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-sports-iowa-animals-dogs-5f00d7b4f37f636d2e6479d15d6a94b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBUQUE, Iowa (AP) — Vera Rasnake laughed as she led a trio of barking, jostling dogs into the Iowa Greyhound Park, but her smile faded when she acknowledged that after 41 years of being around the sleek animals, her sport was teetering on extinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people with agoraphobia struggle as pandemic wanes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-people-with-agoraphobia-struggle-as-pandemic-wanes/ar-AAWJoFr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar rises towards 20-year high...</title>
      <link>https://uk.investing.com/news/economy/dollar-holds-near-20year-high-euro-struggles-2637619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dollar rises towards 20-year high, euro dips after weak data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Erupts After Russian Foreign Minister Lavrov Claims Hitler Had Jewish Blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-erupts-after-russian-foreign-minister-sergey-lavrov-claims-hitler-had-jewish-blood/ar-AAWPhgs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Treasury Buyer Outside USA Quietly Selling Billions...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biggest-treasury-buyer-outside-u-220000326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In times of Treasury turmoil, the biggest investor outside American soil has historically lent a helping hand. Not this time round. Most Read from BloombergNaomi Judd, of Grammy-Winning Duo The Judds, Dies at 76Bored Ape Metaverse Frenzy Raises Millions, Crashes EthereumBiggest Treasury Buyer Outside U.S. Quietly Selling BillionsMusk Engages in Twitter Spat After Rebuttal From Ocasio-CortezOmicron Sublineages Evade Antibodies From Earlier InfectionsJapanese institutional managers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel condemns Lavrov's 'unforgivable' Hitler remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lavrov-russia-israel-hitler-zelensky-037e3622-23a5-40e9-8f7c-3fd470a1c5fd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lavrov falsely claimed that Adolf Hitler had "Jewish blood."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the space hotel scheduled to open in 2025...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/space-hotel-orbital-assembly-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orbital Assembly Corporation is planning to build Voyager Station and Pioneer Station, two space hubs in the sky. The company says its space stations are the future of space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Tycoon Criticized Putin's War. Retribution Was Swift...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/05/01/russian-tycoon-criticized-putins-war-retribution-was-swift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oleg Y. Tinkov was worth more than $9 billion in November, renowned as one of Russia’s few self-made business tycoons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long and gruesome history of people trying to live forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-long-and-gruesome-history-of-people-trying-to-live-forever/ar-AAWNqyu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Kushner to publish White House memoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jared-kushner-book-cb2a57a8-5838-4fe5-8289-650d7d15c0f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The book is titled "Breaking History: A White House Memoir."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers Struggling to Keep Up Food Supply...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-feed-itself-historic-fertilizer-120018356.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For the first time ever, farmers the world over — all at the same time — are testing the limits of how little chemical fertilizer they can apply without devastating their yields come harvest time. Early predictions are bleak.Most Read from BloombergNaomi Judd, of Grammy-Winning Duo The Judds, Dies at 76Bored Ape Metaverse Frenzy Raises Millions, Crashes EthereumMusk Engages in Twitter Spat After Rebuttal From Ocasio-CortezBiggest Treasury Buyer Outside U.S. Quietly Offloading Bill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump bid to shape GOP faces test with voters in May races...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-ohio-donald-trump-campaigns-89a597655ab2c39529c8d38e961a4081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Donald Trump 's post-presidency enters a new phase this month as voters across the U.S. begin weighing the candidates he elevated to pursue a vision of a Republican Party steeped in hard-line populism, culture wars and denial of his loss in the 2020 campaign .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk of 'Victory' Has Some Allies Nervous...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/05/01/world/europe/ukraine-russia-war-pelosi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europeans focused on helping Ukraine withstand the invasion worry that the United States may be “dragging everyone into a different war.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark, Sweden summoning envoys over airspace breaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.rferl.org/a/denmark-sweden-russia-airspace-violation-spy-plane/31829644.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rferl.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark and Sweden are summoning Russia's ambassadors after a Russian spy plane violated the airspace of both countries, their governments said on May 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long and gruesome history of people trying to live forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-long-and-gruesome-history-of-people-trying-to-live-forever/ar-AAWNqyu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This room is like a horror film'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10772773/Washington-Post-reporter-mocked-tweeting-afraid-breathing-near-people-WHCD.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before sparking outrage online, Jada Yuan, a politics correspondent at the Post, shared a picture of herself maskless and smiling at the distinguished event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence erupts in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10772663/Violence-erupts-Paris-Day-demonstrators-throw-fireworks-McDonalds-restaurant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protest marches have been held around the world to mark International Workers' Day and while some remained peaceful parades, others escalated into violent clashes and destruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH:  Too soon remove masks from planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10772527/Oprah-Winfrey-reveals-masker-continue-wear-one-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revealing she spent 332 days without leaving her home during the peak of the pandemic, Oprah went on to tell the LA times she is not quite ready just yet to let go of precautions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek workers march at energy cost surge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greek-workers-protest-energy-cost-161108627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metro trains ground to a halt and ships were docked in ports as thousands of workers joined May Day rallies in the Greek capital to protest against soaring energy and food prices. Gas and power bills have surged, with price rises exacerbated by sanctions against Russia following its Feb. 24 invasion of Ukraine, taking inflation in Greece to multi-year highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans take to streets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cubans-streets-workers-day-first-160535981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban President Miguel Diaz-Canel and former revolutionary leader Raul Castro, wearing a white mask and dressed in hallmark military fatigues, oversaw the rallies from a stage overlooking Havana's "Plaza de la Revolucion." The marches, held each year across the Communist-run country prior to the pandemic, are rife with symbolism, a celebration of the 63-year-old Cuban revolution, but also, a government-led rebuke of the Cold War-era embargo imposed on the island by the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pent-up partying!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/05/white-house-correspondents-dinner-joe-biden-trevor-noah-1235013891/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and comedian Trevor Noah wrapped up their routines at the White House Correspondents’ Association dinner with appeals for the work of journalists and freedom of the press.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trevor Noah lampoons: Things looking up. Gas. Rent. Food. Everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trevor-noah-lampoons-biden-things-are-really-looking-up-gas-is-up-rent-is-up-food-is-up-everything/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily Show host Trevor Noah roasted the D.C. elite on Saturday night, including President Joe Biden at the White House Correspondents' Association Dinner. It was the first time the dinner had been held since 2019 due to Covid, and it was the first time since 2016 a president attended the event. About</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?519515-102/trevor-noah-remarks-white-house-correspondents-association-dinner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence erupts in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/may-day-marchers-france-put-135523129.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (Reuters) -Police fired tear gas to push back black-clad anarchists who ransacked business premises in Paris on Sunday during May Day protests against the policies of newly re-elected President Emmanuel Macron. Thousands of people joined May Day marches across France, calling for salary increases and for Macron to drop his plan to raise the retirement age. Most were peaceful but violence broke out in the capital, where police arrested 54 people, including a woman who attacked a fireman trying to put out a fire, Interior Minister Gerald Darmanin said on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro, Lula competing rallies a preview of presidential campaign...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-lula-competing-rallies-195200135.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian right-wing President Jair Bolsonaro and his main rival, former leftist President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, staged competing rallies on Sunday that were expected to become previews of their campaigns for presidential elections in October. Supporters of Bolsonaro had called during the week protests against the Supreme Court, after he pardoned a congressman sentenced to eight years in prison for threatening judges. The pardoned congressman, Daniel Silveira, said in a rally in Niteroi, in Rio de Janeiro state, that his arrest last year was "unconstitutional."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash Strapped NETFLIX Dumps Meghan Markle Series...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/05/meghan-markle-animated-series-pearl-canceled-netflix-cutbacks-prince-harrs-archewell-productions-1235013893/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Even Netflix’s in-house members of the Royal Family are not immune to a wave of cutbacks going on as the streamer recalibrates after a precipitous stock drop incurred after a drop …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people with agoraphobia struggle as pandemic wanes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-people-with-agoraphobia-struggle-as-pandemic-wanes/ar-AAWJoFr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCWASHPOST:  Biden ticks up, but Republicans hold advantage on economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-ticks-up-but-gop-holds-advantage-on-economy-post-abc-poll-finds/ar-AAWNrz8?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  TUCKER NOW KING OF CABLE...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/30/how-tucker-carlson-stoked-white-fear-to-conquer-cable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tucker Carlson burst through the doors of Charlie Palmer Steak, enfolded in an entourage of producers and assistants, cellphone pressed</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
