<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll ruling arouses controversy in SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-sexdolls/sex-doll-ruling-arouses-controversy-in-south-korea-idUSKCN1US0YG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A petition calling for a ban on importing life-size sex dolls into South Korea h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron isn't same anymore about winning, NBA exec says...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/lakers/story/2019-08-01/lebron-james-david-griffin-lakers-nba-title-pelicans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Cleveland Cavaliers general manager David Griffin says trying to build a roster around LeBron James made him miserable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batters to shatter home run record...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/mlb/story/batters-on-pace-to-shatter-mlb-home-run-record-by-10-080119</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major league batters are on pace to hit 600 more home runs than in any previous season, nearly 10% above record set two years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses take stand in final day of A$AP Rocky assault trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/witnesses-stand-final-day-ap-rocky-assault-trial-044221287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US rapper A$AP Rocky's trial in Sweden entered its expected final day on Friday, with witnesses taking the stand in an assault case that has stirred diplomatic tensions and outraged fans. The 30-year-old rapper, whose real name is Rakim Mayers, was arrested on July 3 along with three other people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Am What I Am, Bolsonaro Says, as Unfiltered Words Rile Allies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/am-am-bolsonaro-says-unfiltered-100000819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro has a clear message for allies and critics alike after a slew of incendiary comments: I am not going to change.Over the past few weeks Bolsonaro has threatened a journalist with jail, mocked the dead father of Brazil’s Bar Association president and canceled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test predicts Alzheimer's 20 years before onset...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/scientists-say-a-blood-test-can-detect-signs-of-alzheimers-20-years-before-onset-of-symptoms-11775417</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in the US say they hope it will become available to GPs within a few years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: TESLA Autopilot steered car under semitruck at 68 mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/delray-beach/fl-ne-tesla-autopilot-lawsuit-20190801-zokyrcqxz5cn7jpjeenaoud6iy-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wrongful death lawsuit against Tesla alleges its Autopilot feature failed in a crash that killed a 50-year-old man in March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: Layoffs pummel news outlets...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/08/01/large-u-s-newspapers-layoffs-2018/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mid-market newspapers were the most likely to suffer layoffs in 2018. Digital-native news outlets also faced continued layoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of bees drop dead around '5G towers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/795681/Hundreds-bees-drop-dead-5G-towers-California-Sierra-Madre-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIEL: Good for GOOGLE, Bad for America...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/peter-thiel-new-york-times-op-ed-google-china-2019-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last month, Peter Thiel called Google 'seemingly treasonous' and called for the FBI and the CIA to investigate its workings in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT 2' To Terrorize Theaters With 'Clowns Only' Screenings...</title>
      <link>https://uproxx.com/movies/it-chapter-2-clowns-only-screenings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uproxx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alamo Drafthouse’s infamous "clowns only" screenings are back for ’It Chapter Two,’ in case you needed another excuse to not go outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan district attorney keeps digging...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/manhattan-da-subpoenas-trump-organization-over-stormy-daniels-hush-money/ar-AAFclrS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson suffers first major defeat as UK PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-brecon-election-result-lib-18815091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welsh Lib Dem leader Jane Dodds has beaten disgraced former Tory MP Chris Davies in the Brecon and Radnorshire byelection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I don't want to be controversial. We want no controversy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/At-Ohio-rally-Trump-escalates-attacks-on-liberal-14274817.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI - President Donald Trump on Thursday escalated his attacks on Baltimore and other diverse, liberal cities, telling a crowd in this key swing state that Democrats "deliver poverty for their constituents and privilege for themselves."  "For decades, these communities have been run exclusively by Democrat politicians, and it's been total one-party control of the inner cities," Trump said. He called federal funding sent to these areas "stolen money and it's wasted money, and it's a shame."  Trump steered clear of mentioning lawmakers by name, in a departure from his recent attacks on Rep. Elijah Cummings, D-Md., whose district includes parts of Baltimore, and four minority Democratic congresswomen, including Rep. Ilhan Omar of Minnesota.  On Thursday night, he made only a passing mention to "four left-wing extremists" who he said are now leading the Democratic Party, then told the crowd in the mostly full U.S. Bank Arena: "We can name one after another, but I won't do that, because I don't want to be controversial. We want no controversy."  The president's remarks were in line with his recent denunciations of liberal enclaves as violent, dirty and outside the mainstream. Trump offered no policy proposals for how he plans to address the problems he says plague numerous cities across the country.  Trump won Ohio by eight percentage points over former secretary of state Hillary Clinton in 2016, and the state is key to his 2020 reelection bid.  In recent days, Trump has escalated his attacks on Baltimore and Cummings, the House Oversight Committee chairman who has been spearheading investigations into Trump's administration. Trump began by tweeting Saturday that Cummings represents a "disgusting, rat and rodent infested mess" and that "No human being would want to live there." The president lashed out anew on Tuesday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Renew Amnesty for Thousands of Syrians...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/08/01/dhs-secretary-kevin-mcaleenan-renews-temporary-amnesty-for-7k-syrians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting DHS Secretary Kevin McAleenan renewed a temporary amnesty program for about 7,000 Syrian nationals on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALARM OVER NEGATIVITY</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/455849-democrats-express-alarm-over-debates-negative-tone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic lawmakers were left shaken and worried by Wednesday night’s bruising presidential debate, which left some fearing the fight will hurt the party and result in a damaged nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lock her up' chant breaks out at rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/455874-lock-her-up-chant-breaks-out-at-trump-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After President Trump mentioned 2016 rival Hillary Clinton at a reelection campaign rally in Cincinnati, the crowd broke into a chant of "lock her up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it time to take Marianne Williamson seriously?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/is-it-time-to-take-marianne-williamson-seriously-225000879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-help guru Marianne Williamson made her mark during the second round of presidential debates. Is she a legitimate candidate for the Democratic nomination?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS IN DISARRAY</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/08/01/debates-identify-plenty-of-democratic-divisions-but-not-a-consensus-favorite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The two rounds of Democratic presidential debates, rather than bringing clarity to the primary or culling the field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump escalates attacks on liberal cities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c2048ba0aa24543a943a4c134ae159a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.1 million expected at southern border this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/flood-of-illegal-migrants-to-the-border-outpaces-last-two-years-with-1-1m-expected-in-fy2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement based on the U.S.-Mexico border are expected to encounter 1.1 million people trying to cross illegally by the end of the fiscal year Sept. 30, despite Mexico's assistance stopping migrants on their journey north.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Says Women Can Travel Without Male Guardians...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/01/saudi-women-can-now-travel-without-a-male-guardian-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okaz newspaper reports key step in dismantling strict controls over nation’s women</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first human-monkey hybrid grown in lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/795498/human-monkey-hybrid-grown-in-china-organ-transplants-scientists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE's extravagant 'climate change' Camp mocked as party for 'entitled fools'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/08/01/googles-extravagant-climate-change-camp-mocked-as-party-for-entitled-fools/?_ga=2.145353844.1565578393.1564527849-644250957.1564527849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire creators of Google each year invite a who’s who of A-listers to the event which is meant to be a conference where influential people discuss how to make the world a better pla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts third test launch in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/north-korea-launches-projectile-us-officials/story?id=64715583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea has fired at least one projectile into the Sea of Japan, a U.S. official confirmed to ABC News. President Donald Trump said, "It's very much under control."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England birth rate hits historic low...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7312075/Birth-rate-England-Wales-hits-80-YEAR-low.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were just over 11 babies born for every 1,000 people in England and Wales last year. It came just days after Harry and Meghan said they plan on having only two babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Mother killed daughters who 'got in way' of sex life...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/louise-porton-mother-guilty-of-murdering-young-daughters-who-got-in-the-way-of-sex-life-11775192</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louise Porton, 23, suffocated three-year-old Lexi in January 2018 and then killed 17-month-old Scarlett two weeks later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON drivers part of $10 million theft ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/amazon-drivers-part-10-million-theft-ring-fbi-says-n1038421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A theft ring in Washington state sold millions of dollars' worth of stolen goods on Amazon.com in the past six years, recently unsealed federal court documents show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114,000 dogs, cats killed in Texas shelters last year...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article233399267.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda as Strong as Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-08-01/al-qaeda-is-as-strong-as-ever-after-rebuilding-itself-u-s-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS stands by 'BULL' star in wake of sex misconduct claim...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/730057b181494a2da5005d74cc3e17db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says not worried...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190801194352-zfg4n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/USA-TRUMP (URGENT):Trump says he is not worried about short-range missiles fired by North Korea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Adds Kids as Young as 11 to Facial Recognition Database...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/01/nyregion/nypd-facial-recognition-children-teenagers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With little oversight, the police have been using the powerful surveillance technology on photos of children and teenagers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 7 Qualified For Next One...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/only-7-candidates-have-qualified-for-the-next-democratic-debate/ar-AAFbiYl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fashion Photographer Who Duped Drug Lords -- and DEA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2019-06-27/the-fashion-photographer-who-duped-drug-cartels-and-the-dea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US officials say ISIS still danger to world...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/591bdd9e809e4fe3bffc1431734a0d7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most frequently stolen vehicle: DODGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/08/01/most-stolen-cars-dodge-chevrolet-infiniti-iihs-hldi/1868237001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cars like the Dodge Charger and pickups like the Chevrolet Silverado 1500 are among the most-stolen new vehicles, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US Navy SEAL tells commanders: 'We have a problem'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/01/politics/navy-seals-collin-green-service-members-misbehavior/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top US Navy SEAL recently sent a blistering letter to the force, writing in boldface type, "We have a problem," following several high profile incidents of alleged misbehavior by the US Navy's elite service members, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President: US imposing 10% tariffs on $300 billion of Chinese goods; Stocks rocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/01/trump-says-us-will-impose-10percent-tariffs-on-300-billion-of-chinese-goods-starting-september-1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump made the announcement via Twitter, shaking financial markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10.7 Million Tune In...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/cnn-second-democratic-debate-ratings-1203288069/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last night’s second Democratic debate on CNN, which was marked by a protestor interruption and featured a rematch between California Sen. Kamala Harris and Former Vice President Joe Biden, to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI:  Conspiracy theories new domestic terror threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-documents-conspiracy-theories-terrorism-160000507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI for the first time has identified fringe conspiracy theories as a domestic terrorist threat, according to a previously unpublicized document obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Orders Stand-Down to Combat Rising Suicides...</title>
      <link>http://www.airforcemag.com/Features/Pages/2019/August%202019/Air-Force-Temporarily-Stopping-Operations-to-Address-Growing-Suicide-Rate.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcemag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air Force units will stand down for one day this summer to address the rising problem of suicides, which Air Force Chief of Staff Gen. David Goldfein said is “an adversary that is killing more of our airmen than any enemy on the planet.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENCE: Gators have taste for Florida Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/environment/gators-have-taste-for-florida-man-according-to-science-20190801/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gator bites have become more common as the gator population has boomed. A lot of the time, the gators aren't sure what they're biting and back off, study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers try to sell Mexican boy for $2,500 in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/nation-world/national/article233387437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos sells $1.8 billion worth of AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/01/jeff-bezos-sells-1point8-billion-worth-of-amazon-stock-in-three-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos previously told reporters he would sell $1 billion in stock each year to fund his space company, Blue Origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS shares shocking video of beheading as children cheer...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/1/isis-shares-shocking-video-beheading-children-chee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Islamic State in Afghanistan today shared shocking images of its fighters beheading a Taliban as children watched and cheered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golf star arrested for urinating in aisle on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/9628397/ian-poulter-pal-thorbjorn-olesen-sexually-assaulted-passenger-ba-flight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GOLF pro was arrested on suspicion of sexual assault after allegedly going on a tirade before molesting a woman on a British Airways flight. Ryder Cup hero Ian Poulter, 43, stepped in to calm pal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK experiment to create device that reads mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/614034/facebook-is-funding-brain-experiments-to-create-a-device-that-reads-your-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big tech firms are trying to read people’s thoughts, and no one’s ready for the consequences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX collecting data on your 'physical activity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.slashfilm.com/netflix-physical-activity-tracking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.slashfilm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Netflix physical activity tracker is being tested on Android users to "see how [it] can improve video playback quality when a member is on the go."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suit after 5 deaths: Frat brother gave 'advice on how to commit suicide'...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/article233350912.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOT RACISM: Humans Prefer White Droids...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/01/tech/robot-racism-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a reason most human-shaped robots are white, say researchers. And the reason is not productive at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makes at Least 7 Gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/08/01/list-top-7-joe-biden-gaffes-at-the-democrat-debate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden added to his long list of gaffes at Wednesday evening's Democrat presidential primary debate in Detriot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German City Rocked After Man Hacked to Death by Migrant in Broad Daylight...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2019/08/01/germany-kazakh-man-hacked-death-syrian-migrant-broad-daylight/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 36-year-old man was hacked to death in Stuttgart with what appeared to be a katana-type sword in the middle of the street on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winnowing 2020 field too soon?</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/154584/democratic-party-culling-field-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates should be focusing on retail politicking in Iowa and New Hampshire. Instead, they're wasting money trying to meet arbitrary debate requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Shut Down 11-Year-Old's Lemonade Stand...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/07/31/kankakee-girl-lemonade-stand-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Countless children set up lemonade stands at this time of year, but one 11-year-old Kankakee girl has found her stand shut down by local health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC attempts to block Yang from future debates with technicalities...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/dnc-attempts-to-block-andrew-yang-from-future-debates-with-technicalities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, Democratic presidential candidate Andrew Yang celebrated an important milestone in his campaign: meeting the polling threshold to qualify for the fall debates. Now the Democratic National Committee is attempting to keep him out, citing a technicality on polling qualifications, which requires candidates to garner at least 2 percent support in at least four …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Pack of teens beat man wearing MAGA hat...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/maga-hat-beating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York City art store owner says he was viciously beaten by a pack of teens for wearing a &amp;quot;Make America Great Again&amp;quot; hat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon lasers beam messages into head...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9629895/pentagon-laser-weapon-message-enemy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILITARY scientists at the Pentagon are developing ‘talking’ lasers which can beam warnings straight into the enemy’s head from hundreds of miles away. Weapons researchers at the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark chocolate lowers risk of depression for 24 hours?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/08/01/dark-chocolate-lowers-risk-depression-24-hours-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is food news guaranteed to put a smile on your face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOVE OVER, EILISH!  Lana Del Rey Drops August 30th...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/08/01/lana-del-reys-long-awaited-long-postponed-album-norman-fcking-rockwell-drops-august-30th</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long awaited, and long postponed by her label: Lana del Rey’s “Norman F**cking Rockwell!” is dropping on August 30th. It’s about f**cking time! Originally meant for earlier …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Gets His Wall at Last -- But It's in Zimbabwe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-za/news/africa/donald-trump-gets-his-wall-at-last-but-its-in-zimbabwe/ar-AAFaWii?li=BBqfP3n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Producer: My Humble Quest to Live Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/gavin-polone-my-humble-quest-live-forever-1228036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By undergoing the latest in genetic and medical testing at a cutting-edge San Diego facility, the film and television producer seeks early detection to avoid the fate of his parents and cheat death or dementia indefinitely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDONESIA: Caned in public for getting too close to opposite sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7310301/Eleven-people-caned-public-hooded-Sharia-officer-Indonesia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One woman begged for mercy and another sobbed uncontrollably in the provincial capital of Banda Aceh in Indonesia as 11 people were flogged for breaking Islamic law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Greenerati'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7309805/Backlash-barefoot-Prince-Harry-hypocrite-celebrities.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 114 fuel-guzzling planes are scheduled to land in Palermo for the event, according to Italian media, while others brought their super-yachts to the three-day conference in Italy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says tested crucial new rocket launch system...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/09c7059291d846a091e139183fe7c4b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scared' rapper A$AP Rocky testifies in Sweden assault trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/717/scared-us-rapper-aap-rocky-testifies-sweden-assault-trial-doc-1j89rm3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs: CIA Pressured Michael Bay To Change Benghazi Movie...</title>
      <link>https://shadowproof.com/2019/07/30/cia-pressured-michael-bay-change-13-hours-benghazi-movie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;shadowproof.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED CUTS QUARTER AS ECONOMY FLASHES WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57dfaefd18e64a4e9f3698f5f3c92bfb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From everyteen to annoying: Young readers turning on 'CATCHER IN RYE'?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/aug/01/the-catcher-in-the-rye-fans-jd-salinger-holden-caulfield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JD Salinger’s Holden Caulfield once seemed the universal voice of teenage angst, but now he’s too quaint for young people. Can we learn to love it again, asks Dana Czapnik</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden memoir to reveal whistleblower's secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2019/aug/01/edward-snowden-memoir-to-reveal-whistleblowers-secrets-permanent-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man who helped build the US’s mass surveillance tech will recount how his work led him to make the biggest leak in history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This California town wants to be 2nd Amendment 'sanctuary' for guns, ammo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-07-30/needles-second-amendment-sanctuary-california-town</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming months, Needles officials say they plan to work with state representatives on legislation that would exempt the city — and possibly other border towns — from rules on purchasing ammunition out of California and reciprocity with other states over concealed weapons permits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN: Panderfest...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/455700-mark-penn-democrats-debate-was-a-panderfest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When not pandering to gender, racial or ethnic groups with offers of cash, the candidates attacked each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: To crush Trump, Michelle Obama needs to run...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/455702-michael-moore-urges-michelle-obama-to-run-against-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Michael Moore said in a new interview that there is only one candidate up to the challenge to “crush” President Trump in 2020, “and her last name rhymes with Obama.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Pitcher Smashes TVs In Dugout After Rough Start...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/08/01/boston-red-sox-rick-porcello-dugout-tvs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rick Porcello wasn’t happy with his start Wednesday night against the Tampa Bay Rays. He took out his frustration on a pair of televisions in the Red Sox dugout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady set for 20th season: 'Hard to imagine doing anything else'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2019/07/31/new-england-patriots-tom-brady-retirement-contract-bill-belichick/1878379001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just a few days shy of turning 42, Tom Brady addressed questions about retirement and his contract with the New England Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic cockroach weighs 0.07 grams -- can withstand weight of human...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/robotic-cockroach-weighs-just-007g-18810982</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of California, Berekely have developed a tiny robot that measures just 3cm by 1.5cm, and weighs less than 0.07 grams</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create fabric that smells better more you sweat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/scientists-create-fabric-that-smells-better-the-more-you-sweat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your gross workout gear could double as an air freshener.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once shrine to retailer's brand, 'flagships' lose luster...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6cb0379d61dc4cad983ffad5bc040555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Talking lasers' beam messages to ears...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/31/talking-lasers-that-beam-messages-to-our-ears-in-the-works-pentagon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hold on to your tinfoil hats, because there’s certainly a conspiracy theory a-brewin’ here. The Pentagon has confirmed it’s testing lasers that can talk. Huh? Weapons researchers …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 'Send her back!' chant, Ohio rally test for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/send-her-back-chant-ohio-042103341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's latest rally will be a test for both candidate and crowd. The Cincinnati gathering Thursday night will be Trump's first since his audience chanted "Send her back!" about a Somali-born congresswoman during a July rally in North Carolina , raising the prospect</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
