<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The wild revelations about behind-the-scenes drama on 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/books/2019/04/02/ladies-who-punch-the-view-book-cohosts-ramin-setoodeh/3329940002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Ladies Who Punch' by Ramin Setoodeh alleges behind-the-scenes betrayal and consistent conflict at 'The View.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would bringing back extinct animals turn out as badly as 'JURASSIC PARK'? </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/lifestyle/article/Would-bringing-back-extinct-animals-turn-out-as-13731918.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a frigid January night, a Harvard genetics professor with a billowing white beard stood stage left in a theater on Manhattan's Upper East Side, an icon of the environmentalist movement in a fleece vest beside him. Both men were staring down a toothy problem: How could they convince their counterparts on the stage, along with the 300 people who'd filed into Hunter College's Kaye Playhouse for a debate, that the world should bring back velociraptors or, at the very least, an extinct pigeon?  The theme from the 1993 blockbuster "Jurassic Park" was playing in the background, chiseling away at their argument before the debate even began. In the film, based on the 1990 Michael Crichton bestseller, dinosaurs are brought back from extinction to fill a theme park. "That film took sides. The experiment blows up. People get hurt," moderator John Donvan told the crowd during introductions. "But not before actor Jeff Goldblum declares, 'Scientists were so preoccupied with whether or not they could that they didn't stop to think if they should.' And then, a dinosaur eats Jeff Goldblum."  Actually, a dinosaur does not eat Goldblum's brainy and brawny mathematician character, but chaos certainly reigns in the movie and its myriad sequels because of de-extinction. Those images are what George Church, 64, of the billowing white beard, who helped launch the Human Genome Project, and Stewart Brand, 80, of the fleece vest, who is a founder and editor of the Whole Earth Catalog, would need to overcome to win this evening's debate.  The official motion for the night, "Don't Bring Extinct Creatures Back to Life," was chosen by Intelligence Squared, a nonprofit that turns academic-level debates into popular live events and podcasts. The Jeff Goldblums of the evening, arguing for the motion - and against Church and Brand - were Lynn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Clooney persuade Hollywood to boycott hotels over Brunei antigay laws?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-clooney-boycott-sultan-brunei-20190402-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Clooney is calling for a boycott of the Beverly Hills Hotel and others owned by Sultan of Brunei over the small nation's antigay laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squabbles and backstabbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6873987/The-View-secrets-laid-bare-Whoopi-gunned-Barbara-Walters-job.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Squabbles and backstabbing were de rigeur at the show Barbara Walters built, says the author of the new book on The View,  Ladies Who Punch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BLAMES BERNIE?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2020-presidential-election-joe-biden-bernie-sanders-99ec8fc7-e9a8-44e8-b52d-6c5a096d7fd3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second woman says a display of affection by Biden made her feel uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Religion Pre-Dated Incas by 500 Years, Stunning Discovery Reveals...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/stunning-discovery-reveals-mysterious-religion-pre-dating-the-incas-by-500-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of years ago, the west coast of South America was ruled by the Incas - a mysterious empire considered to be the most elaborate society to exist in the Americas before the arrival of Columbus. This is not their story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avid traveller, 33, dies mysteriously on filght from LAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6875385/Friends-woman-died-flight-United-States-Melbourne-remain-mystified.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young tech executive who died in mysterious circumstances on board a Qantas flight from Los Angeles to Melbourne was an avid traveller who had flown the same route many times before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg IN if Biden OUT?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2020-presidential-election-michael-bloomberg-biden-2e19cd85-975d-43b4-a7ac-b25359b82b82.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race looked like "a bloody fight for the same slice of voters," a source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Sightings Of Russian Surveillance Jet Over US Military Sites...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/01/russian-surveillance-jets-california-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why is a Russian spy plane flying over California?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APRIL SNOW HITS SOUTH...</title>
      <link>http://www.wmbfnews.com/2019/04/02/watch-snow-falls-sc-second-day-april/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmbfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring may officially be here, but you wouldn’t know it stepping out the door on Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel election vicious and personal as campaigning enters final week...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netanyahu-gantz-ramp-up-attacks-in-israeli-election-11554206400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel’s national election is becoming particularly vicious and personal as campaigning enters its final week, highlighting how the battle for Israel’s premiership remains closely contested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: 50 CENT Sells Massive Connecticut Compound for 84% Less...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/50-cent-sells-massive-connecticut-compound-for-84-less-11554152164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 12 years of trying, the rapper finally unloads the 52-room Farmington property, which includes a night club, for $2.9 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May looks for way out of maelstrom...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu/may-looks-for-a-way-out-of-brexit-maelstrom-as-eu-says-no-deal-exit-looms-idUSKCN1RE0JB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European officials said on Tuesday the prospect of Britain leaving the European ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic waterspout leaves buildings in ruins...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/apocalyptic-water-tornado-speeds-towards-14222947 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The huge water spout headed towards George Town in Penang, Malaysia, forcing people to run for their lives from a nearby beach</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britons most likely to combine sex, drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/uk-sex-drugs-chemsex-alcohol-cannabis-cocain-global-survey-ucl-a8849686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Panic and chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nipsey-hussle-vigil-mass-panic-chaos-suspect-eric-holder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several people were hurt when a crowd of roughly 300 suddenly stampeded; police named a suspect they're seeking in the rapper's slaying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 by the numbers: Dems posting big campaign stats...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a4066e8b915e4587862ec752a1d6db86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — How many ways can you measure the first quarter of the year? For Democratic presidential candidates, it's 300-plus events, 24 states and hundreds of voter questions. The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US officials worry paralyzing illness may grow more common...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2b43b0f510a1419d8c436e13d082dafa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One morning last fall, 4-year-old Joey Wilcox woke up with the left side of his face drooping. It was the first sign of an unfolding nightmare. Three days later, Joey...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam sex workers angry at red light district tours ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ab196e9ddae648cbad8d3773e1b9314c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM (AP) — The city of Amsterdam's latest attempt to rein in the nuisance of over-tourism by banning guided tours of the red light district has run into opposition from some of the people it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: AMAZON employees left to suffer after workplace injuries...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/apr/02/revealed-amazon-employees-suffer-after-workplace-injuries </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon made its CEO is the wealthiest person in the world. So why can’t the company care for those injured while working there?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope warns against hate-fomenting 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190402-pope-warns-against-hate-fomenting-fake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope warns against hate-fomenting 'fake news'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman suffers brain damage after three-week fruit juice diet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6876275/Israeli-woman-feared-irreversible-brain-damage-three-week-fruit-juice-diet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman, in her 40s, was rushed to Sheba Medical Center, in Tel Aviv, weighing less than 90lbs and suffering brain damage that medics fear may be permanent after the extreme diet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence breaks out at rapper memorial; Massive stampede...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6875765/Mourners-injured-violence-erupts-Nipsey-Hussles-memorial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person has been stabbed and 19 were injured after violence broke out at a memorial for rapper Nipsey Hussle outside the Los Angeles store where he was shot dead a day earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Tests His Boundaries and Trump's Patience in Growing Role...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bolton-tests-boundaries-trump-apos-080000935.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An example spilled into the public eye a week ago, when an irked Trump cryptically announced on Twitter he’d undo some North Korea-related sanctions blessed by Bolton. Since joining Trump’s White House, Bolton has pursued an agenda that includes trying to break Iran financially, oust Venezuelan President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considers 'immigration czar' for border security...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/40654a1b83eb45e3b661903305083d9e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As he threatens to shut down the southern border, President Donald Trump is considering bringing on a "border" or "immigration czar" to coordinate immigration policy across...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTER: WASHPOST complicit in CBS #MeToo cover-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecut.com/2019/04/what-was-the-washington-post-afraid-of.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About to publish an investigation of a powerful executive’s alleged sexual misconduct, the newspaper pulled back. Irin Carmon tries to understand why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Says Debris From India's Antisatellite Test Puts Space Station at Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaltrends.com/cool-tech/space-debris-from-indias-anti-satellite-test-a-threat-to-iss-nasa-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaltrends.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Numerous pieces of debris resulting from India's recent anti-satellite missile test pose a threat to the safety of the International Space Station, a NASA official said on Monday. But India insisted the test was conducted in the safety of the lower atmosphere, with any debris likely to decay within a few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND WOMAN SPEAKS</title>
      <link>https://www.courant.com/politics/hc-pol-biden-grabbed-aide-20190401-vl7chim3hrdjtcwu2tszrhozzm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Connecticut woman and former congressional aide says Joe Biden touched her inappropriately and rubbed noses with her during a 2009 political fundraiser in Greenwich when he was vice president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Create 3D Printer -- With Potential To Print Life Itself...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/03/31/cal-lawrence-livermore-scientists-create-3d-printer-with-potential-to-print-life-itself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at UC Berkeley and Lawrence Livermore Lab have created a new kind of 3D printer that could potentially manufacture living human organs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions without water as Venezuela crisis deepens...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/maduro-announces-30-days-electricity-rationing-venezuela-015233386.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's Supreme Court called Monday for Juan Guaido to be stripped of his legislative immunity, tightening the noose on the opposition chief just days after authorities announced a ban on him holding public office. Guaido -- recognized as Venezuela's interim president by some 50 countries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Methane on Red Planet sign of life?</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/mars-methane-plume-confirmed-location.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Hackers Trick TESLA Autopilot Into Wrong Lane...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2019/04/01/hackers-use-little-stickers-to-trick-tesla-autopilot-into-the-wrong-lane/#6f55a2e07c18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers create a "fake lane" to take a Tesla in the wrong lane and, potentially, oncoming traffic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA unveils Mars human colony habitat finalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6874927/Is-human-colonies-look-like-Mars-NASA-announces-finalists-habitat-competition.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA has announced three finalists in an ongoing design competition tasking engineers to dream up sustainable dwellings that can be 3-D printed on Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems cast aspersions on motivations...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/04/can-joe-biden-survive-another-me-too-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another woman has come forward with an uncomfortable Biden story. Democrats are circling the wagons, for now, but Biden’s incipient campaign has been rattled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check-in gets creepy as facial recognition hits hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90327875/facial-recognition-is-coming-to-hotels-to-make-check-in-easier-and-much-creepier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hotel of the future is a little unsettling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: DISQUALIFY? NOT AT ALL!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/436829-pelosi-accusations-against-biden-dont-disqualify-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) said Monday that a pair of allegations of inappropriate kissing and touching against former Vice President Joe Biden should “not at all” disqualify him from the 2020 race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latino outreach or GOOGLE Translate? Spanish sites bungled...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2019/2020-democrats-spanish-translation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crowded early field of presidential contenders wants to court Latino voters, an essential segment of the Democratic base, with Spanish-language campaign websites. But not all of them remembered to turn on spell check.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PISSED WHOOPI DEFENDS JOE...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/04/01/whoopi-goldberg-defends-biden-i-dont-want-joe-to-stop-kissing-and-smelling-womens-hair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday on ABC's "The View," co-hosts Whoopi Goldberg, Meghan McCain and Joy Behar defended former Vice President Joe Biden in the wake of former Nevada | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE A.I. Ethics Council Falling Apart After Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-01/google-s-brand-new-ai-ethics-council-is-already-falling-apart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg raises $7M in first quarter...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/436676-buttigieg-says-he-raised-7-million-in-first-quarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg, who has yet to officially announce his 2020 presidential campaign, said on Monday that he has raised more than $7 million in the first quarter of this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos as warring MPs reject EVERY option AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8768952/brexit-vote-live-theresa-may-soft-brexit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN’S squabbling MPs tonight plunged the country into further Brexit chaos by voting against every possible way forward – AGAIN. The House of Commons rejected four different Brexit …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead cows washing up on Canary Island beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/dead-cows-canary-islands-tenerife-video-spain-a8849566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT BREAKDOWN: NO, NO, NO, NO...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6872617/Mays-polarised-Cabinet-set-mass-walkout-Brexit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The customs union plan proposed by Ken Clarke was closest to victory - losing by just three votes 276 to 273. A second referendum got the most votes overall again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child video game addictions sending parents to couples counseling...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2019/03/31/unexplained-weight-loss-children-boston-nutritionist-makes-her-diagnosis-fortnite/eNMmGkK814IOsCwDDk2ZPN/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An obsession with the video game is sending kids to doctors and therapists, and their parents to marriage counselors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find 'fossil graveyard' linked asteroid that killed off dinosaurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/01/americas/asteroid-dinosaurs-graveyard-scn-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An international team of scientists has discovered a fossil graveyard containing what it describes as "extraordinary evidence" that an asteroid that hit the Earth 65 million years ago was responsible for the extinction of the dinosaurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W Europe tallest skyscraper set for home in town of 7,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/bestseller-tower-denmark-draws-comparisons-to-eye-of-sauron-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bestseller Tower will stretch 1,050 feet, which is almost as tall as the Salesforce Tower in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore mayor leave of absence as 'self-dealing' book scandal heats...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-pugh-developments-20190324-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Mayor Catherine Pugh will take a leave of absence, engulfed by a scandal over hundreds of thousands of dollars in payments for self-published “Healthy Holly” children’s books.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deputies rush into burning home to save pet boa constrictor...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/04/01/deputies-rescue-boa-constrictor-from-burning-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOURBONNAIS, Ill. — Two Kankakee County Sheriff's deputies made an unusual rescue last week. The deputies rushed into a house fire in Bourbonnais, and came out with the homeowner's pet boa constrictor. The snake was reunited with its owner outside. "Deputies Hayden and Zirkle ran into a smoke-filled residence to save this reptile earlier this morning (around 2 am). Willing to bet they never thought that task would be on their list of police officer responsibilities. Great job, fellas!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Most Stressed States...</title>
      <link>https://wallethub.com/edu/most-stressful-states/32218/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wallethub.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS: Black Voters Like Bernie Just Fine...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/black-voters-like-bernie-sanders-just-fine-they-just-might-like-other-candidates-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The narrative after the 2016 Democratic primary was that black voters overwhelmingly chose Hillary Clinton in part because they didn’t like or connect with Sen.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes: Constitution does not ensure 'painless' execution...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-supreme-court-execution-lethal-injection-20190401-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court's conservative majority rejected a Missouri inmate's claim that because of his rare medical condition, the state must find a different means to execute him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most red-light camera tickets go unpaid...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/community/fort-worth/article228546264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA halts F-35 shipments to Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-turkey-f35-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-sends-message-to-turkey-halts-f-35-equipment-shipments-sources-idUSKCN1RD316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has halted delivery of equipment related to the stealthy F-35 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALVE DAMAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6873761/Mick-Jagger-undergo-heart-surgery-week-replace-damaged-valve.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 75-year-old rock icon is set to have the operation in a New York City hospital this week, according to Drudge Report . Jagger was forced to postpone the nine-week ‘No Filter’ tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Zucker eyes run for NYC mayor...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/04/01/jeff-zucker-reportedly-wants-to-run-for-new-york-city-mayor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He reportedly plans to run in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president gives free passage to US...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/31/us-mexico-border-illegal-immigration-superhighway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone crossing the U.S.-Mexico border could end up stuck in longer lines as officers are pulled from the land ports of entry and deployed to help the Border Patrol transport, feed and see to the medical needs of the tens of thousands of people streaming illegally into the U.S. each week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blood everywhere' as mom tackles mountain lion biting 7-year-old... </title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/world/article228685779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NSA spies hacked BBC host, Al Jazeera chair for UAE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/usa-raven-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of former NSA cyber spies helped the United Arab Emirates break into the iPhones of at least 10 media figures, Reuters finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked protesters storm Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/769282/naked-protesters-parliament-brexit-news-house-of-commons-mps-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden spokesperson criticizes 'cottage industry of lies'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/436746-biden-spokesperson-criticizes-cottage-industry-of-lies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesperson for Joe Biden pushed back forcefully on Monday at a "cottage industry of lies" he said has formed about the former vice president supposedly crossing a line between affectionate or supportive behavior with women to something inappro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jagger is expected to make a full recovery and will be back on stage by summer, sources explain.</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-music-stones-jagger/mick-jagger-to-undergo-heart-valve-replacement-surgery-drudge-report-idUSKCN1RD2SC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rolling Stones frontman Mick Jagger is to undergo heart valve replacement su...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Millennials in Hoodies Spend $28 Million on Simpsons-Themed Art...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-01/millennials-in-hoodies-spend-28-million-on-simpsons-themed-art</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic priests burn Harry Potter books...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/catholic-priests-burn-harry-potter-books-poland-131950572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic priests in Poland burned books they say are sacrilegious this weekend, including tomes from British author J.K. Rowling's Harry Potter series of fantasy novels. "We obey the Word," priests said in a Facebook post showing photographs of the public book burning and quoting Biblical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Computer outages cause massive travel delays for five airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2019/04/01/southwest-american-delta-flights-grounded-monday-outage-aerodata/3329537002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airlines experienced temporary groundings due a problem with AeroData, a program that provides weight-and-balance information that is necessary to grant clearance for takeoff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie, Beto battle for younger voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.tribuneledgernews.com/extra/news/bernie-sanders-beto-o-rourke-battle-for-younger-voters/article_07622124-aff1-5d95-9658-507248009e13.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tribuneledgernews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Sen. Bernie Sanders and former Rep. Beto O'Rourke could hardly be more different, but UCLA senior Tim Hoffmann finds himself interested in both Democratic presidential candidates. He attended</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocker Mick Jagger is set to undergo heart valve replacement surgery in NYC this week, the DRUDGE REPORT can reveal... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/8767672/mick-jagger-heart-valve-replacement-surgery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICK Jagger is set to undergo heart valve replacement surgery this week after postponing The Rolling Stones’ US tour, according to a new US report. The Drudge Report claims the 75-year-old ro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aibo's dark side: Why Illinois bans SONY robot dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/what-sonys-robot-dog-teaches-us-about-biometric-data-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony doesn't sell Aibo in Illinois because of the state's Biometric Information Privacy Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi ARAMCO tops APPLE for world's most profitable company...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/01/saudi-aramco-made-111-billion-in-2018-topping-apple-as-the-worlds-most-profitable-company-by-far.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Aramco is by far the most profitable company in the world, according to financial data disclosed by the state-run oil giant in Saudi Arabia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak retail sales underscore slowing economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/01/retail-sales-february-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US retail sales slumped amid declining spending on building materials, electronics, and groceries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Home to Nearly 20% of World's Migrants... ...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/31/pew-research-u-s-home-to-nearly-20-of-worlds-migrant-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is home to nearly 20 percent of the globe's migrant population, the Pew Research Center finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Calls For Better Security at DODGERS Stadium After Fan Brutally Attacked In Parking Lot...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/31/dodger-stadium-parking-lot-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are still looking for a man who attacked 45-year-old Rafael Reyna in the Dodger Stadium parking lot, leaving him on life support with a fractured skull.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DEFENDS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2a11e7e88fb42738773321a1485d2c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former Vice President Joe Biden on Sunday defended his interactions with women, saying he doesn't believe he's ever acted inappropriately. But a Nevada politician's assertion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Options: Stick close to EU, crash out, think again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69f2a330e8c34d67b04617e1cbde23e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain is running out of time and options for Brexit. U.K. lawmakers have three times rejected the divorce deal struck between Prime Minister Theresa May's government and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHISTLEBLOWER:  Trump team overruled 25 security clearance denials...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1759ac2858ee4aafb041f91cbd6d86e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A career official in the White House security office says dozens of people in President Donald Trump's administration were granted security clearances despite "disqualifying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Count in USA This Year Already More Than All of 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-04-01/measles-count-in-us-this-year-already-more-than-all-of-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Magician David Blaine Under NYPD Investigation Over Sexual-Assault Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/david-blaine-under-nypd-investigation-over-sexual-assault-allegations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detectives with the Special Victims Unit took statements from two women in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON, PRIEBUS, HICKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6873081/Trump-jabs-Democrats-former-hero-Muellers-collusion-conclusion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats on a powerful House committee are moving to subpoena Special Counsel Robert Mueller's report and testimony from former Trump aides, including Hope Hicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Turkish political star pulls off Istanbul upset...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rising-turkish-political-star-pulls-off-istanbul-upset-142320496.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan's AKP party appeared so sure of winning Istanbul in Sunday's election that posters of its candidate thanking the city were plastered on walls early Monday. Instead, Ekrem Imamoglu, a soft-spoken opposition figure, appears to have pulled off a shock win</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
