<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Germany 'brutalized' as far-right crimes hit record levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/may/04/rightwing-extremism-germany-stability-interior-minister-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police recorded almost 24,000 far-right crimes last year – the highest level since records began</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDICIAL WATCH sues Secret Service for information on Biden dog biting...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/majorgate-watchdog-sues-secret-service-for-info-on-biden-dog-biting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an investigation fit for “McGruff the Crime Dog,” a fiscal watchdog group has sued for details on the two biting incidents by President Joe Biden’s dog Major.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Will They Split $146 Billion Fortune?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/05/bill-melinda-gates-divorce-fortune-foundation-split-agreement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The divorce petition described the marriage as “irretrievably broken.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India catastrophe worsens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-coronavirus-health-41a6a064b0d22b0ed4d2d1753e4ff31c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — COVID-19 infections and deaths are mounting with alarming speed in India with no end in sight to the crisis and a top expert warning that the coming weeks in the country of nearly 1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US trade deficit hits new record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/global-trade-business-03afb2924c164f98c9947ca5f700d6c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. trade deficit surged to a record $74.4 billion in March as an improving U...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XI CLAIMS 'HELMSMAN'</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/3/xi-jinping-adopts-mao-zedong-title-helmsman-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President and Communist Party General-Secretary Xi Jinping continues to consolidate power and has reached new status, adopting the title “helmsman,” a descriptor not used since Mao Zedong and denoting ultimate authority, according to U.S. intelligence officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grim warning could last until 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2819814/covid-mutant-india-brazil-pandemic-2024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID mutant variants spawning from out of control outbreaks like in India and Brazil mean “no one is safe” unless vaccine rollouts are widened, it has been warned. The People’s V…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wore BLM T-shirt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/photo-of-chauvin-juror-wearing-blm-t-shirt-at-march-raises-questions-of-impartiality-experts-say/ar-BB1gkrE1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The juror says he was at a Martin Luther King Jr. commemoration, not a George Floyd-related protest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 6G chip downloads entire film faster than blink of eye!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/new-6g-chip-could-download-24033680</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next generation chip is decades away from transmitting data more than 30 times faster than 5G internet – allowing hundreds of films to be downloaded in a second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEST SEEKS BROAD ALLIANCE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210504085907-w5ri6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-G7/FOREIGN (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-G7 mulls a message to China: the West ain't over just yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman, 77, hurled Whopper, racial slurs at BURGER KING worker...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/whopper-rage-arrest-284593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 4--A 77-year-old retiree who was upset about the thickness of the tomato on her Whopper allegedly threw the sandwich at a Burger King employee and then spewed racial slurs at the worker, accordin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenner brands self 'compassionate disrupter' in debut ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dqg8pmGDZ5Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paid for by Caitlyn Jenner for Governor 2021, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cox Hits Campaign Trail with 1,000-lb Bear!</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/news/california-connection/john-cox-campaign-to-launch-bus-tour-in-sacramento-featuring-1000-pound-bear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (KTXL) — John Cox is gearing up for another race against his former gubernatorial rival, Gavin Newsom, and this time the Republican candidate wants people to “meet the beas…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Rules...</title>
      <link>/https://www.wsj.com/articles/inside-facebook-jail-trump-the-secret-rules-that-put-users-in-the-doghouse-11620138445</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crist becomes first prominent Dem to challenge DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2021/05/04/floridas-crist-becomes-first-prominent-democrat-to-challenge-desantis-1380022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crist is scheduled to hold a kickoff event later Tuesday in his hometown of St. Petersburg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK, Trump at turning point in long, tortured relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facebook-and-Trump-are-at-a-turning-point-in-16150066.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Jan. 6, as an angry mob stormed the U.S. Capitol, President Donald Trump posted on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGECOIN New All Time High...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/05/04/dogecoin-blasts-through-50-cents-barrier-to-new-all-time-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cryptocurrency spiked more than a third Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss diplomat found dead after fall from high-rise in Tehran...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/swiss-embassy-employee-iran-dies-fall-high-rise-2021-05-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first secretary at the Swiss embassy in Tehran was found dead on Tuesday after falling from a high-rise building where she lived in the north of the city, a spokesman for emergency services was quoted as saying by Iranian news agencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER earned $3.5 billion on vaccine in first quarter...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/551651-pfizer-earned-35-billion-on-covid-vaccine-in-first-quarter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine earned the company $3.5 billion in the first three months of this year, representing nearly a quarter of its total revenue, the company announced ahead of its earnings call Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird photo of Carters with Bidens creates buzz...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/551633-weird-photo-of-carters-with-bidens-creates-major-online-buzz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A picture of what appears to be a pint-sized version of the Carters posing with the jumbo-sized Bidens is triggering a gigantic reaction online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradshaw Rips Rodgers: 'Him Being That Upset Shows How Weak He Is'...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/05/04/terry-bradshaw-aaron-rodgers-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Steelers Hall of Fame quarterback and NFL analyst didn't mince words when asked whether Rodgers has a right to be upset with the Packers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside America's Forced-Marriage Epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-america-sickening-forced-marriage-085914002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courtesy KnotstheFilm.comKnots: A Forced Marriage Story is driven by a noble aim: to give voice to the voiceless. Director Kate Ryan Brewer’s documentary (May 7, in theaters) concerns three women from different geographic, religious and social backgrounds who found themselves in comparable circumstances—namely, being bullied into matrimony with strangers by their parents and cultural leaders, with no way out. It’s a familiar tale of misogynistic coercion except that in this case, the disparate victims in question didn’t reside in the Middle East, India, or another foreign land where such practices are more common. On the contrary, they took place right here in the United States.That such rancid behavior still goes on in various parts of this country probably won’t come as an enormous shock to many, especially given the recent success of Netflix’s Unorthodox, which dramatized the based-on-real-events efforts of one Hasidic Jewish woman to flee her Orthodox Jewish community in Williamsburg, Brooklyn, and, with it, her arranged marriage. Nonetheless, Knots: A Forced Marriage Story shines a spotlight on what remains an intensely pressing issue, since today, only four states (Delaware, New Jersey, Minnesota, and Pennsylvania) limit marriages to individuals who are 18 and over, and 10 states have no minimum age limit at all for tying the knot. The result is a recurring paradigm in which women are susceptible to being trapped in permanent captivity, cut off from the larger world (and the legal rights that might empower them), and denied any recourse for escape. Is Rapper Blueface’s OnlyFans ‘Cult’ Exploiting Young Women?Knots: A Forced Marriage Story provides a comprehensive cross-section of religious victimization. Michigan’s Nina was raised in a strict community known as the Christian Patriarchy Movement that prized dowdy old-fashioned clothing and conservative ideas about gender roles, with men in charge of everything and women relegated to dutiful servants. Nina was married off at 18 to a random man hand-selected by her father, which was basically the same fate that befell California native Sara, whose Muslim father was part of an outfit known as the Group that saw fit to pair her with a 28-year-old stranger when she was only 15 years old. Fraidy, brought up in New Jersey’s Orthodox Jewish community, suffered similar hardship, compelled by her parents, her rabbis, and those in her insular enclave to marry a man whom she barely knew.While the particulars of their experiences were somewhat different—Nina was told that disobedience made her, for all intents and purposes, a “witch,” whereas Fraidy was simply conditioned and shamed into complying—Knots: A Forced Marriage Story makes clear that the basic mechanisms of subjugation were the same in all three cases. The common link binding this trio is that they all hailed from extremist religious environments. Yet puzzlingly, that facet goes largely unexplored here. To contextualize her first-hand narratives, director Brewer provides a cursory recap of 20th century American cultural attitudes toward child marriage, which goes some way toward illustrating how onerous laws about the practice first got on the books.However, not for a second does the filmmaker directly address the fact that her subjects were casualties of fanatical faiths that indoctrinated members about female subservience and then established women’s powerlessness through oppressive and domineering rules and demands.This is ignoring the elephant in the room, and it’s exacerbated by Knots: A Forced Marriage Story’s refusal to even verbally identify Sara as Muslim; a quick glimpse of Arabic writing is the only overt clue to her religious background. Such a willful lack of specificity abounds in Brewer’s documentary, which glosses over much-needed details at myriad turns. Whether refraining from referencing Nina, Sara, and Faidy’s husbands by name, or discussing the means of their eventual liberation in vague terms, the proceedings feel at odds with themselves, trying to intimately probe these horror stories while simultaneously maintaining a measure of arm’s-length detachment that—even if it’s designed to protect Nina, Sara, and Faidy in some way—proves frustrating.Sara and Nina, consequently, come across as sympathetic if largely unknown; there’s a nebulousness to their tales that stymies true engagement with their plights. Knots: A Forced Marriage Story does slightly better by Faidy, who openly recounts the abuse she endured from her husband, and the precise actions she took—involving fleeing in a car with her kids on the Sabbath (a big no-no), and later changing the locks on her home’s doors—to achieve the freedom she increasingly realized she needed. Alas, her account is also sometimes undercut by murkiness, such as her post-escape decision to found Unchained at Last, a nonprofit organization that aids women in situations similar to the one Faidy found herself in at a young age. Brewer depicts a few Unchained at Last press events, but largely fails to outline its origins or mission—an approach it also takes with the Tahirih Justice Center, which is never properly introduced even though its members speak on-camera at multiple points.Knots: A Forced Marriage Story is driven by virtuous intentions, and it lucidly explains how forced marriages are allowed to occur in the U.S. thanks to draconian (and inconsistent) state laws that first allow young girls to be married off—with parental consent—at early ages, and then deny them the adult right to get divorced (because technically, they’re still minors). Unfortunately, so much basic information is left out of the film that it comes across as a rough draft of a documentary. To compensate for that skimpiness, Brewer embellishes her action with cutaways to both painted illustrations that mirror Nina, Sara, and Faidy’s ordeals, and to the sight of an anguished woman dancing against a blank wall while bound up in red string—a visual evocation of forced marriage that’s awkward and unnecessary.Unlike Heidi Ewing and Rachel Grady’s One of Us, which immersed itself in the nightmare of trying to break free from the Orthodox Jewish community, Knots: A Forced Marriage Story casts a wider net and yet comes up with considerably less. It’s a timely documentary whose formal shortcomings prevent it from getting at the bigger picture.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food of future? EU nations put mealworms on menu...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-worms-science-business-oddities-c12bf770addd95eed248a0deee5e5d95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Dried yellow mealworms could soon be hitting supermarket shelves and restaurants across Europe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican No. 2 intervenes to shed light on Swiss Guard deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-62a88533d11a11bfa27ae453cdf49fff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican secretary of state has intervened personally to shed light on one of the most sensational Vatican scandals of recent times: The 1998 murder of the Swiss Guard commander and his wife, purportedly by a disgruntled younger Swiss Guardsman who then took his own life...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far-right crime rises; Police arrest alleged neo-Nazi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-migration-arrests-race-and-ethnicity-immigration-5b12a6caed6103ba3976c6349fe6dee6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Berlin police arrested a 53-year-old German man on suspicion of sending dozens of threatening letters to politicians, lawyers and journalists that were signed with the acronym of a neo-Nazi group, as officials warned Tuesday that statistics show a disturbing rise in far-right extremism across Germany...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wine that went to space for sale with $1 million price tag...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-wine-lifestyle-oddities-08574dbc6e456db731abb9cacb6b61be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The wine is out of this world. The price is appropriately stratospheric. Christie’s said Tuesday it is selling a bottle of French wine that spent more than a year in orbit aboard the International Space Station...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney served more MAGA hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/liz-cheney-slams-trumps-attempt-to-brand-2020-election-the-big-lie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Rep. Liz Cheney, R-Wyo., pushed back again at former President Trump's repeated claim that the 2020 election was stolen. But her critics in the GOP are making it clear that the third-ranking House Republican may pay a high price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARRIAGE DELETE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9540931/Bill-Gates-hires-Warren-Buffetts-right-hand-man-lawyer-split-wife-Melinda.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles T Munger, a 97-year-old father-of-eight and the vice president of Warren Buffett's holding company Berkshire Hathaway, is listed as an attorney representing Gates in his divorce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wake of COVID, employers step up automation and use of robots...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wake-covid-employers-step-automation-110042845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic brought home to managers the high cost of unforeseen disruptions, so they are turning more to automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones show CA great white sharks closer -- and more common -- than think...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drones-show-californias-great-white-120031464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Malibu photographer captures images of great white sharks along the Southern California coast, many just feet from unknowing swimmers and surfers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen acquitted in trial over breaking hate speech laws...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210504104945-tt7f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-POLITICS/LEPEN (URGENT):French politician Marine Le Pen acquitted in trial over breaking hate speech laws</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of World's Top Restaurants Goes Meat-Free...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/one-of-nycs-and-the-worlds-top-restaurants-to-go-totally-meat-free/3032729/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven Madison Park is considered one of the finest restaurants in both New York City and the world — and starting next month, it will also be completely meatless and almost entirely vegan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In TX, frustration with high-speed chases, increased crime exacerbates political tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-South-Texas-frustration-with-high-speed-16149553.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COTULLA, Texas - About 300 yards from the LaSalle County courthouse on Main Street is a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capri, Italy's blue island, emerges from the pandemic blues...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210504072302-30iww</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-CAPRI (PIX, TV):Capri, Italy's blue island, emerges from the pandemic blues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolls can be hunted down and rooted out. So why aren't social media giants doing it?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/blog/2021/may/03/solution-to-online-abuse-lies-with-social-media-firms-and-its-not-rocket-science</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four-day sporting boycott reinforces the need for Twitter, Facebook and others to get rid of those dishing out abuse – now</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sperminator' has fathered 78 children...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9540829/Sperminator-fathered-78-children-says-just-say-no.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York college professor, Ari Nagel, 44, has fathered 78 children and currently has 13 women pregnant. He appeared on The Dr. Oz Show and told how he just 'can't say no.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life and Death on Lighthouse of Mediterranean...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/04/life-and-death-on-the-lighthouse-of-the-mediterranean/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you stand at the summit at night, and you turn your flashlight off, all you can see are diamantine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jenner brands self 'compassionate disrupter' in 1st ad seeking Newsom recall...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/caitlyn-jenner-brands-compassionate-disrupter-1st-ad-seeking/story?id=77473990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner has branded herself a "compassionate disrupter" fighting against "elitist politicians" in a three-minute video launching her bid for California governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill key figure in push to pitch White House plans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/551605-jill-biden-a-key-figure-in-push-to-pitch-white-house-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is deploying first lady Jill Biden across the country as a key asset to build support for President Biden’s proposed investments in infrastructure, child care and education.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu has hours to form new govt and no clear path to do it... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-s-netanyahu-has-hours-to-form-a-new-government-and-no-clear-path-to-do-it/ar-BB1gliMU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the prime minister can’t woo reluctant partners by midnight, his rivals get a chance to try.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Mexico City metro overpass collapses onto road; At least 23 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-city-mexico-faee07a9250174f58365db6c915476d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — An elevated section of the Mexico City metro collapsed and sent a subway car plunging toward a busy boulevard late Monday, killing at least 23 people and injuring about 70, city officials said. Rescuers searched a car left dangling from the overpass for hours for anyone who might be trapped. Those efforts were suspended early Tuesday, however, because of safety concerns for those working near the precariously dangling car. A crane was brought in to help shore it up. “We don’t know if they are alive,” Mayor Claudia Sheinbaum said of the people possibly trapped inside the car following one of the deadliest accidents in the city’s subway system, which is among the busiest in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet adoptions still strong as cats, dogs melt stress...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210503220542-97fmr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-PETS (TV, PIX):U.S. pet adoptions still strong as cats, dogs melt stress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico apologizes to indigenous Maya for centuries of abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-world-news-ap-top-news-latin-america-north-america-1e4d21e35f1d35d434b6bd5ccf9145b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico on Monday marked the anniversary of a 1901 battle that ended one of the last Indigenous rebellions in North America, by issuing an apology for centuries of brutal exploitation and discrimination. Monday's ceremony was held in the hamlet of Tihosuco in the Mayan township of Felipe Carrillo Puerto, the headquarters of the rebellion. It comes amid broader commemorations of the 500th anniversary of the 1519-1521 Spanish Conquest of Mexico, and 200 years of Mexico's 1821 independence from Spain. “For centuries, these people have suffered exploitation and abuse,” said Interior Secretary Olga Sánchez Cordero. “Today we recognize something which we have denied for a long time, the wrongs and injustices committed against the Mayan people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former circus elephants begin to arrive at Florida sanctuary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/florida-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-4cb473fcd5cc4d066abee8dfbb5a9c42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YULEE, Fla. (AP) — Former circus elephants are starting to arrive at a new wildlife sanctuary in north Florida. The White Oak Conservation Center announced Monday that a dozen female Asian elephants have already arrived at the Yulee refuge, located north of Jacksonville. Up to 20 more elephants are expected once more areas are completed at the planned 2,500-acre (1,010-hectare) space. The pachyderms are coming from the Center for Elephant Conservation in Polk County. Most of the animals previously traveled with the Ringling Bros. and Barnum &amp;amp; Bailey Circus until they were retired in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security Sees Slowdown in Retiree Rolls Amid Covid Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/social-security-sees-slowdown-in-retiree-rolls-amid-covid-deaths/ar-BB1gjRgR?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rate of growth in retired Americans who collect Social Security has slowed down sharply, and the drop may be due in part to the disproportionate number of deaths from Covid-19 among the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Tensions Spill Over as Europe Moves Toward Biden's Side...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-tensions-spill-over-europe-230112672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A major investment deal reached in December between the European Union and China — after seven years of painful negotiations — may end up being the high-water mark for ties that are quickly deteriorating again.Since then, the EU’s executive branch and Germany have each formulated legislation that would make life harder for Chinese entities to invest, while joining the U.S. in swapping tit-for-tat sanctions with Beijing. Italy’s government has turned from an enthusiastic backer of President Xi Jinping’s Belt and Road Initiative to blocking planned acquisitions by Chinese companies. And in France, China’s ambassador didn’t even show up when summoned in March, citing “agenda reasons.”Taken together, the moves signal a hardening of the European stance on Beijing. And the biggest shift could be yet to come, with polls showing the German Greens party on course for a significant role in government after September’s election, raising the prospect of a more China-skeptic chill from Europe’s biggest economy.Chancellor Angela Merkel spoke with Chinese Premier Li Keqiang last week, and the two pledged closer cooperation on Covid-19 vaccines and fighting climate change. Yet the talk in Berlin is that optimism around the relationship is gone, and one Chinese official characterized ties with Europe as on a downward trajectory. Whether the Greens come to power in Germany or not, EU-China relations are at a critical juncture, said the official, asking not to be identified speaking about strategic matters.The multiple signs of strain suggest Europe’s biggest players are moving closer to the views of President Joe Biden’s administration in its standoff with China. As Secretary of State Antony Blinken holds talks in London this week with his Group of Seven counterparts, a Europe more aligned with Washington would signal some repair to the damage done to transatlantic ties by the Trump administration, with implications for trade, tariffs and access to technology.“There’s been a mood shift,” said Joerg Wuttke, Beijing-based president of the European Chamber of Commerce in China and a board member of the Mercator Institute of China Studies in Berlin, one of the entities sanctioned by China in March.He cited the “perfect storm” of China’s assertiveness toward Taiwan, its move to impose political control over Hong Kong, and international sanctions over alleged human-rights abuses in the Xinjiang region, overlaid by the fact that China hasn’t followed through on its promises of opening up economically.To be sure, Europe is not uniform in its outlook, with EU members such as Hungary still eager to engage with China. And whereas Biden has said that China can expect “extreme competition” from the U.S. while it also seeks to work with it on global issues such as climate change, Europe faces more of a dilemma as its strives to forge its own path.Economic ties remain paramount since China is the EU’s biggest trading partner, with a total volume of some $686 billion in 2020 outstripping U.S.-China trade of $572 billion. Yet now even the Netherlands, which is among China’s top 10 trading partners, is growing more wary, protecting its high-tech companies from takeover and enacting a dedicated China strategy. According to the Chinese official, the U.S. has forced the EU to take sides.The sentiment was different just four months ago when Merkel helped steer the bloc to seal the EU-China Comprehensive Agreement on Investment, which Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said was “an important landmark in our relationship with China.” Still subject to ratification by the European Parliament, it would provide improved access to the Chinese market for European investors while committing China to “ambitious principles” including on forced labor.Yet by late March, the EU had joined the U.S., Canada and the U.K. in imposing sanctions on China over alleged mistreatment of Muslim Uyghurs in Xinjiang, including forcing them to work. Beijing responded with its own sanctions, while a public backlash saw Swedish fashion retailer Hennes &amp; Mauritz AB subject to an unofficial boycott.“The EU has recently added more agenda items tied with human rights, ideology, democracy,” said Zhang Monan, senior fellow at the U.S.-Europe Institute at the China Center for International Economic Exchanges in Beijing. “This kind of opposition and friction is expected to continue.” She added that the EU is expected to formulate policy independently since it doesn’t want to be subordinate to the U.S.The European Commission is now proposing rules to levy fines and block deals targeted at foreign state-owned companies, while Merkel’s cabinet approved additional powers over foreign investment last week aimed at high-tech sectors including artificial intelligence and quantum computing. Both measures would hinder China.China had hoped to separate economic issues from political issues and to bind Europe with its huge consumer market, but that’s increasingly impossible now, said an academic at a Chinese government-affiliated think tank. Ratification of the CAI has become more challenging, said the person, who is not authorized to comment publicly due to rules on speaking to foreign media.Signs of the tensions were on show during the virtual talks led by Merkel and Li. In a departure from usual practice, the opening remarks were not live-streamed and there was no concluding press conference. A transcript posted several hours later by Germany showed that Merkel addressed human rights, saying there were differences of opinion particularly over Hong Kong.“China and Germany have different views on some issues, this is a fact,” Li told Merkel, urging Germany not interfere in internal matters, according to a statement from the Chinese Foreign Ministry. Li said he hoped they could “eliminate unnecessary distractions” to maintain “healthy and stable” bilateral ties.The shift in Europe has not been lost on Washington. A Biden administration official said there’s been a sea change in European thinking, coming on board with the U.S. stance on China. There’s been real evolution in Germany too, the official said.That change could get more pronounced if the Greens convert their opinion poll lead into a strong showing or even victory in September, with Merkel set to step aside. While all coalitions involve policy trade-offs, the Greens have a harsher line on China than the current administration, calling for an end to Beijing’s “blatant human-rights violations” and for closer European and transatlantic coordination on China.A coalition with the conservatives as suggested by polls would see continuity in German foreign policy but with “different nuances” on China, said Jana Puglierin, head of the Berlin office of the European Council on Foreign Relations. “The Greens would clearly advocate a less mercantilist policy than we have seen under Merkel,” she said.For now, Europe is determined to avoid decoupling entirely with China. French President Emmanuel Macron and Merkel held a joint call with Xi in April, and a report in China’s Global Times on April 28 referred to “optimism and confidence in China-Germany cooperation” despite the risk of “some impacts” after the election. Merkel’s would-be successors and business leaders know the “great potential” of Europe working with China, “so they need to ensure healthy ties won’t be interrupted by any third party or internal conservative forces.”Still, Wuttke at the European trade chamber said that China underestimates the concern over human rights in Germany. Especially after the departure of Merkel, who favored engagement with China, that’s likely to “translate into possibly more assertive policy in Berlin,” he said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentina Wealth Tax Fought by Millionaires Raises $2.4 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/argentina-wealth-tax-fought-millionaires-184426549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Discover what’s driving the global economy and what it means for policy makers, businesses, investors and you with The New Economy Daily. Sign up hereArgentina’s government raised 74% of the amount it had targeted from a controversial new tax on the country’s wealthiest citizens.The government collected 223 billion pesos ($2.4 billion), according to an official statement. Early data show that 10,000 people with assets over 200 million pesos paid the new tax, which goes as high as 5.25% of their assets’ value.Initiatives to tax the rich have gained support throughout Latin America as the region struggles to recover from its worst recession in two centuries. In Argentina, millionaires resisted paying the levy right up to the government’s April 16 deadline. In early April, only 2% of taxpayers subject to the levy had paid it, according to a preliminary report.The amount raised is higher than expected, equivalent to 0.5% of GDP, and will improve the government’s tax collection numbers for April, according to Buenos Aires-based consulting firm Alberdi Partners. The government expects to use the proceeds for pandemic spending including health policies, small business subsidies, scholarships and housing projects.The government announced it had raised 817.9 billion pesos in taxes in April, up 105.2% from the previous year.Local PushbackThe tax was met with local backlash by those affected. About 220 taxpayers, including the family of late soccer legend Diego Maradona and soccer star Carlos Tevez, took legal steps against the government to avoid paying, claiming it’s confiscatory or unconstitutional. If the justice system rules against the tax, that would create a setback for the government, according to Marcos Buscaglia, founder at Alberdi.“It’s likely that part of the proceeds will have to be returned to taxpayers if the judiciary rules against the tax,” Buscaglia said.Some tax lawyers say that the real number of millionaires in Argentina is much higher than the figure from the AFIP, the tax authority, meaning that thousands may be holding onto their cash.“The data released by the taxman is an attempt to show that lots of people are paying, but it does not reflect reality,” Ivan Sasovsky, CEO of tax law firm Sasovsky &amp; Asociados said.Even though the deadline has passed, wealthy Argentines are expected to continue filing challenges to the tax. Gaston Miani, a partner and head of tax and customs law at Tavarone, Rovelli, Salim &amp; Miani, said he expected at least 5,000 suits to be filed during the month of May as lawyers and clients gather proof to show the tax’s harmful effects.AFIP wasn’t immediately available for comment.(Updates with April tax collection figure in fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  More people diagnosed with covid in past 2 weeks than in first 6 months of pandemic!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/more-people-diagnosed-covid-19-194000156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Americans continue to take steps toward normal life, India and several other countries are dealing with an explosion of new coronavirus infections likely to delay the world’s recovery from the deadly crisis, health authorities warned Monday. The number of COVID-19 cases reported around the world in the last two weeks was higher than the total of confirmed infections in the first six months ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police crowd-control chemical weapons pose mystery for medical researchers...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/operation-safety-net-s-crowd-control-chemical-weapons-pose-a-mystery-for-medical-researchers/600052860/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tear gas, banned in war, was used against Brooklyn Center, Mpls. protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA saw fewest April tornadoes in over 20 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/us-saw-fewest-april-tornadoes-since-2000/ar-BB1gjYnA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary count of only 73 tornadoes occurred, less than half the normal number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico apologizes to indigenous Maya for centuries of abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mexico-marks-end-of-last-indigenous-revolt-with-apology/ar-BB1gka4C?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico on Monday marked the anniversary of a 1901 battle that ended one of the last Indigenous rebellions in North America, by issuing an apology for centuries of brutal exploitation and discrimination. Monday's ceremony was held in the hamlet of Tihosuco in the Mayan township of Felipe Carrillo Puerto, the headquarters of the rebellion. It comes amid broader commemorations of the 500th anniversary of the 1519-1521 Spanish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  How did THREE major news organizations get a story about Rudy wrong?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-three-major-news-organizations-all-got-a-story-about-rudy-giuliani-wrong/ar-BB1gkiZd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post, the New York Times and NBC News all reported the same mistaken assertion about an FBI briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising tsunami triggers may lurk off California coast, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/surprising-tsunami-triggers-may-lurk-203944642.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earthquakes along strike-slip faults can cause tsunamis in certain contexts, a new model shows — and such faults exist right off parts of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mindblowing: Advances in brain tech spur push for 'neuro-rights'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mindblowing-advances-brain-tech-spur-124851281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As sci-fi thriller "Inception" topped box offices across the world, audiences were delighted and appalled by its futuristic story of a criminal gang invading people's dreams to steal valuable data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia walks back 'racist' India ban after backlash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-walks-back-racist-india-012908334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's prime minister fended off accusations of racism and having blood on his hands Tuesday, as he retreated from a threat to jail Australians trying to escape Covid-wracked India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin juror who attended pre-trial rally may jeopardize guilty verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/3/brandon-mitchell-derek-chauvin-juror-who-attended-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A juror in the Derek Chauvin trial may have jeopardized the guilty verdict by attending a rally last year and wearing a “Get Your Knee Off Our Necks/BLM” T-shirt, raising questions about whether he told the truth during jury selection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Armed man shot by officers outside CIA headquarters...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2818404/fbi-shoots-suspect-gates-cia-headquarters-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN FBI agent reportedly shot and wounded a suspect after a “suspicious vehicle” drove up to CIA headquarters in Virginia. Both the CIA and FBI responded after an unauthorized person tri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA REPORTS ZERO COVID DEATHS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9536541/Los-Angeles-County-reports-NO-new-COVID-19-deaths-time-410-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA County marked its first day without a fatality from COVID-19 in more than a year on Sunday. Officials say the figure may be adjusted as there are often reporting delays on weekends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gates divorce could break Bezos record!</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/22418060/bill-melinda-gates-divorce-foundation-charity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire couple is getting a divorce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder stopped by armed guards from driving through CIA main entrance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/intruder-stopped-armed-guards-driving-through-cia-main-entrance-n1266169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One official said no shots had been fired, and another source said CIA security officers were negotiating with the person, who remained inside a vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Set to Authorize PFIZER for 12-15 Year Olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/fda-set-to-approve-pfizer-covid-vaccine-for-12-15-year-olds-by-next-week-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news comes weeks after Pfizer announced results from its trial in adolescents showed the vaccine is at least as effective in that age group as it is in adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Set to Authorize PFIZER for 12-15 Year Olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/03/health/pfizer-covid-vaccine-teens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move opens up the U.S. vaccination campaign to millions more Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC SUBWAYS TO RUN 24/7...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-york-to-begin-major-reopening-on-may-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York State will begin a major reopening on May 19 and around-the-clock subway service will resume May 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL GATES DIVORCING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/03/bill-gates-and-melinda-gates-are-splitting-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill and Melinda Gates got married in 1994 and are involved with one of the world's top nonprofits, with over $51 billion in assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey Evades Another Sex Assault Case As Judge Demands Acusser Reveal Identity...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/kevin-spacey-sexual-assault-suit-ruling-anthony-rapp-anonymous-uk-prosecutors-1234749010/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Crown Prosecution Service in the UK may be weighing whether to bring sexual assault charges against Kevin Spacey in half a dozen cases. However, on this side of the Atlantic, the much-accused O…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Now Has Players Born After Brady's Career Began...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/03/nfl-now-has-players-who-were-born-after-tom-bradys-career-began/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a new way to show just how long Tom Brady's been playing in the NFL, and it came over the weekend when players who were born after Brady's career began were drafted into the NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 People Involved in Tokyo Olympic Torch Relay Infected...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6045498/olympic-torch-relay-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the latest sign of trouble for Japan as it both struggles with a spike in infections and prepares for the Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Damage Reported as Tornadoes Tear Across South... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/damage-reported-as-tornadoes-tear-across-the-south/ar-BB1gjLTw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cities across the South were reeling from damage caused by tornadoes that touched down late Sunday night and Monday morning. There were no immediate reports of injuries, but damage — including downed trees and utility poles, and buildings whose roofs were torn off — was reported in parts of Mississippi, Kentucky and Georgia, and tornado warnings were issued for parts of Tennessee and South Carolina. In northeast Mississippi, the National Weather...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychedelic Drug Passes Big Test for PTSD Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/03/a-psychedelic-drug-passes-big-test-for-ptsd-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an important step toward medical approval, MDMA, the illegal drug popularly known as Ecstasy or Molly, was shown to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notable rappers pay bond for murder suspect, others...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/atlanta-news/notable-atlanta-rappers-pay-bond-for-fulton-murder-suspect-others/SWFTV6U2YVCPZPUWNXMCUSHOQY/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta rap stars recently spent about $300,000 bonding six people out of the over-crowded Fulton County Jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assisted Living Center Shut Down For Allegedly Neglecting, Humiliating, Punishing Residents...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/30/like-prison-assisted-living-facility-shut-down-neglecting-humiliating-punishing-residents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the order suspending the facility's license, residents were underfed and underweight. Inspectors even saw residents licking dirty plates and going through the trash for scraps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Whoever came up with that s*** needs to be fired'...</title>
      <link>https://nba.nbcsports.com/2021/05/03/lebron-on-play-in-games-whoever-came-up-with-that-s-needs-to-be-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nba.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After their loss to the Raptors Sunday, the Lakers are in danger of falling into the play-in games, and now LeBron is speaking out against the play-in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Mocked for embarrassing flop...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/05/03/lebron-james-flop-video-raptors-lakers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James flopped in embarrassing fashion Sunday against the Raptors. Watch a video of him flopping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COKE Rethinking Woke?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/04/is-coke-rethinking-woke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the soft-drink giant is pulling back from its left-wing posturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Era of Big Government Here...</title>
      <link>https://thedispatch.com/p/conservatism-hits-rock-bottom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s agenda is a reflection of how little regard both parties have for conservatism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii-Bound Flight Lands With Additional Passenger After Mid-Flight Birth...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/03/hawaii-bound-flight-lands-with-additional-passenger-after-mid-flight-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Raymond Mounga didn't waste much time making his first visit to the Hawaii Islands. It came just hours after his birth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
