<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Crises keep travel-hungry Biden close to White House...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/594971-crises-keep-travel-hungry-biden-close-to-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden wants to leave Washington more and promote his policies directly to the American people, but outside circumstances — such as the resurgence of the pandemic or the threat of war between Russia and Ukraine — keep pulling him back to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris: 'Real possibility of war in Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/video/ukraine-crisis-we-are-talking-about-the-real-possibility-of-war-in-europe-says-kamala-harris-12547076</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Vice President Kamala Harris told reporters in Munich that "we are talking about the real possibility of war in Europe".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeii: Rebirth of Italy dead city that nearly died again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-technology-business-italy-europe-fd7499b179f254ad442c468fdc94394b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POMPEII, Italy (AP) — In a few horrible hours, Pompeii was turned from a vibrant city into an ash-embalmed wasteland, smothered by a furious volcanic eruption in A.D. 79. Then in this century, the excavated Roman city appeared alarmingly close to a second death, assailed by decades of neglect, mismanagement and scant systematic maintenance of the heavily visited ruins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebron says final NBA season will be played with son...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/20/sport/lebron-james-cavaliers-lakers-bronny-nba-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebron James said there are no certainties over his future in the NBA, though he is certain about one thing -- he'd like to play his final season alongside his son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Infected in England won't need to self-isolate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boris-johnson-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-pandemics-2a717a276b483431f30622f7fa7602cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — People with COVID-19 won't be legally required to self-isolate in England starting in the coming week, the U.K. government has announced, as part of a plan for “living with COVID” that is also likely to see testing for the coronavirus scaled back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASSIVE NUKE DRILLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-oversee-nuclear-drills-ukraine-crisis-mounts-2022-02-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's strategic nuclear forces held exercises overseen by President Vladimir Putin on Saturday, and Washington accused Russian troops massed near Ukraine's border of advancing and being "poised to strike".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minister dives for cover as frontline heats up...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220219-ukraine-minister-dives-for-cover-as-frontline-heats-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bent in a semi-crouch Ukraine's interior minister ran back from an exposed frontline position, as mortar shells crashed in the fields around him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New study finds Ivermectin ineffective...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-697027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients administered Ivermectin had a "notably higher" incidence of adverse events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once-taboo ketamine booms for at-home mental care...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220220-once-taboo-ketamine-booms-for-us-at-home-mental-care</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are paying to get a star of the psychedelic medicine movement –- ketamine -– shipped to them for at-home mental health treatments that are being called both a breakthrough and a gamble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truckers Arrested at Gunpoint as Police Advance Against Ottawa Protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-canada-ontario-arrests-9125c793e27a3fce81d3baaa953d6f2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA, Ontario (AP) — Hundreds of police in riot gear swept through Canada’s capital Saturday, retaking control of the streets around the Parliament buildings and appearing to end the siege of Ottawa after three weeks of protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison pumps $15M into super PAC aligned with Tim Scott...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/19/larry-ellison-pumps-15m-into-super-pac-aligned-with-tim-scott-00010377</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The donation brings the Oracle chair's giving to the group, Opportunity Matters Fund, to $25 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th Shot In Fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/19/health/fourth-covid-19-vaccine-dose-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world approaches the second anniversary of the declaration of the Covid-19 pandemic by the World Health Organization, on March 11, more nations are rolling out -- or are discussing the possibility of -- fourth doses of coronavirus vaccine for their most vulnerable. In the United States, leading public health officials say they are "very carefully" monitoring if or when fourth doses might be needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once savvy, NBC Olympics deal shakier after Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-figure-skating-eileen-gu-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-7f07dd3e1a4b299d9171e5ee2b53410a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — There were many reasons to think NBC made a savvy business deal in 2014 when it locked up the American media rights to the Olympics through 2032 for $7.75 billion. As the Beijing winter games come to a close, it's harder to see them now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock gas, grocery price hikes spur states to pursue tax relief...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/personal_finance/shock-gas-grocery-price-hikes-spur-states-to-pursue-tax-relief/article_eaec6926-843c-5661-a2c5-1881320075c4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapidly climbing inflation in the U.S. is accelerating calls from governors and state leaders to provide immediate tax relief to cash-strapped residents facing higher prices on everyday products such as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN WANTS KYIV</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10530371/Kamala-Harris-warns-Putin-face-swift-severe-consequences-invades-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris publicly warned Vladimir Putin of the 'swift and severe' consequences he will face if Russia invades Ukraine and branded him a 'lying propagandist'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another effort to tax 'extreme wealth' in California launched in Legislature...</title>
      <link>https://denvergazette.com/ap/business/another-effort-to-tax-extreme-wealth-in-california-is-launched-in-legislature/article_0eda17d2-c734-552e-b0f0-b487b57c546b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denvergazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — A handful of Democrats in the state Legislature are pushing again for a tax on "extreme wealth" in California, a move they say could bring the state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week of legal setbacks for Trump in DC, New York...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ivanka-trump-business-lawsuits-donald-trump-mar-a-lago-69af082122a3b6461b07a4a2e1b87450</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former President Donald Trump faced one legal setback after another this week as a judge ruled he must sit for a deposition in New York to answer questions about his business practices, his accounting firm declared his financial statements unreliable, another judge rejected his efforts to dismiss conspiracy lawsuits and the National Archives confirmed that he took classified information to Florida as he left White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Financial Support in Spotlight as Duke Settles Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/queen-e2-80-99s-financial-support-in-spotlight-as-prince-andrew-settles-sex-abuse-case/ar-AAU3Jt7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Chancellor rejects calls to sanction now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/19/ukraine-olaf-scholz-says-west-must-keep-russia-guessing-on-sanctions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The Russian government cannot be really sure exactly what we'll do," German Chancellor Olaf Scholz tells CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With sound therapy, healing is earshot away...</title>
      <link>https://www.newindianexpress.com/lifestyle/health/2022/feb/16/with-sound-therapy-healing-is-an-earshot-away-2419908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newindianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walking on dry leaves, the sound of rainfall, wind cruising through leaves on a quiet summer day — the rhythmic sounds of nature are undeniably soothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Vanlife Is Really Like...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vanlife-really-043128628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyI was raised on road trips, with the best always being weeks-long trekking across the American West. They usually ended with all of our neatly packed stuff spread out in every corner of my parents’ van. A bed that my dad constructed in the back for my brother and me to hang out on became a sea of scattered books, discarded ripe socks, and torn candy wrappers covered in melted chocolate.Ah, good times.On Instagram, road-trip life has taken the more trendy form of vanlife culture—adventurous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truckers Arrested at Gunpoint as Police Advance Against Ottawa Protest...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/19/truckers-arrested-at-gunpoint-as-police-advance-against-ottawa-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OTTAWA — Canadian police officers advanced on demonstrators at gunpoint, smashing truck windows and arresting protesters in front of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE OFFICIALS ATTACKED</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/02/19/ukrainian-military-officials-shelled-during-tour-of-separatist-conflict-zone-16135062/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They were forced to flee to a bomb shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Behind QANON? Linguistic Detectives Find Fingerprints...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/19/who-is-behind-qanon-linguistic-detectives-find-fingerprints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Open your eyes,” the online post began, claiming, “Many in our govt worship Satan.” That warning, published on a freewheeling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's go Brandon: Driver caught in unwinnable culture war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-donald-trump-nascar-daytona-beach-26de0b361560dd8858f26ae1ec18a120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAYTONA BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Brandon Brown drove into NASCAR’s home track and immediately saw his name everywhere. Banners. Yard signs. T-shirts. Flags waving atop row after row of flashy RVs. “Hopefully, they know it’s for me and they’re pulling for me,” Brown said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Race Is on to Save Burning Cargo Ship Full of Luxury Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/news/44351/salvage-crews-racing-to-save-burning-cargo-ship-full-of-porsches-bentleys-and-vws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 4,000 vehicles are on board as the fire consumes the ship—and the electric cars it’s carrying pose an extra danger for firefighters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 43%  Turn To Food For Pick-Me-Up When Feeling Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/gut-brain-mental-health-connection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey reveals that although 90% of adults think about their gut health to some degree, 40% weren't aware that the gut is linked to mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise boosts brain -- and mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Exercise-boosts-the-brain-and-mental-health-16931993.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mental health disorders such as depression and anxiety aren't easy to treat. Medications...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hit 30-year high for House retirements...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/594797-democrats-hit-30-year-high-for-house-retirements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of House Democrats not seeking reelection this year has hit a 30-year high — a bleak benchmark reflecting frustrations with the gridlock on Capitol Hill, the toxicity of relations between the parties and the challenges facing Democrats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once He Kept Russia at Distance. Now He Is Docile Putin Satrap...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/19/once-he-kept-russia-at-a-distance-now-he-is-a-docile-putin-satrap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINSK, Belarus — In a winter military coat trimmed with fur, Aleksandr G. Lukashenko stepped out of his white presidential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris, Blinken navigate Munich as Europe holds breath...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/harris-blinken-navigate-munich-security-conference-as-europe-holds-its-breath/ar-AAU4iXj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Comes Too Soon for Some...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/unmasking-comes-too-soon-for-some-still-wary-of-covid-s-wiles/ar-AAU29RJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO raises readiness level...</title>
      <link>https://www.anews.com.tr/world/2022/02/18/nato-raises-readiness-level-for-tens-of-thousands-of-troops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.anews.com.tr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO raises readiness level for tens of thousands of troops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol girding for potential trucker protest at State of Union...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2022/02/18/capitol-potential-freedom-convoy-protest-state-of-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truck drivers protesting vaccine requirements have snarled the Canadian capital of Ottawa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind China's Olympics, saga of chained woman unfolds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-chained-woman-eileen-gu-fa30a04d74a91f5beff9983442353971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — The post, on China's Weibo social platform, resembled many others posted by official media during these Olympics — an ode to freestyle skier Eileen Gu, known to Chinese as Gu Ailing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rebels mobilize troops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-europe-moscow-donetsk-4596388ab5f4ee61cee94f4f9a993915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Separatist leaders in eastern Ukraine ordered a full military mobilization Saturday amid a spike of violence in the war-torn region and fears in the West that Russia might use the strife as a pretext for an invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan woman turning 100 adds another tattoo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-lifestyle-michigan-st-joseph-tattoos-08f26bfdc667ed4a0625f901e3324d51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. JOSEPH, Mich. (AP) — A Michigan woman soon will celebrate a milestone birthday. How old? Look at her decorative upper arm. Gloria Weberg has “NY NY 1922” tattooed on her left arm, the year and place of her birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican army sends anti-mine squads to cartel turf war zone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-mexico-caribbean-improvised-explosives-drug-cartels-a49c12cd0539940f165659f211316c42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NARANJO DE CHILA, Mexico (AP) — Special squads of Mexican army troops equipped with metal detectors and bomb suits have deployed to the western state of Michoacan, where warring drug cartels have planted land mines or improvised explosive devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could artificial intelligence wipe out humanity?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4718282/artificial-intelligence-wipe-out-humanity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANY fear that artificial intelligence will be the end of humankind – here’s the truth according to experts. By now, most people around the world use some sort of AI-utilizing device that is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men at risk of weak sperm depending on which city live in?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4719840/men-risk-weak-sperm-pollution-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEN are at risk of weaker sperm depending on where they live, a study warns. The fertility of thousands, potentially millions of men, may be experiencing fertility decline without realising. Resear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Officials Warn of Imminent Russian Invasion of Ukraine With Tanks, Fighter Jets, Cyber...</title>
      <link>https://wsj.com/articles/ukraine-troops-told-to-exercise-restraint-to-avoid-provoking-russian-invasion-11645185631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prospects for averting war appear dim, officials said, even as the Biden administration is working to arrange new talks with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROKU's Record Stock Collapse Expands List of Fallen Pandemic Favorites...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roku-record-collapse-expands-list-145434032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Roku Inc. shares tumbled Friday, with the streaming-video platform company the latest example of a one-time pandemic favorite to see a precipitous decline as investors look past an era where consumers are no longer stuck indoors.Most Read from BloombergMorgan Stanley Relationships on Wall Street Snared in ProbeLavrov Agrees to Meet Blinken, U.S. Says: Ukraine UpdateIndia Protests Against Singapore PM’s Comments on LawmakersThe Housing Boom’s Mortgage Rate Threat Is Worse Than It S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 'Convinced'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-europe-russia-moscow-c2e55b8b2b061b58e2b140d2a6dc1d57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — U.S. President Joe Biden said Friday that he is “convinced” Russian President Vladimir Putin has decided to invade Ukraine, including an assault on the capital, as tensions spiked along the country's militarized line with attacks that the West said could be “false-flag” operations meant to establish a pretext for invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Archives: Classified items taken to Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-mar-a-lago-national-security-9c1f6dca7e3e8073ee029604c8253a5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Classified information was found in the 15 boxes of White House records that were stored at former President Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago residence, the National Archives and Records Administration said Friday in a letter that confirmed the matter has been sent to the Justice Department.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
