<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ramen shop vandalized with racist messages after owner speaks out against TX  reopening...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/local/2021/03/14/ramen-shop-vandalized-with-racist-messages-after-owner-speaks-out-against-texas-reopening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ramen noodle shop on the Northwest Side was vandalized just days after its owner spoke against Governor Greg Abbott’s decision to end the state’s mask mandate in an interview with CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will return on NEWS UK TV?</title>
      <link>https://inews.co.uk/news/media/rupert-murdoch-opinionated-news-uk-tv-channel-launch-ofcom-approval-779383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;inews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murdoch's nightly TV channel is in a race to air with GB News led by Andrew Neil — both believe they can take viewers from the BBC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota legislators want to rename highway after Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-legislators-want-to-rename-highway-after-prince/600034298/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow the StarTribune for the news, photos and videos from the Twin Cities and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild horse on southern Outer Banks dies at 25, North Carolina group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/life/wildlife-nature/vp-nw-shackleford-wild-horse-dies-outer-banks-20210314-5b3f3itkxjgadcjk7wt2jmmk6i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mare, nicknamed Dusty, died at age 25, the Foundation for Shackleford Horses wrote Saturday on Facebook. She was “one of the grand dames of the wild herd” that lives on the Shackleford Banks, which is the southernmost island on Cape Lookout National Seashore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN:  'I've got the whole world talking about me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/14/business/media/piers-morgan-walks-off-british-tv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British TV executives see opportunity — and money to be made — in bringing American cable-style clashes to their screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI 'MAYFLOWER' CREW-LESS CROSSING OF ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9337833/AI-Mayflower-attempt-cross-Atlantic-autonomously-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayflower Autonomous Ship (MAS) will depart from Plymouth, England on April 19. MAS will take the same route as the original Mayflower ship to Massachusetts back in 1620.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Pelosi stop short of calling for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Nancy-Pelosi-says-Cuomo-should-look-inside-his-16024879.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., said Sunday that New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo should...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel unveils guided mortar system for future urban warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/elbit-defense-ministry-reveal-laser-gps-guided-mortar-munition-661959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ‘networked precision fire system’ that engages targets accurately and prevents collateral damage • 10-year development concludes with successful trials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THAT'S ALL FOLKS:  Brees Retires After Decorated 20-Year Career...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/drew-brees-retires-after-20-seasons-in-nfl-this-is-not-goodbye-rather-a-new-beginning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 42-year-old steps down with a future Hall of Fame induction surely on the horizon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl over members getting vaccinated riles Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/congress-schedule-vaccinations-2f2a1aca-2204-4f54-a396-c9939fe28c05.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting in waves, meant to ensure social distancing inside the House chamber, is slowing a full legislative schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STELTER DECLARES TUCKER NEW TRUMP!</title>
      <link>https://view.newsletters.cnn.com/messages/1615765705261dcd683330d7f/raw?utm_term=1615765705261dcd683330d7f&amp;utm_source=cnn_Reliable+Sources+-+March+14+2021&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=1615765705262&amp;bt_ee=cBw8YNDDQqbyphBdXSISnyzW7QZ7Kd4Z2m0CtlaJ4xs%3D&amp;bt_ts=1615765705262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;view.newsletters.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNHOLY:  Kirk Franklin's son releases explicit audio of gospel singer's threats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kirk-franklin-son-releases-explicit-012513775.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kirk Franklin's son Kerrion Franklin released audio on social media which allegedly revealed threatening words from father to son. This is why I'm done. No father should speak to their children like this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY forecast to steal NETFLIX's crown as world's biggest streaming firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/mar/14/disney-forecast-to-steal-netflix-crown-as-worlds-biggest-streaming-firm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On back of Disney+ service launched in 2019, company predicted to be No 1 by 2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE SPEECH? NC high court backs judge who made blogger write essay and delete negative comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/article249893653.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can a judge in North Carolina order you to post pro-government content on social media and then take down any critical comments? The answer seems to be yes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says vaccine hesitancy among Republicans poses big risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/fauci-says-vaccine-hesitancy-among-republicans-poses-a-big-risk/ar-BB1ezov8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Reluctance among Republicans to receiving a vaccine is one of the biggest risks to coronavirus control efforts, President Joe Biden’s chief medical adviser said, although one GOP governor said attitudes may change. “I just don’t get it,” Anthony Fauci, said on NBC’s “Meet the Press” when asked about polling showing many Republicans, especially men, don’t want a vaccine. He noted the various diseases that have been stamped out with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italians Rush to Get Haircuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/italians-flock-to-parks-rush-to-get-haircut-before-new-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italians Flock to Parks, Rush to Get Haircut Before New Lockdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel's party profiting from face mask deals?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-party-braces-drubbing-german-091716254.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel's conservative party suffered heavy losses in two key regional elections Sunday, early estimates showed, as voters vented anger over pandemic setbacks and a face-mask procurement scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE SUN major test for nonprofit news model...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/baltimore-sun-deal-sets-major-034959225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of staff cuts, shrinking budgets and declining readership, the Baltimore Sun finally has some good news to report about itself: a deal for a new nonprofit group to take over, and potentially revive the struggling newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investment Manias Abound...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/13/from-crypto-art-to-trading-cards-investment-manias-abound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — This past week, a trading card featuring the quarterback Tom Brady sold for a record $1.3 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Covid wave sweeps across EU and forces new restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/14/third-covid-wave-sweeps-across-eu-and-forces-new-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New variants blamed as Italy, France, Germany and Poland see infection rates surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montecito home broken into TWICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2509342/meghan-markle-prince-harry-montecito-home-intruder-twice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry’s California mansion was invaded twice by an intruder over Christmas, reports claim. Cops arrested the alleged trespasser after he was caught for the second tim…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSOPRAH hit with complaint for 'deliberate distortion and doctoring' interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2505058/oprah-meghan-harry-misleading-newspaper-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry’s interview with Oprah “misled viewers”, according to a newspaper group. Associated Newspapers, which owns the Daily Mail and MailOnline, has compla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress and high anxiety caused by phone use revealed in new study...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/stress-and-anxiety-caused-by-phone-use-revealed-in-new-tel-aviv-uni-study-661981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An excessive amount of time spent on social media is also likely to cause teeth-grinding and facial muscle pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can predict whether someone will die if infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/ai-can-predict-whether-someone-will-die-if-infected-with-covid-19-study-661857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An artificial intelligence algorithm developed by the University of Copenhagen managed to predict, with up to 90% accuracy whether someone undiagnosed is at risk of dying from COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald and Melania trolled over private jet downgrade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/donald-melania-trump-trolled-ex-23714235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former US president, 74, and his First Lady were targeted by social media users after being seen boarding a "regular", ageing plane from Trump Tower in New York to Florida on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi boss's former mansion to be turned into a haven for hippies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/evil-sex-mad-nazi-bosss-23717168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former mansion of Nazi propaganda minister Joseph Goebbels, close to Berlin, where he bedded aspiring female German film star, is to be turned "alternative living" centre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN'S SILENCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-cuomo-scandal-sexual-harassment-e728c796-94f6-471a-b417-121355c56d7d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike many of his other Democratic critics, Cuomo respects and likes Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO's Year of Empty Offices, Island Getaways and Strife...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/goldman-ceo-empty-offices-island-120000417.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Goldman Sachs Gulfstream descended into the sun-kissed Bahamas that Friday with a familiar passenger aboard: David Solomon.It was the final days of February, and Solomon, the chief executive officer of Goldman Sachs Group Inc., had booked another weekend getaway on the new jet -- his seventh in as many weeks.Behind him in New York, the bank’s workforce was left buzzing over his public bashing of work from home, an arrangement he labeled an “aberration” that needs to be fixed. The remarks capped months of grousing to lieutenants about his perception that for some employees it’s more home than work.In many ways, it should all be sunny at Goldman Sachs: Its Wall Street businesses are booming, the stock is on a tear and the bank finally put to rest the 1MDB scandal that dogged it for six years. Instead, the firm is riveted by palace intrigue over executive defections, bristling over the use of company jets for personal trips and debating how flexible the workplace will be after Covid subsides.The line through it all is Solomon, who took the helm over two years ago, casting himself as a more modern CEO. He loosened Goldman’s dress code and conspicuously kept his kitesurfing, disc-jockey pastimes.Yet there’s also the ethos of a corporate boss whose career took root at Michael Milken’s ruthlessly commercial 1980s Drexel operation and later Bear Stearns. Solomon is known for working relentlessly and for an abrasive style, which has rubbed raw at times during the virus outbreak as he’s shown annoyance with a scattered workforce.“David has been running the firm from our headquarters at 200 West Street since the pandemic hit hard last March, and the results speak for themselves,” said Goldman spokesperson Jake Siewert.The pandemic unleashed a windfall for Wall Street and the firm in particular as clients rushed to make bets or raise capital to weather the crisis. Goldman’s revenue jumped 22% last year to $44.6 billion, the highest in more than a decade. The stock doubled in the past 12 months, trailing only Morgan Stanley in its peer group.When the board ended CEO Lloyd Blankfein’s 12-year reign in 2018, it swapped the former trader’s affability for the investment banker’s more exacting approach. Solomon winnowed the bank’s fleet of prestigious partners and took a hard line on costs.“This is the first management team in a long time that actually pays attention to the shareholder,” said John Thornton, a former Goldman president.But a year into the pandemic, Goldman Sachs’s bulging profits are accompanied by signs of internal strain. Three business heads -- investment-bank boss Gregg Lemkau, consumer-bank chief Omer Ismail and asset-management head Eric Lane -- made surprise departures in recent months. The trio were part of the management team that Solomon had shaped.Those defections and others are now stirring debate at Goldman over the CEO’s leadership and whether something fundamental is changing at the elite firm long renowned for discretion and loyalty.Interviews with two dozen current and former senior executives found veterans are frustrated. As subordinates contend with the rigors of pandemic life, the boss has risked appearing out of touch -- pressing deputies to join him at the office but also toggling to the Hamptons and taking the company-owned aircraft for frequent getaways.Goldman GulfstreamsAn executive jet might seem normal on Wall Street, but Goldman long made a point of not buying one, worried the extravagance could invite public scorn.Then came a 2019 incident in which Goldman power broker John Rogers and a notably miffed Solomon logged in to an internal Goldman meeting from an Anchorage hotel, according to a participant. Their NetJets plane had broken down on an Alaskan pit-stop en route to meetings in Asia and they were left waiting for a replacement ride. It wasn’t the first time Solomon was stranded because of problems with NetJets, a fractional-ownership travel venture owned by Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway.Goldman got its own Gulfstreams in August, with aviation’s equivalent of vanity plates. The customized tail numbers, featuring the letters WS, are an ode to Wall Street and the firm’s West Street home.The planes have been used for business, such as scouting office locations in Florida and Texas. They’ve also served as pandemic vacation ferries, making almost a dozen getaways -- mostly to the Bahamas, but also locales in the Caribbean and Montana.“It certainly looks terrible,” said Nell Minow, who advises institutional investors on corporate governance issues as vice chair at ValueEdge Advisors. “There is a Marie Antoinette aspect to it.”Goldman policy is to limit personal use of aircraft and require reimbursement, according to a filing. The board of a publicly traded company shouldn’t let the CEO use its resources for personal benefit, Minow said. Bill George, a former Goldman Sachs board member, disagrees.“Bravo if he’s going off to the Bahamas for the weekend,” George said in an interview from St. Thomas. “I am from the work-hard, play-hard culture. I bet you dollars to doughnuts, he’s working the phones and talking to clients while in the Bahamas.”Behind the scenes, the use of the jets has been a source of consternation within the firm’s upper rungs.Rogers, the bank’s chief of staff, has expressed concern that their purchase could sully Goldman’s reputation, people familiar with the matter said. There’s also been hand-wringing in what’s known as Goldman’s executive office about their personal use. Eileen Dillon and Beverly O’Toole, two executives in that department, participated in discussions on policies for the planes, mapping out a detailed reimbursement plan to stave off any criticism.“When he’s away for a weekend, David continues to work, pays for his travel, follows Covid protocols and is back in the office first thing on a Monday morning,” said Siewert, the company spokesperson.Hamptons EncounterFew things annoyed Solomon more last year than an encounter with a junior employee in the Hamptons. The Goldman Sachs boss has told lieutenants how the underling walked up at a restaurant, introduced himself and pointed to associates with him -- in the middle of a workday.The tale has become the CEO’s go-to anecdote when he vents about his mostly-empty offices: proof that remote work has run amok.Some who’ve heard the story note the apparent disconnect. The boss is perturbed by bumping into staff while he himself was spending extended summer weekends in the Hamptons at a luxe seaside rental. Solomon’s time there even made national news after he deejayed a concert where attendees flouted social-distancing guidelines, leaving New York state officials fuming.As early as July, Solomon sought to make a big push to bring back more people to offices but relented after executives around him intervened. In private conversations, Solomon bemoaned that it was politically incorrect to say people need to return to work. He groused about a drop in innovation and the decay of social connections because of the damage done from working at home.George, who spent 16 years on Goldman’s board, said it’s ultimately up to the CEO to decide how things should be run. “He feels strongly about being in-person,” he said of his chats with Solomon. “Goldman has that big, beautiful office in the lower west side, and I know he would like to see it buzzing.”Solomon made that known at a Feb. 24 conference. “This is not ideal for us and it’s not a new normal,” he said. “It’s an aberration that we are going to correct as quickly as possible.”Soon after the remarks, a former senior Goldman executive’s phone began ringing. His longtime colleagues at the bank were looking for a confidant to vent their own frustrations over Solomon’s tone.The Goldman HaloSolomon is a rare executive atop Goldman who already had a thriving career before he made his way to the Wall Street giant in 1999. Unlike predecessors, he’s less attached to the Goldman halo and has spent his time running the once-famed partnership more like a regular corporation -- less fraternal and more commercial.But that can also weaken loyalty. Goldman bankers always have attractive job prospects elsewhere, and opportunities are particularly numerous now.When Solomon rose to the top, he quickly made a flurry of leadership shuffles, leaving only one major division head at the time, Ashok Varadhan, in the same post now. Then a few months ago, even members of the senior management team that Solomon built began leaving.Lemkau stunned Wall Street late last year by jumping to Michael Dell’s investment firm. Ismail and a deputy left to help Walmart Inc. build a financial venture.When Lane agreed to join Tiger Global Management, he informed Solomon of his plan to go, and the two got into an argument. Once things cooled off, Solomon tried to persuade Lane over dinner to stay. Lane declined.It isn’t just veterans -- even people who made partner in recent years have departed for other jobs. Examples from the class that ascended in 2019 include Earl Hunt, David Stark and Rana Yared.“In the old days, people would have gasped: ‘Wait, wait, wait a minute, you just won the lottery, you were made a general partner at the firm, and now you are leaving?’” said Janet Hanson, who formed a prominent Goldman alumni network and has been associated with the investment bank for over four decades. “The status of being a partner at the firm is not what it used to be, and I think David Solomon is OK with that.”Pink SandsSolomon’s blunt style irks colleagues. He’s known to make haranguing phone calls to senior executives when he’s upset over missed business or management moves. Some say the calls sting more than those of his predecessor, Blankfein, who wrapped criticisms in quips. Executives also perceive that Solomon doesn’t like to be challenged publicly, one management committee member said, and some have turned to Chief Financial Officer Stephen Scherr, seen as a unifying figure, as their bridge to communicate with the top brass.If executives can’t handle candor, “it’s a litmus test of their own character, not a failure of David’s,” said Jeff Sonnenfeld, a professor at Yale School of Management who’s followed Goldman for years. “It’s not intended to be cruel.”More recently, Solomon’s chief of staff, Ida Hoghooghi, resigned as a managing director, ending more than 16 years at the firm. The post directly under Solomon is prestigious, but one that colleagues have taken to calling the hardest job at the bank. She declined to comment.Despite rankles, griping and defections, the bottom line at Goldman looks good.Net income rose 12% to $9.5 billion last year, despite billions in penalties for the 1MDB bribery probes. That helped send Goldman’s market capitalization soaring to $126 billion -- up 43% since Solomon took over.More than 70% of analysts covering the stock recommend investors buy it -- the strongest endorsement in 10 years. When Solomon announced full-year results in January, some of those analysts were particularly impressed with the restraint he showed in managing expenses, keeping a lid on employee compensation after the banner year.Just days before disclosing the numbers, Solomon set out for the first of his spree of weekly getaways. On a Thursday morning, the CEO stepped on to the company’s G-VI on its way to the Caribbean. He celebrated his 59th birthday at an exclusive enclave, surrounded by family, associates and the Barbuda oceanfront’s blush-pink sands.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Anti-mask airline passenger charged after urinating in cabin...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/03/12/mask-denver-urinating-alaska-airlines-seattle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Colorado man accused of disrupting an Alaska Airlines flight from Seattle to Denver by refusing to wear a mask and then standing up and urinating in the cabin faces a federal charge of interfering with a flight crew and attendants that carries a maximum term of 20 years in prison and a possible $250,000 fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year later, treatment better but doctors 'still flying blind'
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/health/2021/03/14/covid-treatments-have-improved-but-more-rigorous-study-trials-needed/4433230001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Care has improved, but in the last 12 months it's been largely trial and error. That's led to missed opportunities to ease suffering, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Strip sees big crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/las-vegas-strip-sees-big-crowds-as-capacity-limits-set-to-ease-2303342/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowds flooded the Strip on Saturday, just two days before casino capacity restrictions increase to 50 percent from 35 percent on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems: No cooperation with Republicans who questioned election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-democrats-draw-line-no-bipartisan-cooperation-republicans-who-questioned-n1261015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the Jan. 6 riot, some Democrats say they simply can't work with anyone who voted against certifying the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus tolls similar despite governors' contrasting actions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/public-health-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-ron-desantis-889df3826d4da96447b329f524c33047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a year after California Gov. Gavin Newsom ordered the nation’s first statewide shutdown because of the coronavirus, masks remain mandated, indoor dining and other activities are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris may face new lockdown as ICUs fill up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-pakistan-islamabad-coronavirus-pandemic-europe-48d675ad33ab33fff3c78fe74e36dfcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — Officials say the Paris region may be headed toward a new lockdown as new variants of the virus fill up intensive care units and limited vaccine supplies drag down inoculation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump was supposed to be political Godzilla in exile. Instead, he's adrift...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/14/trump-post-presidency-475733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even allies say the president is lacking an apparatus and direction as he sorts out just what he wants to do in his post-presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Markle preparing bid to be America's first woman President?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9359141/Is-Meghan-Markle-preparing-bid-Americas-woman-President.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One senior Labour figure claimed that Meghan Markle, 39, was networking among senior Democrats with a view to building a campaign and fundraising teams for a tilt at the US Presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Hagler dead at 66; Was 'in ICU fighting effects of vaccine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/boxing/article-9359529/Undisputed-middleweight-champion-Marvelous-Marvin-Hagler-passes-away-unexpectedly-aged-66.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boxing was in mourning on Saturday night after the shock early death of one its all-time greats, Marvin Hagler, at just 66. Hagler was floored officially only once in his incredible brutal career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Woody Allen's Close Friendship With Jeffrey Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-woody-allen-close-friendship-090038127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyOver the past several weeks, audiences have been watching—and endlessly debating—Allen v. Farrow, the eye-opening HBO docuseries examining Dylan Farrow’s allegation that on Aug. 4, 1992, her adoptive father, Woody Allen, took a 7-year-old Dylan up to the attic of their Connecticut country home and molested her.The film, whose fourth and final chapter airs Sunday, March 14, provides testimony from numerous members of the Farrow-Previn clan, including Dylan, her brother Ronan, and their mother Mia; eyewitness accounts from family friends, neighbors, and hired help; interviews with state and city officials in New York and Connecticut; never-before-heard recordings of phone calls between Woody and Mia; and unearthed documents from the New York and Connecticut investigations into Dylan’s welfare. (Allen and Soon-Yi, who declined to participate in the series, released a written statement through Allen’s sister calling it “a hatchet job riddled with falsehoods” and the abuse claim “categorically false.”)Kirby Dick and Amy Ziering, the filmmaking team behind Allen v. Farrow, feel that the Annie Hall filmmaker, whose behavior toward Dylan was deemed “grossly inappropriate” by a judge in the child-custody trial he lost, shouldn’t merely hide behind a prepared statement. “If you had nothing to hide, and you were really being falsely maligned, wouldn’t you want to speak to journalists?” Ziering told The Daily Beast. “What are you afraid of?”‘Allen v. Farrow’ Filmmakers Call Out Woody Allen: ‘What Are You Afraid Of?’ One thing Woody Allen is not afraid of is defending powerful men who have been credibly accused of sexual misconduct. He’s served as one of Roman Polanski’s most vocal defenders, saying the fugitive filmmaker is “a nice person” who’s “paid his dues” for raping a 13-year-old girl and then fleeing the country, and in the immediate wake of the sexual assault allegations against Harvey Weinstein, accused the movie mogul’s victims of conducting “a witch hunt” against him, before walking it back.And then there’s his friendship with Jeffrey Epstein.It’s not clear when Allen and Epstein first crossed paths, though the two were longtime friends and neighbors on Manhattan’s Upper East Side for years. The director and his wife, Soon-Yi Previn, have been photographed a few times leaving the financier’s townhouse—including in September 2013, five years after Epstein pleaded guilty to child prostitution charges, when a Page Six headline declared: “Woody Allen pals around with child-sex creep.”Epstein “was hugging him and talking close to his ear,” and “had his arm on Woody’s shoulder,” one witness told the tabloid, adding that the pals appeared to enjoy a stroll down Madison Avenue before arriving at Epstein’s seven-story mansion.Diplomat Terje Rød-Larsen joined this walk, along with his friend, filmmaker Håkon Gundersen, who told the Norwegian newspaper DN last October: “I heard that Epstein knew Woody Allen and several other famous film producers. With my background, I thought it was very interesting.”When Allen arrived, Epstein allegedly told Gundersen, “Here you will meet someone else who is also very interested in film.” Gundersen said they all visited Central Park for about two hours that day before heading back to Epstein’s home. (Woody Allen and Soon-Yi did not respond to multiple requests for comment for this story.)Woody Allen spotted chumming up with convicted child-sex creep Jeffrey Epstein http://t.co/ziZl1wkhaP— Page Six (@PageSix) September 24, 2013 Around the same time, Epstein hosted another dinner at his New York home, where he introduced Allen to a connection at MIT. Joi Ito, former director of the MIT Media Lab, “met other influential individuals at meetings with Epstein, including Woody Allen, a senior executive at the Hyatt Corporation, and a former prime minister of Israel,” according to a report commissioned by the school on its ties to Epstein.MIT staff even raised the possibility that Epstein would bring Allen to campus during his October 2013 visit. “Ito expressed concern that inviting Epstein and Woody Allen to campus could create a public relations headache for MIT,” the report states. Apparently citing the Page Six story, Ito tried to dissuade Epstein from bringing Allen. “Since you two were just in the news recently, I wonder if that might be bad,” Ito emailed the financier.REVEALED: We Found Billionaire Pedophile Jeffrey Epstein’s Secret CharityYet Allen apparently had no qualms about consorting with a convicted sex offender who served jail time in 2008 and 2009 for soliciting an underage girl, and appeared to stay close to him until his death. In New York, Epstein was registered as a Level 3 offender, meaning he was a threat to public safety and at high risk for committing similar crimes again.The duo also reportedly had another mutual friend: Allen’s former teenage mistress, model Christina Engelhardt, who was 16 when she began dating the director in 1976. Their secret relationship lasted eight years, according to The Hollywood Reporter. Engelhardt tells The Daily Beast that she worked as a personal assistant for Epstein in the early 1980s, back when he was “only a millionaire” and “wasn’t there yet” when it came to sex-trafficking underage girls. She says she told Epstein that she’d dated Allen, but that the two New Yorkers weren’t friendly yet. Christina Engelhardt Amy Graves/Getty “Nothing surprises me with either one of those men,” Engelhardt offers. “I still am shocked that these very talented people choose these sadistic paths that bring them down. There’s nothing good about it.”Working for Epstein eventually became toxic, and Engelhardt decided to flee to Italy to serve as an assistant (and muse) to director Federico Fellini, whom she says was a lovely man. As for her time with Allen and Epstein, Engelhardt says, “I escaped one monster and ran away from the other.”“Woody is a bad guy,” she adds. “And the documentary really helped open my eyes to just how bad.”In December 2010, Allen attended a lavish dinner at Epstein’s residence toasting Britain’s Prince Andrew, who faces abuse accusations himself from Virginia Roberts Giuffre, an alleged victim of Epstein’s. Other celebrity guests at the soiree included TV journalists Katie Couric, Charlie Rose, and George Stephanopoulos, publicist Peggy Siegal, and comedian Chelsea Handler.Back then, Daily Mail columnist Richard Kay reported that “Andrew was in [a] jolly mood... ­especially when other guests, including Hollywood star Woody Allen, asked him for an invite to” the upcoming nuptials of Prince William and Kate Middleton.Handler recently spoke up about the event, which she described as “weird,” claiming she tagged along with Couric and was seated next to Allen and Soon-Yi. “When we got there I was like, what is this gathering?” Handler recently said on Rob Lowe’s podcast. “We had dinner and it was so awkward and so weird. I was like, what are we doing here? And then I asked Woody Allen how he and Soon-Yi met and that was when I left.”“I really was curious!” Handler added. “I had forgotten for a moment… but as it came out of my mouth, I knew that it was too late.” Allen, however, was apparently amused. “And he loved it, and Soon-Yi, I don’t think she heard it…”Epstein reportedly decorated his New York home with photos of himself and famous friends, including Allen, former President Clinton, and Mohammed bin Salman, the crown prince of Saudi Arabia who ordered the assassination of journalist Jamal Khashoggi.Following Epstein’s suicide whilst awaiting trial on charges of sex-trafficking minors, New York Times scribe James B. Stewart detailed visiting Epstein’s Manhattan mansion in August 2018, and spotting the snapshots with Allen and Clinton. “Displaying photos of celebrities who had been caught up in sex scandals of their own also struck me as odd,” Stewart wrote, adding that Epstein called him a week later and invited him to a Saturday dinner with Allen. The reporter declined.“The overriding impression I took away from our roughly 90-minute conversation was that Mr. Epstein knew an astonishing number of rich, famous and powerful people, and had photos to prove it,” Stewart continued. “He also claimed to know a great deal about these people, some of it potentially damaging or embarrassing, including details about their supposed sexual proclivities and recreational drug use.” Ghislaine Maxwell, Jeffrey Epstein, and Michael Bolton Davidoff Studios Photography Allen wasn't Epstein's only Hollywood connection. The financier was friendly with disgraced film mogul Harvey Weinstein, who allegedly tried to attack a woman in Epstein’s orbit. His rolodex included a host of other celebrities including media investor Ron Burkle and actors like Kevin Spacey, Alec Baldwin, Elizabeth Hurley, and Minnie Driver.As The Daily Beast previously reported, Epstein and Allen also had mutual friends in Paris. Former French politician Jack Lang—who’s publicly defended Allen amid Dylan’s child sexual abuse allegations—claimed he met Epstein in 2012 at a party hosted by Princess Camilla of Bourbon Two Sicilies. The socialite threw the party in Allen’s honor.One victim of Epstein even mentioned meeting Allen in a lawsuit she filed against the financier’s estate. The woman, referred to as Priscilla Doe, says she was a 20-year-old dancer in New York when Epstein began abusing her in 2006 until 2012—including when he was on “work release” at the Palm Beach County lockup.“On one occasion, Jeffrey Epstein forced [Priscilla Doe] to serve hors d’oeuvres at Epstein’s private party with Woody Allen,” Doe’s lawsuit states. “This server’s role was forced upon [her] in order to demean her, frighten her, and impress upon her the need for her to conceal the commercial sex trafficking enterprise he was running.”Asked about Doe’s complaint, her lawyer Brad Edwards said, “Woody was a very close friend of Epstein’s. They hung out quite frequently. I cannot comment beyond that.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call me? US-Turkey reset faces hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-turkey-recep-tayyip-erdogan-russia-d122c8e2c8e547fa998698f03b0bcef6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has toned down his anti-Western and anti-US rhetoric in an apparent effort to reset the rocky relationship with his NATO allies, but so...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom created 'deepfake' videos to force rivals off daughter's cheerleading squad...</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/news/2021/03/pa-woman-created-deepfake-videos-to-force-rivals-off-daughters-cheerleading-squad-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman is also accused of telling the teenagers "to kill themselves," according to the Philadelphia Inquirer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli anti-vaxxers submit ethics complaint to ICC...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/coronavirus-israeli-anti-vaxxers-submit-ethics-complaint-to-icj-report-661925</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the suit's claims of severe side effects and deaths allegedly related to the vaccine, only about 0.25% of Israelis who received the vaccine experienced any side effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic redefines 'public' access to govt meetings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/legislature-state-legislature-coronavirus-pandemic-4d6cf5821b44cb0ce70587305d5e1175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t long ago when a “public meeting” of the city council or state legislature meant the general public could show up to watch and, quite often, speak about proposals and perceived...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Markets be damned!': Fed standing firm on inflation fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210314-markets-be-damned-fed-standing-firm-on-inflation-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Markets be damned!': Fed standing firm on inflation fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breonna Taylor marches turn ugly: LAPD runs over 2 protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9360007/Breonna-Taylor-marches-turn-violent-LAPD-patrol-car-runs-two-protesters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters have clashed with cops and members of the public at marches across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel party braces for drubbing in German state polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210314-merkel-party-braces-for-drubbing-in-german-state-polls-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel party braces for drubbing in German state polls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffers stop showing up to work...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/13/cuomo-staffers-have-stopped-showing-up-to-work-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disillusioned staffers are abandoning embattled Gov. Cuomo, sources said. “I hear that most people aren’t even coming into work, and the offices at the Capitol are empty,” said on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police forcibly break up vigil for slain woman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/kidnapping-crime-arrests-london-europe-b25b5340d30221edf6656c6e2e3c8db0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — London’s police department is under scrutiny for the way officers handled some participants at an unofficial vigil Saturday night for a London woman whose death led to murder charges...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Andrew Cuomo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-rise-and-fall-of-andrew-cuomo/ar-BB1eyEW5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last spring, when the coronavirus outbreak was surging in New York, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo’s daily briefings became appointment television for many, as he authoritatively ticked through the latest statistics on infections, hospital beds and deaths. Behind the scenes, Mr. Cuomo was often obsessed with another set of numbers: his ratings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA deployed to help process children in border facilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fema-deployed-to-help-process-migrant-children-amid-overcrowding-in-border-facilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migrant children have reported sleeping in overcrowded conditions and having limited access to showers while in Border Patrol custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon leader says family donation to Biden was 'oversight'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-salt-lake-city-mitt-romney-e905c04166cff85343ddd7f744e30bbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A top leader with The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints said Friday political donations made in his name to several Democratic candidates, including President Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tried to quietly reach out to NKorea. It ignored him...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/13/politics/north-korea-biden-administration-outreach/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration launched a behind-the-scenes push last month to reach out to North Korea through multiple channels, a senior administration official has told CNN, but thus far Pyongyang has been unresponsive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC SPRINGS BACK TO LIFE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-new-york-city-birthdays-coronavirus-pandemic-881a5e0b7878d83275015ccd0f0b42b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Pamela Puchalski still remembers how frightening it felt when the coronavirus upended life in her New York City neighborhood last March. With terrifying swiftness came the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
