<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Two young women in Florida 'dressed up as grannies' to get jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/two-young-women-in-florida-dressed-up-as-grannies-to-get-vaccinated-health-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women, both younger than 45, wore bonnets, gloves and glasses to disguise themselves as older than 65, the age cut-off to be prioritized to get the coronavirus vaccine in Florida. They were in line for their second dose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TED ON THE ROPES...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/19/texas-storm-response-cruz-abbott-perry-470109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The swaggering, Texas brand of free-market governance that’s central to the state’s political identity is taking a beating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins have similar personality traits to humans, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/dolphins-have-similar-personality-traits-to-humans-study-finds/ar-BB1dPn0a </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Ditch 'America First' in Appeal for Global Partnership...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-to-ditch-e2-80-98america-first-e2-80-99-in-appeal-for-global-partnership/ar-BB1dPbxH?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will re-introduce himself and the U.S. to world leaders at a pair of international conferences on Friday, calling on industrialized democracies to partner in confronting the pandemic and climate change in a sharp departure from his predecessor’s foreign policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Everyone's Here': Microstate Unlikely Hub for YOUTUBE Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/everyone-s-here-microstate-is-unlikely-hub-for-youtube-stars/ar-BB1dPii8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tiny, isolated nation in the Pyrenees is turning into a creative hub for some of Spain’s biggest social media stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She used to be agent. Now one of Border Patrol's loudest critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/she-used-to-be-an-agent-now-she-is-one-of-border-patrols-loudest-critics/article_34d07bbf-a337-55e4-8122-e8078ad863b1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — The migrant girl was around 6 years old, dehydrated, fluish and despondent. Her head looked too big for her body — a sign of malnutrition — and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese fighters buzz Taiwan air zone as it appoints new defense minister...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210219100552-nm4rb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIWAN-CHINA/SECURITY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Chinese fighters buzz Taiwan's air zone as it appoints new defence minister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Nears $1 Trillion Value as Crypto Jump Tops Other Assets...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-nears-1-trillion-value-055731771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin is closing in on a market value of $1 trillion, a surge that’s helping cryptocurrency returns far outstrip the performance of more traditional assets like stocks and gold.The largest token has added more than $415 billion of value in 2021 to about $956 billion, data compiled by Bloomberg show. The Bloomberg Galaxy Crypto Index, which includes Bitcoin and four other coins, has more than doubled.Speculators, corporate treasurers and institutional investors are thought to have stoked Bitcoin’s volatile ascent. Crypto believers are dueling with skeptics for the dominant narrative around the climb: the former see an asset being embraced for its ability to hedge risks such as inflation, while the latter sense a precarious mania riding atop waves of monetary and fiscal stimulus.FOMO -- fear of missing out -- may be at play, said Shane Oliver, head of investment strategy with AMP Capital Investors Ltd. in Sydney, adding that “in times of easy money this gets magnified and it’s partly what’s driving the current interest.”Bitcoin traded at around $51,300 as of 1:30 p.m. on Friday in Hong Kong after quintupling in the past year. The crypto index’s performance towers over stocks, gold, commodities and bonds in 2021.This month, Tesla Inc. disclosed a $1.5 billion investment and MicroStrategy Inc. boosted a sale of convertible bonds to $900 million to buy even more of the token. That brought the coin closer to corporate America.“If companies’ fundamentals are going to become closely tied to movements in Bitcoin because they’ve suddenly become speculators on the side, we’re going to be in bubble territory before you know it,” said Craig Erlam, senior market analyst with Oanda Europe Ltd.Tesla Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk posted a somewhat cryptic tweet Friday that appeared in part to defend the company’s action, saying Bitcoin “is simply a less dumb form of liquidity than cash” while adding that the electric vehicle maker’s decision isn’t “directly reflective of my opinion.”Read More: Musk Defends Tesla Bitcoin Move, Says Token Less Dumb Than CashThe “long Bitcoin” trade is seen as among the most crowded in the world alongside technology exposure and dollar shorts, according to the February edition of Bank of America’s global fund manager survey.AMP’s Oliver said if Bitcoin “falls out of favor -- for example due to government regulation or investors just moving on to the next new thing -- then it could quickly plunge.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They left family poodle Snowflake behind!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9276959/Ted-Cruz-LEFT-family-poodle-named-Snowflake-fled-frigid-Texas-resort-Cancun.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snowflake, the Cruz family poodle, was left behind when they left Houston on Wednesday afternoon. The house, Ted Cruz said, was without heat and in the 30s. Cruz returned 24 hours later, chastened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICAL STORM WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Texas-Democrats-call-for-Cruz-to-resign-after-15960036.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Sen. Ted Cruz was met with a wave of fury Thursday on his return to Houston...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm confronts Biden with early leadership test...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Amid-winter-storm-Biden-seeks-to-showcase-15961142.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden has quickly approved states of emergency in Texas,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGRETS CANCUN TRIP...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9273075/Ted-Cruz-jets-Cancun-millions-Texas-remain-without-power.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ted Cruz on Thursday evening landed back in Houston, after a one-night trip to Cancun made while 3.4 million Texans were still without electricity. He insisted it was to drop off his daughters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancun jaunt 'so bizarre'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/02/18/ted-cruz-knows-politics-is-theater-thats-why-his-cancun-jaunt-is-so-bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People want to know their leaders care about them. A quick trip to Mexico communicates the opposite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More hospitals evacuate patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox4news.com/news/beleaguered-texas-hospitals-with-no-water-evacuate-patients-amid-winter-storm-power-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox4news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some hospitals in Texas were dealing with water shortages, loss of heat and have even been forced to evacuate patients following a deadly blast of winter weather this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC cidery unveils 'Cruz in Cancun' cocktail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/539442-dc-cidery-unveils-cruz-in-cancun-cocktail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Sen. Ted Cruz (R) already has a cocktail named after his widely criticized trip to Cancun amid the deadly winter weather crisis in his home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy crises stretches to sixth day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218045837-xi4om</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/TEXAS-ENERGY (PIX, GRAPHIC):Texas energy freeze stretches to sixth day, raises Mexico's ire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATER WOES GROW IN TEX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-power-outages-icy-weather-186cf801ead7e2d21f001a99b3aaa936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Power was restored to more homes and businesses Thursday in states hit by a deadly blast of winter that overwhelmed the electrical grid and left millions shivering in the cold...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaiian tourists bribed airport screener with $3,000 to bypass protocols...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/hawaiian-tourists-bribed-an-airport-screener-with-243000-to-bypass-covid-19-protocols-police-say/ar-BB1dO5zO?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two travelers from Louisiana were booked, released and flown back to the mainland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-it-alone state rattled by failure to keep lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/texas-the-go-it-alone-state-is-rattled-by-the-failure-to-keep-the-lights-on/ar-BB1dNYgi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political leaders in Texas prize what they see as the state’s self-reliance, its go-it-alone ethos, and its cheap power – all of which they regard as related. The independence of the power sector may not last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas man freezes to death in recliner...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-man-reportedly-freezes-to-death-in-his-recliner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Texas suffered through days of power outages, a man reportedly froze to death in his recliner with his wife clinging to life beside him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK CUT SHORT:  Cruz arrives back in Texas with armed police escort...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/sen-ted-cruz-arrives-back-in-texas-with-armed-police-escort/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz touched down in Texas on Thursday afternoon with an armed police escort amid outrage over his 24-hour trip to Mexico during a catastrophic storm in the Lone Star State. The Repub…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest at Bay Area church that flouted public health orders dies of covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/priest-bay-area-catholic-church-180500539.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sts. Peter and Paul Church closed its doors after a coronavirus outbreak sickened three priests and three caregivers. One of the priests has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Ready to Meet With Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2021-02-18/biden-administration-ready-to-meet-with-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement regarding Tehran’s nuclear program offers the first clues on how President Joe Biden will address one of the thorniest foreign policy problems he faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREIGN COUNTRIES MOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-02-18/an-ordinary-country-with-serious-shortcomings-us-foes-blast-deadly-texas-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration should spend more time trying to take care of its own citizens in Texas and elsewhere than denouncing other countries, one report published in China suggested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He repeatedly slammed OTHER politicians for vacationing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/politics/vacationing-during-crisis-ted-cruz/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Sen. Ted Cruz, who is facing backlash for traveling to Mexico as a winter disaster ravages his home state, has repeatedly criticized politicians who vacationed or took part in leisure activities during times of crisis, a CNN KFile review finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA on verge of decriminalizing psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-california-bill-would-decriminalize-psychedelics-expunge-criminal-records-n1258261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The war on drugs has been a complete failure," state Sen. Scott Wiener said. "It hasn't stopped people from using drugs and it hasn’t stopped addiction."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD roasted...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/under-fire-robinhood-ceo-apologizes-congress-restricting-trading-n1258285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Americans feel the system is stacked and, no matter what, Wall Street wins,” said Maxine Waters, Chairwoman of the House Committee on Financial Services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plumber Receives 2,200 Calls In 24 Hours!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/17/texas-plumber-calls-24-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many North Texans are feeling the effects of the deep freeze, with bursting pipes and floods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>53% Of People Kiss Their Dog More Than Their Partner...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-owners-risk-lives-for-pets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over half of married dog owners admit to kissing their hound more than their partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era for exploration...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/18/nasa-perserverance-mars-rove-landing-469771</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perseverance begins a series of missions over the next decade to pave the way for humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top French TV presenter named in rape complaint...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-french-tv-presenter-named-195856970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of France's most famous television presenters Patrick Poivre d'Arvor is the subject of a rape investigation, prosecutors told AFP on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA Recruits Top Prosecutor for The Don Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/18/manhattan-d-a-recruits-top-prosecutor-for-trump-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Manhattan district attorney’s office steps up the criminal investigation of Donald J. Trump, it has reached outside its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and China ready to sign deal to build first moon base...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/14089099/russia-china-sign-historic-deal-build-first-moon-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA and China are joining forces as they prepare to sign a historic deal to build the first moon base after they snubbed the US. The two countries are to collaborate on the international lunar s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell admitted Epstein DID have tapes of Trump, Clintons...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9270769/Ghislaine-Maxwell-admitted-Jeffrey-Epstein-DID-tapes-Donald-Trump-Clintons-2016.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell appeared to admit Jeffrey Epstein was taping his famous friends, including Donald Trump and the Clintons, during a 2016 meeting with former CBS producer Ira Rosen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mr. Kitty' goes virtually to Washington...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-social-media-fee89914ac530675c0017a485b6aa8ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social media movement that made a beloved icon of GameStop enthusiast Keith Gill continued to rally behind the YouTube personality known as Roaring Kitty as he testified to Congress on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands reportedly attempt to obtain easily forged vaccinated certificate...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/thousands-reportedly-attempt-to-obtain-easily-forged-vaccinated-certificate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Green Pass' uses a simple QR code to store inoculation status and personal information; Health Ministry says it will fine those with fake documents, issue more secure ones soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC guidance would keep 90% of schools at least partially closed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/18/cdcs-classroom-guidance-would-keep-90percent-of-schools-at-least-partially-closed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new guidance would keep more than 90% of schools, including in almost all of the 50 largest counties in the country, from fully reopening, doctors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones' natural gas company 'hits jackpot'...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/02/17/texas-freeze-allows-jerry-jones-natural-gas-company-to-hit-jackpot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 4 million Texans have had no power during the historic winter weather experienced by the state this week. As of Wednesday night, 7 million in the state had water issues with either boil notices or no water at all. Fingers are pointing. Pipes are bursting. Homes are flooding. Grocery store shelves are [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax at Vatican? You might lose your job...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/italy-coronavirus-pandemic-rome-pope-francis-europe-f3214bfe787e783f8779d3f0fa9edfe8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Vatican is taking Pope Francis’ pro-vaccine stance very seriously: Any Vatican employee who refuses to get a coronavirus shot without a valid medical reason risks being...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames his kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/18/ted-cruz-cancun-power-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First spotted at an airport by a social media user who posted his photo, there was an immediate outcry overnight that a U.S. senator would travel out of the state amid the worst storm in many Texans' lifetimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Dems scramble to fight Newsom recall, close ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/18/california-democrats-newsom-recall-469795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But it may already be too late to convince the disorderly Democratic ranks to put aside their political differences and stand in unity with their embattled governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER In Standoff With India Over Free Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/17/968641246/twitter-in-standoff-with-indias-government-over-free-speech-and-local-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter blocked hundreds of accounts the Indian government said were inciting violence. Then it unblocked them. Now it's stuck between Indian law and defending free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolly Parton asks TN not to put her statue at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dolly-parton-tennessee-no-statue-capitol-ee80ab68ca93f29d5f600b99008fadfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Dolly Parton is asking Tennessee lawmakers to withdraw a bill that would erect a statue of her on the Capitol grounds in Nashville. “Given all that is going on in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka WILL NOT challenge Rubio for Senate seat in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/539407-ivanka-trump-wont-challenge-rubio-for-his-senate-seat-in-2022-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump will not challenge Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Fla.) for his Senate seat in 2022, a source familiar with the matter confirmed to The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet Earth its quietest in decades as lockdowns reduce seismic noise...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218132810-5xify</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambient noise generated by human activity such as travel and machinery dropped by 50% last year, researchers find</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFINING BATTLE...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218154054-m3g6j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIA-MEDIA/FACEBOOK-PUBLISHERS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Time to get tough with 'bully' Facebook, UK lawmaker and publishers say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans told to ration power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218150220-2du16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/MEXICO-LNG (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-'Switch off lightbulbs:' president asks Mexicans to ration power as Texas limits fuel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA COVID TOLL NEARS 500,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218142847-768v9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TEXAS-FUNERAL HOME (PIX, TV):WIDER IMAGE-'I just ask God to help me': Texas funeral home crushed by death as U.S. COVID toll nears 500,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/did-you-bring-home-covid-spouse-sues-company-for-infection/ar-BB1dNsvg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge is weighing what she called a first-of-its-kind lawsuit that would hold an employer responsible for a worker’s spouse getting sick with Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of Ten May Have to Switch Occupations Post Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/one-of-ten-in-us-may-have-to-switch-occupations-post-pandemic/ar-BB1dNyqj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- One out of every ten U.S. workers -- about 17 million, all told -- will likely be forced to leave their jobs and take up new occupations by 2030 as Covid-19’s after-effects destroy huge swathes of low-paying positions in a labor market that was primed for disruption before the pandemic. Women, minorities, the young and the less educated will probably be the hardest hit by what consultant firm McKinsey &amp; Co. foresees in a new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky city's plan to build church with public money raises objections...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/counties/woodford-county/article249279410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Versailles plans to use public funds to build a worship center for a local church that would double as an emergency shelter, sparking objections from a national atheist group and concern among local farmland preservationists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE MOVES ON TO 6G!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-hiring-engineers-develop-6g-110000382.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. launched its first iPhones with 5G wireless speeds a few months ago. Now it’s looking to start work on sixth-generation cellular connectivity, or 6G, indicating it wants to be a leader in the technology rather than relying on other companies.The Cupertino, California-based company this week posted job ads seeking wireless system research engineers for current and next-generation networks. The listings are for positions at Apple’s offices in Silicon Valley and San Diego, where the company works on wireless technology development and chip design.“You will have the unique and rewarding opportunity to craft next generation wireless technology that will have deep impact on future Apple products,“ according to the job announcement. “In this role you will be at the center of a cutting-edge research group responsible for creating next generation disruptive radio access technologies over the next decade.”People hired for the positions will “research and design next generation (6G) wireless communication systems for radio access networks” and “participate in industry/academic forums passionate about 6G technology.” Industry watchers don’t expect 6G to roll out until about 2030, but the job listings indicate Apple wants to be involved at the earliest stages in the development of the new technology. A company spokeswoman declined to comment.Read more: Apple Starts Work on Its Own Cellular Modem, Chip Chief SaysApple’s current swath of iPhones use 5G modems designed by Qualcomm Inc. While the company launched its first 5G devices at an opportune time, several phone makers beat it to market and Apple relied heavily on Qualcomm for connection to the new wireless network, which dramatically improves the amount and speed of data that consumers can download. In order to get 5G into the latest iPhones, Apple settled a contentious lawsuit with the San Diego-based chipmaker. Apple’s early involvement in 6G research and design indicates it won’t wait around for the next major advancement.Late last year, Apple joined an alliance of companies working on standards for 6G and other next-generation cellular technologies. The standards and timing for 6G are still loosely defined, but some analysts say the technology could enable speeds more than 100 times faster than 5G.The job listings are another signal of Apple’s continued push into developing more technology in-house. The company has designed main processors for the iPhone and iPad and last year expanded that effort to the Mac. It has also ramped up work on its own custom screens and camera technologies, in addition to wireless chips for AirPods, Apple Watch and precise location data.Apple last year started developing its first custom modem, the chip that allows phones to connect to wireless networks. In a town hall meeting with employees in December, Johny Srouji, Apple’s custom technology and chip head, said that “long-term strategic investments like these are a critical part of enabling our products and making sure we have a rich pipeline of innovative technologies for our future.”Though Apple is laying the groundwork to be a key player in 6G, it has much work ahead to take full advantage of 5G, a technology in its infancy. The company hasn’t expanded 5G to other devices like the Apple Watch and iPad, and it sells multiple iPhones that use older 4G technology. It’s likely that Apple’s first modem will be for 5G connectivity.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Flees to Cancun Amid Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/ted-cruz-airport-power-crisis-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz flew to Cancun, Mexico, with his family this week as Texas dealt with a winter storm that left millions without power, a Republican source confirmed to Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dole reveals he has stage 4 lung cancer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/former-sen-bob-dole-reveals-he-has-stage-4-lung-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, the 97-year-old former Republican senator and 1996 presidential candidate, announced Thursday that he is battling lung cancer. “Recently, I was diagnosed with stage four lung cancer. My f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas congresswoman leads renewed push to study slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/texas-congresswoman-leads-renewed-push-to-study-slavery-reparations/article_ca9c3143-32d6-51b5-af1e-a2aa24905b76.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — U.S. Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee of Texas is renewing a 30-year congressional push to establish a commission that would study the impact of slavery and possible reparations for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Caffeine Changes Brain Structure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/caffeine-brain-structure-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings reveal that even consuming caffeine for a short period of time can change the volume of gray matter in the brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans may be BANNED from entering UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9273329/UK-add-red-list-countries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers arriving from the US could soon be added to the UK's 'red list' of countries as officials consider the risk of new variants from the two countries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lopez Obrador says Mexico will not retaliate over gas export ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210218135213-636a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/MEXICO-DIPLOMACY (URGENT):Lopez Obrador says Mexico will not retaliate over Texas's gas export ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz Flees to Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/02/18/barbs-fly-at-ted-cruz-for-heading-to-cancun-as-millions-in-texas-freeze-without-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – With 3 million Texans shivering in the dark, Sen. Ted Cruz jetted off to Cancun with his family, outed instantly by fellow vacationers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singer Luke Combs apologizes for past use of Confederate flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/entertainment/luke-combs-apology-confederate-flag-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luke Combs has issued an apology for past use of the Confederate flag in his performances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Delete'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/18/ex-australian-facebook-ceo-urges-users-to-delete-the-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former chief executive of Facebook’s Australian business urged users to delete the social network’s app in response to Mark Zuckerberg’s “sad” decision to block ne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/photos-of-ted-cruz-allegedly-fleeing-to-cancun-during-texas-arctic-blast-disaster-spark-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of Ted Cruz emerged on Twitter that claim to show the Texas Senator flying to Cancun, Mexico to escape the brutal and dangerous cold spell causing blackouts in his home state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/did-you-bring-home-covid-spouse-sues-company-for-infection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did You Bring Home Covid? Spouse Sues Company for Infection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/02/17/texas-food-supply-power-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texans running low on food are finding empty grocery store shelves. Food pantries are running out of supplies. And the freeze has wiped out substantial portions of the state's citrus and vegetable crops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA rover hurtles toward historic landing attempt on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/perseverance-mars-rover-landing-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perseverance's landing caps a decade of preparation by Mars teams worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House announces sweeping immigration bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/18/politics/biden-immigration-legislation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House announced a sweeping immigration bill Thursday that would create an eight-year path to citizenship for millions of immigrants already in the country and provide a faster track for undocumented immigrants brought to the US as children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers facing off with GAMESTOP saga's key players...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maxine-waters-financial-services-media-social-media-36042603229c758b74008bb69dcaafca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Lawmakers in Washington are digging into the GameStop saga at a congressional hearing. The episode has been portrayed as a victory of the little guy over Wall Street...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNERS-LEE: Could render internet unworkable...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/australia-internet-law-tim-berners-lee-b1803988.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning comes amid rising tensions between Australian law makers, news publishers and tech giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irregular sleep schedules connected to bad moods...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-irregular-bad-moods-depression.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An irregular sleep schedule can increase a person's risk of depression over the long term as much as getting fewer hours of sleep overall, or staying up late most nights, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
