<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>London Underground introduces First Class Carriages -- With A Bar!</title>
      <link>https://www.suffolkgazette.com/news/london-underground-introduces-first-class-carriages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.suffolkgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London Underground is introducing luxurious first-class carriages so well-heeled commuters do not need to mix with common riff-raff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wailing, white light and angel wings: 'Possessed' man's terrifying exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/wailing-white-light-angel-wings-21024749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comedian found himself being the subject of an exorcism after visiting a throat specialist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan arrested over 'racist gesture' at soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7768919/Manchester-City-fan-accused-making-monkey-sounds-United-star-Fred-family-man-40.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Anthony Burke, 41, (pictured) from Manchester appeared to make racist gestures and monkey noises at United midfielder Fred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems embrace exact surveillance tactics they used to warn about...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/07/democrats-have-embraced-the-exact-surveillance-tactics-they-used-to-warn-about/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Democrats have been warning Americans about the dangers of law enforcement metadata collections. They cautioned that communication giants were working in cahoots with law enforcement to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheelchair thief in reindeer slippers stopped in his tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article238168529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I am Jesus Christ' lets gamers play through being crucified; Fight Satan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/i-am-jesus-christ-lets-21051487</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial game allowing people to play through key moments from the Bible is due to be released on Steam for PC - but Christians have argued it is blasphemous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Ronstadt Needles Secretary of State Pompeo to his face for 'Enabling Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/linda-ronstadt-needles-secretary-of-state-mike-pompeo-for-enabling-trump-to-his-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exchange happened during a State Department dinner for Kennedy Center Honors recipients on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires warning shot at Kim Jong-un...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10508799/trump-warning-shot-north-korea-nuke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump today warned trigger-happy North Korea it has “too much to lose” hours after its latest controversial “missile” test. The tough-talking US president took to Twi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  VOTE POSSIBLE THIS WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/08/politics/jerry-nadler-donald-trump-impeachment-obstruction-of-justice/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With sources telling CNN a vote in the Judiciary Committee to impeach President Donald Trump is expected as soon as this week, House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler said Sunday that he sees the Ukraine evidence as part of "a pattern" of conduct by the President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER:  Vote possible THIS week...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/8/jerrold-nadler-impeachment-vote-possible-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler said there could be a vote as early as this week on articles of impeachment against President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Typo' overvalued Utah home by $1B -- now county residents have to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/Typo-may-have-overvalued-Utah-home-at-nearly-1B-14888778.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) - Utah officials say a possible dropped phone resulted in a typo that overvalued a home for almost $1 billion.  And taxpayers may have to pay for the mistake.  The Deseret News reports a house built in 1978 in an unincorporated area of the county was recorded in 2019 tax rolls with a value of more than $987 million. That's an overestimate of about $543 million in taxable value.  Wasatch County Assessor Maureen "Buff" Griffiths told officials last month a staff member may have dropped a phone on a keyboard. Griffiths said the accident has resulted in a countywide overvaluation of more than $6 million.  Griffiths added that the blunder also produced revenue shortfalls in five taxing entities.  Wasatch County officials say residents will likely see an increased tax rate over the next three years to make up for the lower amount collected in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after Moonves, 'toxic' culture remains in CBS TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-12-08/cbs-tv-stations-toxic-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Times investigation uncovers claims of discrimination, retaliation and other forms of mistreatment at CBS-owned TV stations, including L.A. outlets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cool Kids of the Left Turned...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/08/elizabeth-warren-jacobin-socialist-left-072693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The socialists of Jacobin magazine used to treat her like a promising alternative to Bernie Sanders. Now they write as if she’s almost as bad as Joe Biden. What gives?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number of African migrants at U.S.-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/story/2019-12-08/record-number-of-african-migrants-at-u-s-mexico-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of migrants from African countries in Mexico who have had contact with Mexican immigration officials has increased from 460 in 2007 to more than 5,800 in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan arrested over 'racist gesture' at soccer game...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/man-arrested-over-racist-gesture-manchester-derby-135444971--sow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British police on Sunday arrested a 41-year-old man after a video posted on social media showed a supporter apparently making racist gestures during Saturday&amp;#39;s Manchester derby. &amp;quot;Police were called to a report of a supporter making alleged racist gestures and sounds towards players during the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough or threat? Research on genetics of same-sex behavior ignites ethical debate...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/breakthrough-or-a-threat-research-on-genetics-of-same-sex-behaviour-ignites-ethical-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Were we to avoid studying sexual preference or other such topics … we would be leaving these important aspects of human diversity in the dark’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson promises lower immigration if he wins election...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191208075449-7amri</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/ (PIX):UK PM Johnson promises lower immigration if he wins election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Go after your enemies': Trump's 21-year-old playbook...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/08/trump-impeachment-playbook-clinton-077717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump shared his real-time thoughts about the Clinton impeachment two decades ago. Those same views are echoing through the president’s fight today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicare chief asked taxpayers to cover stolen jewelry...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/07/medicare-chief-asked-taxpayers-to-cover-stolen-jewelry-077761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seema Verma requested $47,000 for items taken from an SUV that took her to a speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to Pentagon: 'We are the good guys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/07/bezos-says-country-in-trouble-if-big-tech-turns-its-back-on-the-pentagon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Silicon Valley courts a closer relationship with the Pentagon, tech firms have faced backlash for pursuing lucrative Defense Department contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservationist attacked by her own tigers at animal sanctuary...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/conservationist-attacked-tigers-animal-sanctuary/story?id=67575571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wildlife conservationist was attacked an injured by several of her own tigers during an event at a wildlife sanctuary in southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Mysterious Case of Babies Buried With Helmets of Other Children's Skulls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-mysterious-case-of-babies-buried-with-helmets-of-other-childrens-skulls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Papers around the world have sensationalized the discovery of babies buried with the skulls of other children around their heads. But what’s really going on here?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wacky, big-money world of pet influencers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wacky-big-money-world-pet-influencers-082651201.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grumpy Cat, Lil Bub, Boo the Pomeranian and Doug the Pug are just some of the internet's star animals, who do everything from support worthy causes to promote major brands. The death this week of Lil Bub, a cat whose tongue was always hanging out due to genetic anomalies, inspired a wave of emotion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kongers mark half year of protest with mammoth rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-democracy-protesters-aim-massive-turnout-rare-210115805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast crowds of democracy protesters thronged Hong Kong's streets on Sunday in a forceful display of support for the movement as it marks six months with organisers warning the city's pro-Beijing leaders they had a "last chance" to end the political crisis. Authorities have repeatedly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete Turns to God to Win Over Black Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mayor-pete-turns-to-god-to-win-over-black-supporters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“All candidates should prioritize achieving greater understanding of issues that impact African Americans and other minority groups,” Rep. André Carson (D-IN) said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Chief Won't Call 'Terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-shooting-pentagon-idUSKBN1YB0LH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Mark Esper said on Saturday that he was not prepared at t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea conducts 'important test' at once-dismantled site...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/771a2235054d115a526ee8dcc2bd6295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea said Sunday that it carried out a “very important test” at its long-range rocket launch site that it reportedly rebuilt after having partially dismantled it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 more detained...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10504744/saudi-airmans-colleagues-us-naval-base-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Saudi air force pilot in the US for training who killed at least three people when he opened fire at a military base in Florida was filmed by his colleagues as he went on his killing spree. Moh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation broadens...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Investigation-broadens-in-shooting-at-Naval-Air-14890151.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. - FBI officials broadened their probe Saturday into the deadly shooting rampage at a Navy flight school here amid reports that several of the alleged gunman's Saudi compatriots took video footage as the killing spree was underway.  The shooting at the Naval Air Station Pensacola was labeled an act of terrorism by congressional officials, even as investigators continued to explore why a Saudi military student blasted his way through a classroom building early Friday, killing three people and wounding eight. The gunman, identified as Ahmed Mohammed al-Shamrani, was shot dead by a sheriff's deputy.  Law enforcement officials combed through the suspect's belongings and social media accounts on Saturday while questioning six other Saudi nationals, at least some of them fellow students in the same Navy flight training program. Three of the Saudis were said to have taken cellphone video at the scene, according to a U.S. official familiar with investigation. The official spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss an ongoing criminal probe.  The FBI declined to ascribe a motive for the attack, and it was unclear Saturday whether any of the Saudis questioned had prior knowledge of the gunman's plans. Officials said they were investigating claims, first reported by the Associated Press, that al-Shamrani showed videos of previous mass shootings at a dinner party he hosted in the days before the attack.  There also was no official confirmation of a possible link between al-Shamrani and a Twitter account that surfaced Friday bearing the same name and containing a note in English criticizing U.S. support for Israel and accusing Washington of "funding crimes against Muslims."  The account, which was suspended by Twitter on Friday, did not express an allegiance to any particular extremist group. Law enforcement...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI HUNTS MISSING SAUDIS IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7768107/FBI-hunt-missing-Saudi-soldiers-Pensacola-Naval-base-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Mohammed Saeed al-Shamrani, 21, killed three and wounded 12 others in the attack before he was shot dead by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi airman radicalized before U.S. Navy base attack...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191207213105-2bnc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORIDA-SHOOTING/ (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-Saudi airman may have become radicalized before U.S. Navy base attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy base victim 'saved countless lives,' family says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/07/joshua-kaleb-watson-pensacola-navy-base-shooting-victim/4364650002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Watson was shot at least five times, according to his dad. After being shot, he reached first responders and gave a description of the shooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pig monkey hybrids created in bizarre world first...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10500959/worlds-first-monkey-pig-hybrids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s first monkey-pig hybrids have been born, which could pave the way for human organs grown by animals. A groundbreaking experiment produced creatures with hearts, livers, spleens, lungs a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 more Saudis on base detained as others go missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10504744/saudi-airmans-colleagues-us-naval-base-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Saudi air force pilot in the US for training who killed at least three people when he opened fire at a military base in Florida was filmed by his colleagues as he went on his killing spree. Moh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida top cop caught telling deputy to act like 'white supremacist,' 'neo-Nazi'... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/florida-keys/article238145954.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Someone ate the $120,000 banana at Art Basel!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/entertainment/visual-arts/art-basel/article238148809.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police tactics questioned after  hijacked UPS truck chase ends in deadly shootout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ups-truck-police-chase-ends-in-deadly-shootout-police-tactics-questioned-2019-12-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were killed, including a UPS driver who was taken hostage and an innocent bystander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWELL LAWYERS UP FOR 'AMERICA'S GOT TALENT' INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/tv/news/simon-cowell-lawyer-americas-got-talent-investigation-1203428490/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“America’s Got Talent” executive producer Simon Cowell has set his legal representation for an investigation into the NBC competition series, which was announced by the network th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech finds surprise ally in Trump amid high-stakes tax fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/473482-tech-finds-surprise-ally-in-trump-amid-high-stakes-tax-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is defending Google, Facebook and other big tech companies he's repeatedly railed against when it comes to France's digital tax, a position that underscores how Trump's policies on tech don't always match his fiery, antagonistic rhetoric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor renowned for predicting elections says 2020 'too close to call'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/07/professor-renowned-for-predicting-elections-says-2020-too-close-to-call/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is a very close and very difficult call. I don’t think either the Democrats or the Republicans should be sending up any victory flags at this point,” Allan J. Lichtman told The Po…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch a Deepfaked Trump Say Epstein Didn't Kill Himself!</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/deepfake-trump-epstein-didnt-kill-himself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These things are getting dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founding Fathers Were Obsessed With Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/founding-fathers-were-obsessed-impeachment-130026472.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- It was weirdly cold in the room — that was the only thing everyone could agree on. Somehow, despite the bright lights and television cameras in the hearing room where I and three other law professors were testifying on the potential impeachment of President Donald Trump, the temperature</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor watched starving prisoners 'roast and eat child'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/holocaust-survivor-watched-starving-prisoners-21045977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nazi Holocaust survivor Josef Lewcowicz witnessed "so much cruelty" from the Nazis that "nothing surprised" him during his time in five brutal concentration camps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal rights YOUTUBer viciously beaten in Miami pizza shop...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7767097/Videos-Brother-Nature-savagely-assaulted-Miami-pizza-shop-just-days-beach-clean-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brother Nature - whose real name is Kelvin Peña - was in Miami doing a beach clean up and had stopped at the La Sandwhicherie on early Saturday morning when he was brutally attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary panel releases report defining offenses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473515-house-judiciary-committee-releases-staff-report-on-constitutional-grounds-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee on Saturday released a report explaining the constitutional grounds for the impeachment of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems battle for Hollywood cash...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/473419-democrats-battle-for-hollywood-cash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle for celebrity support — and dollars — is growing in the Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis distance selves...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudis-distance-themselves-us-naval-shooter-113700686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia sought to distance itself Saturday from a student who carried out a fatal shooting at an American naval base, as it seeks to repair its image of being an exporter of Islamic extremism. The Saudi military trainee reportedly condemned the US as a "nation of evil" before going on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says denuclearization talks 'out of negotiation table'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-says-us-denuclearization-talks-negotiation-table-173115232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea on Saturday said denuclearization talks with the United States were "out of the negotiation table," while slamming European UN Security Council members who had recently denounced its "provocative" ballistic missile launches. The statement from North Korea's ambassador</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk defamation win may reset legal landscape for social media...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191207011842-sg7qs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSK-LAWSUIT/LANDSCAPE (ANALYSIS):Musk's defamation win may reset legal landscape for social media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Deen Accuser Disgusted by His Porn Awards Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/james-deen-sexual-assault-accuser-disgusted-by-his-porn-awards-nominations-nobody-seemed-to-care</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashley Fires was the third of nearly a dozen women to accuse porn actor James Deen of sexual assault. Now, she’s found herself nominated for an award with her alleged attacker.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
