<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SC fire chief breaks up crowded pool party: 'Almost like Mardi Gras'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/coronavirus/article245364830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA WAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-praises-supporters-amid-deadly-clashes-with-15526134.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump on Sunday amplified his call for federal forces to help subdue protests in American cities, denouncing local Democratic leaders and fanning partisan tensions a day after a deadly clash between his supporters and social justice demonstrators in Portland, Ore., underscored the threat of rising politically motivated violence.  Scenes of Trump supporters firing paint and pellet guns at protesters during a "Trump cruise rally" caravan through downtown Portland - a liberal bastion that has been the site of weeks of street demonstrations - raised the specter that the nation's summer of unrest had entered a new phase in which the president's backers are rallying to defend businesses and fight back against Black Lives Matter and other groups he has labeled "anarchists" and "terrorists."  One man, thought to be a member of a pro-Trump group, was shot and killed Saturday night during the Portland unrest.  In tweeting a video of the caravan on the move, Trump called the participants "GREAT PATRIOTS!" The reaction marked a sharp contrast to his silence during a large and peaceful civil rights march on Friday in Washington that drew thousands to the National Mall, where some speakers denounced his leadership.  In a statement Sunday afternoon, Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden "unequivocally" condemned the Portland shooting and accused Trump of "fanning the flames of hate and division in our society and using the politics of fear to whip up his supporters."  "We must not become a country at war with ourselves; a country that accepts the killing of fellow Americans who do not agree with you; a country that vows vengeance toward one another," Biden said. "But that is the America that President Trump wants us to be, the America he believes we are."  The violence has escalated as Trump has seized...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police face complaints of tolerating vigilantes...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/police-face-complaints-of-tolerating-vigilantes/?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a video recorded shortly before two people were fatally shot last week in Kenosha, Wis., the accused gunman - Kyle Rittenhouse, 17 - circulates among a group of gun-wielding men who claim to be guarding a service station amid...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican beach resort tries to lure tourists back... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/mexican-beach-resort-tries-to-lure-tourists-back-in-the-midst-of-the-pandemic/?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CABO SAN LUCAS, Mexico - This city was literally built for tourists: A blank expanse at the edge of the desert converted into a haven for gringos looking to get away. Now, Cabo is trying to lure them back -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France tightens protocols...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/france-tightens-mask-protocols-after-surge-in-virus-infections/ar-BB18wjDd?li=BBnbcA1&amp;ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWEETSTORM...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-in-tweetstorm-over-portland-death-pushes-law-and-order/ar-BB18w4AW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA chief 'promises' transparency ahead review...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/fda-chief-promises-transparency-for-covid-19-vaccine-review/ar-BB18wugN?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri reports record number of virus deaths in single day... </title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/coronavirus/article245363550.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man attempts to rape woman on busy subway platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-man-arrested-after-brazen-attempted-rape-on-ues-subway-platform</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD says it has arrested a man caught on a shocking video attempting to rape a 25-year-old woman on a subway platform on the Upper East Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin protests against restrictions continue...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/berlin-protests-against-virus-restrictions-continue/article_539bd5a4-dae8-5ff2-9407-5b7c2a36f10b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests against the German government's coronavirus policies continued on Sunday, after demonstrations ended in clashes with the police the day before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLLEGE PLANS CRUMBLE: REOPENING DISASTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/colleges-parties-reopening-coronavirus-c23b7f87-343c-41aa-99dd-168801e4c089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's hard to prevent gatherings when students have been starved of social contact all summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTOBER SURPRISE:  FEDS FLOAT EARLY APPROVAL OF VACCINE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-floats-idea-early-approval-205016039.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the US Food and Drug Administration raised the possibility in an interview published Sunday that a future vaccine against the coronavirus might be given emergency approval before the end of trials designed to ensure its safety and effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald turning unrest to his advantage?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-allies-seek-turn-violence-192251455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump hopes violence at protests will generate a backlash against Democrats; opponents accuse him of inciting more violence with his rhetoric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accuse President of stoking violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ae3e27918764908f4ad78ea02c0e189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democrats on Sunday accused President Donald Trump of trying to inflame racial tensions and incite violence to benefit his campaign as he praised supporters who clashed with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rally supporting cops draws scores to downtown Kenosha...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f8b184872f489a75548914049e41b13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — Scores of police supporters gathered Sunday in downtown Kenosha where protesters have been demonstrating against police brutality since the shooting of Jacob Blake last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  CONVENTION GAVE NO BOUNCE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trumps-favorability-perceptions-covid-19-response-stagnate-post/story?id=72705268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's efforts to build his appeal and define his opponent at the RNC, had little apparent impact on the electorate, a new ABC News/Ipsos finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 St. Louis police officers shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/gunman-shoots-wounds-two-st-louis-police-officers-responding-to-call-one-officer-critical/article_aca46ef4-c749-561f-928f-3054ccf32df5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The officers were shot in the 3700 block of Hartford Street in the Tower Grove South area. The suspect was arrested hours after he barricaded himself in a home in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California moves to consider reparations for slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/California-moves-to-consider-reparations-for-15524833.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) - California lawmakers are setting up a task force to study and make recommendations for reparations to African Americans, particularly the descendants of slaves, as the nation struggles again with civil rights and unrest following the latest shooting of a Black man by police.  The state Senate supported creating the nine-member commission on a bipartisan 33-3 vote Saturday. The measure returns to the Assembly for a final vote before lawmakers adjourn for the year on Monday, though Assembly members overwhelmingly already approved an earlier version of the bill.  "Let's be clear: Chattel slavery, both in California and across our nation, birthed a legacy of racial harm and inequity that continues to impact the conditions of Black life in California," said Democratic Sen. Holly Mitchell of Los Angeles.  She cited disproportionate homelessness, unemployment, involvement in the criminal justice system, lower academic performance and higher health risks during the coronavirus pandemic.  Although California before the Civil War was officially a free state, Mitchell listed legal and judicial steps state officials took at the time to support slavery in Southern states while repressing Blacks.  The legislation would require the task force to conduct a detailed study of the impact of slavery in California and recommend to the Legislature by July 2023 the form of compensation that should be awarded, how it should be awarded, and who should be should be eligible for compensation.  The panel, which would start meeting no later than June 2021, could also recommend other forms of rehabilitation or redress.  In the last two years, Texas, New York, and Vermont have considered similar legislation, according to a legislative analysis. It said reparations could...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise lost: How Hawaii went from Covid-19 star to cautionary tale...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/30/hawaii-coronavirus-cautionary-tale-404564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state's infection surge shows the risk of complacency, say local officials who fault the governor for neglecting basic public health measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 KILLED</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/2020/08/1-person-shot-killed-near-downtown-portland-protests-saturday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have begun investigating the incident as a homicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to resume in-person campaigning...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-journal.com/biden-to-resume-in-person-campaigning-as-race-with-trump-kicks-into-gear-a1/article_0c14159c-ea57-11ea-b12a-77c12ddee76b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden will resume in-person campaigning across the country in coming days amid the still-raging coronavirus pandemic, an answer to allies imploring him to meet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos erupts in Germany as hundreds STORM Reichstag...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1329162/Germany-Berlin-Reichstag-protest-coronavirus-COVID-19-lockdown-latest-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS protesters tried to storm the historic Reichstag, the German parliament building, as chaos erupted at 'anti-coronavirus' protests across European capitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass use of hand sanitizer could create unstoppable superbugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1329220/coronavirus-superbug-warning-hand-gels-health-danger-andrew-kemp-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC TENSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8678051/Kenosha-protests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos erupted outside the White House on Saturday following another night of Black Lives Matter protests that saw police clash with demonstrators, firing rubber bullets and tear gas towards crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chapter closes on religious right's Falwell era...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/29/politics/falwell-liberty-university-trump-religious-right-evangelicals/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, Jerry Falwell Jr. was among those who took the stage at the Republican National Convention to praise Donald Trump. As president of Liberty University, the massive Christian college in Virginia founded by his televangelist father, Falwell had made waves earlier that year when, on the eve of the Iowa caucus he'd endorsed Trump rather than Ted Cruz. Falwell's early support helped Trump solidify his hold on evangelical Republicans and propel him to the nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama counseled NBA players amid boycotts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/28/politics/obama-chris-paul-lebron-james-nba/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before NBA players decided to resume playing, National Basketball Players Association President Chris Paul reached out to Barack Obama, a person familiar with the call told CNN, and asked the former President if he would offer his counsel to a group of NBA players.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges With Outbreaks Advised to Keep Students ON Campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-30/colleges-with-covid-outbreaks-advised-to-keep-students-on-campus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53964147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-right activists broke away from a large protest in Berlin against coronavirus restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWAMPY:  Ex-Chief of Staff Mulvaney to start hedge fund...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/514296-mick-mulvaney-to-start-hedge-fund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney is launching a hedge fund named Exegis Capital that aims to bet on financial services stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Alabama hit hard -- 1,200 students now infected...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/30/1200-students-now-infected-with-coronavirus-at-university-of-alabama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coronavirus tide is rolling at the University of Alabama — where 1,200 students have tested positive since the school opened this month. The alarming stat was reported on the university&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom, 63, and son, 43, arrested for incest after daughter-in-law catches them on the couch...</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/massachusetts-mom-son-incest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mother-son lovers each face up to 20 years in prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers Fleeing to Suburbs: 'Demand Insane'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/30/new-yorkers-are-fleeing-to-the-suburbs-the-demand-is-insane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over three days in late July, a three-bedroom house in East Orange, N.J., was listed for sale for $285,000, had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Coronavirus Test Is Positive. Maybe It Shouldn't Be...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/29/your-coronavirus-test-is-positive-maybe-it-shouldnt-be/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the nation’s leading public health experts are raising a new concern in the endless debate over coronavirus testing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUGUST SNOW: Colorado Peaks See First Dusting...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/08/29/colorado-weather-first-dusting-of-snow-on-peaks-near-aspen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of August pattern change has also, brought in a few flakes of snow for some mountain spots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Chicago cops gunned down...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/crime/2020/8/30/21407345/chicago-police-officers-suspect-shot-west-side</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting happened at 2:33 a.m. Sunday in the 3300 block of West Polk Street after police pulled over a vehicle that matched a description for an earlier call about a person driving around with a gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope has become 21st century 'prisoner of the Vatican'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/da2ee1bd2528078b04f52284341cd99b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — On the March day that Italy recorded its single biggest jump in coronavirus fatalities, Pope Francis emerged from lockdown to offer an extraordinary prayer and plea to his flock to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS, TRUMP SUPPORTERS CLASH IN PORTLAND</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6706c916dc6a156b9847baca437a91de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — One person was shot and killed in Portland, Oregon, as a large caravan of President Donald Trump supporters and Black Lives Matter protesters clashed in the streets of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel responds to explosive balloons with tank fire on Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e771ff2e9be4a550ddc890776732d55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — The Israeli military said it struck militant targets in Gaza early on Sunday in response to continued launches of explosives-laden balloons out of the Hamas-run...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
