<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Handcuffed, drugged with ketamine: Truth behind Thai cave rescue...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/asia/handcuffed-drugged-with-ketamine-truth-behind-thai-cave-rescue/news-story/172803c159e20de5cef5dee324266d30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the story that gripped the world: twelve boys from a Thai soccer team and their coach were trapped in a flooded cave so deep under ground a rescue was almost impossible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy moves to unleash killer robot ships...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2019/01/15/the-us-navy-moves-toward-unleashing-killer-robot-ships-on-the-worlds-oceans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy is planning to take the first few steps into a radical future, which, if it comes to pass, will upend how the fleet has fought since the Cold War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE WON'T INTERVENE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6594953/Judge-order-Trump-pay-employees-say-theyre-SLAVES-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some workers claim Trump is violating their constitutional rights by taking their salaries without due process. Others say he's treating them like slaves, forcing them to work for free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor badly beaten by stranger in unprovoked attack...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/15/holocaust-survivor-badly-beaten-by-stranger-in-unprovoked-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An elderly Holocaust survivor was badly beaten last November in the back of a public transport vehicle, according to a report. Montreal resident Hanka Fogelman, 92, called for a cab operated by Soc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pets -- key to obesity crisis?</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20190109-what-we-can-learn-from-overweight-pets-about-human-obesity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even animals that aren’t eating too much or exercising too little are getting fat. If we can figure out why, we may have the key to our own obesity crisis – and how to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young adults dropping out of church...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/religion/2019/01/15/lifeway-research-survey-says-young-adults-dropping-out-church/2550997002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-thirds of young people say theyÂ stopped regularly goingÂ to church for at least a year between theÂ ages of 18 and 22, LifeWay Research survey says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-top FBI lawyer subject of criminal media leak probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/former-top-fbi-lawyer-james-baker-is-subject-of-federal-media-leak-probe-transcript-reveals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former top lawyer at the FBI has been under federal investigation for leaking to the media, a letter from House Republicans revealed Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholics Urged to Avoid Touching as Flu Spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-01-15/catholics-encouraged-to-avoid-touching-communion-curtailed-as-flu-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YES OR NO?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8198119/labour-vow-to-bring-down-theresa-may-within-24-hours-and-could-overturn-brexit-completely/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LABOUR is set to try and bring down Theresa May’s government within 24 hours of her expected Brexit loss tonight. Jeremy Corbyn is expected to table a motion of no confidence in the Governmen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Americans Spend Nearly Half Waking Hours Looking At Screens...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-americans-spend-half-waking-hours-looking-screens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perhaps it's no surprise that Americans spend nearly half of their waking hours looking at screens, according to a survey of 2,000 adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Miami tech whiz groomed and molested exchange students -- and evaded cops for years...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article223207285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly released police and court documents offer a detailed look at Dale Leary, the Cutler Bay man who sexually abused exchange students for years before killing himself in 2017. One of his former students is suing CCI Greenheart, the company that cleared Leary to be a host, as well as the man’s former wife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG Nominee Barr Breaks From Trump: Mueller Not on a Witch Hunt...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/ag-nominee-barr-breaks-from-trump-sessions-should-have-recused-himself-mueller-not-on-a-witch-hunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SHE GO!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6592903/PM-faces-crushing-Brexit-defeat-vote-no-confidence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allies of the Prime Minister acknowledged her plans could be rejected by a majority approaching 200 votes – eclipsing record government loss of modern times in 1924.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Walls, fences around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/14/photos-from-vatican-walls-to-obamas-fence-20-barriers-around-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Trump requests full funding for a wall along the border, elected Democrats continue to claim that walls are "immoral" and "racist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/us/los-angeles-ca/90012/weather-radar/347625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Storm Arrives...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-01-14-california-parade-rain-snow-impacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on the situation in Southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classrooms resemble arcades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5f748251c2245da8ff84acab19edf36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WALLINGFORD, Conn. (AP) — It's 1 o'clock on a Wednesday afternoon in Wallingford, Connecticut, and about 20 children are watching a screen at the front of the room as they take turns navigating challenges and collecting virtual currency to unlock powers, outfits and pets for their characters. The game they're playing has some similarities to the online battle game "Fortnite." But the kids aren't fighting one another — they're racking up points for participation and good behavior in their classroom at Dag Hammarskjold Middle School, where their teacher is presenting a home economics lesson with help from Classcraft, a fantasy-themed educational program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Star' DEA agent stole millions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7bbc49156a7e47e6a1f6b3a37946ee12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A U.S. federal narcotics agent known for his expensive tastes and high-profile drug seizures has been implicated in a multimillion-dollar money-laundering conspiracy that involved the very cartel criminals he was charged with fighting in Colombia. A once standout Drug Enforcement Administration agent, Jose Irizarry is accused of conspiring with a longtime DEA informant to launder more than $7 million in illicit drug proceeds, sometimes using an underground network known as the black-market peso exchange, according to five current and former law enforcement officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUD IN CALI:  Deputies Go Door-To-Door To Evacuate Malibu Residents...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/01/15/malibu-door-to-door-evacautions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mandatory evacuations were ordered for: Corral Canyon/El Nido, Escondido/Old Chimney, Escondido Drive/Latigo Canyon, Malibu West/Trancas Canyon, Malibou Lake, all of Ramirez Canyon Road and adjacent streets and the Paradise Cove Mobile Home Park and Restaurant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Trump TV News 90% Negative in 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2019/01/15/networks-trashed-trump-90-negative-spin-2018-did-it-matter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the midpoint of Donald Trump’s first term, the establishment media’s obvious hostility shows no signs of relenting: 90% negative, vs. just 10% positive, matching the historically bad press we documented in 2017. But polls show this negative coverage has had no discernible impact on the public’s attitudes toward the President. Instead, the media's partisan approach has earned them high marks from Democrats, while alienating most Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF FILTH: Dirty diapers hurled from Manhattan high-rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Dirty-Diapers-Throwing-Hurling-NYCHA-Building-New-York-City-Report-504326281.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of a NYCHA building in the Lower East Side have allegedly found themselves in a stinky situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did speaking Spanish get this cook fired from ritzy restaurant?</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/did-speaking-spanish-get-this-cook-fired-from-ritzy-restaurant/article_bd832cd5-d1bc-573a-a843-aa0af9339b7b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Francisca Perez came to Osteria Fasulo, a high-end Italian restaurant in Davis, Calif., searching for a job in 2007. She had years of kitchen experience in Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'At any cost': China warns US Navy over Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190115-cost-china-warns-us-navy-over-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'At any cost': China warns US Navy over Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tlaib pictured with activist who calls Jews 'Zionist terrorists'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6591487/Now-Rep-Tlaib-pictured-activist-calls-Jews-Zionist-terrorists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan first-term Rep. Rashida Tlaib has been pictured with a Palestinian activist who has praised Hezbollah and called Jews 'Zionist terrorists.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Dimon warns shutdown could reduce growth to ZERO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/15/jamie-dimon-says-shutdown-could-reduce-economic-growth-to-zero-this-quarter-if-it-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.P. Morgan CEO Jamie Dimon, who has been bullish on the U.S. economy, said the partial government shutdown could wipe out growth from the world's biggest economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolution at gates of protest-hit Paris men's fashion...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/revolution-gates-protest-hit-paris-mens-fashion-151116359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris men's fashion week starts Tuesday with a tsunami of new talent, the first ever Celine men's collection but with shows also threatened by the "yellow vests" protest movement that has been shaking France. Dior moved its show from Saturday to Friday to avoid the weekly Paris demonstrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House shifts shutdown strategy, invites rank-and-file to lunch ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6128489e74e45a6b87329cf4fc744a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Shifting strategy, the White House invited rank-and-file House Democrats to lunch Tuesday with President Donald Trump, bypassing Speaker Nancy Pelosi and her leadership team in an effort to get centrist and freshman lawmakers on board with funding Trump's long-promised U.S.-Mexico border wall. Pelosi approved of lawmakers attending the meeting, telling her team that the group can see what she and others have been dealing with in trying to negotiate with Trump to end the partial government shutdown, now in its 25th day with no resolution in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death penalty for Canadian escalates China-Canada tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8425d7649b48405398792b5cc6d224b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Chinese President Xi Jinping's government is sparing no expense to its international reputation in its determination to force Canada to back down over the case of a Chinese telecommunications executive it detained last month. While Beijing formally denies any connection, the arrest of two Canadians on vague national security charges and the re-sentencing of a convicted Canadian drug smuggler to death on Monday point to a determined campaign of intimidation and retribution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT D-DAY!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/544adda6dd594190a7b60437d146b95c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Parliament neared a historic vote Tuesday as British Prime Minister Theresa May lobbied vehemently for a positive verdict on her proposed divorce deal with the European Union. Lawmakers will finally get their chance to say yes or no to May's deal after more than two years of political upheaval, with all signs indicating a resounding rejection. The final debate on the bill has begun, with no signs of a shift in momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects citizenship question for 2020 U.S. census...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115143936-yfedz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CENSUS/DECISION (URGENT):Judge rejects citizenship question for 2020 U.S. census</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLIES: Striking LA teachers post names of subs crossing picket line...</title>
      <link>http://eagnews.org/bullies-striking-la-teachers-post-names-of-substitutes-who-cross-picket-line/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles teachers walked out on students Monday in a massive teachers strike over pay and benefits for educators, though schools remain open with substitute teachers. March With Striking #UTLA Teachers Monday Jan 14 9:30 AM Grand Park Meet by the restrooms in Grand Park, right across the street from City Hall. All welcome.https://t.co/u8UdknDT6V#DTLA#LAUSD #redfored #utlastrong #strikeready #UTLAStrike #LosAngeles pic.twitter.com/09PTOV2tsN — PMbeers (@PMbeers) January 13, 2019 Pictures posted to the social media site and others show UTLA members decked out in red, toting signs in front of schools that read “Austin Beutner is the enemy of public education,” “Fund Our</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MINCEMEAT ALL OVER': 'Four dead' as terrorists attack five-star hotel in Nairobi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8199715/nairobi-terror-attack-gunfire-explosions-kenya-hotel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOUR people are reportedly dead and 14 injured after Al Shabaab terrorists launched a bomb and gun rampage on a Kenyan hotel in an ex-pat district. Images too graphic to show reveal the bodies of m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bombings in Brazil reveal growing power of gangs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/jan/15/climate-of-panic-bombings-in-brazil-reveal-growing-power-of-gangs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wave of attacks in Ceará state exposes how poverty and creaking prison system add up to perfect storm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE under fire for 'pray away the gay' app...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/01/14/google-fire-pray-away-gay-app-play-store/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google has come under fire for featuring an app that encourages gay people to seek controversial conversion therapy in its online store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stowaway bird causes chaos in business class during 14-hour flight to London...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/14/stowaway-bird-causes-chaos-business-class-14-hour-flight-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stowaway bird caused chaos in business class on a 14 hour flight as officials remain puzzled about how it came to be on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi says stepson subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/425360-corsi-says-stepson-subpoenaed-to-testify-before-grand-jury-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative author and conspiracy theorist Jerome Corsi said Monday that his stepson has been summoned to testify before a grand jury in special counsel Robert Mueller's investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: COULD PELOSI BE NEXT PRESIDENT?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/425344-could-nancy-pelosi-be-the-next-president-of-the-united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This scenario will not happen by election in 2020, but by succession to the White House this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORKERS TURN TO PAWN SHOPS</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/01/14/government-shutdown-pawn-shop-chicago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-four days into the government shutdown, a local pawn shop owner says he sees 10 to 20 federal employees come in each day in order to continue feeding their families and paying their bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moss Stepping Down as NYMAG Editor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/15/business/media/new-york-magazine-adam-moss-resigns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 61, an editor known for his obsessive style steps away from a publication that told New Yorkers where to eat and what to think. “I don’t wake up obsessed every morning, and I used to,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nairobi 'terror' attack: Explosions and gunfire at five-star hotel... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-nairobi-terror-attack-explosions-13859664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dusit Hotel complex in Kenya was evacuated and there are reports of civilians covered in blood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Trump administration doubles estimate of shutdown cost to economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/15/source-white-house-believes-shutdown-will-be-twice-as-costly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The original estimate that the partial shutdown would subtract 0.1 percentage point from growth every two weeks has now been doubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Hollywood's Biggest Media Companies Avoid Getting Crushed by Debt?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/features/att-disney-comcast-debt-1203107407/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Randall Stephenson, AT&amp;T’s chairman-CEO, summoned all of his folksy Oklahoma earnestness as he made an enthusiastic pitch to Wall Street analysts about the telephone company’s bold efforts to t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel's 'crown princess' seeks to chart own path...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190115-merkels-crown-princess-seeks-chart-own-path</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel's 'crown princess' seeks to chart own path</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian temple trailblazer beaten by mother-in-law...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190115-indian-temple-trailblazer-beaten-mother-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian temple trailblazer beaten by mother-in-law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Asks State Firms to Avoid Travel to America and Its Allies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-said-to-ask-state-firms-to-avoid-travel-to-u-s-allies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China also advised extra precautions to protect their devices in the U.S. and its allies if there arises a need to travel.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump's side, Border Patrol union leader in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/eb348270991d4d238e6aa83f18930263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Brandon Judd, president of the union that represents thousands of border patrol agents, has flipped the axiom that there are no winners in a government shutdown. His proximity to President Donald Trump has elevated the union leader's profile while burnishing the image of the U.S. Border Patrol, a backwater in prior administrations when compared to other federal law enforcement agencies like the FBI and Secret Service. At the same time, Judd, president of the National Border Patrol Council, has helped to validate Trump's fiery immigration rhetoric and affirm his conviction that a wall at the southern border is urgently needed to stop what they've described as a humanitarian crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carol Channing, iconic Broadway star of 'HELLO, DOLLY!', dies at 97...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/51d9bd38bc0b48e598f2372983a261e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Carol Channing, the lanky, ebullient musical comedy star who delighted American audiences over almost 5,000 performances as the scheming Dolly Levi in "Hello, Dolly" on Broadway and beyond, has died. She was 97. Publicist B. Harlan Boll said Channing died of natural causes at 12:31 a.m. Tuesday in Rancho Mirage, California. Boll says she had twice suffered strokes in the last year. Besides "Hello, Dolly," Channing starred in other Broadway shows, but none with equal magnetism. She often appeared on television and in nightclubs, for a time partnering with George Burns in Las Vegas and a national tour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's domestic spy agency to investigate far-right AfD: newspaper...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115115341-xmig0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-POLITICS/AFD (URGENT):Germany's domestic spy agency to investigate far-right AfD -newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Hondurans set off toward USA in new caravan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115044000-9lp3o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last October, another migrants caravan left Honduras made up of men, women and children, mostly claiming that they were fleeing entrenched poverty and gangland violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germinates first lunar seed?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/jan/15/china-germinates-first-seed-on-moon-cotton-shoot-change-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small cotton shoot is growing onboard Chang’e 4 lunar lander, scientists confirm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers forced to CRAWL on street after 'failing to hit annual targets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6593631/Staff-forced-CRAWL-street-failing-hit-annual-targets.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staff, all female, were on their hands and knees as they made their way through the busy traffic of Tengzhou, eastern China, yesterday afternoon. Police soon arrived and stopped the punishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can U.S. Make Employees Work Without Pay? Judge Could Force Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/can-u-s-make-staff-work-without-pay-judge-could-force-its-hand#gs.UiI7JWfi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can U.S. Make Staff Work Without Pay? Judge Could Force Its Hand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 2nd-deadliest Ebola outbreak reaches 600 confirmed cases...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/worlds-2nd-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-reaches-600-confirmed/story?id=60383138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second-largest, second-deadliest Ebola outbreak in history has reached 600 confirmed cases in five months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fails to launch satellite into orbit after ignoring warnings from US...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/iran-satellite-launch-ballistic-missile-nuclear-warheads-un-payam-doosti-a8728246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKLASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-46874617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video about toxic masculinity, bullying and men's behaviour sparks outrage online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President rebuffed request for Mueller interview in recent weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-interview-mueller-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's legal team rebuffed special counsel Robert Mueller's request in recent weeks for an in-person session with Trump to ask follow-up questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Star With Worst Shooting Season in NBA History...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/russell-westbrook-worst-nba-shooter-11547488655</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russell Westbrook is on pace for the lowest 3-point shooting percentage ever among high-volume shooters. He keeps shooting anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREXIT D-DAY!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/8194676/theresa-may-second-vote-brexit-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May will try to force a second vote on her Brexit deal despite facing a catastrophic defeat on it, allies have revealed. It has emerged that the PM has been given fresh hope of eventual suc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD Debuts Most-Powerful MUSTANG Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/jan/14/the-mature-stoner-why-are-so-many-seniors-smoking-weed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Older people are the fastest-growing group of cannabis users, as stigma fades and some seek an alternative to prescription drugs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says 'completely mischaracterized'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/01/rep-steve-king-releases-statement-debunks-new-york-times-report-and-outrageous-accusations-of-racism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking just one joint enough to change brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/legal-pot/even-little-marijuana-may-change-teen-brain-study-finds-n958536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say even one or two joints cause changes in areas of the brain involved in emotion-related processing, learning and forming memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposition gambling all on young, untested activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Venezuela-s-opposition-is-gambling-it-all-on-a-13532833.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a week ago, few outside of Venezuela knew of Juan Guaidó. But the 35-year-old industrial engineer has suddenly emerged as a cause celebre, heralded by global leaders for his challenge to the near-total power of President Nicolás Maduro. Following May elections internationally derided as a fraudulent power grab, Maduro was sworn in for a new six-year term Thursday. One day later, Guaidó - the new head of the opposition-controlled National Assembly - took a step Venezuelan critics had long considered too dangerous:Invoking articles in the constitution that allow the head of the assembly to assume national leadership if a "usurper" takes office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT PARALYZED</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-and-lawmakers-paralyzed-over-shutdown-as-13533754.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's dismissals of his own party's calls for compromise and his seeming indifference to shuttered federal agencies left the snowbound capital paralyzed Monday, with lawmakers in both parties scrambling to jump-start talks but increasingly uncertain about Trump's interest in ending the longest government shutdown in history. "I did reject it," Trump told reporters, when asked about a suggestion by Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., to temporarily reopen the government while continuing negotiations over money for a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border. "I'm not interested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic blast to hit KC for AFC championship game...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/nfl/story/arctic-blast-due-to-hit-kc-for-afc-championship-game-011419</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Break out the parkas for Sunday night's AFC title game at Arrowhead Stadium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Feds Can't Force To Unlock Phone With Finger, Face...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2019/01/14/feds-cant-force-you-to-unlock-your-iphone-with-finger-or-face-judge-rules/#4c236ac842b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops can't just hold an iPhone up to a suspect's face to search it, judge rules. It could be a landmark decision in modern privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Striking Teachers March in L.A...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/education/2019/01/14/photos-thousands-of-l-a-teachers-march-on-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Educators and parents wearing ponchos and rain boots and carrying umbrellas gathered downtown to march from City Hall to district headquarters in the pouring rain, pressing for higher pay and smaller class sizes that the district says could bankrupt the school system with 640,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems zero in on Trump and Russia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/425289-dems-zero-in-on-trump-and-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats vowed to introduce tough oversight of President Trump if they won back the House majority, and they are signaling a new aggressiveness to meet their promises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg's 'WEST SIDE STORY' Finds Its Cast... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/steven-spielberg-west-side-story-cast-ariana-debose-david-alvarez-josh-andres-rivera-rachel-zegler-1202535002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: After auditioning more than 30K people from around the world, Steven Spielberg’s West Side Story has found its Maria in fresh face 17-year old New Jersey High School student Rachel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Company known for deep cost-cutting offers to buy GANNETT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cce61bd08b664e39a7f39fdd6cb819b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A hedge fund-backed bid to buy Gannett Co., the publisher of USA Today and several other major dailies, is renewing fears of consolidation and job losses — as well as a decline in the quantity and quality of news coverage — in the already battered newspaper industry. MNG Enterprises, better known as Digital First Media, offered $1.36 billion on Monday for Gannett, saying in a letter that it can run the company more profitably via tight cost controls and consolidation of operations such as printing and administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIANT FOOD to place robotic assistants inside all 172 stores...</title>
      <link>http://www.wfmz.com/news/berks/giant-food-stores-to-use-in-store-robots-at-all-locations/975253313</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GIANT food stores will begin introducing a new robotic assistant to all of its 172 stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez freaking out media. And it's working for her...</title>
      <link>http://www.heraldnews.com/opinion/20190114/opinion-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-is-freaking-out-media-and-its-working-for-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's been on the job for less than two weeks and already has generated more national press coverage than some members of Congress get in their whole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces worst govt defeat in 95 years...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190114181416-s90vt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/VOTE (EXPLAINER, PIX, TV):EXPLAINER-What happens if PM May loses vote on her Brexit deal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christianity in Communist China: Churches close, pastors jailed, scripture rewritten...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jan/13/china-christians-religious-persecution-translation-bible</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Communist party is intensifying religious persecution as Christianity’s popularity grows. A new state translation of the Bible will establish a ‘correct understanding’ of the text</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Loses Committee Seats Over 'White Supremacy' Remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/house-republican-leaders-move-to-strip-rep-steve-king-of-his-committee-assignments-over-comments-about-white-nationalism/ar-BBSfGt2?li=AAa0dzB&amp;page=2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year-long domestic deployment of forces... </title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-military/2019/01/15/dod-extends-border-deployment-to-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Active duty troops were first sent to the border in October 2018 to secure it from an arriving caravan of migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album tops Billboard chart --  after selling just 823 copies!</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/ny-rapper-tops-charts-less-1-000-sales-002417838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Industry tracker Billboard, whose chart ranks the most popular albums of the week in the United States, said Monday that A Boogie Wit Da Hoodie's album "Hoodie SZN" climbed to the top with the equivalent of 58,000 sales for the week ending January 10. The figures lay bare the ever-widening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death penalty for Canadian escalates China-Canada tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ad12b3e9cebe4c25ae1b4143bc74e347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — A Chinese court sentenced a Canadian man to death in a sudden retrial of a drug smuggling case and Beijing said that it has denied a Canadian diplomatic immunity, ratcheting up tensions since Canada's arrest of a top Chinese technology executive last month. A Chinese court in northeastern Liaoning province announced Monday that it had sentenced Robert Lloyd Schellenberg to death, reversing an earlier 2016 ruling that sentenced him to 15 years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN TURNS NIGHTMARE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a50e00cb683b4b9697c1c957bae39cd2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The number of airport security screeners failing to show up for work around the country is soaring as the partial government shutdown goes into its fourth week. No-shows among screeners jumped Sunday and again Monday, when the Transportation Security Administration reported a national absence rate of 7.6 percent compared with 3.2 percent on a comparable day a year ago. Monday marked the first business day after screeners did not receive a paycheck for the first time since the shutdown began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon extends mission to Mexico border...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190115013923-guxn7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/PENTAGON (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Pentagon extends mission to Mexico border through September</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans strip congressman's committee assignments after 'white nationalism' comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/mccarthy-strips-steve-king-of-committee-assignments-after-white-supremacist-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., and House Republicans voted Monday night to strip Rep. Steve King, R-Iowa, of all of committee assignments days after he openly wondered when "white supremacist" and "white nationalism" became offensive terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems mull subpoenas for Putin meet interpreters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-secrecy-russia-interpreter/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers are discussing how to have the interpreter in President Donald Trump's meetings with Russian President Vladimir Putin appear before them to learn what transpired amid reports the President has worked to keep the content of his huddles with Putin a secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>River of chocolate clogs highway after tanker spills...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox10phoenix.com/news/arizona-news/tanker-truck-carrying-40k-gallons-of-chocolate-spills-onto-i-40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10phoenix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk about a sweet cleanup! The Arizona Department of Public Safety says a tanker truck carrying 3,500 gallons of liquid chocolate has spilled onto the westbound lanes of Interstate 40, east of Flagstaff at milepost 211.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With staff furloughed, Trump feeds CLEMSON fast food feast...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/14/clemson-tigers-white-house-donald-trump-fast-food-buffet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's burger time for the national champs!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard sees surge in West Coast migrant intercepts...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2019/01/14/coast-guard-working-without-pay-government-shutdown-sees-surge-west-coast-migrant-intercepts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The service is part of the U.S. military, but not paid because they are part of the Department of Homeland Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT GREAT AGAIN:  China Trade Surplus With USA Hits Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-annual-trade-surplus-with-u-s-hits-record-despite-trumps-tariff-offensive-11547439977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s trade surplus with the U.S. hit a fresh record last year, as robust American demand for Chinese goods undercut the Trump administration’s tariff offensive aimed at narrowing the countries’ lopsided trade gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Angry EAGLES fan attacks girlfriend, puts dog in microwave...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/news/breaking/mc-pol-angry-eagles-fan-attacks-girlfriend-puts-dog-in-microwave-20190114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upset about the Eagles playoff loss on Sunday, a 31-year-old woman attacked her girlfriend inside their room at the Best Western hotel in Hanover Township, Northampton County and placed her dog inside a microwave, according to court records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Replacing 30 mins of sitting with activity lengthens life...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/health/sitting-30-minutes-exercise-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Replacing 30 minutes of sedentary time with 30 minutes of physical activity at a light intensity was associated with a 17% lower risk of early death in a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL LOWEST IN YEAR</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jan14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bolsonaro is Hitler!' Nicolas exclaims...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-brazil/bolsonaro-is-hitler-venezuelas-maduro-exclaims-amid-brazil-spat-idUSKCN1P82FJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Monday called Brazilian President Jair Bo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House mulls wooing moderate Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/14/trump-on-declaring-national-emergency-im-not-looking-to-do-that-1098886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unlikely, however, that members in either party would split with leadership as the fight for Trump's border wall stretches into its 24th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal charity accused of secretly killing dogs to increase flow of donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/care-south-korea-dog-meat-charity-killing-animals-coexistence-animal-rights-on-earth-park-soyeon-a8726821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans now more likely to die from opioids than car accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/americans-more-likely-to-die-from-accidental-opioid-overdose-than-in-a-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the National Safety Council sheds light on the most common causes of accidental death in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA Proposes More Commercial Drone Operations at Night, Over People...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/faa-proposes-more-commercial-drone-operations-at-night-and-over-people-11547495257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal air-safety regulators for the first time proposed allowing small drones to routinely fly over crowds of people and at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Fund Known for 'Milking' Newspapers Takes Aim at GANNETT...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-14/hedge-fund-known-for-milking-newspapers-takes-aim-at-gannett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver Strips Down to Bra as Stolen Car Pursuit Comes to Bizarre End in LA...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/01/14/authorities-in-pursuit-of-vehicle-in-southeast-l-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman stripped down to her bra and undershorts before being taken into custody in South Los Angeles after an hourlong chase came to a bizarre end on a rainy Monday morning. Authorities were chasing the suspected stolen silver Kia sedan, which was carjacked at gunpoint on Saturday, according to Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department Deputy Charles Moore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2019/01/14/shutdown-tsa-shortages-airport-delays/2569551002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travel troubles from the government shutdown continue to mount, with some airports closing select security checkpoints to handle staffing shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Checkpoints Close at Dulles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/TSA-Closes-Some-Security-Checkpoints-at-Dulles-Amid-Staff-Absences-504319511.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steam-powered spaceship could cruise cosmos indefinitely...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/steam-powered-spaceship-could-cruise-cosmos-indefinitely-without-running-out-ncna958486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say the microwave-sized craft would suck its watery fuel right out of the asteroids, planets and moons it's exploring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next American Car Recession Already Started...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-13/the-next-american-car-recession-has-already-started</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spanish police arrest 182 people at illegal cockfight...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-spanish-police-arrest-182-people-illegal-cockfight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spanish police arrest 182 people at illegal cockfight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INSTAGRAM Effect' Forces Travel Destinations To Limit Tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90291704/these-5-travel-destinations-are-fighting-back-against-the-instagram-effect-on-tourism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers are all headed to the same places in pursuit of selfies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon shipping jumbo cell to Gitmo for al-Qaeda trial from hospital bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/sns-tns-bc-guantanamo-cell-20190114-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUANTANAMO BAY NAVY BASE, Cuba The Pentagon is shipping a handicapped-accessible cell big enough to accommodate a hospital bed and wheelchair that, in a first,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacist flyers posted outside Myrtle Beach newspaper, TV station...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/south-carolina/article224502495.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriot Front, known as a white supremacist organization, posted flyers outside The Sun News newspaper in Myrtle Beach. The group formed out of the Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville, VA in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: TV News Reporter Attacked While Broadcasting Live...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/01/13/reporter-attacked-live-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone attacked the reporter while she was live on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
