<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Modelers Warn Baltimore, Boston, Chicago Next Hot Spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/baltimore-boston-and-chicago-could-be-next-coronavirus-hot-spots-modelers-warn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time is running out as we move to the fall. We just don’t know when the match ignites.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMNER DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sumner-redstone-dead-cbs-viacom-media-mogul-was-97-622455</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He bested business rivals throughout his long career as he engineered deals for Viacom, Paramount and CBS and displayed an unwavering passion to win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot that 'remembers' hailed 'most ambitious AI creation ever' ...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-remembers-hailed-most-22506718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of new book, Sex Robots and Vegan Meat, was introduced to Abyss Creation's flagship sex robot Harmony that is hailed its most ambitious AI creation ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Pandemic Boost Cementing Its Retail Dominance...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2020-08-12/amazon-s-coronavirus-boost-is-cementing-its-retail-dominance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 could change views of social safety net...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ive-now-dipped-pie-covid-120000120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more Americans benefit from federal aid during the pandemic, some believe the discourse about the role of government in U.S. life could shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerns Grow Over Rising Infections in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/concerns-grow-over-rising-covid-132235459.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s government urged citizens Wednesday to keep their guard up and stick to public health guidelines, as new COVID-19 infections hit a three-month high and schools reopened in the country&amp;#39;s most populous state. Germany&amp;#39;s response so far has widely been seen as successful in slowing the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM TICKET SET FOR FIRST APPEARANCE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9fa729b2c5920a004b7b0cc56acd5e01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden is making his first appearance with newly chosen running mate Kamala Harris on Wednesday, betting that the California senator’s historic profile and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN-HARRIS SET FOR FIRST APPEARANCE... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden-harris/democrat-biden-and-new-running-mate-harris-to-make-first-campaign-appearance-idUSKCN25819L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden and his new running mate, Senator Kamala Harris, will make their first appearance as a ticket on Wednesday in Wilmington, Delaware, as the campaign for the White House enters a more frenetic phase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will COVID-19 change views of social safety net?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-08-12/covid19-coronavirus-welfare-unemployment-economy-ppp-loans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more Americans benefit from federal aid during the pandemic, some believe the discourse about the role of government in U.S. life could shift.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA TITAN</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/sumner-redstone-dead-97-viacom-cbs-paramount-1234732722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sumner Redstone, a towering figure in media who built his father’s drive-in theater business into an empire that included Viacom, Paramount Pictures and CBS Corp., only to see his legacy tarnished …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dark side of wellness: NETFLIX series on murky industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2020/aug/12/unwell-netflix-series-dark-side-of-wellness-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do trends such as essential oils and fasting live up to their promises? Netflix’s (Un)well searches for answers with believers, skeptics and scientists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can movement behind AOC conquer New York?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/12/aoc-ocasio-corteznew-york-city-394021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest iteration of the movement will face its first citywide test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College towns fear super-spreader semester as students descend...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/college-towns-coronavirus-393881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local officials are bracing for a virus explosion triggered by young people living in tight quarters who disregard social distancing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic crisis in Kentucky has workers, businesses furious with McConnell...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/An-economic-crisis-in-Kentucky-has-workers-15474739.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parade of cars honked incessantly as they crawled past the federal courthouse on West Broadway, their message clear to anyone who bothered to steal a glance at their signs outside.  "Mitch better have my money."  The Kentucky representatives from the AFL-CIO, Teamsters and other labor groups had grown incensed with Mitch McConnell, their home state senator and the chamber's most powerful lawmaker. For months, they said, he had been blocking much-needed congressional coronavirus aid, the kind of dollars that might help workers and businesses in the Bluegrass State struggling to survive financially.  So they hit the streets on Thursday, drove down to McConnell's Louisville office and started to circle the block, their 30 or so vehicles plastered with not-so-subtle orange and gray signs featuring a family-friendly rewrite of a popular Rihanna tune.  The labor protest marked only the latest in a series of exasperated complaints from Kentuckians directed at McConnell, a Republican, as some locals find themselves frustrated by the absence of their powerful political representative on Capitol Hill. In more than two dozen interviews, out-of-work residents, struggling restaurant owners and other business leaders, as well as a cadre of annoyed food, housing and labor rights groups, all said they are in dire need of more support from Congress - the likes of which McConnell has not been able to provide.  About five months after Kentucky reported its first loss of life from covid-19, its economy continues to sputter amid the coronavirus pandemic. Many unemployed workers say their benefit checks aren't enough to afford their bills, and some here simply have stopped looking for jobs. Businesses say they're also hemorrhaging cash, and local governments fear they're on the precipice of financial ruin, too.  The economic tumult in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood test predicts if will kill you?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-8617439/Could-blood-test-predict-coronavirus-kill-you.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GWU team believes a blood test for these biomarkers could give doctors a clearer picture of who might need ventilator support or early aggressive treatment amid supply shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery workers say morale all-time low: 'They don't treat us like humans anymore'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Grocery-workers-say-morale-is-at-an-all-time-low-15477599.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This spring, for the first time, Angel Manners found purpose and pride at the supermarket where she has worked the past decade. Customers praised her as a hero for putting herself at risk during the pandemic. Bosses boosted her hourly pay by $2. Suddenly, her job was essential.  Nearly five months in, and it is all gone.  "In the last month, we've lost our hazard pay, and people are quitting every day," said Manners, 43, who processes vendor deliveries at a Meijer store in northern Kentucky. "Those of us who are left are really stretched thin - working so much harder for $11.50 an hour."  Grocer workers across the country say morale is crushingly low as the pandemic wears on with no end in sight. Overwhelmed employees are quitting mid-shift. Those who remain say they are overworked, taking on extra hours, enforcing mask requirements and dealing with hostile customers. Most retailers have done away with hazard pay even as workers remain vulnerable to infection, or worse. Employees who took sick leave at the beginning of the pandemic say they cannot afford to take unpaid time off now, even if they feel unwell.  The mounting despair is heightened by the lack of other job options: Supermarkets are among the few bright spots in an industry that has been ravaged by covid-related store closures and a sharp drop-off in consumer spending. The retail sector has shed 913,000 jobs and chalked up more than a dozen bankruptcies during the pandemic.  "At the beginning they valorized what was deemed a dead-end job, but four months later they don't even treat us like humans anymore," said Fox Wingate, 24, who works at a Safeway in Maryland.  Workers' renewed sense of expendability comes after four straight months of double-digit unemployment. With more than 32 million Americans collecting unemployment benefits, labor experts and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: New York Exodus...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/11/new-yorkers-flee-nyc-in-droves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers reveal why they’re giving up on Gotham, with one fed-up mother declaring the city “a nightmare.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whether Night Owl or Early Bird May Affect How Much You Move...</title>
      <link>https://www.carihargaterupdate.com/health/whether-you-are-a-night-owl-or-early-bird-may-affect-how-much-you-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.carihargaterupdate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone Mountain braces for another armed protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/stone-mountain-braces-for-another-armed-protest/YCO2G6COUVACFLAAM5LYYHTODM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black and white militias are threatening to converge on Stone Mountain Saturday, Aug. 15, for protests that could provoke confrontation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Depression 11 is here; Could shatter another Atlantic record...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-depression-11-develops-in-atlantic-could-become-tropical-storm-josephine/793056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538: BIDEN FAVORED TO WIN...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecast of the 2020 presidential election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALIN OFFERS ADVICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1294489/sarah-palin-advises-kamala-harris-joe-biden-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SARAH Palin advised Kamala Harris to “trust no one” as she became the third woman on the presidential ticket. On Tuesday, Biden announced Harris would be his running mate as he attempts…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAR HOLDS ON!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/ilhan-omar-beats-primary-challenger-in-minnesota-394053</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omar is the third member of the liberal 'Squad' to defend her seat successfully this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  She's 'nasty' and 'disrespectful'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/phony-kamala-trump-campaign-responds-harris-vp-pick-n1236467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and his campaign focused their attention Tuesday on Harris' criticism of Biden during the Democratic primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES in Crisis: Digital Subscription Goals Missed, Top Editor 'Asleep in Meetings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/los-angeles-times-stalled-subscriptions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Times lags far behind national competitors in its attempt to build a robust digital subscription base, TheWrap has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech millionaire McAfee arrested for wearing lacy thong as mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1288314/tech-millionaire-john-mcafee-arrested-thong-coronavirus-mask-norway/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA:  'Nailed' it...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-Latest-Trump-campaign-blasts-Kamala-Harris-15476254.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) - The Latest on Democratic presidential contender Joe Biden's selection of California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate (all times local):  6 p.m.  President Donald Trump says he's "a little surprised" that his Democratic rival, Joe Biden, has selected Kamala Harris as his running mate.  Trump told reporters at a White House briefing that Harris "was very disrespectful to Joe Biden" during the Democratic primaries, and said "it's hard to pick somebody that's that disrespectful."  He's also noting that Harris "did very poorly" when she ran for the nomination - she dropped out in December - and says, "That's like a poll."  Trump is trying to paint Harris as too far left, saying she wants to raise taxes, slash funds for the militarily and ban fracking. He's also noting her tough questioning of now-Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh during his Senate confirmation hearing.  Trump says, "She was my No. 1 draft pick and we'll see how she works out."  Biden's campaign announced his decision to pick Harris as his running mate earlier Tuesday.  Trump last month had said she would be "a fine choice."  __  5:50 p.m.  Vice President Mike Pence is welcoming his Democratic rival to the race after former vice president Joe Biden named California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate.  Speaking in Arizona, the Republican used the opportunity to attack the Biden-Harris ticket. "As you all know, Joe Biden and the Democratic Party have been overtaken by the radical left," Pence said. "So given their promises of higher taxes, open borders, socialized medicine and abortion on demand, it's no surprise that he chose Senator Harris."  Pence plugged the Oct. 7 vice presidential debate, scheduled to take place in Utah....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S KAMALA</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/11/joe-biden-vp-pick-kamala-harris-393768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris, the daughter of immigrants from Jamaica and India, was the wire-to-wire frontrunner for Biden’s No. 2 job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Escape Illness, Grandma's Living in Backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/to-escape-covid-19-grandma-s-living-in-the-backyard/ar-BB17Ppzd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  CNN's Jeff Zucker once feted...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article233256089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD:  Picked as 'do no harm' candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/opinions/why-kamala-harris-won-vp-content-axelrod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Axelrod writes that Joe Biden chose Kamala Harris, the charismatic and telegenic Black politician, as his vice president because, as a former prosecutor, she is best prepared to play a lead role in bringing the case against Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN-HARRIS First Appearance Set For Wednesday In Delaware...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kamala-harris-joe-biden-vice-president-democratic-presidential-running-mate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden campaign made the announcement in a text message to supporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Cartel Flooding U.S. with Meth at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2020/08/11/jaeson-jones-exclusive-mexican-cartel-labs-are-flooding-u-s-with-meth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increases in seizure data represented a significant tripwire from normal production amounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicious in primary, now Kamala and Joe as one...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/11/kamala-harris-and-joe-biden-beefs-when-the-running-mates-clashed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody knows better than Joe Biden that his veep pick Kamala Harris can be a pit bull — she regularly went after him while still vying for the top spot on the Democratic presidential ticket. Harris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$250 Fine in Hoboken For Not Wearing Mask  -- Outside!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/11/hoboken-new-jersey-mask-fines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masks are already mandated in New Jersey, but one city is taking it a step further, saying if you don't wear one outside where you can't social distance, you could face a fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First black woman on party ticket!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ac8fff8bbe1c70479604e3ff62ecb10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Joe Biden named California Sen. Kamala Harris as his running mate on Tuesday, making history by selecting the first Black woman to compete on a major party’s presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bans blackface, anti-Semitic stereotypes in 'hate' speech update...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/8/11/21363890/facebook-blackface-antisemitic-stereotypes-ban-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This type of content has always gone against the spirit of our hate speech policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Ten pulls plug on fall football season...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/college-football/story/_/id/29640222/sources-big-ten-pulls-plug-fall-football-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Big Ten Conference has decided to postpone all fall sports, including football, and will look to play those sports in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pac-12 cancels too...</title>
      <link>https://www.conquestchronicles.com/2020/8/11/21363837/usc-football-pac-12-cancels-football-fall-sports-season-2020-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conquestchronicles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s over — USC’s re-emergence into a national powerhouse will have to wait another year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following conservative playbook, progressives look to Supreme Court to motivate voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/conservatives-progressives-supreme-court-voters-2020-presidential-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new poll found that 57% of Democratic voters said the Supreme Court was "very important" in deciding which candidate to vote for in the presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot near White House had shouted threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/321832b186f689e6d8ce20087a6b1c0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A man shot and wounded by a uniformed Secret Service officer, prompting President Donald Trump to be abruptly escorted out of a briefing room during a televised news conference,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarium Washing Old Wishes To Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/08/10/901014658/aquarium-is-washing-old-wishes-to-pay-bills-during-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No coin shortage here: While it's closed for the pandemic, the North Carolina Aquarium at Pine Knoll Shores has drained a 30-foot waterfall and cleaned off 100 gallons of pocket change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PICK IS IN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/politics/biden-vp-pick/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden has selected his running mate, revealing to top advisers on Tuesday the woman he will invite to join his Democratic presidential ticket, two people familiar with the matter tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida deaths reach another grisly record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/11/florida-coronavirus-deaths-reach-another-grisly-record-as-state-grapples-with-testing-constraints.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is one of the hardest-hit states in the country by the coronavirus, but daily new cases have appeared to decline in recent days. Testing, however, has fallen even faster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines: Rodrigo Duterte Volunteers to Take It...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/08/11/philippines-duterte-volunteers-take-putin-approved-russian-coronavirus-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte volunteered to be the first person to receive Russia’s new coronavirus vaccine on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simon Cowell Walking Again After Back Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/simon-cowell-is-walking-again-after-back-surgery-151128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 'America's Got Talent' judge is continuing to recover in the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'taken off suicide watch'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8614925/Ghislaine-Maxwell-moans-conditions-hell-hole-Brooklyn-jail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell says she is under constant surveillance at Brooklyn's Metropolitan Detention Center despite recently being taken of suicide watch, and wants to be moved out of solitary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PICK IS IN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/2020-election-biden-vp-pick/h_afa9a64115c1cc49f873a18670b7cce6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden, the presumptive Democratic nominee, is expected to announce his running mate for the 2020 election ballot. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California BLM Leader Charged With 5 Felonies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2020/08/10/tianna-arata-charged-five-felonies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtag #FreeTianna and a petition have gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo adds more states to quarantine list...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/11/gov-cuomo-adds-2-more-states-virgin-islands-to-ny-travel-advisory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY — Visitors from Hawaii, South Dakota and the US Virgin Islands coming into New York will have to quarantine for two weeks, as Gov. Andrew Cuomo announced the additions to his travel ad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court wary of ordering dismissal of Flynn case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5197ecacce9125418a68d3a7bf24917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal appeals court in Washington appeared inclined Tuesday to let a judge decide on his own whether to grant the Justice Department's request to dismiss the criminal case...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  DC-Area Real Estate Had Record-Breaking July...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2020/08/11/dc-area-real-estate-had-a-record-breaking-july/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The market has more than rebounded from the Covid-19 slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-Altered Squid Could Be Next Lab Rats...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/08/10/900886442/gene-altered-squid-could-be-the-next-lab-rats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first genetically-altered squid is here. NPR's Nell Greenfieldboyce explains how this breakthrough was made and why it's a game changer for scientists who study these critters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apt Bible passage at Catholic Mass coincides with temblor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/33478d1002b8d27a590e51460d223ae0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — The Scripture quite literally came to life for several Catholic churches in North Carolina as a rare earthquake rattled portions of the state over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How pet chihuahua rushed to save life of man having stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnct.com/local-news/man-shares-how-his-pet-chihuahua-saved-his-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnct.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORIENTAL N.C. (WNCT) – People say dogs are a man’s best friend.  That is proving to be especially true for a Pamlico County man. Rudy Armstrong spends most of his time with his chi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDROID Becoming Worldwide Earthquake Detection Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2020/8/11/21362370/android-earthquake-detection-seismometer-epicenter-shakealert-google</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google starting small, but the implications are huge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii seeing fastest rate of spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/08/10/experts-covid-is-spreading-hawaii-faster-rate-than-anywhere-else-nation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s just a glaring example of how we need to be serious about this."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China increases military drills as tensions with USA heat up...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/11/asia/china-taiwan-guam-military-exercises-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is stepping up military drills around East Asia as a war of words with the United States heats up over Washington's military activities and the visit of a US cabinet secretary to Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain again grapples with Europe's worst infection rate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spain-again-grapples-europes-worst-155113562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just seven weeks after bringing its first coronavirus wave under control, experts say Spain is once again in a &amp;quot;critical&amp;quot; situation with the worst infection rate in Western Europe. The country reported an average of 4,923 new daily cases of the respiratory disease during the last seven days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no end to pandemic in sight, coronavirus fatigue grips nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/With-no-end-to-the-pandemic-in-sight-coronavirus-15475104.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabe Rice began sheltering in his suburban Phoenix home with his wife and three youngest children in March. They worked remotely, learned remotely and put social events on hold to hunker down alongside much of the country.  It was challenging and frustrating, but, Rice initially assumed, temporary. It seemed like a plausible plan to help the nation get the pandemic under control within a couple of months.  But Arizona's economic reopening in May, urged by Republican Gov. Doug Ducey, was soon followed by a spike in coronavirus infections in June, which became a terrible surge in hospitalizations and deaths by July.  Then came August, and the devastating realization for many Americans that the pandemic, which has killed at least 159,000 people across the country and sickened more than five million, is far from over.  "It's difficult when you think you have a light at the other end of the tunnel to look forward to, and then all of a sudden you realize it's a train," said Rice, 44, a program coordinator at Arizona State University.  An exhausted, exasperated nation is suffering from the effects of a pandemic that has upended society on a scale and duration without parallel in living memory.  The Rice family and millions of other Americans are wrestling with difficult questions about how to juggle school, pay their bills and look after their mental and physical health.  Parents lie awake, their minds racing with thoughts of how to balance work with their newfound role as home-schoolers. Frontline health workers are bone tired, their nerves frayed by endless shifts and constant encounters with the virus and its victims. Senior citizens have grown weary of isolation. Unemployed workers fret over jobs lost, benefits that are running out, rent payments that are overdue. Minority...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Quentin disaster exposes dangerous road to 'herd immunity'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/san-quentin-coronavirus-disaster-exposes-120059867.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disastrous situation unfolding at California&amp;#39;s oldest prison over the last two months is shaping up to be the latest of several cautionary tales of how many people must get infected before &amp;#39;herd immunity&amp;#39; might be achieved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defiance of law, protesters in Thailand demand curbs on king's powers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/illegal-criticize-thailands-king-theyre-103403046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Student-led protests are calling for curbs on King Maha Vajiralongkorn&amp;#39;s wealth and power, openly defying laws against insulting the monarchy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Delay dental checkups until risk known...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200811130634-e0bs0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-DENTAL (TV, PIX):Delay routine dental checkups, WHO urges, until COVID-10 risk is known</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
