<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HALF Americans don't change underwear daily, new survey says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-change-underwear-tommyjohn-survey-20190815-2jmi33jahvbi3eytrtpfydzxqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Americans apparently wear the same pair of skivvies two days in a row, and 13% of them can go a week or more without changing, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man committs 10 felonies, 2 misdemeanors in 21 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/16/us/rodney-edward-king-indictment-crime-spree-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio man committed 10 felonies and two misdemeanors against seven people within a span of 21 minutes, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'IT: CHAPTER TWO' Could Float to $110 Million Debut...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/box-office-it-chapter-two-opening-weekend-tracking-1203302473/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros.’ thriller “It” jolted the box office when it debuted two years ago, delivering the best debut for an R-rated horror movie with $123 million. Pennywise is floating bac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surrounded by Tragedy, Venezuelans Laughing Like Crazy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/surrounded-tragedy-venezuelans-laughing-crazy-100005285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Editors Note: There are few places as chaotic or dangerous as Venezuela. “Life in Caracas” is a series of short stories that seeks to capture the surreal quality of living in a land in total disarrayHe knew this one was going to get laughs. “Raise your hands if you’re only in here because</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of porn sites track user data -- without telling...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/nationworld/os-ne-porn-sites-track-user-data-20190815-4vadt77nyfdqzbiv2c6jn3zfp4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 9 in 10 pornography websites send user data to at least one third party, a new study has found. And going incognito may not always help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MULAN' Star Support for Crackdown Prompts Call for DISNEY Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hong-kong-protestors-call-disney-boycott-mulan-star-voices-support-police-crackdown-1232216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese-American actress Crystal Liu has pulled Disney into the heated political fray surrounding Hong Kong's pro-democracy and anti-police brutality protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet neglected 43-year-old stepchild of US military industrial complex...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/meet-the-neglected--year-old-stepchild-of-the-us/article_e05514c9-c9ac-5cd7-b2fc-f677b2426049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — The icebreaker Polar Star was 1,000 miles out of its home port of Seattle last December, three days into its yearly voyage to resupply scientific bases in Antarctica,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crying on the job? 8 in 10 workers shedding tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/crying-on-the-job-youre-not-alone-with-8-in-10-workers-shedding-tears/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workplace weeping is a common experience, with almost half of workers blaming their boss or colleagues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel grants Tlaib West Bank visit on humanitarian grounds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7d180b153a84170be53dfe2c365e439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel's interior minister said Friday he has received and granted a request by Democratic Rep. Rashida Tlaib to enter the Israeli-occupied West Bank on humanitarian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATHAY PACIFIC CEO resigns after Beijing pressure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6abb13ad13154d74aca766b368f668bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — The CEO of Cathay Pacific Airways, one of Hong Kong's most prominent companies, resigned Friday following pressure by Beijing on the carrier over participation by some of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROCKS RALLY</title>
      <link>https://youtu.be/oM8_hTdP4WA?t=721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;youtu.be&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is rallying supporters Thursday night in Manchester, New Hampshire, a state he narrowly lost in 2016 and hopes to capture in 2020. Watch live...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST LEAD FRIDAY:  President frets over possible economic downturn... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-banking-on-strong-economy-to-win-14308399.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEWATER, N.J. - Mounting signs of global economic distress this week have alarmed President Donald Trump, who is worried that a downturn could imperil his reelection, even as administration officials acknowledge that they have not planned for a possible recession.  Trump is banking on a strong economy to win a second term in 2020, and in recent weeks has impulsively lashed out at the Federal Reserve, pressured Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin to label China a "currency manipulator," and unexpectedly delayed tariffs on Chinese imports out of fear they could depress holiday retail sales.  Yet despite gyrations in the U.S. stock market and economic slowdowns in other countries, officials in the White House, at the Treasury Department and throughout the administration are planning no new steps to attempt to stave off a recession. Rather, Trump's economic advisers have been delivering the president upbeat assessments in which they argue the domestic economy is stronger than many forecasters are making it out to be.  In turn, Trump has sought to use his Twitter pulpit to drown out negative indicators. On Thursday he promoted the U.S. economy as "the Biggest, Strongest and Most Powerful Economy in the World," and, citing growth in the retail sector, predicted that it would only get stronger. He also accused the news media of "doing everything they can to crash the economy because they think that will be bad for me and my re-election."  Privately, however, the president has sounded anxious and apprehensive. From his golf club in New Jersey where he is vacationing this week, Trump has called a number of business leaders and financial executives to sound them out - and they have provided him a decidedly mixed analysis, according to two people familiar with the discussions who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT PAGE ONE:  Trouble Signs Hang Over Trade War... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/15/business/economy/trump-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House advisers discount warnings of a possible recession. But the president may be gambling that the Federal Reserve can ward off that prospect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAR WARS' Obi-Wan Kenobi Series Coming to DISNEY Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/star-wars-ewan-mcgregor-talks-an-obi-wan-kenobi-series-disney-1201364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor has played the role in three films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'KIMMEL' Fined $395K by FCC for Emergency Alert Misuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/abc-pay-395000-fcc-fine-jimmy-kimmel-live-emergency-alert-misuse-1232481 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMC and Discovery were also hit with fines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:  Trump losing to Biden, Warren, Sanders and Harris...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/457645-fox-news-poll-shows-trump-losing-to-biden-warren-sanders-and-harris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll released Thursday showed President Trump losing head-to-head matchups against four of the top Democratic presidential primary contenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI BLOCKS OMAR, TLAIB FROM ENTERING ISRAEL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/19a6c707c401467d91297e6e027308ee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — With a push from President Donald Trump, Israel on Thursday barred two Muslim-American congresswomen from entering the country for a visit, an extraordinary step bringing the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunderstorm unleashes 18" of hail in Michigan...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/whopping-18-inches-of-hail-accumulates-in-parts-of-michigan/70009085 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had taxidermied tiger, poodle in NYC mansion...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/15/jeffrey-epstein-had-creepy-taxidermied-tiger-poodle-in-ues-mansion-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton in a blue dress was the least of it. Jeffrey Epstein kept a creepy home office in his Upper East Side townhouse that was decorated with a $5.9 million painting of a woman cupping her b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG IOWA LEAD</title>
      <link>https://iowastartingline.com/2019/08/15/poll-elizabeth-warren-jumps-out-to-big-lead-in-the-iowa-caucus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;iowastartingline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Iowa Starting Line-Change Research poll shows a major shake-up in the Iowa Caucus standings as Warren takes a commanding lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Doctors Purposely Misdiagnose Patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2019/08/when-doctors-purposely-misdiagnose-patients/596068/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people say a Michigan doctor falsely diagnosed them with epilepsy. He wouldn’t be the first to lie to patients about how sick they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dale Earnhardt Jr.'s plane crashes... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/sports/2019/08/15/dale-earnhardt-jr-wife-ok-plane-crash-elizabethton-tennessee/2023565001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASCAR legend Dale Earnhardt Jr. and his wife are OK after a plane crash Thursday afternoonÂ at an Elizabethton, Tennessee airport, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water crisis grips US city after lead contamination...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/water-crisis-grips-us-city-after-lead-contamination/ar-AAFQUso</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rushed to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://wcyb.com/news/local/plane-crashes-at-elizabethton-municipal-airport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wcyb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE: The Carter County Sheriff's Office has confirmed that Dale Earnhardt Jr. 's plane crashed at the Elizabethton Municipal Airport. Earnhardt Jr. has been transported to the hospital. The department also says Earnhardt Jr. 's wife Amy Reimann was also on board. The Elizabethton Fire Chief Barry Carrier says everyone survived the crash and none of the injuries were serious. We have exclusive footage sent to us of Dale Earnhardt, Jr. being treated at the scene. Earnhardt, Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gal pal finally found; At IN-N-OUT reading book on 'Deaths of CIA Operatives'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/15/jeffrey-epsteins-gal-pal-ghislaine-maxwell-spotted-at-in-n-out-burger-in-first-photos-since-his-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once spotted, Maxwell — who was sitting alone with a pet pooch — told an onlooker: “Well, I guess this is the last time I’ll be eating here!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese military personnel parade near Hong Kong border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chinese-military-personnel-parade-near-hong-kong-border-055151905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Chinese military personnel waving red flags paraded at a sports stadium in a city across the border from Hong Kong on Thursday, an AFP reporter witnessed. Armoured vehicles were also seen inside the stadium in Shenzhen, with the event taking place as concerns build that China may intervene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff: Escaped without serious injuries...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/dale-earnhardt-jr-family-escape-plane-crash-tennessee/story?id=65000224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NASCAR driver Dale Earnhardt Jr. and his wife and child escaped a plane crash in Tennessee without serious injuries on Thursday, said Carter County Sheriff Dexter Lunceford. The Cessna Citation rolled off the end of a runway after landing at Elizabethton Municipal Airport in Elizabethton,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC told reporter not to 'look too Latina'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/books/2019/08/15/msnbc-reporter-mariana-atencio-boss-told-me-dont-look-too-latina/2017294001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC reporter Mariana Atencio says a higher-up at the company told her to not "look too Latina" at theÂ 2017 White House Correspondents' Dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT MIC: O'Donnell caught saying 'sounds like someone here' during CBS report on opera star...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7361189/Norah-ODonnell-makes-remarks-sexual-harassment-story-Placido-Domingo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Norah O'Donnell could be heard saying 'Sounds like somebody else here' on hot mic during a segment on sexual assault allegations against Placido Domingo on CBS Evening News on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's purge of own national security team almost complete...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/15/politics/dni-coats-gordon-last-day/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Director of National Intelligence Dan Coats and his deputy Sue Gordon leave their offices for the last time on Thursday, it will mark a turning point for an administration that has already endured the highest level of senior staff turnover in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1975 frontman defies Dubai gay laws with kiss...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-49357442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British singer kisses a fan on the lips during a gig in the UAE, where homosexuality is illegal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage After Flags Lowered to Half-Staff on Private Islands...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/trending/2019/08/15/american-flags-lowered-half-staff-jeffrey-epstein-islands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flags on islands belonging to Jeffrey Epstein were lowered to half-staff four days after his [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Attorney Blames 'Soros-Funded Prosecutors' for Increased Violence...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/after-philly-shooting-trump-u-s-attorney-says-soros-funded-prosecutors-responsible-for-uptick-in-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly discovered organ may be lurking under skin...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/08/newly-discovered-organ-may-be-lurking-uinder-your-skin-senses-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Identified in mice, the simple organ most likely exists in humans, too, offering fresh insight into how we experience painful pressure and pricks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle': Woman survives fall from plane after parachute fails...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/montreal/skydiving-accident-quebec-survive-1.5247744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 30-year-old who has experience skydiving is recovering in hospital with several fractures after her parachute failed during her fall from a plane last weekend in Trois-Rivières, Que., but police say her life is not in danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plants can tell time...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/plants-tell-time-even-without-180645367.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plant cells signal between each other in order to agree what time it is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  AXIOS moves into software selling business...</title>
      <link>https://www.theinformation.com/articles/axios-joins-media-push-into-software-with-newsletter-product</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theinformation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Digital media publisher Axios is planning to enter a new business that includes selling software for helping companies create newsletters for their employees. The move comes at a moment when more media businesses are seeking to diversify their revenue through software sales.Axios wants to sell ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasurys drop more...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/15/us-bonds-30-year-treasury-yield-falls-below-2percent-for-first-time-ever.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic drop in long-term U.S. bond yields comes shortly after interest rates on the closely watched 10-year and 2-year Treasurys inverted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAME OVER: Middle-Class, Poor Kids Ditching Youth Sports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uneven-playing-field-middle-class-and-poor-kids-are-ditching-youth-sports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youth sports participation is rising among richer families, as children lower down the ladder exit the field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman pulls gator from yoga pants during stop...</title>
      <link>https://toronto.citynews.ca/2019/08/15/authorities-woman-pulls-gator-from-pants-during-stop-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;toronto.citynews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUNTA GORDA, Fla. — Officials say a Florida woman who pulled a small alligator from her yoga pants during a traffic stop and illegally possessed numerous other wild animals has been sentenced to probation after pleading guilty to four charges. Florida prosecutors say a Charlotte County sheriff’s deputy stopped a pickup truck in May after …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIPAC condemns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/middle-east-north-africa/457568-aipac-pushes-back-against-israel-decision-we</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) on Thursday broke with Israel's decision to bar Democratic Reps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recession question should be isn't 'when' but 'how bad?'</title>
      <link>https://business.financialpost.com/investing/investing-pro/the-recession-question-we-should-be-asking-isnt-when-but-how-bad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;business.financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Chidley: The triggers of previous downturns aren’t entirely the same today, but there is one new near-to-bursting bubble</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the World of Tom Ford...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/man-for-all-seasons-tom-ford</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Ford’s life may be centered in Los Angeles these days, but with his recent appointment as the chairman of the CFDA, he’s flexing global ambitions for American fashion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN GALACTIC reveals first photos of passenger lounge and mission control... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9729382/virgin-galactic-reveal-spaceport-passenger-mission-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIR RICHARD Branson has finally unveiled the Spaceport that he will use to fire space tourists into orbit next year. His wacky space venture Virgin Galactic plans to charge £200,000 a ticket to lau…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO MEAT, NO WATER:  Inside WHOLE FOODS CEO's daily health routine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/inside-whole-foods-ceo-john-mackeys-health-and-fitness-routine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whole Foods co-founder and CEO John Mackey has dedicated his life's work to eating healthy. He says he credits his success to his daily health habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor tensions flare at AMERICAN AIRLINES over hundreds of canceled flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/14/american-airlines-wants-mechanics-unions-to-pay-for-canceled-flights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines wants the union representing its mechanics to cover the airlines' financial losses from hundreds of flight cancellations that American alleges were the result of an "illegal work slowdown."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBT video-makers sue YOUTUBE for discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-49343823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube denies it discriminates on the basis of sexual orientation or gender identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PACKS CROWDS IN NH</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/warren-speaks-to-crowd-of-hundreds-in-franconia/28704327</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren campaigned Wednesday in Franconia as she continues to climb in the New Hampshire polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pull of Yang's Pessimism...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/08/andrew-yang-2020-message/596122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once derided as a “novelty candidate,” the outsider Democrat is poised to hang on longer than many senators and governors in the 2020 primary race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFENSE: Jay-Z Faces Backlash For NFL Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/jay-z-helps-nfl-banish-colin-kaepernick/596146/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former quarterback caused a problem for the league—which turned to the celebrated rapper for assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Nate Silver's war with NYT...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/15/nate-silver-new-york-times-1461666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The paper’s onetime data guru can’t stop kicking his ex-employer for its 2020 polling analysis and supposed capitulation to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPY?  Jeffrey Epstein traveled to Cuba at Fidel Castro's invitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article234009227.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake shook LA skyscrapers so hard some got vertigo...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-14/ridgecrest-earthquake-produced-minutes-of-shaking-new-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from seismic sensors in buildings across Southern California show how the 7.1 Ridgecrest earthquake produced surprisingly long periods of shaking in some areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian tanker 'released by Gibraltar' despite US bid to seize ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/us-iran-oil-tanker-gibraltar-released-gulf-latest-vessel-seized-a9061071.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Amendment Advocates Warn Over 'Red Flag' Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/red-flag-laws-second-amendment-advocates-warn-trump-about-support-for-gun-reform-measure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If he basically tries to dismantle the Second Amendment community, he's going to be a one-termer. I firmly believe that," one activist said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film claims group plotted to infect black Africans with HIV...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/film-claims-group-plotted-infect-black-africans-hiv-020555865.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plot by white mercenaries to spread HIV through black South Africa via a phony vaccination program: it sounds like the stuff of pulp spy novels, but documentary-maker Mads Brugger is clear that this is one sensational conspiracy that actually happened. Jones tells the filmmaker that the group undertook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hepatitis A Races Across Country...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/hepatitis-a-spreads-across-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of the opioid crisis, the highly communicable hepatitis A virus is spreading in more than half the states and making its way into the general public. Underfunded health officials are va…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodyguard on Lifestyle, Cruelty, Suicide...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/08/jeffrey-epsteins-bodyguard-igor-zinoviev-on-his-old-boss.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former UFC fighter Igor Zinoviev went everywhere with Epstein. In his first interview, he says he thinks Epstein had help ending his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthed Recordings...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-14/epstein-tapes-emerge-jeffrey-epstein-describes-his-lifestyle-unearthed-recordings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans fear Trump will lose Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/republicans-concerned-over-trumps-strength-in-arizona-heading-into-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats are eyeing Texas as a longshot pickup in the 2020 presidential race. But Republicans who are keeping an eye on the national electoral landscape say the party should be more concerned that Arizona could go from red to blue this time around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My night with a male sex doll'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/9721275/two-bendy-willies-and-a-brief-moment-of-passion-my-night-with-a-male-sex-doll/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HENRY is tall, dark and handsome, doesn’t answer back and is always up for sex. Only thing is he isn’t real, he’s a male sex doll. Increasing numbers of British men – and women – are se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List of Inconsistencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/08/here-it-is-complete-list-of-inconsistencies-in-prison-policy-surrounding-jeffrey-epsteins-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Veterinarians At High Risk Of Depression, Anxiety, Suicidal Thoughts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-veterinarians-people-who-treat-animals-face-higher-risk-of-mental-health-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that veterinarians and others who work with animals on a daily basis deal with stressful and emotional events that put them at a higher risk of developing mental health conditions such as depression, anxiety, and, in some cases, suicidal thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast, low, hard to stop: NKorea missile tests crank up threat level...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/North-Korea-s-missile-tests-crank-up-the-threat-14305847.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - President Donald Trump has brushed off North Korea's resumption of missile launches, but the volley of tests in the past four months has significantly raised the country's military capabilities and the threat they pose to South Korea and U.S. forces on the peninsula, experts say.  The launches have included at least two new types of short-range ballistic missiles and a mobile multiple-rocket launcher. Pyongyang has also seen fit to show off a submarine that may be intended to carry nuclear warheads.  Trump says he's been told that Kim Jong Un, the North Korean leader, "only smiles when he sees me." But photos released by North Korean state media show the dictator beaming from cheek to cheek at the successful tests.  "There's no question that the 2019 testing campaign that began in April has showcased some quite serious qualitative advancement in North Korean missile capabilities," said Ankit Panda, an adjunct senior fellow in the Defense Posture Project at the Federation of American Scientists. "The core theme across all of the new weapons seems to be survivability, responsiveness, and missile-defense defeat."  The weapons that North Korea has showcased, including a road-mobile short-range ballistic missile known as the KN-23, with a range of at least 280 miles, appear specifically designed to confound South Korea's missile-defense system.  "The three missiles have several things in common: they are solid fuel, they are mobile, they are fast, they fly low, and at least the KN-23 can maneuver in-flight, which is very impressive," said Vipin Narang, an associate professor of political science at MIT.  "Any one of the missiles would pose a challenge to regional and [South Korean] missile defenses given these characteristics. Together, they pose a nightmare."  On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More common in strangulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/jeffrey-epsteins-injuries-more-common-in-victims-of-strangulation-than-hanging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials refuse to comment on autopsy results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal Justices Still Notching Victories Despite Conservative Court...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/14/scotus-conservative-crossovers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court's liberal minority forged winning alliances in unexpected rulings, suggesting the new conservative majority is hardly a cohesive unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi assaulted in Berlin -- second attack in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/rabbi-assaulted-in-berlin-second-such-attack-in-as-many-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incidents are the latest in a wave of racially and religiously motivated crimes against Jews in Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YIELDS FLASH RECESSION WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-us-treasuries-yield/u-s-yield-curve-remains-inverted-for-second-day-idUSKCN1V50KM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. yield curve was inverted for the second straight trading session on Thu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodstock glorified them. Tarantino barbecued them. In 2019, whither the hippie?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2019-08-14/hippie-woodstock-1969-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hippiedom's place in history is still unsettled, 50 years after the original Woodstock and as hippie-hating "Once Upon a Time ... in Hollywood" is in theaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US moves to seize Iranian tanker detained off Gibraltar...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190815-usa-moves-seize-iran-oil-tanker-gibraltar-tehran-london-standoff-persian-gulf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US on Thursday applied for the seizure of an Iranian oil tanker detained near the British overseas territory of Gibraltar, now the centre of a stand-off between Tehran and London, the public prosecutor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALACTIC unveiling mission control for space tourism...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-08-virgin-galactic-unveiling-mission-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spaceport America is no longer just a shiny shell of hope that space tourism would one day launch from this remote spot in the New Mexico desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PACKS CROWDS IN NH</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/warren-matches-sanders-n-h-101516732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democratic presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren drew almost as many supporters as Bernie Sanders during half as many campaign events in New Hampshire this week, as the two New England senators made their pitch to Granite State voters.About 700 people gathered at a Warren town hall in</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
