<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA halts ASTRAZENECA production...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-astrazeneca-johnso-idUSKBN2BR00Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has put Johnson and Johnson in charge of a plant that ruined 15 million doses of its COVID-19 vaccine and has stopped British drugmaker AstraZeneca Plc from using the facility, a senior health official said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000-dolphin 'stampede' off California coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/video-rare-california-coast-1000-dolphin-super-pod-16072983.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rare spectacle dazzled tourists for four hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to pilot 'certificates'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/united-kingdom-coronavirus-certificate-sporting-events-nightclubs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plan aims to post-lockdown economic reopening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greatest NCAA Tourney game ever? Gonzaga's buzzer-beating win vs. UCLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/ncaab/2021/04/03/gonzaga-ucla-top-moments-ncaa-tournament-final-four-game/7081597002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unbeaten Gonzaga defeated No. 11 UCLA in an overtime thriller. Here are the best moments from the men's Final Four contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacies score customer data in jab effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/03/pharmacy-covid-vaccine-customer-data-478977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pharmacy chains hope information from vaccine seekers could translate to new business, while privacy watchdogs are calling for restrictions on the data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Sandra Lee and Andrew Cuomo's split...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/03/inside-sandra-lee-and-andrew-cuomos-split/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friends of Sandra Lee believe that Gov. Cuomo’s cheating and his staff of “mean girls” killed their 14-year romance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle spins donuts in middle of Beltway...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/prince-georges-county/2021/04/watch-vehicle-spins-donuts-in-middle-of-beltway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A car spun donuts in the middle of the beltway in Prince George’s County Saturday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris fears worst of wave still to come...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/paris-medics-fear-worst-covid-054707057.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Covid-19 intensive care unit of the Antony Private Hospital south of Paris, no bed stays free for long and medics wonder when their workload will finally peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wheeled through Cairo streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2635156/pharaohs-golden-parade-cairo-mummies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mummies of 22 ancient Egyptian pharaohs were yesterday wheeled through the streets. Dubbed the Pharaohs’ Golden Parade, the 18 kings and four queens travelled from Cairo’s Egyptian Museum. They…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In apology, AMAZON admits drivers have to 'pee in bottles' ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-za/news/world/in-apology-amazon-admits-some-drivers-have-to-pee-in-bottles/ar-BB1fgYq5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E-commerce giant Amazon has apologized to a US lawmaker after falsely denying that some of its drivers are forced at times to urinate in plastic bottles. The flap started last week with a tweet from Mark Pocan, a Democrat from Wisconsin. "Paying workers $15/hr doesn't make you a 'progressive workplace' when you union-bust &amp; make workers urinate in water bottles," Pocan tweeted, in an apparent reference to Amazon's opposition to efforts to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Golden Parade'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/golden-parade-carries-pharaohs-to-new-home-in-egyptian-capital/ar-BB1fh8RI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A procession of floats carried the mummified remains of 22 pharaohs, including Egypt's most powerful ancient queen, through Cairo Saturday evening, in an eye-catching parade to a new resting place. Dubbed the "Pharaohs' Golden Parade", the 18 kings and four queens travelled in order, oldest first, each aboard a separate vehicle decorated in ancient Egyptian style.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  10 best places in world to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/here-are-the-10-best-places-in-the-world-to-retire-11617116826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International Living recommends these destinations where you can live a healthier and happier life, while spending a lot less money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even with narrow edge in Congress, Biden goes all-out from start...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-narrow-edge-congress-biden-170214460.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his plan for massive investment to create "millions of jobs" coming on the heels of an equally titanic economic stimulus program, President Joe Biden is thinking big in his first weeks in office. He has to -- he knows that his narrow window for action may close as soon as 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON apologizes for denying workers urinate in bottles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/546312-amazon-apologizes-for-tweet-denying-contract-workers-urinate-in-bottles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon on Friday issued an apology for a tweet last week denying claims from some Amazon workers that they were worked so hard that they were forced to urinate in plastic bottles instead of going to the re</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argentine President Tests Positive for Covid; Was Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://english.alarabiya.net/coronavirus/2021/04/04/Argentina-s-President-who-was-vaccinated-tests-positive-for-COVID-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.alarabiya.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Argentina’s President Alberto Fernandez, who received two doses of Russia’s Sputnik V vaccine earlier this year, has tested positive for Covid-19, his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy enters 3-day Easter lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-travel-italy-rome-coronavirus-pandemic-1adf3d6ff48ed02921a3f76073329c21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italy entered a three-day nationwide coronavirus lockdown Saturday to deter Easter travel and get-togethers even as the country's variant-fueled spike in new infections began to wane....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest flash point in virus politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-new-york-data-privacy-immunizations-coronavirus-pandemic-f1c7623849d5458bcda3aed67f4c3d90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — Vaccine passports being developed to verify COVID-19 immunization status and allow inoculated people to more freely travel, shop and dine have become the latest flash point...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly breach could delay decisions about Capitol fencing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-coronavirus-pandemic-98239730a4af17a9f7677980aa218968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The latest deadly breach of the Capitol’s perimeter could delay the gradual reopening of the building’s grounds to the public just as lawmakers were eyeing a return to more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany faces 'crisis of trust' in pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-coronavirus-pandemic-germany-frank-walter-steinmeier-europe-727e8fc5096f1916244fcf20a3951cbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — Germany's president says the country is enduring a “crisis of trust” and urged people to “pull together” as they weather a second Easter amid pandemic restrictions and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE:  BEGIN ANEW</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/italy-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-pope-francis-easter-0e1e76b2250529be81f38a7f8c0efb4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis urged his coronavirus-weary flock to not lose hope even through the continued “dark months” of the pandemic as he celebrated a scaled-back Easter vigil service in St....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffered delusions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-politics-451c5c5154045d404d0db76270f78aac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The man who rammed a car into two officers at a barricade outside the U.S. Capitol, killing one of them before he was shot to death by police, had been suffering from delusions,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 20 arrested in alleged plot against Jordan's King Abdullah II...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/jordanian-royal-detained-in-alleged-plot-against-king-abdullah-ii/ar-BB1fh5Pi </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Bay stares down environmental disaster from phosphate plant; Evacuations ordered...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2632716/piney-point-evacuation-radioactive-water-tampa-bay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAW ENFORCEMENT officials are evacuating Florida residents from their homes due to an “imminent” collapse and release of toxic wastewater. A leak at a Gypsum containment pond near Port Manatee is t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family claim 'football injuries triggered mental illness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2632522/captitol-attack-noah-green-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPITOL attack suspect Noah Green’s family have reportedly suggested his many years of football may have contributed to his declining mental health. Green, 25, once a promising college footba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE IN SECOND PANDEMIC EASTER</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-world-e2-80-99s-second-easter-under-pandemic-brings-more-restrictions-and-a-few-bright-spots/ar-BB1fgQ1n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This time last year, the language of "social distancing" and "flatten the curve" was still novel for many Christian communities and clergy suddenly adjusting to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA reports most passenger screenings since beginning of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tsa-record-screening-pandemic-covid-6e3b1ec5-5a60-4fe9-9403-58cc8b3c215a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers come a day after the CDC released new travel guidelines for fully vaccinated people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Ocasio-Cortez challenge Biden or Harris in 2024?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/546275-will-ocasio-cortez-challenge-biden-or-harris-in-2024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political parties and incumbents underestimate Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) at their own peril.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears grow WW3 could be triggered as Russian military on move...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/fears-grow-ww3-could-triggered-23847342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian military analyst Pavel Felgenhauer has warned WW3 could be sparked by rising tensions between Russia and Ukraine – and things could really kick off in early May</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd trial leaves many Black viewers emotionally taxed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-trials-us-news-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-20138097a2c3719d87187442ff3a7dac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For some it’s too much to watch. Others just can’t turn away. The televised trial of Derek Chauvin, the former white police officer charged in the death of George Floyd, has provoked strong...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confederate symbols prove difficult to remove in many states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/laws-slavery-texas-native-americans-0062fa106a270f7ae9001c7c3598e0f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Just past the gate at an entrance to the Texas Capitol, a large monument honoring the soldiers of the Confederacy looms, with towering statues and an inscription that reads,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming out of the cave: As life creeps back, some feel dread...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/anxiety-fort-lauderdale-coronavirus-pandemic-vacations-caves-b4dd53c4e498116296388c5afa7872b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Dinner reservations are gleefully being made again. Long-canceled vacations are being booked. People are coming together again, in some of the ways they used to....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ: DMX OD'S AND IN GRAVE CONDITION...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/04/03/dmx-suffers-od-overdose-hospital-grave-condition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DMX suffered a drug overdose Friday night and is currently in the hospital ... and the prognosis is not good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is That? 40% Don't Recognize Selves In Mirror Due To Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/body-image-covid-stress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over half the poll (51%) believe the pandemic has negatively affected how they feel about their body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobs report adds to Biden momentum...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/546257-jobs-report-adds-to-biden-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stellar March jobs report is helping President Biden make his case for a major investment in U.S. infrastructure funded by corporate tax hikes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Issue in Divorces: Who Gets the Embryos?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/03/the-latest-issue-in-divorces-who-gets-the-embryos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Peter Goldin, a 44-year-old communications director, and his husband decided to start a family through in vitro fertilization, they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle': Israel Vaccine Success Allows Easter Crowds in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/03/like-a-miracle-israels-vaccine-success-allows-easter-crowds-in-jerusalem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — On Friday morning, in the Old City of Jerusalem, in the limestone alleys of the Christian quarter, it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 'curse of Pharaohs' will be unleashed as royal Egyptian mummies moved...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/fears-curse-pharaohs-unleashed-royal-23845872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3,000-year-old mummies are set to be transferred to a new museum and showcased in a 'golden parade' in Egypt this weekend, but locals fear a curse will be cast on the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet FN Meka, the World's First AI Rapper Who Sells NFTs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/meet-fn-meka-world-first-053125067.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VydiaRapper FN Meka is certainly a product of his times. He drives a gold-plated Rolls-Royce, a Gucci-print Tesla truck, and a slime green Lamborghini. On TikTok, where he has racked up 9 million followers, he smirks as he sits between a woman’s legs and is hand-fed grapes off a vine as a stack of $100 bills are thrown over him.FN Meka seems to follow the modus operandi of other outrageous young musicians attempting to break into the music scene: the flashier, the better. The only difference is that FN Meka isn’t technically real; rather, he’s the self-proclaimed first artificial intelligence robot rapper.He’s already released a handful of semi-successful songs—most recently “Speed Demon,” previously “Internet,” and his most popular song to date, “Moonwalkin’,” which is reminiscent of Tekashi69’s amped-up scream-rap style.The Gorillaz Guide to Surviving a Trump VictoryAnd the virtual artist doesn’t just make music, he also sells non-fungible tokens (NFTs), recently unloading a Lamborghini-styled porta-potty NFT to Dutch DJ Don Diablo for $6,500.FN Meka is part of an emerging trend of virtual influencers. In terms of a business model, he can best be compared to Miquela Sousa, a popular computer-generated image Instagram influencer who’s partnered with brands such as MINI, landed covers of magazines, “attended” fashion weeks, and also dipped their toe in the music waters.Of course, there are real people behind FN Meka, including the team at Vydia that provides a platform for his record label Factory New, which only has virtual artists. It can be a bit hard to wrap your head around, but Anthony Martini, co-founder of Factory New, explained to The Daily Beast that the concept of FN Meka is no different than the DJ Marshmello, Gorillaz, or even 50 Cent.“You look at any great human artist, the more fantastic you are, the more of a character that you are,” Martini said. “Any great artist, you’re buying into some sort of story. This is just the next level of actually doing that. There’s been some precedents in the past, even for pseudo virtual characters. You can look at Gorillaz. You could look at a guy like Marshmello—he’s not real for all intents and purposes either. He could be a digital being too and it wouldn’t make a difference to the fans of the music. We’re trying to blur those lines even more and trying to bring everyone to the future.”Roy LaManna, co-founder and CEO of Vydia, agrees with Martini, using Tekashi69 as a further example of how larger-than-life artists are basically just caricatures of themselves.“I think that he’s the epitome of what we’re talking about here. He’s kind of like a meme,” LaManna said. “The music, primarily in the early days, was co-written or ghostwritten by his producer. There’s Daniel Hernandez, who is the real guy and then there’s the Tekashi character, which is almost a cartoon-like character that has people compelled and drawn into his storyline. So, the question is whether or not Daniel Hernandez’s character Tekashi69 could exist in a virtual space, and I think Anthony and his team are proving that the answer is yes.”LaManna brings up BTS, One Direction, and Britney Spears to question how important the human element is compared to the storyline and content the artist puts out. Using Spears as an example, LaManna said, “It’s a personality. She arguably wasn’t necessarily the best singer; a lot of the music was written by other people. Then it went into a storyline, you know, she dated Justin Timberlake, it was a whole thing that people really got invested in.”“So, what portion of that is contingent on the human factor?” he asked. “I think it’s less than people realize, and it’s being tested today because the technology has gotten to a certain point in which this is a viable option. I think we’re just seeing the beginning stages of this stuff.”Martini chimed in to add that most entertainers’ images today are manufactured by a label or a management team. “At least in the beginning, when you’re trying to put a certain narrative out there and you’re building a brand,” he said. “We’re doing the same thing, except we’re not limited to the human world, or the human form. We’re going to take that old idea of building brands and building a storyline behind some of these artists and just take it to the next level.”There’s definitely still a process of trial and error, Martini admitted, mostly because the anonymous creator behind FN Meka really never intended for him to be a rapper, originally creating the character to help sell his popular virtual items.“He’s a creative genius that comes from the video game world,” Martini explained. “His background is in making digital skins and virtual items. He was almost selling NFTs before they were NFTs. But he created FN Meka almost as a platform for some of these insane items that he was creating and then it sort of just morphed into FN Meka.”In the early stages of FN Meka’s music career, the robot artist released other demos, which ended up being taken down to maintain quality control. Martini said if FN Meka is going to be taken seriously, their team needs to make sure his work is of the highest quality. “At the bottom line, if you’re going to be in the music space, we want the music to be able to compete with any artists that are out there, whether they’re human or virtual,” he said.FN Meka primarily lives on TikTok, where his videos have been watched a billion times and most importantly, users are actively engaging with his content. (He has an Instagram too, but a comparatively smaller following with only 206K followers.) His fans primarily come to gawk at his hypebeast designs, such as a Starbucks-themed espresso-making PS5, a Louis Vuitton baby stroller, an Apple AirPods shotgun, and a Gucci Batmobile.Both Factory New and Vydia are using FN Meka as a sort of marketing test to gauge audiences’ interest in these types of characters and to see if these virtual personas can turn a profit in the music industry or even in the NFT space.“FN Meka basically has the ability on TikTok to test-market the virality of songs by releasing small snippets of songs, asking people when he should release it, what he should release, what should be put in as a component of it, whether it’s an NFT, or any other kind of designs that go along to help fuel this,” LaManna said. “Then [we can] really look at the data and say, alright, this is working.”Martini believes FN Meka has the potential to do so much more besides music, including being an ambassador for various companies. “We’ve been approached by a ton of brands, some pretty prestigious, luxury fashion brands,” he said. “There’s a lot of interest in the space for the type of things that we do, but for Meka it’s really about finding things that fit organically with his fanbase, his brand aesthetics.”That’s why partnering with virtual streetwear brand RTFKT studios to help hawk NFT items was a perfect fit, tying in the sale of the Lamborghini toilet with the release of his latest single on the NFT action site, SuperRare.But the overall hope, LaManna explained, is that FN Meka won’t just be around for a few years, but for a lifetime: “The character of Batman transcends Adam West, transcends Michael Keaton, Christian Bale, and everyone.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious rumblings from inside Mars detected by NASA...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/mysterious-rumblings-from-inside-of-mars-detected-by-nasa-lander-12263691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space agency's scientists believe the seismic events are caused by a sudden release of energy from the planet's interior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside supersonic presidential jet that can fly TWICE speed of sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2631486/inside-supersonic-presidential-jet-speed-sound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is what a supersonic presidential plane that could hit speeds of 1,380mph as it jets at nearly twice the speed of sound could look like. New renderings show the incredible supersonic president…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NATION OF ISLAM FOLLOWER'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9431911/How-college-football-star-lost-job-devout-Nation-Islam-follower.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noah Green's descent into paranoia and deeply-troubling mental illness began in 2019, it appears, and rapidly worsened this year when he went to Botswana and attempted suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orgies, blackmail, extortion, Iran hostages...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/matt-gaetzs-alleged-scandals-include-orgies-blackmail-extortion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged orgy with prostitutes. Accusations of sex with an underage girl. A trophy photo of a woman wearing only a hula hoop. And a convoluted extortion plot involving a likely dead American host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills store let criminals stash guns, drugs, cash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/beverly-hills-store-let-criminals-013647942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI and DEA raid of an Olympic Boulevard strip mall found safe deposit boxes crammed with contraband, indictment says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unique 4/3/21 date draws lines for Vegas wedding licenses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/occasions-weddings-couples-marriage-las-vegas-39d3418e06b212a63ade2e61eda295dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Soon-to-be newlyweds lined up out the door of the marriage license office in Las Vegas on Friday, ahead of a unique date to tie the knot: 4/3/21. Nearly 700 couples obtained...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAR RAMMING,  EMERGED WITH KNIFE</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2628651/capitol-lockdown-suspect-knife-car-barrier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect who was shot dead by cops in the fatal car-and-knife rampage at the US Capitol on Friday was a devoted follower of ‘Nation of Islam’ leader Louis Farrakhan, according to his…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'END TIMES'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/suspect-custody-after-car-rams-two-officers-u-s-capitol-n1262917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slain officer, William Evans, was an 18-year-veteran of the force and a member of the Capitol Division’s First Responder’s Unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NATION OF ISLAM FOLLOWER'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9431125/Capitol-cops-injured-car-smashes-barrier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capitol police officer killed by a knife-wielding driver in Washington DC on Friday has been identified as veteran cop Billy Evans. Evans had worked for the Capitol Police for 18 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece of SPACEX rocket debris lands at Washington state farm...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-04-piece-spacex-rocket-debris-washington.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A piece of burning rocket debris seen streaking across the Pacific Northwest sky last week crashed on a farm in eastern Washington state, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROTHER NOAH X KILLS CAPITOL COP</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/02/suspect-who-smashed-into-barrier-at-us-capitol-identified-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver who killed a US Capitol cop before he was gunned down by police is a Nation of Islam devotee from Indiana, according to reports and his social media. Noah Green, 25, who may have been li…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach partygoers in Barcelona defy restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210403104641-ah1sh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SPAIN-TOURISM (PIX):Beach partygoers in Spain's Barcelona defy COVID-19 restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen kidnap pastor during FACEBOOK live ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210403014317-21gqq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-VIOLENCE/:Gunmen kidnap Haiti pastor during Facebook live church ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Swarms of Ships, Beijing Tightens Grip on South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/03/with-swarms-of-ships-beijing-tightens-its-grip-on-south-china-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese ships settled in like unwanted guests who wouldn’t leave. As the days passed, more appeared. They were simply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot artist sells art for $688,888, now eyeing music career...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/music-hong-kong-robotics-asia-pacific-3e9cf6949ad3cd8c5884e63b6630b774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Sophia is a robot of many talents — she speaks, jokes, sings and even makes art. In March, she caused a stir in the art world when a digital work she created as part of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aiming big, Joe looking to restore faith in government...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lyndon-johnson-e1980730f351435701e80dfa4c001800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As President Joe Biden preaches patience but acts with urgency, his vision of the powers of the Oval Office is quickly taking shape, modeled after Democratic predecessors who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some dying while awaiting jab...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immunizations-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-veterans-d43aade61cf70abe1f9de070a8d1280b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of hoping to receive a COVID-19 immunization and then weeks of fighting the illness after one never came, Air Force veteran Diane Drewes was down to her last few breaths at a hospice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California OKs indoor sports, concerts as cases plunge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-nba-theater-los-angeles-lakers-ed9645feef26e713d4a84aaa189791dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Sports, theater and music fans will be able to take their seats again in California as the state's coronavirus cases plummet and vaccinations jump. After a...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
