<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Restore Function In Brains Of Dead Pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/04/17/714289322/scientists-restore-some-function-in-the-brains-of-dead-pigs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cells regained a startling amount of function, but the brains didn't have activity linked with consciousness. Ethicists see challenges to assumptions about the irreversible nature of brain death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVERSATIONS WITH WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/concerns-among-some-white-house-aides-said-to-grow-on-eve-of-mueller-report/ar-BBW2HE5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 60 companies paid no federal income tax on $79,000,000,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/amazon-netflix-chevron-ibm-federal-taxes-trump-tax-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In total, the 60 companies zeroed out their federal income taxes on $79 billion in U.S. pretax income, according to the study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just one in 50 people can see stars as Nature intended......</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6930051/Starry-skies-masked-veil-light-pollution-cosmic-census-shows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two per cent of the UK were able to gaze at ‘truly dark skies’ while 57 per cent struggled to count more than 120 stars, the research by Campaign to Protect Rural England found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver who rescued Thai soccer team now missing in cave...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/diver-who-helped-free-thai-soccer-team-now-missing-in-tenn-cave/5256366/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man was reported missing from the Mill Pond Cave early Wednesday in Jackson County in northern Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires face 'yellow vest' scorn over cathedral pledges...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/04/17/billionaires-face-yellow-vest-scorn-cathedral-pledges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire French tycoons faced a mounting backlash on Wednesday over tax breaks on their huge donations to restore Notre-Dame, as Yellow Vest protestors said the hundreds of millions of euros should be spent on tackling France's social problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awaiting trial and under gag, Roger Stone still talking...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/politics/roger-stone-life-under-gag-order/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his recent court-approved tour through Florida, Roger Stone fielded questions about the raid on his home, the media coverage of his case and the plight of his former business partner and 2016 Trump campaign chair Paul Manafort -- all while trying not to obviously run afoul of his gag order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to clone extinct horse using 42,000-year-old blood...</title>
      <link>https://siberiantimes.com/science/casestudy/news/unique-in-palaeontology-liquid-blood-found-inside-a-prehistoric-42000-year-old-foal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;siberiantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STRANGER THINGS' Creators Fail To Get Plagiarism Case Tossed; Trial Set...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/stranger-things-duffer-brothers-lawsuit-plagiarism-trial-1202597763/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third season of Stranger Things is set to launch on Netflix on July 4th, but series creators the Duffer Brothers are probably more focused on another date after a judge today rejected their att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why Media Dumped Beto for Buttigieg...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/17/media-dumped-beto-mayor-pete-buttigieg-226660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists love a candidate who loves them back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Strait Tension Rising: 'Will Not Bow'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/17/cross-strait-tension-rising-taiwanese-official-declares-island-will-not-bow-to-intimidation-of-the-chinese/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between the Chinese communists on the mainland of China and capitalists in the democracy of Taiwan are rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast food chain tests CBD-infused burger...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com/article/life/food/carls-jr-to-test-cbd-infused-burger-in-denver-on-420/73-0ac4139d-a2e0-438c-b7ce-bb3930451620</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rocky Mountain High: CheeseBurger Delight (CBD) will be sold for one day only on April 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELECT LAWMAKERS VIEW WITHOUT REDACTIONS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/439410-feds-doj-will-allow-some-lawmakers-to-view-mueller-report-without</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice will allow some members of Congress to view a copy of special counsel Robert Mueller’s report “without certain redactions,” federal prosecutors said in a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite images show activity at nuke site...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/north-korea-nuclear-plant-satellite-photos-reprocessing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images from last week show movement at North Korea's main nuclear site that could be associated with the reprocessing of radioactive material into bomb fuel, a U.S. think tank said on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone-Assembly Tycoon Presidency Bid May Shake Up Taiwan-China Relations...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/iphone-assembly-tycoon-launches-bid-for-taiwans-presidency-after-consulting-sea-goddess-11555508498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwanese billionaire Terry Gou, CEO of iPhone assembler Foxconn, declared his candidacy for president of Taiwan, in a marked shift for the island’s politics, his company and, potentially, relations with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having sex could cure hayfever, scientists claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/health/sex-could-help-cure-hayfever-scientists-claim-a4119881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having a healthy sex life could help alleviate hay fever symptoms, according to a team of scientists. Researchers in Iran found that the reproductive system is linked to the nasal system.  They said that sex constricts blood vessels in the nose and eyes, which causes eyes to stop streaming and helps unblock stuffy noses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Pitcher goes full 'MATRIX' to avoid line-drive to face...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlb.com/news/collin-mchugh-makes-matrix-like-move</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND -- Collin McHugh literally bent over backwards to help the Astros turn a double play Tuesday night, and, in the process, prompted a shrewd comparison from the home-plate umpire.   In the second inning of Houston's 9-1 victory Tuesday night over the A's, Oakland's Kendrys Morales lined a 91 mph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor faces prosecution for instructing students to make ecstacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2019/04/17/national/crime-legal/professor-western-japan-says-instructed-students-produce-mdma/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pharmaceutical science professor at a university in Shikoku was referred to prosecutors Tuesday for allegedly instructing his students to produce the syn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Peru president shoots himself as police try to arrest..</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6473eb980f4c45f88312070a8d048fd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMA, Peru (AP) — Former Peruvian President Alan Garcia shot himself in the head and died Wednesday as officers waited to arrest him in a massive graft probe that has put the country's most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elusive molecule, first in Universe, detected in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/826/elusive-molecule-first-universe-detected-space-doc-1fq04m1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  SAMSUNG fold screen breaks after day of use...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/4/17/18411510/samsung-galaxy-fold-broken-screen-debris-dust-hinge-flexible-bulge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yikes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese block visit of Trump confidant...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/china-denies-visa-to-us-expert-michael-pillsbury-1bf32caa-2b4c-422b-bac3-19bb20c439b0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese experts seeking to visit the U.S. have also been rejected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar bear lost in Russia, hundreds of miles from home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/880824c34e324626a037847474d1dbe4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Residents of a village in Russia's far eastern Kamchatka Peninsula were stunned by the sight of a polar bear prowling for food hundreds of miles away from its usual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naval Academy To Bar Trans Students...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/04/17/naval-academy-will-bar-transgender-students-in-fall-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Naval Academy will ban people who are transgender from attending the school, beginning with the 2020 school year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both sides want Weinstein hearing closed to press, public...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/entertainment/both-sides-want-weinstein-hearing-closed-to-press-public/article_aa4d856f-8158-5cd0-b235-1fb803386a41.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Both sides in Harvey Weinstein's sexual assault case want the media and the public barred from the disgraced movie mogul's next court appearance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK working on voice assistant...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/17/facebook-building-voice-assistant-to-rival-amazon-alexa-and-apple-siri.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team in Redmond, Washington, is working to build a competitor to Alexa, Siri, and the Google Assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Brexit Party opens up lead in European elections...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brexit-party-opens-lead-european-elections-poll-154527248.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brexit Party set up by anti-EU firebrand Nigel Farage is leading Britain's other political parties ahead of European Parliament elections in May, according to an opinion poll published on Wednesday. The new party, which formally launched its campaign for next month's votes on Friday, has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron to executive produce boxing series...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c415f2b2ceb148d4975be3ce31730e18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — LeBron James is getting into the boxing business. James is an executive producer of "40 Days," a documentary series about the buildup to big fights that will debut with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITISH AIRWAYS yanks FT after critical coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressgazette.co.uk/british-airways-has-stopped-offering-financial-times-over-coverage-of-airline-source-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressgazette.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Airways has stopped stocking the Financial Times in a reaction to the paper's journalism, a source has claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning strike at Acropolis injures 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190417-lightning-strike-acropolis-greece-injures-four</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lightning strike at Acropolis, Greece, injures four</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared electric scooters surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/deec1b3bc84e41b88fb41aba0ea83c16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Electric scooters are overtaking station-based bicycles as the most popular form of shared transportation outside transit and cars in the U.S. Riders took 38.5 million trips...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare look at West Point Mint's massive gold vaults...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/west-point-mint-gold-inside-look</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About an hour and a half&amp;rsquo;s drive north from New York City lies a treasure &amp;ndash; the gold kind. But it&amp;rsquo;s not one that you can go and find.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Biden aide: 'Everything going ahead as scheduled'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/politics/biden-aide-hill-democrats-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top aide to former Vice President Joe Biden met with Democrats on Capitol Hill on Wednesday to remind them of Biden's work in the 2018 midterm elections in a not-so-subtle nod to the 2020 race ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar doing FOX NEWS town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/439313-klobuchar-to-appear-in-fox-news-town-hall-in-may</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News announced on Wednesday that it will feature a town hall with 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Sen. Amy Klobuchar (D-Minn.) next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds swarm NYC streets in censorship protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Over-100-New-Yorkers-Will-Pose-Nude-508656351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This June, artist Spencer Tunick has organized an event to challenge Facebook and Instagram’s “Community Guidelines” by organizing a large-scale nude photography shoot in New York City called #WeTheNipple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant in coma after contracting measles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/health/measles-israel-flight-attendant/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli flight attendant has slipped into a coma after contracting measles, according to health officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Starr Fears Anti-Trump Screed...</title>
      <link>https://video.foxnews.com/v/6027126662001/#sp=show-clips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many questions have been raised about the political leanings of special counsel Robert Mueller's staff and their freedom to write whatever they want, former independent counsel Ken Starr says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Laguna Beach Votes To Keep Patriotic Patrol Cars After Debate...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/04/16/laguna-beach-american-flag-police-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's official. The red, white and blue will stay on Laguna Beach police patrol cars. The decision followed a debate. Some people wondered if it was even appropriate to place an abstract version of the flag on patrol cars. Stacey Butler reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHASE Bank shuts down 'alt-right' accounts...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2019/04/major-u-s-bank-shuts-down-alt-right-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chase Bank is shutting down accounts of people and organizations with controversial political views, according to an undercover investigation by James O’Keefe’s Project Veritas. O’Keefe’s latest probe found that Chase, without explanation, abruptly closed the account of a political activist that had existed for 15 years in good standing. Enrique Tarrio, chairman of the Proud […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORPORATE CENSORSHIP ALARM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-review-repeat-offender-11555455821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hollywood-connected libertine takes aim at liberals and then trolls them with some well-worn conservative tropes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PSYCHO' AUTHOR RIPS TRUMP HATING CRAZIES!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/bret-easton-ellis-tells-spoiled-children-liberals-how-to-deal-with-trump-he-was-elected-president-get-over-it'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE HOLLYWOOD  HYSTERICS...</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.com/article/bret-easton-ellis-white-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My job isn’t to trigger millennials into hysteria," Ellis says, "but I have to say that when it happens, it’s rather delicious."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCUSED OF POACHING 'MADAME X' PERSONA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/apr/15/madame-x-madonna-new-album-alter-ego</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a Sargent painting to a miffed DJ, Madonna is just the latest woman to adopt the moniker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suprise Beyonce release wrecks rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/17/beyonce-drops-surprise-film-and-album-goes-straight-to-number-1-wrecks-madonnas-launch-of-new-medellin-single</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beyonce is back! Her 40 track live “Homecoming” album was dropped overnight by Sony/Columbia and is number 1 on the iTunes album chart. In two places– Number 1 and Number 5. Like,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK PORN BAN SET FOR SUMMER...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/uk-porn-ban-july-deadline-when-date-online-websites-adult-age-verification-a8874181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 60: MADONNA ATTEMPTS COMEBACK OF THE CENTURY!</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8507435/madonna-madame-x-album-what-we-know</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna is coming. On Sunday (April 14), the pop icon announced the title of her fourteenth studio album, Madame X, after two weeks of teasing the project on Instagram. While a release date has yet to be announced, here’s everything we know about the Material Girl’s first LP since 2015’s Rebel Heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIGGERS WITH FIRST NON-FICTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/White-Bret-Easton-Ellis/dp/0525656308/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW SONG TRIBUTE TO MEDELLIN... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/music/2019/04/14/madonna-new-music-madame-x/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The queen is back. Madonna announced Sunday her long-awaited return to pop music, unveiling a mysterious Instagram video in which…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER EDITS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f10d72362c374301b6505459b23bbd7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The special counsel's Trump-Russia report will be out on Thursday for all to see. But not all of it. The Democrats' demands for a full, unredacted version of Robert...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circus from hell forces tormented bears and monkeys to dance, do tricks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8881263/north-korea-circus-tormented-bears-monkeys-dance/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTURBING footage has emerged showing bears and monkeys being forced to dance and do tricks in a vile North Korean circus. Aussie Mark Woodman, 42, was taken to the circus in Pyongyang as part of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 HOURS</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/white-house-braces-mueller-report-obstruction-questions-linger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is bracing for the public’s first glimpse at some of Mueller’s findings, but Trump’s odds of securing a second term are unlikely to change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-tax Republicans softening on idea of gas tax increase?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/latest-news/article229287359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of texts, emails about Jussie Smollett probe made public by State's Attorney office...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/ct-met-jussie-smollett-kim-foxx-documents-20190416-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late Tuesday, Foxx’s office made public hundreds of internal texts and emails on the Smollett case to the Chicago Tribune in response to public-records requests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just one in 50 people can see stars as Nature intended...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6930051/Starry-skies-masked-veil-light-pollution-cosmic-census-shows.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two per cent of the UK were able to gaze at ‘truly dark skies’ while 57 per cent struggled to count more than 120 stars, the research by Campaign to Protect Rural England found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glitch signalled blaze in wrong location...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/notre-dame-fire-cathedral-fund-074833496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters lost valuable time in reaching the blaze at Notre Dame after a computer glitch sent investigators to the wrong part of the cathedral, according to French reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete responds to protesters yelling about 'Sodom and Gomorrah'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/439236-buttigieg-responds-to-protesters-yelling-about-sodom-and-gomorrah</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential hopeful Pete Buttigieg (D) was recently confronted by two protesters shouting about the biblical cities of Sodom and Gomorrah.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Couple Forces Day Laborer To Have Sex At Gunpoint...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/day-laborer-assault-745319</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 16--An Arizona couple is charged with luring a day laborer to their Phoenix home and forcing the man to have sex at gunpoint with the female suspect, an assault that the male suspect described</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American in line to become next Usain Bolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/2019/04/17/noah-lyles-usain-bolt-track/3148550002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Noah Lyles had the world's fastest time in the 200 meters last year, and hasn't lost a race at that distance since the 2016 Olympic trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Brightest ever seen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Possible-Meteor-Fireball-Spotted-in-Skies-Over-Maryland-DC-Virginia-508686551.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people in the Mid-Atlantic and New England reported they looked up on Tuesday night and saw a meteor hurtling through the skies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireball streaks across DC skies...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Fireball-streaks-across-Washington-skies-late-13773923.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A bright fireball streaked across the skies in the Washington region late Tuesday night.  People throughout the District of Columbia, Maryland and Virginia indicated that it seemed close to them.  "Did anyone else just see the fireball in the sky in Ellicott City/Marriottsville?!!" someone asked on Twitter around 11 p.m.  Many people apparently did, throughout the region.  A man in the District reported "a huge bright Fireball with bright blue fire falling very close to Capitol Hill at around 11:30pm. "  In a message to a reporter, Kumar Shrestha said he was certain that a search of the area might find its remnants.  "It was very very close," he said.  A woman in the Arlington area exclaimed as follows in a Tweet"Guys!! That was a #FIREBALL that just came shooting through the sky- going due South along the #Potomac."  An Alexandria resident said she saw a large fireball "fall from the" sky.  The American Meteor Society, a clearinghouse for fireball reports, listed a dozen from Maryland and Virginia. Reports were also received at about the same time from other parts of the country.  Estimates of sighting times ranged from about 10:45 p.m. to 11:30 p. m. EDT.  Several fireball photos were posted on twitter feeds late Tuesday and early Wednesday.  Some of the reports to the meteor society indicated that the fireball made a relatively small visual impact. The accounts classed the experience as only one on a scale of five.  However, a witness in Fairfax County rated it as a three.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When die 'you know you're dead,' scientist claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/when-you-die-you-know-youre-dead-because-your-brain-keeps-working-scientist-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We know we are dead when we die because our brains keep working to make us aware of what's happening around us, haunting new research suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches new attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6932005/Trump-launches-new-Twitter-attack-24-hours-Mueller-report-drops.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump launched a new attack on the FBI ahead of the release of Special Counsel Robert Mueller's report, again labeling them 'dirty cops' and claiming he's a victim of a witch hunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What was saved -- and lost...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2c082238d29f4584a9035d4ed842680f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — More than simply an iconic cathedral and jewel of Gothic architecture, Notre Dame was a treasure trove, housing priceless and irreplaceable marvels of immense religious, artistic,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubts rise over Macron's 5-year plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/232c126bee2e462aa8787ac956f92c3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Nearly $1 billion in donations have poured in for the vast restoration of the fire-ravaged Notre Dame cathedral — but a pledge by French President Emmanuel Macron that it will be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For its health and yours, keep cat indoors...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/health-yours-keep-cat-indoors-231058784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one running argument among cat lovers is now over: Whiskers, Lucy and Tigger are definitely better off staying indoors, scientists reported Wednesday. Pet cats allowed outdoors, in fact, are nearly three times as likely to become infected with pathogens or parasites than those confined to quarters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diet Rich in Red Meat Linked to Earlier Death...</title>
      <link>https://medicalresearch.com/author-interviews/diet-rich-in-red-meat-linked-to-earlier-death/48624/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalresearch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It seems that it is especially detrimental to consume a diet that is very high in animal protein, especially meat, and at the same time low in plant protein sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dazzles East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://bnonews.com/index.php/2019/04/meteor-lights-up-night-sky-along-the-u-s-east-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bnonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A meteor was seen along the U.S. East Coast on late Tuesday night, witnesses say. The white streak of light was visible in Washington, D.C., Maryland, New Jersey, and several other states. It happened at 10:57 p.m. ET on Tuesday when witnesses in multiple states reported seeing a “fireball” in the night sky. Steve Chazin […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Outbreak Upends Passover Traditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/measles-outbreak-upends-passover-traditions-11555502400 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As New York health officials fight outbreak in ultra-Orthodox communities, they predict a rise in cases after the holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pained Pope pays tribute to firefighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-notredame-pope/pained-pope-pays-tribute-to-notre-dame-firefighters-idUSKCN1RT0PW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Wednesday thanked rescuers who put their lives at risk to salvag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precious rooster statue found 'battered' in debris...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190417-notre-dames-precious-rooster-statue-found-battered-debris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Notre-Dame's precious rooster statue found 'battered' in debris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS warns of future attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6931361/ISIS-fanatics-warn-future-attack-fire-ravaged-Notre-Dame.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extremist media group published the graphic (pictured) showing flames in front of the Paris cathedral's bell towers, which survived Monday's blaze, alongside a warning: 'Wait for the next'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Too Powerful? Its Merchants Starting to Wonder...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/is-amazon-too-powerful-its-merchants-are-starting-to-wonder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bezos Disputes Amazonâ€™s Market Power. But His Merchants Feel the Pinch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trudeau Bloc Takes Shape With Conservative Win in Alberta...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/anti-trudeau-bloc-takes-shape-with-conservative-win-in-alberta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Trudeau Bloc Takes Shape With Conservative Win in Alberta</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump makes moves to resist subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/439245-trump-makes-moves-to-resist-congressional-subpoenas-for-financial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's lawyers are preparing to do battle with Congress over a number of issues the new Democratic majority is seeking to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France launches global contest to design new spire...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/investigators-probe-notre-dame-inferno-donations-pour-084844411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France will invite architects from around the world to submit designs for rebuilding the spire of Notre-Dame cathedral that was destroyed in a devastating blaze, Prime Minister Edouard Philippe said Wednesday. The goal is "to give Notre-Dame a new spire that is adapted to the techniques and the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bare-faced cheat: Women 'better at hiding infidelity'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bare-faced-cheat-women-better-hiding-infidelity-043250430.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Western Australia took a group of 1,500 people and showed them pictures of 189 Caucasian adults (101 men and 88 women), having first asked them if they had been unfaithful to their partners. The scientists wanted to examine not only whether men and women could spot potential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 100 Most Influential People...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/collection/100-most-influential-people-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungry for change, Ukrainians set to elect comedian as next president...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190417054638-xyhru</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-ELECTION/PREVIEW (PREVIEW, PIX):PREVIEW-Hungry for change, Ukrainians set to elect comedian as next president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea nuke site shows signs of activity...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190416220609-cxof9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-NUCLEAR/REPORT (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Satellite images may show reprocessing activity at North Korea nuclear site -U.S. researchers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuma, Arizona declares state of emergency over surge of illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/16/yuma-arizona-declares-state-emergency-over-surge-m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuma, a city on the U.S.-Mexico border in Arizona, declared a state of emergency Tuesday, saying it cannot handle the crush of illegal immigrants the government is being forced to release onto its streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRACLE: Most interior intact...</title>
      <link>https://www.theepochtimes.com/notre-dame-cathedral-interior-is-miraculously-intact-after-devastating-blaze_2881664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theepochtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Notre-Dame Cathedral in Paris, which was undergoing renovations, suffered extensive damage on Monday, April 15, 2019, after ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craftsmen built Notre Dame eight centuries ago. Now robots may save...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattlepi.com/news/article/Craftsmen-built-Notre-Dame-eight-centuries-ago-13773005.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattlepi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the first images of charred wreckage inside the Notre Dame cathedral appeared online Tuesday, engineers around the world said one observation was already clear: To return the ancient structure to its glorious past, builders will likely have turn to cutting-edge technology that many associate with the future.  Even before engineers had been able to access the deepest corners of the still-smoldering structure, design experts, preservationists and engineers were contemplating which modern technologies might be brought to bear to restore one of Europe's most iconic structures to its fabled past.  It's a speculative exercise, they admit, but one that is to be expected with the future of a UNESCO World Heritage Site at stake.  The rebuilding effort will likely draw upon expertise gleaned from disasters like the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear disaster in Japan and the Brazilian National Museum fire, where experimental robots and new digital tools have been used to go places people cannot safely venture and replicate detailed artifacts lost to fire.  Throughout the rebuilding effort, experts say, engineers and preservationists will be forced to wrestle with an ever-present question.  "How do they meld brand new 21st century technologies with ancient craftsmanship and building trades in ways that keep the cathedral preserved and alive?" said Katherine Malon-France, the interim chief preservation officer of the National Trust for Historic Preservation, a privately funded nonprofit based in Washington. "This is going to be a very interesting intersection of technology and craft, and the world will be closely watching how they pull it off."  Some of the technology that will be used to restore Notre Dame has already been on display. As a wall of orange flames roared across the cathedral's roof Monday, and hundreds of firefighters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/17/politics/bernie-sanders-midwestern-trump-voters-2020/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders guessed right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: Hispanics to Outpace Blacks as Largest Voting Minority in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/16/pew-research-hispanics-to-outpace-black-americans-as-largest-voting-minority-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hispanic Americans are set to outpace black Americans as the largest voting minority group in the 2020 election for the first time ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group of 170 Surrender at Texas Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/04/16/photos-group-170-migrants-surrender-at-texas-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McALLEN, Texas – A group of 170 migrants from Central America surrendered to U.S. authorities shortly after crossing the Rio Grande.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bernie or Bust' Voters Create Predicament for Dems in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-bust-apos-voters-create-080000566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The fierce loyalty Bernie Sanders inspires in his supporters is creating a dilemma for the Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some see Jesus in flames...</title>
      <link>https://heavy.com/news/2019/04/jesus-christ-notre-dame-flames-fire-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heavy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people have started to spot visions of Jesus Christ within photos of the Notre Dame fire. See the photos here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: Barr sowing public mistrust...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/16/judge-barr-mistrust-mueller-1278030</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;The attorney general has created an environment that has caused a significant part of the public … to be concerned,&amp;quot; a district court judge said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists test gene editing on US patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/04/16/712402435/first-u-s-patients-treated-with-crispr-as-gene-editing-human-trials-get-underway</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This could be a crucial year for the powerful gene-editing technique CRISPR as researchers start testing it in patients to treat diseases such as cancer, blindness and sickle cell disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbine threat by woman with gun shuts Denver-area schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/04/16/jefferson-county-schools-lockout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials secured schools across the Denver area Tuesday as the FBI and local police hunted for a woman “infatuated with (the) Columbine school shooting” who had traveled to Colorado th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison smuggling ring: Guards and inmates trade drugs, phones for sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/crime/bs-md-prison-corruption-20190416-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities dismantled yet another ring of guards and inmates allegedly peddling heroin, cellphones and pornography-loaded flash drives behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Great Whites flee when Orcas arrive, don't return for year...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-04-white-sharks-areas-orcas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research from Monterey Bay Aquarium and partner institutions published today in Nature Scientific Reports challenges the notion that great white sharks are the most formidable predators in the ocean. The study "Killer Whales Redistribute White Shark Foraging Pressure On Seals" shows how the great white hunter becomes the hunted, and the elephant seal, the common prey of sharks and orcas, emerges as the winner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dershowitz wanted trial over sex trafficking accusations -- gets one...</title>
      <link>https://abovethelaw.com/2019/04/dershowitz-wanted-a-trial-over-sex-trafficking-accusations-hes-getting-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abovethelaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boies Schiller brings powerhouse talent to bear in the fallout of sex-trafficking matter.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
