<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Dark Patterns' Push FACEBOOKGOOGLE Users Towards Less Privacy...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/06/27/study-calls-out-dark-patterns-in-facebook-and-google-that-push-users-towards-less-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More scrutiny than ever is in place on the tech industry, and while high-profile cases like Mark Zuckerberg's appearance in front of lawmakers garner headlines, there are subtler forces at work. This study from a Norway watchdog group eloquently and painstakingly describes the ways that companies l…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITE AIDS blast Barry Manilow tunes to deter vagrants...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/28/rite-aids-are-blasting-barry-manilow-tunes-to-deter-vagrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He writes the songs that make people run. Some Rite Aid stores in California have taken to blasting Barry Manilow tunes as part of a plan to make loiterers scramble. Employees told the Wall Street …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>575 Arrested In Capitol Office Building...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/28/dem-congresswoman-among-anti-trump-protesters-arrested-inside-capitol-office-building.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Democratic Rep. Pramila Jayapal is among the numerous female protesters who were arrested inside a Capitol office building on Thursday while demonstrating against President Trump’s illegal immigration policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivy Leaguer known for fighting sex violence charged with child sex crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/06/28/ivy-league-student-known-for-fighting-sexual-violence-is-charged-with-child-sex-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities came across Joel Davis when an FBI agent posted a message on a 'fetish' website where people leave ads soliciting children for sex, according to the criminal complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gowdy Tells Rosenstein to Hurry Mueller Probe: 'Finish The Hell Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/finish-the-hell-up-gowdy-tells-rosenstein-to-show-evidence-of-wrongdoing-by-trumps-camp-or-end-mueller-probe-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROUP MEMBERSHIP SOARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/democratic-socialists-of-america-membership-surges-after-alexandria-ocasio-cortezs-stunning-victory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The day after the self-described democratic socialist unseated a long-serving Democratic congressman on Tuesday, DSA experienced a membership surge 35 times larger than normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive data leak could affect all Americans, researcher says...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/28/massive-data-leak-could-affect-nearly-all-american-adults-security-researcher-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactis, a marketing and data-aggregation firm, leaked information on individual adults and businesses. The leak involved about 340 million records on a publicly available server, security research…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HEAT DOME' EXPANDS: Dangerous heat wave to scorch USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/06/28/heat-wave-dangerous-weather-central-eastern-us/741841002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dangerous and oppressive heat wave is forecast to scorch the central and eastern U.S. over the next few days. The worst of the heat will start in the Midwest on Friday before creeping its way east toward the Northeast and Mid-Atlantic by Saturday and Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PA homes raided by feds in mystery explosions investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yorkdispatch.com/story/news/local/pennsylvania/2018/06/28/pennsylvania-homes-raided-investigation-mystery-explosions/36455421/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yorkdispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents and state and local police have swarmed two homes as part of an investigation into a series of mysterious explosions around a county about an hour north of Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Host city shopping malls evacuated after bomb threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-world-cup-host-city-12815215</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We'll be bringing you the very latest updates, pictures and video on this breaking news story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crows 'reverse engineer' tools from memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/2265/crows-reverse-engineer-tools-memory-study-doc-16s2cf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French lawmakers urge fix for 60-year-old typo in constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-lawmakers-urge-fix-60-old-typo-constitution-161552735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French lawmakers are pushing for an official correction to a decades-old grammatical error which slipped into the country's constitution 60 years ago. The constitution was revised in 1958 when France switched from being a parliamentary to a presidential regime. MPs from the right-leaning UDI-Agir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranormal Researcher Claims To Find 'Time Warp' Near Vegas...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/time-warp-las-vegas-paranormal-investigator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Warren says he is the first person to ever discover a time warp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel graduates first women tank commanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-graduates-first-women-tank-commanders-161531054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jérusalem (AFP) - The Israeli army on Thursday graduated the first four women from its tank commanders' school, a step toward the formation of all-female tank crews. Another six have completed training as crew members, but actual deployment of any of the women will depend on the outcome of a review</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Weighing Senator Mike Lee for Supreme Court Vacancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-28/trump-is-said-to-weigh-senator-mike-lee-for-high-court-vacancy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has asked advisers their opinions about nominating Utah Senator Mike Lee to replace Justice Anthony Kennedy on the Supreme Court, according to three people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU leaders press ahead with tough new migrant plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cc82506a683f4a8eab8aa436eed8e2db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — European Union leaders vowed Thursday to move forward with plans to screen migrants in northern Africa for asylum eligibility to dissuade many of them from setting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>84% support turning illegals into authorities...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/394624-mark-penn-84-percent-support-turning-undocumented-immigrants-over-authorities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent Democratic pollster Mark Penn said on Thursday that a vast majority of Americans don’t really support so-called "sanctuary cities" that shield undocumented immigrants from deportation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA Readies For Busiest Day -- EVER!</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/tsa-busiest-day-friday-fourth-of-july-airport-screening-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA projects it will screen about 2.7 million passengers and crew on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil ace blames 'soft mattress' for World Cup injury...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6645736/marcelo-brazil-injury-bed-mattress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCELO’s mysterious injury during Brazil’s win over Serbia was reportedly caused by a BED. That’s according to doctor Rodrigo Lasmar, who believes a mattress at Brazil’s hotel in Moscow was respon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED SEALS DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trumps-no-1-deal-maker-jared-kushner-takes-winning-streak-to-wisconsin-for-13-000-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh from a whirlwind peace mission through the Middle East, the administration’s top deal maker, Jared Kushner, is heading to Wisconsin with President Trump to celebrate the biggest jobs deal of his young White House career, the groundbreaking of the massive Foxconn Technology Group project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Aide to Stone Subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/28/us/politics/roger-stone-andrew-miller-subpoenaed-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former aide, Andrew Miller, worked for Roger Stone, a longtime informal adviser to President Trump, during the 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel eyeing Russians granted 'unusual access' to inauguration parties...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-eyeing-russians-granted-unusual-access-trump/story?id=56232847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several billionaires with deep ties to Russia attended exclusive, invitation-only receptions during Donald Trump’s inauguration festivities, guest lists show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space weapons in 'Near Future'... </title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/06/pentagon-intelligence-chief-russia-and-china-will-have-weapons-space-near-future/149335/?oref=d-channelriver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Intelligence Agency’s director says the U.S. lead in space is diminishing and tomorrow’s skies will be filled with enemy robot satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump touts new FOXCONN plant in Wisconsin... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/trump-heads-to-wisconsin-to-tout-a-new-foxconn-plant-while-harley-dav.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A groundbreaking for a massive $10 billion Foxconn factory complex in Wisconsin is supposed to be evidence that the manufacturing revival fueled by President Donald Trump's "America First" policy is well underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rx: Zucchini, brown rice, turkey soup. Medicaid plan offers food as medicine...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/rx-zucchini-brown-rice-turkey-soup-medicaid-plan-offers-food-as-medicine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small group of insurers offers some members with serious illnesses medically tailored meals to improve their health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SOCIALIST REVOLUTION'</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-wins-democratic-socialist-21st-century-vision/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a values-based campaign that championed Medicare for All and the abolition of ICE, the 28-year-old Latina beat a top Democratic incumbent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ WANTS TO BE PREZ!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/27/ocasio-cortez-wants-to-be-president-mom-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurgent Democrat Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez wants to take her budding political career all the way to The White House, her mother told The Post on Wednesday. “Her aspiration is to be the pres…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENEZUELA HELL: Inflation rises to 43,378%!</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/781952/minimumwage-worker-venezuela-could-afford-5-cups-coffee-each-month--nothing-else</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five million Venezuelan bolivars is the equivalent of $1.45. It's also roughly a minimum-wage worker's entire monthly salary in the South American country. Thanks to stunning inflation, it now takes 1 million bolivars to buy a cup of coffee in a Venezuelan cafe, Bloomberg reports. That's one-fifth of Venezuela's monthly minimum wage, and 10,000-bill stack of Venezuela's most common bank note, the 100-bolivar bill. To illustrate Venezuela's rampant inflation, Bloomberg has tracked the price of a cup of coffee since December 2016 on its Cafe Con Leche index. One dose of caffeine cost 450 bolivars when the index launchedtwo years ago, but 43,378 percent inflation in the last year has led to today's astronomical price. Incredibly bleak moment milestone for Venezuela. The cost of one cup of coffee just hit 1 million Bolivars. https://t.co/Fbv2NqnAFl pic.twitter.com/LvziiWUynI — Joe Weisenthal (@TheStalwart) June 28, 2018 Additionally, if the pace of inflation over the past three months continues, Bloomberg estimates that inflation would be 482,153 percent after a year. Check out the Cafe Con Leche index at Bloomberg for a detailed — and astonishing — visual. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman drove 19 miles with ex-boyfriend clinging to car's hood...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/wild-car-hood-ride-178592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 28--A woman who drove nearly 20 miles with her ex-boyfriend clinging to the hood of her speeding car has been arrested on a negligence charge in connection with her vehicular antics on a Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Man Knocked Out Cold, Robbed In Middle Of NYC Intersection......</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/police-man-attacked-robbed-by-two-groups-of-suspects-in-the-bronx/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a man was attacked, knocked out and robbed in the Bronx by two different groups of suspects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star Ron Jeremy sued for sex assault...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/27/ron-jeremy-sued-sexual-assault-battery-washington-radio-model/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ron Jeremy isn't out of the woods in Washington State -- his sexual assault case is going to civil court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Abramson, Ex-NEW YORK TIMES Editor Slams Paper: Making 'Horrible Mistakes,' Needs 'Course Correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jill-abramson-ex-new-york-times-editor-the-narcissistic-nyt-is-making-horrible-mistakes-needs-a-course-correction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After her ‘pissed off’ tweet, the former editor slams the newspaper staff’s ‘narcissism,’ its ‘crucifying’ Ali Watkins profile, and ‘missing’ the rise of Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog trapped in hot car honks horn...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/dog-trapped-inside-hot-truck-12810651</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small dog was filmed apparently locked inside the truck amid 27C temperatures by 17-year-old customer Gabrielle Dart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin summit set...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-putin/trump-putin-summit-to-unfold-in-cold-war-venue-helsinki-on-july-16-idUSKBN1JO1A5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin will hold their first summit on July 16 in Helsinki, a renowned venue for Cold War diplomacy, with nervous U.S. allies in Europe and Russia skeptics looking on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP new battleground for political warfare...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-big-picture-yelp-battleground-political-warfare-fake-posts-8b22b23f-f6b4-4ce6-ad8e-956f5c3fa63c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politically-motivated "fake reviews" are on the rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump launches direct attack on Mueller...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5896975/Trump-goes-Robert-Mueller-hiding-conflicts-interest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump rarely targets Special Counsel Robert Mueller but took that step on Thursday, questioning on Twitter whether he has undisclosed conflicts that taint his Russia probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBORG ALERT: Lab-grown human brains put into droids...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/frankenstein-cyborg-crabs-artificial-intelligence-12812604 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US scientific study is trying to find out why Neanderthals went extinct</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  OIL SPIKES TO HIGHEST PRICE IN 4 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/iran-sanctions-could-soon-push-oil-prices-above-90-a-barrel-boaml-sa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s sustained bid to disrupt Iran’s petroleum exports could soon help to push oil prices above $90 a barrel, analysts told CNBC on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE barricades DC headquarters to prevent 'occupation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/ice-barricades-washington-dc-headquarters-to-prevent-activist-occupation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers barricaded an employee and visitor entrance Wednesday to prevent activists from performing an "occupation" of the agency's D.C. headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump Get Another?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/politics/with-kennedy-gone-everybody-is-looking-at-85-year-old-ruth-bader-ginsburg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA attendant kicks passengers off plane over airplane mode dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/nation-now/2018/06/28/delta-attendant-kicks-passengers-off-plane-over-airplane-mode-dispute/741161002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Delta Air Lines flight attendant forced passengers off a plane at Fort Wayne International Airport after a dispute with a black flier over whether or not her phone was turned to airplane mode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents interrupt news interview with whistleblower...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/394575-government-agents-interrupt-news-interview-with-ice-whistleblower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents from the Department of Homeland Security (DHS) interrupted an interview with a former Immigrations and Customs Enforcement (ICE) spokesman on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Sheeran Sued for $100 Million for Ripping Off Marvin Gaye...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/28/ed-sheeran-sued-thinking-out-loud-lets-get-it-on-marvin-gaye/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ed Sheeran sued over "Thinking Out Loud" for allegedly ripping off Marvin Gaye's "Let's Get it On."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI ambulances and robot doctors: China seeks to ease hospital strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/asia/ai-ambulances-and-robot-doctors--china-seeks-digital-salve-to-ease-hospital-strain-10480900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the eastern Chinese city of Hangzhou, an ambulance speeds through traffic on a wave of green lights, helped along by an artificial intelligence ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP Revised Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/final-reading-on-first-quarter-2018-gdp.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final reading on first-quarter gross domestic product was expected to show an increase of 2.2 percent, in line with the previous estimate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket Chain to Introduce Driverless Grocery Deliveries...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/kroger-to-soon-begin-driverless-grocery-delivery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kroger is partnering with autonomous car company Nuro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal cops move in on ICE protest in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://www.kgw.com/article/news/local/federal-cops-move-in-on-ice-protest-in-sw-portland/283-568461821</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kgw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officers in riot gear moved into the protest siege of ICE headquarters in Southwest Portland at 5:30 a.m. Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now AMAZON to Sell Meds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/walgreens-cvs-shares-tank-after-amazon-buys-online-pharmacy-pillpack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania to make second visit to immigration centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jun/28/melania-trump-border-immigration-visit </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No details of Thursday’s trip to migrant shelters yet released after previous visit last week overshadowed by jacket controversy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death on foot: Distracted driving, cell phones seen as factors...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/money/cars/2018/06/28/pedestrian-deaths-distracted-driving/692668002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. emergency room visits blamed on cellphone use spiked 83.5 percent from 17,851 in 2007 — the year Apple introduced the iPhone — to 32,755 in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farting unicorn causes kerfuffle between Elon Musk and artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/farting-unicorn-causes-kerfuffle-between-elon-musk-and-artist-2018-06-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An image of a farting unicorn is causing a stink between a Colorado artist and Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia steps up legal attack against hunter of Stalin's mass graves...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180628120536-i1o7m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/HISTORY (PIX):Russia steps up legal attack against hunter of Stalin's mass graves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Putin summit set...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/28/trump-putin-meeting-set-forjuly-16-in-helsinki-finland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China caps film star pay, citing 'money worship' and fake contracts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/28/china-caps-film-star-pay-citing-money-worship-and-fake-contracts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lead actors’ pay packets restricted to 70% of total wages for the cast of a show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The day conservatives have been waiting for...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article213932564.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservatives have been waiting for the moment when President Trump can make another nomination to the Supreme Court. With Anthony Kennedy's announcement Wednesday that he is retiring, that day has come. They will likely get what they want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Just 23% of adults get enough exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/28/health/cdc-exercise-report-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado had the highest percentage of adults meeting federal exercise guidelines with 32.5% doing so, according to the report. Mississippi at just 13.5%, was significantly lower than the national average of 23%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Sucker-Punching Duo Leave Man Unconscious in Street, Then Take Pictures...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Bronx-NYC-Man-Punched-Knockout-Robbery-Pictures-486792521.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was left in a street in the middle of the day after a punch knocked him out, leaving him behind for people to pick his pockets and take pictures of him while he's unconscious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEMUNDO host faces backlash for making on-air racist gesture...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/soccer/worldcup/2018/06/27/telemundo-host-makes-racist-gesture-live-tv-world-cup/740525002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Telemundo's 'Chef James' Tahhan is guilty of the latest incident of racist or offensive behavior during the World Cup, during a live TV celebration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen cancels appearance due to ill health...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/980869/queen-health-latest-st-pauls-cathedral-queen-elizabeth-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has been forced to pull out of a service at Paul's Cathedral at last minute as she is "under the weather", Buckingham Palace officials have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists warn of possible eruption at restless Alaska volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/scientists-warn-possible-eruption-restless-alaska-volcano-030729563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “nuisance” volcano on a remote Alaska Aleutian island is showing signs of a potentially disruptive explosion in the coming days that could disrupt air traffic, scientists said on Wednesday. Cleveland Volcano, a 5,676-foot (1,730-meter) peak about 950 miles (1,500 km) southwest of Anchorage, has been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's Maduro calls Pence 'poisonous viper'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelas-maduro-calls-pence-a-poisonous-viper-idUSKBN1JO03X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Wednesday called U.S. Vice President Mike Pence a "viper" and vowed to defeat what he called Washington's attempts to force him from power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS IN TEHRAN: Protesters Chase Police Down Street, Torch Bikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/chaos-in-tehran-iranian-protesters-chase-police-down-the-street-then-torch-their-bikes-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU faces 'destiny' at crunch migration summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/205/eu-faces-destiny-crunch-migration-summit-doc-16q7kz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sandwich poisoner' feared to have killed 21 colleagues sprinkling toxic powder in lunches...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-feared-killed-21-colleagues-12808410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police said they had arrested a 56-year-old man but have not named him, any of his alleged victims, or the company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Putin summit set...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/bolton-due-moscow-talk-possible-us-russia-summit-075546236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — A summit that brings together Russian President Vladimir Putin and U.S. President Donald Trump will be a success in itself regardless of the results, Trump's national security adviser said Wednesday while in Moscow to lay the groundwork for the meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I would support impeachment'...</title>
      <link>http://www.sfexaminer.com/primaries-upend-political-landscape-ahead-midterm-elections-spell-trouble-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE:  Feds to begin distributing grant money to non-sanctuary cities...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/27/feds-distributing-grant-money-non-sanctuary-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department said Wednesday it has begun distributing hundreds of millions of dollars in grant money that had been tied up in a major court battle over sanctuary cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE:  Feds to begin distributing grant money to non-sanctuary cities...</title>
      <link>https://amp.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/27/feds-distributing-grant-money-non-sanctuary-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;amp.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Mayor Warns City Cannot Handle Surge in Asylum Seekers...</title>
      <link>http://www.newsweek.com/toronto-mayor-warns-city-cannot-handle-any-more-asylum-seekers-claims-rise-997194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have exhausted our available sites, our resources and our personnel," John Tory said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-FOXNEWS BOSS BILL SHINE TO BECOME WHITE HOUSE COMMS CHIEF...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-likely-to-name-ex-fox-news-executive-white-house-communications-director/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Shine met with Trump Wednesday to seal the deal, CBS News' Major Garrett reports</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Under Investigation for Streaming Disturbing 'Child Pornography' Scenes...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/netflixs-desire-streams-disturbing-scenes-of-child-pornography/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What kind of pervert does this to a child?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger with unbearable odor that caused emergency landing dies of infection...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5891339/Man-dies-plane-diverts-Portugal-horrific-smell-caused-flesh-eating-disease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian rock star Andrey Suchilin, 58, suffered an infection while on holiday in the Canary Islands, but the smell from it got so bad on his flight to Amsterdam, the plane was diverted to Faro, Portugal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARMING:  Arctic Ocean almost totally ice-covered...</title>
      <link>https://www.iceagenow.info/arctic-ocean-almost-totally-ice-covered-map/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iceagenow.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the 26th of June! Where’s that (so-called) global warming? Look at this map. Purple signifies sea-ice thickness of approximately ½ to 1½ meters (20 inches to 5 ft). Blue or green signifies 1½ to 3 meters ( 5 ft to 10 ft) of ice. Yellow or orange signifies 3 to 4 meters (10 ft to ... Read moreArctic Ocean almost totally ice-covered – Map</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious sonar 'anomaly' off NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article213925044.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious "sonar anomaly" had NOAA explorers diving off the coast of North Carolina, aka Graveyard of the Atlantic, on Wednesday, hoping for an explanation. NOAA says it could be "an archaeology site, a geological formation or otherwise."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God is racist,' legislative candidate says... </title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/latest-news/article213937944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A website tied to a candidate for the North Carolina General Assembly says God is a racist white supremacist and that Jews are descended from Satan. The candidate has also protested using signs that said "God is racist" and What's wrong with being a racist." Russell Walker is a Republican candidate running for state House District 48 which includes Scotland and Hoke counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full horror of Aztec 'skull tower' revealed...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5893933/The-horror-Aztec-tower-skulls-revealed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2015 archaeologists found a gruesome 'trophy rack' near the site of an Aztec temple. Now, they say the find was just the tip of the iceberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creatures of habit: Humans only visit 25 places regularly... </title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5892903/Humans-really-creatures-habit-Researchers-visit-25-places-regularly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The London study found we really are creatures of habit - even though our 25 places often change over time. The researchers behind it say it reveals 'entirely new aspects of human behaviour.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt for US corporations tops $6 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/debt-for-us-corporations-tops-6-trillion-sp-global.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record $6.3 trillion in corporate debt should trouble Wall Street investors facing a stricter rate environment even as cash hoarding reaches a peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACANCY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/43de809e3c144a1f9048055386394263/Justice-Kennedy-retiring,-giving-Trump-pivotal-court-pick</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Justice Anthony Kennedy, the Supreme Court's decisive man in the middle on abortion, gay rights and other contentious issues, announced his retirement Wednesday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA PLANS FALL CAMPAIGN BLITZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/obama-expected-to-hit-the-campaign-trail-in-september.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting in September, former President Barack Obama is expected to hit the campaign trail for House, Senate and gubernatorial candidates running in the midterm elections, according to two sources with direct knowledge of the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS VOW INSURGENCY, FLOAT 'CARETAKER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/27/us/politics/democrats-joe-crowley-ocasio-cortez.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stunning primary defeat of Representative Joe Crowley by a young Latina progressive raised the pressure on the Democrats’ aging leadership to step aside for a new generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>132 candidates killed during campaign season!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/27/americas/mexico-political-deaths-election-season-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even for a country numbed by escalating violence, the toll the campaign season has exacted is horrifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEX PREZ RACE: 'AMLO' THE UNSTOPPABLE?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-campaign-closes-leftist-amlo-looking-unstoppable-185532134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's presidential campaign drew to a close with a fiesta of rallies Wednesday, as establishment candidates made last-ditch pleas for voters to reject the radical break with the past promised by leftist front-runner Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador. All four candidates were holding a series of huge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTENTIOUS FIGHT LOOMS</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-kennedy/justice-kennedy-u-s-supreme-courts-pivotal-vote-to-retire-idUSKBN1JN2OF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Anthony Kennedy said on Wednesday he plans to retire after three decades as a pivotal vote on the highest U.S. judicial body, giving President Donald Trump an opportunity to make the court more firmly conservative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACANCY AT SUPREME COURT</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/27/anthony-kennedy-retiring-from-supreme-court.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The retirement gives President Trump another chance to fundamentally reshape the top of the judiciary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KENNEDY STEPS ASIDE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/43de809e3c144a1f9048055386394263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Justice Anthony Kennedy, the Supreme Court's decisive man in the middle on abortion, gay rights and other contentious issues, announced his retirement Wednesday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-FOXNEWS BOSS BILL SHINE TO BECOME WHITE HOUSE COMMS CHIEF...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bill-shine-fox-news-exec-accepts-white-house/story?id=56204272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News co-president Bill Shine will join the White House communications shop as deputy chief of staff for communications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caveman Robots: Neanderthal brains used in 'Frankenstein plot'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/712561/artificial-intelligence-cyborg-frankenstein-neanderthal-brain-robots-university-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Ranked 'Most Patriotic' State...</title>
      <link>http://wjla.com/news/local/virginia-most-patriotic-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WalletHub has ranked all 50 states, from sea to shining sea, and has determined that Virginia is the most patriotic of them all.While ranking the states, WalletHub used two main metrics, military engagement and civic engagement. Those were broken down into</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 59% fear violence from Trump haters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/poll-59-fear-violence-from-trump-haters-31-predict-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The division in the United States that has escalated into the organized harassment of presidential aides has six in 10 worried about the violence from anti-Trump advocates and nearly a third fearing it will end in civil war.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
