<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GAME OVER? REDDIT trader behind surge 'loses $13 MILLION in day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2263010/gamestop-reddit-rally-roaring-kitty-keith-gill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE REDDIT trader who sparked the GameStop frenzy says he has lost $13MILLION in a single day after share prices plummeted this week. Keith Gill — otherwise known as as DeepF—ing Value on Reddit an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial slur costs chart-topping country star spot on radio...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/nation-world/national/article248972905.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I used an unacceptable and inappropriate racial slur that I wish I could take back,” Wallen said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom approval plummeting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/poll-newsom-approval-plummeting-third-134650084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a third of the state's registered voters said they would vote to oust Newsom from office if the recall qualified for the ballot, though 45% said they would oppose such a move, a Berkeley IGS poll found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA causing arm side effects in some...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2262521/moderna-vaccine-causing-covid-arm-rash-side-effects/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MODERNA’S vaccine is causing a rash on some people’s arms after injection. The side effect, dubbed “Covid arm”, appears around a week after receiving a dose and affects very few patients, doctors s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASH OF THE TITANS:   Who is richest tech CEO as Bezos steps away from AMZN...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2262604/who-is-the-richest-tech-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON founder Jeff Bezos is stepping down as CEO of the company that once made him the richest man in the world. As Bezos aims to focus “time and energy” on new ventures away from Amaz…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Weather Has Greater Impact On Spread Than Distancing...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/weather-impact-covid-19-spread/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the lack of climate data included in epidemiological models has left a glaring hole in the plans to defend against COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 2 million seek appointments in Chicago  -- during first hour!</title>
      <link>https://www.radio.com/wbbm780/news/local/cook-county-covid-website-sees-1-9m-hits-in-first-hour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook County has another mass-vaccination site opening Wednesday morning at Triton College in River Grove - the second of four such sites – and to say interest is high would be an understatement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Sues NETFLIX Over Work Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/actor-sues-netflix-over-covid-19-work-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face of NYC prevention tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-health-commissioner-tests-positive-for-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City's health commissioner announced Wednesday that he has been infected with the virus himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documentary shows how influencers fake their way to fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/02/hbo-fake-famous-how-instagram-influencers-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO's 'Fake Famous' features an experiment where three Instagram users try to boost their social media followings using tricks sometimes employed by top influencers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locations Being Kept Secret...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/sacramento-vaccines-secret-locations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The location of some vaccination sites are not being made public until someone makes an appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates' Sentences Shortened If They Get Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/massachusetts-prison-inmates-coronavirus-vaccine-good-time-sentences/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates in the Massachusetts Department of Correction can get a week taken off their prison sentence by getting the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation Shows CHIEFS Winning Super Bowl 37-27...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/02/03/madden-nfl-21-simulation-chiefs-super-bowl-lv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madden is picking the Chiefs to repeat as champions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES, HOSPITALIZATIONS CONTINUE FALL...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EtQmLA4VgAEmtA9?format=jpg&amp;name=4096x4096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Scottish lawmakers want to pursue The Don with 'unexplained wealth' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/scottish-lawmakers-want-to-pursue-trump-with-e2-80-98unexplained-wealth-e2-80-99-probe-over-his-purchase-of-golf-courses/ar-BB1dm3LR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If ordered by a court, the Trump Organization would be required to reveal how it financed the purchases of the Turnberry and Aberdeen golf resorts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashian thief recounts Paris heist in tell-all book...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210203-kardashian-thief-recounts-paris-heist-in-tell-all-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kardashian thief recounts Paris heist in tell-all book</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Penn fires back at criticism over jab site: 'Betrayal of all'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sean-penn-fires-back-criticism-130008456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two anonymous comments disparaged the actor's vaccination effort at Dodger Stadium. Penn fired back in an email: "And to whoever authored these, understand that in every cell of my body is a vitriol for the way your actions reflect so harmfully upon your brothers and sisters in arms."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weird New Era of Cosmic Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/02/spacex-elon-musk-jared-isaacman/617910/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s SpaceX just started launching NASA astronauts last spring, and it’s already moving on to private citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders reach deal to fully transfer power to Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/03/senate-reaches-deal-on-organizing-resolution-chuck-schumer-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans technically controlled Senate committees for two weeks after Democrats took a majority in the chamber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS, SURPRISES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/golden-globes-snubs-nominations-bridgerton-zendaya-tom-hanks-spike-lee-surprises-1234685955/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the tumultuous year that’s just ended, you may feel hard pressed to be surprised by anything at this point, but the Golden Globes this morning aimed to prove that notion incorrect Offering pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX DOMINATES GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/golden-globe-nominations-2021-0e5be6d70f02b936b0a5025bb026e761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After a year where the pandemic nearly emptied movie theaters, Netflix dominated nominations to the 78ths Golden Globe Awards on Wednesday, with David Fincher's “Mank" leading film...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Building, related properties now powered solely by wind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-empire-state-building-and-its-related-buildings-are-now-powered-by-wind/ar-BB1dlK2q?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire State Building and its 13 related properties are buying wind power, making it the nation's largest real estate portfolio to go green.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNUBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/02/03/live-golden-globes-updates-big-snub-for-one-night-in-miami-minari-comedy-actress-nominees-no-one-knows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Golden Globes are always full of surprises. Today they snubbed Spike Lee and “Da 5 Bloods” and star Delroy Lindo. They totally ignored Regina King’s “One Night in Miami&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/2021-golden-globes-nominations-list-nominees-1234686095/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 78th annual Golden Globe Awards are being revealed this morning beginning at at 5:35 a.m. PT/8:35 a.m. ET as the Hollywood Foreign Press Association sets its noms for the best f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B9N_NgEQ5PE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live as Sarah Jessica Parker and Taraji P. Henson reveal this year's nominees for the 78th Golden Globe Awards on the TODAY Show and E! News. Full nomi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler to release debut album recorded in womb...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/feb/03/us-toddler-to-release-debut-album-recorded-in-the-womb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luca Yupanqui was recorded by her parents using ‘biosonic MIDI technology’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lin Wood spent months claiming fraud cost Trump election. Now Georgia investigating whether he voted illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/l-lin-wood-spent-months-falsely-claiming-voter-fraud-cost-trump-the-election-now-georgia-is-investigating-whether-he-voted-illegally/ar-BB1dlM2z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative attorney L. Lin Wood faces an investigation in Georgia over whether he illegally voted in the Nov. 3 elections after buying a home in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog Keeps Guard Over Owner's Body For 2 Days After Dying on Hike...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/david-deshon-missing-foresthill-dog-doesnt-leave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Deshon was found dead two days after he was reported missing near his Foresthill home last week - but his dog wouldn’t leave his side, family says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinfection NOT Rare?</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/02/02/covid-reinfection-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's some bad news and perhaps some good news for people who've been previously infected with the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna? Harry Potter? Churchill? Tom Brady May Be Beyond Compare...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/03/madonna-harry-potter-churchill-tom-brady-may-be-beyond-compare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arc of Tom Brady’s career — his rise to Super Bowl mainstay as quarterback of the New England Patriots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys Dealt Another Blow as Feds Crack Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/proud-boys-dealt-another-blow-as-feds-crack-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Proud Boys’ former lawyer says he’s taking the name back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shockingly Realistic Porn Movie Has SUNDANCE Talking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pleasure-is-the-shockingly-realistic-porn-movie-that-has-sundance-talking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swedish filmmaker Ninja Thyberg opens up to Marlow Stern about “Pleasure,” her feature directorial debut centered on a young woman navigating the adult industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Truthers' New Freakout: Being Forced to Eat Bugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/covid-truthers-new-freakout-is-over-supposedly-being-forced-to-eat-bugs </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVERY state will see below freezing temps next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/02/weather/polar-vortex-forecast-freezing-cold/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coldest air of the season will be diving south, not leaving anyone out. Every single state in the lower 48 US will be below freezing Monday morning. This includes 86% of the country and 235 million people, and this one system alone is responsible for much of that. Check how cold your low will be Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA to oversee investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/02/tech/spacex-starship-sn-9-test-launch-faa-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Aviation Administration said it will oversee an investigation into a crash landing of a SpaceX prototype rocket on Tuesday. The announcement comes after the FAA forced SpaceX to delay the launch as it investigated a previous explosion of a similar rocket prototype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Barts shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/02/st-barts-is-shutting-down-due-to-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jetsetters should bid “adieu” to upcoming St. Barts vacations. The Caribbean island popular with celebrities will bar most visitors beginning Wednesday to comply with coronavirus protoc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark to develop digital passport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-health-denmark-coronavirus-pandemic-europe-8ffacf05453c6f259d5e2cea033ae5ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Denmark's government said Wednesday it is joining forces with businesses to develop a digital passport that would show whether people have been vaccinated against the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa's famed strip clubs brace for unusual Super Bowl...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-super-bowl-health-football-coronavirus-pandemic-27ba9985cfc3aaa4c5ba5eae7f8a2d93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — Elizabeth Reed dances at Scores Gentleman's Club, a strip club near the stadium hosting the Super Bowl, and says wearing masks while working is like “doing cardio” with her nose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-1 Bombers Deploying To Norway For First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39053/b-1-bombers-are-deploying-to-norway-for-the-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deployment is part of the Air Force's new focus on the Arctic and will position the bombers near Russia's sprawling Naval bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For billionaire Jared Isaacman, cosmic tourism era begins...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-02-billionaire-jared-isaacman-space-tourism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Isaacman is not a professional astronaut, but by the end of the year the young billionaire will have shot around the Earth multiple times at the helm of a space mission made up entirely of tourists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets face, hands in rare surgery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-face-transplants-1e11f620bd84c817e99b00bdf874625a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Almost six months after a rare face and hands transplant, Joe DiMeo is relearning how to smile, blink, pinch and squeeze. The 22-year-old New Jersey resident had the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political storms swirl...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/gavin-newsom-california-coronavirus-pandemic-kevin-faulconer-9d2032fd2aff2d48f4350fc5b861be6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — In the year since California saw its first coronavirus case, Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom has gone from a governor in command to one lurching from one political crisis to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned with low reimbursement, doctors stop testing...</title>
      <link>https://newyorknewstimes.com/burned-with-a-low-reimbursement-some-doctors-stop-testing-covid/103087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyorknewstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Robin Lullaby was excited to start offering coronavirus tests at a pediatric clinic in Denver last fall.The test for kids Often lacking, And her new machine was able to return results within minutes. She soon discovered an unexpected obstacle. It’s a major health insurance company that paid her for less than the cost of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO team visits Wuhan lab, meets 'Bat Woman'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210203100527-9j9ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-CHINA (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-WHO team probing COVID-19 visits Wuhan lab, meets 'Bat Woman'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen Summons Regulators to Discuss Market Volatility...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-summons-regulators-discuss-financial-021235999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen has summoned U.S. financial regulators to discuss recent volatility in financial markets, in her first public effort to address the tumult involving GameStop Corp. shares and broker-dealer Robinhood Markets Inc.Yellen called a meeting with the Securities and Exchange Commission, the Federal Reserve Board, the Federal Reserve Bank of New York and the Commodity Futures Trading Commission, the Treasury said in a statement late Tuesday. The Biden administration and regulators have faced pressure in recent days to respond to the market frenzy.“Secretary Yellen believes the integrity of markets is important and has asked for a discussion of recent volatility in financial markets and whether recent activities are consistent with investor protection and fair and efficient markets,” the department said.Yellen’s predecessors, including Steven Mnuchin, also organized meetings of financial agencies during times of tumult. They aren’t necessarily a signal that any policy moves are imminent. The SEC already said Friday it’s seeking to identify potential misconduct and will scrutinize brokerages’ decisions to halt buying that triggered a retail-investor revolt.GameStop, a video-game retailer, was one of a handful of companies whose shares began soaring in late January, driven by an army of retail investors active on the online forums hosted by Reddit. Some investors openly called on others to bid up the shares of certain names in order to trigger losses for hedge funds that had bet their prices would fall.GameStop shares went from $19.95 to a peak of $347.51 on Jan. 27 in just 10 trading days, and with no meaningful change in the company’s profit outlook. It has since swung wildly and fell 60% to close at $90 on Tuesday, suggesting the frenzy may be easing.The episode has raised questions about whether broader risks for the financial system are brewing. As Treasury secretary, Yellen is chair of the Financial Stability Oversight Council, which was set up in the wake of the global financial crisis to monitor systemic risks. This week’s meeting about GameStop is not a formal FSOC session, but more of an ad hoc gathering of top financial regulators.The SEC’s acting chair, Allison Herren Lee, said Monday that the agency is keeping a close eye on stocks that have surged to extraordinary heights during the recent bouts of wild trading but has seen no evidence that the broader market is under threat.“We haven’t seen anything to indicate anything that suggests it would bring down the market,” Lee told NPR in an interview.The wild trading has left politicians in both parties grasping for responses to the new phenomenon of retail investors banding together on social media.On Monday, the House Financial Services Committee announced that it would hold a hearing on Feb. 18 regarding “recent market volatility” involving GameStop and other companies.Yellen has requested an ethics waiver to hold the meeting, a Treasury spokeswoman said, confirming a Reuters report.Yellen received more than $700,000 in speaking fees from Citadel, the financial empire run by billionaire Ken Griffin. Griffin runs a hedge fund and controls Citadel Securities, a giant market making firm that executes trades for Robinhood’s customers.Read more: The Citadel Link: What Ken Griffin Has to Do With GameStopRichard Berner, professor at New York University’s Stern School of Business and the former director of the Treasury’s Office of Financial Research, said it’s important that the SEC and other regulators are monitoring markets for any signs of fraud or manipulation.“Both are potentially financial stability issues,” he said. “Were they to escalate and persist, these events might erode investor trust. Trust in markets and market integrity is absolutely critical for markets to function and for people to engage in them.”The market turbulence comes at a particularly awkward time in Washington, where the Biden administration is still taking wing. Many of the president’s cabinet choices and picks for other crucial jobs await Senate confirmation -- including Gary Gensler, his nominee as SEC chairman.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Down Side to Life in Supertall Tower: Leaks, Creaks, Breaks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/03/the-down-side-to-life-in-a-supertall-tower-leaks-creaks-breaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nearly 1,400-foot tower at 432 Park Avenue, briefly the tallest residential building in the world, was the pinnacle of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas becoming worthless?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/finance/news/gasoline-is-becoming-worthless-210636353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are beginning to value internal-combustion technology at 0 or less, which is forcing the faster adoption of electrics at GM, Ford and other automakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate takes first steps toward ANOTHER massive covid bailout...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-senate-takes-first-steps-001459627.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Senate took a tentative step Tuesday towards pushing through a massive economic aid package proposed by President Joe Biden, but bipartisanship was absent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Got to work on that landing'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spacex-prototype-rocket-poised-lift-202209401.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prototype of a SpaceX rocket the company hopes will one day journey to Mars crashed in a fireball as it tried to land upright after a test flight Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN DOMINATES JANUARY...</title>
      <link>https://cnnpressroom.blogs.cnn.com/2021/02/02/cnn-smashes-ratings-records-has-most-watched-month-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnnpressroom.blogs.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues man who shot her in back with AR-15 for tearing down one of his Nazi flags...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/flag-shoot-lawsuit-285930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 2--The unarmed woman who was shot in the back after tearing down a Nazi flag flying in front of the gunman’s Oklahoma home has sued her assailant for negligence, according to court records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin America and Caribbean top 600,000 deaths...</title>
      <link>http://www.jamaicaobserver.com/latestnews/Latin_America_and_Caribbean_top_600,000_COVID-19_deaths?profile=1228</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jamaicaobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLE:  Bannon pardon was final middle finger to his base...</title>
      <link>https://www.takimag.com/article/the-con-is-back-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.takimag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The damnedest thing about Trump’s pardon of Steve Bannon is that it’s not getting the attention it merits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam WILL move its red-light district out of city center, citing tourist behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amsterdam-will-move-its-red-light-district-out-of-the-city-center-citing-tourist-behavior/ar-BB1dkxsj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city’s council has gained bipartisan support to shutter and relocate its famous brothels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity crisis at FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/sean-hannity-is-the-face-of-the-post-trump-identity-crisis-at-fox-news/ar-BB1dks0O?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dramatic ratings drop has the network scrambling to find its way after a breakup with the ex-president. The anxiety plays out on screen on Hannity’s hit prime-time show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Starship prototype rocket launches -- but again explodes on landing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/02/spacex-starship-sn9-explodes-on-attempted-landing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest prototype of SpaceX's next-generation Starship rocket exploded on impact during an attempted landing after a test flight on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters Set Sights on Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-02-02/navalny-sentenced-to-3-1-2-years-in-penal-colony-as-anti-putin-protests-escalate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin acknowledged the explosive consequences of imprisoning the leading Russian dissident in a statement hours before the court ruling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New CEO 'win-at-all-costs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/andy-jassy-amazon-ceo-aws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using lessons honed from a stint as outgoing CEO Jeff Bezos' right hand, Jassy changed the way enterprise tech is bought and sold in building the most profitable division of the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden signs executive orders ripping up Trump immigration policies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/biden-sign-executive-orders-immigration-including-family-reunification-n1256431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One executive order will create a task force to reunite children who were separated from their parents under Trump's "zero tolerance" policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE JUNK SPEEDING AROUND EARTH, THREATENING NASA MISSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/nasa-protect-satellites-space-junk-89818dfe-1be3-48bc-8d79-811d93528b83.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report suggests NASA isn't doing enough to mitigate the threats posed by space debris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden boosting vaccine allotments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/feds-send-covid-19-vaccines-pharmacies-a351bbc776eb3acd27dc3d951c4f4e81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden’s administration announced Tuesday that it is moving to expand access to COVID-19 vaccines, freeing up more doses for states and beginning to distribute them...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS: 'Never had more energy, this isn't about retiring'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/02/963370968/jeff-bezos-to-step-down-as-amazons-ceo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New CEO will be Andy Jassy, the head of Amazon's cloud computing division. "As much as I still tap dance into the office, I'm excited about this transition.," Bezos said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New PM for Italy: Mario Draghi, ex-European Central Bank chief, may get nod...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-new-prime-minister-for-italy-mario-draghi-former-european-central-bank-chief-may-get-the-nod/ar-BB1dkuCV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He led Europe’s central bank during the Greek debt crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andy Jassy, the New Face of AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/aws-chief-andy-jassy-once-served-as-jeff-bezos-first-shadow-adviser-now-hell-replace-bezos-as-amazon-ceo/ar-BB1dkwLh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jassy has since become one of the most established and influential figures in the world of corporate technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LETTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/company-news/email-from-jeff-bezos-to-employees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aboutamazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fellow Amazonians:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seniors Driving 400+ Miles for Jab...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/01/colorado-covid-vaccine-seniors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those in the 65-69 age group are being told to get ready. They, along with educators, will soon become eligible to receive the CVOID-19 vaccine in Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren rails on ROBINHOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/02/elizabeth-warren-asks-robinhood-to-explain-gamestop-trade-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren asked stock trading app firm Robinhood to explain its restriction on trading in shares of GameStop after hedge funds suffered big losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Schools Call Acronyms White Supremacy...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/02/san-francisco-schools-acronyms-white-supremacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are prioritizing antiracist arts instruction in our work."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interview flap shows challenges as Harris settles in as VP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-health-coronavirus-pandemic-west-virginia-united-nations-363b5098fc812a67a3e5a9efadb7cb78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Vice President Kamala Harris has spent her first two weeks in office working with the president on coronavirus relief, consulting with the head of the World Health Organization...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House visitor logs to be looked into...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-white-house-logs/bidens-white-house-will-look-into-trumps-visitor-logs-and-whether-it-can-release-them-idUSKBN2A22W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said on Tuesday it would look into whether it can make visitor logs from former President Donald Trump's administration public, a move that will be in line with the Biden administration's vow to release its own records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Common HIV Drugs May Prevent Vision Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hiv-drugs-may-prevent-blindness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nucleoside Reverse Transcriptase Inhibitors (NRTIs) can help treat dry macular degeneration, a very common cause of blindness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Gov Launches Ambitious Crackdown on Big Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2021/02/02/florida-gov-ron-desantis-launches-ambitious-crackdown-on-big-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) announced a major push to curb Big Tech's political bias and censorship today, with measures including a ban on the censorship of political candidates and mandatory opt-outs of content filters for citizens of the Sunshine State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mummies with golden tongues unearthed in Egypt...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-55902631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is thought the dead were given the tongues 2,000 years ago so they could speak in the afterlife.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Mask Cops To Start Targeting Travelers Today...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/01/federal-masks-cops-to-start-targeting-travelers-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: Trump's PAC windfall, the European Union's dairy protectionism, and more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Socialism Wiped Out Venezuela's Spectacular Oil Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/02/01/how-socialism-wiped-out-venezuelas-spectacular-oil-wealth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela has the world’s largest proven oil reserves. It's out of gasoline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Normal People Deployed Facial Recognition on Mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4ad5k3/how-normal-people-deployed-facial-recognition-on-capitol-hill-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial recognition is now freely accessible to random people on Twitter using a Polish website called Pimeyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE bubble fears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-stock-markets-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-1f6918bbe537f2cc40c8f4629423f08a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Now, even the pros on Wall Street are asking if the stock market has shot too high. U.S. stocks have been on a nearly nonstop rip higher since March, up roughly 70% to record...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese hackers spied on U.S. payroll agency...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210202173759-c9s5v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CYBER-SOLARWINDS/CHINA (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Suspected Chinese hackers used SolarWinds bug to spy on U.S. payroll agency – sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Accidentally Sends Out Amber Alert -- For 'Chucky' Doll...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/01/mistake-texas-dps-amber-alert-chucky-doll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alert was emailed out three separate times to subscribers of the Texas Alerts System last Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don lawyers call unconstitutional in laying out defense...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/536975-trump-lawyers-call-impeachment-trial-unconstitutional-in-laying-out-defense</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers representing former President Trump on Tuesday detailed the defense they’ll lay out at next week’s impeachment trial, arguing that it is unconstitutional to impeach a former president and that Trump’s speech did not directly lead to the de</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Teen Carjackers Terrorizing City 'For Thrills'; 80% Of Suspects Kids...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/02/01/at-virtual-townhall-officials-say-youngsters-are-committing-carjackings-for-thrills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a thrill - that's what the feds are calling the carjackings terrorizing Chicago - and 80 percent of those charged are kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A farewell to bulls? Leaders disagree on Spain's Pamplona festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-spain/a-farewell-to-bulls-regional-local-leaders-disagree-on-spains-pamplona-festival-idUSKBN2A21CN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's San Fermin festival, which attracts tourists from all over the world for the running of the bulls through the streets of Pamplona, will be cancelled for the second year in a row because of COVID-19, the regional head said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginni Thomas apologizes to husband's Supreme Court clerks after Capitol riot fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ginni-thomas-apologizes-to-husbands-supreme-court-clerks-after-capitol-riot-fallout/ar-BB1djYNx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative activist, who is married to Justice Clarence Thomas, told a private online group comprising his former staff: “I would ask those of you on the contrary side to have grace and mercy on those on my side of the polarized world.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ David Guetta says fair if festivals REQUIRE vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210202144932-imp8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-DAVID GUETTA/ (PIX, TV):French DJ David Guetta says fair if festivals require vaccinations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXXON posts first annual loss...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210202132317-dkl5y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXXON MOBIL-RESULTS/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 3-Exxon posts first annual loss as a public company on COVID-19 blow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Door-to-door testing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210202125644-gaqdw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-VARIANT (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-UK begins door-to-door testing of 80,000 people to halt South African variant</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
