<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Should We Sell?' After Collapse, Hot Florida Market Faces Uncertainty...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/should-we-sell-after-collapse-hot-florida-market-faces-uncertainty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. — Ines Mason bought the 14th-floor condo, perched on an island in Biscayne Bay, five years ago as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Jose has highest share of superrich residents in world!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-u-s-city-has-the-highest-share-of-superrich-residents-in-the-world-its-not-san-francisco-new-york-or-seattle-11625247163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global population of people worth $30 million or more grew by 1.7% in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As corona probe deepens, Bolsonaro increasingly threatened by corruption scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-coronavirus-probe-deepens-Bolsonaro-16294592.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO - For months, the congressional probe into Brazil's lax coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX yet to discover a great film director, says Cannes chief...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-yet-discover-great-film-185518206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix and the other streaming giants have yet to discover one great director, the head of the Cannes film festival said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORMER FOX PRESIDENT TURNS ON 'NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-murdoch-exec-fox-news-052129970.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos via GettyRupert Murdoch, whom I served for seven years, has many business and journalistic achievements. He owes himself a better legacy than a news channel that no reasonable person would believe.It was my great honor to join Rupert, Barry Diller (who now is the chairman of IAC, The Daily Beast’s parent company), Jamie Kellner and many others in the early days of Fox Broadcasting Company, the network that’s the home to The Simpsons and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measures in England Become 'Matters of Personal Choice'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-government-and-politics-650b09e7babe362e1777606e6b1a369b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain plans to scrap laws requiring face masks and social distancing later this month, Prime Minister Boris Johnson confirmed Monday, even as he acknowledged that lifting the restrictions will drive surging coronavirus cases higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE GROWS ON ANTI-VAXXERS</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-07-compulsory-jabs-pressure-anti-vaxxers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of countries and territories around the world are forcing people, often in specific sectors, to be vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As condo crashed down, they escaped through smoke and ruin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/surfside-building-collapse-71a19269343a1172f0c5bf782373a175</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — Alfredo Lopez and his wife Marian were asleep when the first thundering blast jolted them awake. Moments later, a second boom, much louder than the first, shook the bed on the sixth floor of their Miami apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout continues from biggest global ransomware attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-government-and-politics-technology-business-88c51d8041b1afdd42fa9f571c3de446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The single biggest ransomware attack yet continued to bite Monday as more details emerged on how a Russia-linked gang breached the exploited software company. The criminals essentially used a tool that helps protect against malware to spread it globally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada FINALLY reopening border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/canada-lifestyle-travel-coronavirus-pandemic-health-2b873761884d6aed7b7088a15fefb654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Pandemic restrictions on travel between Canada and the U.S. began to loosen Monday for some Canadians, and Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said plans to totally reopen the border would be announced over the next few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tribe becomes key water player with drought aid to Arizona...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arizona-science-government-and-politics-business-environment-and-nature-3d27c894e028629e87a14d7a41ddd5db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLAGSTAFF, Ariz. (AP) — For thousands of years, an Arizona tribe relied on the Colorado River's natural flooding patterns to farm. Later, it hand-dug ditches and canals to route water to fields. Now, gravity sends the river water from the north end of the Colorado River Indian Tribes reservation through 19th century canals to sustain alfalfa, cotton, wheat, onions and potatoes, mainly by flooding the fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S1t90INfeGY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to boost birth rate by adopting Nordic position?</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/economics/article/3136991/can-china-boost-its-birth-rate-adopting-nordic-position</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As China drops its two-child limit to increase its birth rate, experts are hoping it can learn from Scandinavian countries that boosted fertility with pro-family policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emhoff carves out path as first second gentleman...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/561441-doug-emhoff-carves-out-path-as-first-second-gentleman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doug Emhoff has spent the first six months of the Biden administration carving out his role as the first second gentleman of the United States, traversing across the country to promote coronavirus vaccines and extend support to small businesses.&amp;n</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In final days, Khashoggi juggled secret wife and fiancee...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/he-gave-nobody-a-full-view-of-his-life-in-his-final-days-jamal-khashoggi-juggled-a-secret-wife-in-the-us-and-a-fiance-in-turkey-090031920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Khashoggi had a penchant to be secretive about much of his life. “If somebody sits across from you when you’re interviewing people about Jamal and tells you that Jamal told them everything, they are 100 percent lying to you,” said one friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA left Afghan airfield at night, didn't tell new commander...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bagram-afghanistan-airfield-us-troops-f3614828364f567593251aaaa167e623</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGRAM, Afghanistan (AP) — The U.S. left Afghanistan's Bagram Airfield after nearly 20 years by shutting off the electricity and slipping away in the night without notifying the base's new Afghan commander, who discovered the Americans' departure more than two hours after they left, Afghan military officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like zoo animals': Eats alone at 'roped-off table' at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/like-zoo-animals-donald-and-melania-trump-eat-alone-at-a-roped-off-table-at-a-mar-a-lago-restaurant-book-says/ar-AALNMQC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They are like a newly married couple: every night is a wedding at which they spend their dinner greeting friends and wellwishers," Michael Wolff wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large fire reported near Tehran, background unclear...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/large-fire-reported-near-tehran-background-unclear-report-672964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fire broke out in Karaj, south of Tehran, the city where an alleged attack targeted a nuclear facility reportedly used to produce centrifuges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists clone cow to produce lactose-free milk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9757939/Russian-scientists-clone-cow-edit-genes-remove-protein-causes-lactose-intolerance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in Moscow have cloned a cow whose milk doesn't contain the protein that causes lactose intolerance in humans. Born in April 2020, the calf is healthy with a normal reproductive cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inked Mummies, Linking Tattoo Artists With Their Ancestors...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/05/inked-mummies-linking-tattoo-artists-with-their-ancestors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1970s, hunters stumbled upon eight 500-year-old bodies preserved by the Arctic climate near Qilakitsoq, an abandoned Inuit settlement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy 13-year-old dies 3 days after receiving PFIZER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9756975/CDC-launches-investigation-healthy-boy-dies-three-days-receiving-second-Covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jacob Clynick, a 13-year-old from Michigan has died in his sleep three days after receiving his second Coronavirus vaccine, prompting an investigation by the Centers for Disease Control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4-day week 'overwhelming success' in Iceland...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-57724779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majority of workers in Iceland now look set to move to shorter hours for the same pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANNES COVID CONFUSION: FESTIVAL GOERS MUST SPIT IN TUBE...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/cannes-covid-saliva-tests-1235011802/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday afternoon, Olivia Wilson had arrived from her home in Tennessee to the Cannes Film Festival, where she’ll be working as an intern at the American Pavilion. But before she got to enjoy the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE, MICROSOFT end 5-year cease-fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/google-and-microsoft-end-their-5-year-cease-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The old nonaggression pact between Google and Microsoft, forged at the time by two new CEOs wanting a fresh start on a formerly acrimonious relationship, had already been fraying before it lapsed in April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moguls, Deals, Vests: Look Inside 'Summer Camp For Billionaires'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/07/05/1012587989/moguls-deals-and-patagonia-vests-a-look-inside-summer-camp-for-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg is expected to attend. So is Apple's Tim Cook. A look inside the Sun Valley conference for top media and tech moguls organized by a little known investment firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts want to re-normalize mask-wearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/should-fully-vaccinated-people-continue-wear-masks-experts-weigh-n1272890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Do whatever it takes for Covid to go away," one doctor said. That includes continuing to wear a mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain restricts nightlife as virus surges among young...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-spain-coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-c03dead9ceedeb6f1e3e563d8cea2a68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Faced with soaring numbers of new coronavirus infections among unvaccinated young people, some Spanish regions are reinstating curbs on nightlife only weeks after dropping them. Fearing that the surging contagion could strain health care services as stressed employees try to go on summer holidays, health officials in several parts of the country are also rushing to get COVID-19 vaccine shots to people under 30.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever AI drone swarm in battle to hunt down, blitz terrorists...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3222879/israel-first-ever-drone-swarm-hamas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL used the first ever drone swarm deployed in battle to hunt down Hamas terrorists, it was reported. The drones have no human input but instead link together using artificial intelligence to s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'animal slaughter festivals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3222148/animal-slaughter-festival-world-yulin-dog-meat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of dogs were brutally killed as part of the Yulin Dog Meat Festival last month – but the controversial event is far from the only one around the world. Animal rights activists and celebri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lizard venom inspired promising weight loss drug...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22553793/gila-monster-lizard-venom-inspired-obesity-drug-semaglutide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Semaglutide is the start of a new chapter in obesity treatments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran forever dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/essays/article/End-of-the-Golden-Gate-book-review-16281983.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As San Franciscans, we’ll always be looking over our shoulders at Austin and Portland...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Neighborhood runs for cover as U-HAUL full of fireworks explodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article252579913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three people were injured in the explosion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compulsory jabs: Pressure grows on anti-vaxxers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nursinginpractice.com/covid-19/government-to-consult-soon-on-compulsory-covid-jabs-for-healthcare-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nursinginpractice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A public consultation on making Covid-19 and flu jabs compulsory for patient-facing staff across all healthcare settings will be launched ‘shortly’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa suffers record number of cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-africas-coronavirus-cases-surge-160236823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa's resurgence of COVID-19 is setting record numbers of new daily cases, centered in Johannesburg and driven by the delta variant, health officials said Sunday. More than 26,000 new cases were reported on Saturday, up from 24,000 the previous day, according to the National Institute for Communicable Diseases, surpassing the highest number of new cases in previous waves and quickly bringing many hospitals to capacity. More than 13,800 COVID-19 patients are currently in South African hospitals where some facilities are canceling elective surgeries to free up beds and health care workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel data 'preliminary signal' Delta variant can bypass vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-07-israel-preliminary-delta-variant-bypass.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising coronavirus cases in Israel, where most residents are inoculated with the Pfizer/BioNTech vaccine, offer "a preliminary signal" the vaccine may be less effective in preventing mild illness from the Delta variant, a top expert said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HTFulTnlG7c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newark Airport 'emergency' sparks evacuation... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3221987/newark-airport-evacuated-passengers-screaming-running/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN “EMERGENCY” at Newark Airport sparked an evacuation with passengers reportedly being seen screaming and running. Reports emerged that Terminal C was evacuated just after 10.30am. Ima…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL goalie dead at 24 in 'tragic accident'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/05/blue-jackets-goalie-matiss-kivlenieks-dead-at-24-in-tragic-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Jackets goaltender Matiss Kivlenieks died Sunday night as a result of what the organization described as a “tragic accident,” in which he suffered an apparent head injury after a fall. He was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party all night? NYC agency floats nightlife district plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nyc-state-wire-ny-state-wire-lifestyle-fe4f57a5339fd94294e5baf070f81762</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The city that never sleeps could live up to its name under a New York City agency's proposal for 24-hour entertainment districts where revelers can party all night. The city's Office of Nightlife is recommending that officials identify areas with low residential density “where a limited 24-hour program might be tested.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man bitten by neighbor's escaped python in toilet...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-austria-environment-and-nature-f6197c876b74881cca252980f8ed98c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A man in Austria was bitten by a 1.6-meter (5 1/4-foot) python during an early-morning visit to the toilet at his home on Monday, police said. The reptile, which apparently escaped from a neighbor's apartment and may have slithered through the drains, was cleaned and handed back to its owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg posts bizarre vid waving flag while riding electronic surfboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3218640/mark-zuckerberg-july-4th-american-flag-wakeboarding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARK Zuckerberg shared a bizarre video of himself carrying an American flag while surfboarding to celebrate July 4 on Sunday. The Facebook CEO, 37, posted the wacky video to his Instagram page with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Year Is It? Number 1 and 2 Albums on iTunes Are 40 and 50 Years Old...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/04/what-year-is-it-the-number-1-and-2-albums-on-itunes-are-40-queen-and-50-joni-mitchell-years-old</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What year is it again? Over the weekend, Queen’s Greatest Hits went to number 1 on iTunes. Joni Mitchell’s “Blue” is number 2. They are from 1981 and 1971, respectively.  I …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare scenario: Alarm as advertisers seek to plug into dreams...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/nightmare-scenario-alarm-advertisers-seek-080045887.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Coors sought to steer unconscious minds to thoughts of beer, scientists have called for curbs on ‘targeted dream incubation’ Mmm … insipid lager. Photograph: wunkley/Alamy When brewing giant Coors launched a new advertising campaign earlier this year, the format came as a surprise to many. The company was planning to infiltrate people’s dreams to get them to buy, and presumably drink, Coors beer. Coors encouraged people to watch a short online video before bed, then play an eight-hour “sou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far-Right Militia Infiltrated Island in Washington...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/far-militia-infiltrated-island-washington-052033469.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heath Druzin for The Daily BeastLANGLEY, Washington—On Saturday, about 100 people gathered in a park in this normally sleepy town of about 1,200, some wearing Black Lives Matter shirts, others with peace symbols. Speakers took turns inveighing on fighting racism and standing up for LGBTQ rights, regular causes in the left-wing activist space.But their target was not racist cops, conservative Republicans, or some other traditional bête noire. Instead, their anger was squarely trained at the param</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years after 9/11, lawsuit against Saudis hits key moment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sept-11-saudi-arabia-lawsuit-1b5fec1d2507eb27fffdac25bab79bb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As the 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks approaches, victims' relatives are pressing the courts to answer what they see as lingering questions about the Saudi government's role in the attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian singer claims hacked after X-rated photo appears on TWITTER account...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3219948/songs-of-praise-aled-jones-twitter-hack-rude-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SONGS Of Praise star Aled Jones said his Twitter was hacked after a very rude photo was posted on his account. The singer, 50, apologised to fans after a close up picture of a man’s crotch in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundbreaking Microchip Measures Stress Hormones In Real Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/microchip-measures-stress-hormones-from-drop-of-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A groundbreaking microchip that can measure stress hormones in real-time from a drop of blood has been developed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MASSIVE RANSOMWARE ATTACK HITS MILLION COMPANIES!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3220095/million-cyber-attack-russia-hackers-revil-ransom-bitcoin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN hackers REvil have demanded a $70 million ransom in Bitcoin for a decryption key, after a cyberattack that targeted 1,000 US firms.  The breach, which is the largest ransomware attack on re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange signal coming from Milky Way. What's causing it?</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/strange-signal-from-milky-way</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space Mysteries: A fast radio burst was detected from within our galaxy for the first time. We may be closer to uncovering its origin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure grows to ease travel bans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/561390-pressure-grows-for-biden-to-ease-pandemic-travel-bans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is coming under pressure to ease travel bans for international tourists that were originally put in place to stem the spread of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare scenario: Alarm as advertisers seek to plug into dreams...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jul/05/advertisers-targeted-dream-incubation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Coors sought to steer unconscious minds to thoughts of beer, scientists have called for curbs on ‘targeted dream incubation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST, AMERICAN delays hint at hard summer for travelers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-travel-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-34a82df567df3f3def46cfca1af601a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This summer is already shaping up to be a difficult one for air travelers. Southwest Airlines customers have struggled with thousands of delays and hundreds of canceled flights this month because of computer problems, staffing shortages and bad weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope alert and in good condition after intestinal surgery, Vatican says...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210705091340-ukbhe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-SURGERY/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Pope alert and in good condition after intestinal surgery, Vatican says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACKERS DEMAND $70 MILLION TO RESTORE DATA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210705044556-8apae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CYBER/KASEYA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Hackers demand $70 mln to restore data held by companies hit in cyberattack - blog</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colon Cancer Rising in Younger Adults. Do Sugary Drinks Play Role?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/05/colon-cancer-is-rising-in-younger-adults-do-sugary-drinks-play-a-role/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colon and rectal cancers are rising in younger adults, though researchers aren’t sure why. A new study of women and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber insurers struggle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-government-and-politics-4c2272cdd428ddfa1f3644d513566c06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — In the past few weeks, ransomware criminals claimed as trophies at least three North American insurance brokerages that offer policies to help others survive the very network-paralyzing, data-pilfering extortion attacks they themselves apparently suffered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search back on after rest of Surfside condo demolished...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-fl-state-wire-florida-surfside-building-collapse-bd072f3a85777f2d0be8ef19d2499b33</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — Rescuers were given the all-clear to resume work looking for victims at a collapsed South Florida condo building after demolition crews set off a string of explosives that brought down the last of the building in a plume of dust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MASSIVE RANSOMWARE ATTACK HITS THOUSANDS OF COMPANIES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-government-and-politics-technology-business-fc0df4c42f8cd6148bf936ca24bb5cbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Cybersecurity teams worked feverishly Sunday to stem the impact of the single biggest global ransomware attack on record, with some details emerging about how the Russia-linked gang responsible breached the company whose software was the conduit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavily Armed Militia Group Shuts Down I-95 in Bizarre Standoff...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/armed-standoff-wakefield-massachusetts-9ee61b69ca96bb5ce212f56651f0dd11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAKEFIELD, Mass. (AP) — An hourslong standoff with a group of heavily armed men that partially shut down Interstate 95 ended Saturday with 11 suspects in custody, Massachusetts state police said. The standoff shut down a portion of I-95 for much of the morning, causing major traffic problems during the Fourth of July holiday weekend.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
