<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People who post selfies seen as less likable, less successful...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/life/lifestyle/people-who-post-selfies-are-seen-as-less-likable-and-less-successful-wsu-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a study that will publish this fall in the Journal of Research in Personality, individuals who posted a lot of selfies were almost uniformly viewed as less likable, less successful and more insecure than people who posted more "posies" — that is, traditionally...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: 'Afghan asylum seeker' kills one, wounds dozen in knife rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-lyon-knife-attack-one-19114957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man alleged to be an Afghan asylum seeker knifed almost a dozen people at random while armed with a blade and a barbecue fork in the Lyon suburb of Villeurbanne, it is claimed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling protests break out at 'Straight Pride Parade' in Boston...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/boston-straight-pride-parade-today-dueling-protests-break-out-city-hall-2019-08-31/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Straight Pride Parade" kicked off in Boston Saturday afternoon with a "Trump 2020" float</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies in Death Valley National Park as temps approach 120 degrees...</title>
      <link>https://heraldpublicist.com/woman-dies-in-death-valley-national-park-as-temperatures-approach-120-degrees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;heraldpublicist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces more 2020 danger if Dem scores upset in NCarolina special election...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-faces-more-2020-danger-if-democrat-scores-upset-n-n1047226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: The closely watched Sept. 10 vote will fill a House seat that is vacant after last year's results were invalidated due to election fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details of Tyler Skaggs' death could trigger legal battle with millions at stake....</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/sports/angels/story/2019-08-31/tyler-skaggs-death-drugs-angels-employee-legal-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details of how Tyler Skaggs died from drugs could determine whether his family and the Angels are drawn into a legal battle with millions at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie plan to cancel all medical debt!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/459518-sanders-previews-plan-to-cancel-all-past-due-medical-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House hopeful Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) on Saturday previewed his upcoming plan to cancel all past due medical debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside al-Hawl camp -- incubator for ISIS resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/aug/31/inside-al-hawl-camp-the-incubator-for-islamic-states-resurgence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camp for Iraqis and Syrians fleeing caliphate flooded by families of Isis fighters, brewing deeper problems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden earthquake risk found lurking beneath Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/08/hidden-earthquake-risk-discovered-under-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fault was once thought dead, but recent research suggests it’s likely still active—and poses a hazard to the metropolis above.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran taunts Trump with selfie over rocket explosion tweet...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/31/iran-taunts-trump-with-selfie-over-rocket-explosion-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s IT minister fired back at President Trump’s allegation that a rocket exploded on a test site in northern Iran — by tweeting a selfie with Tehran’s prized satellite fully in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 10 teens shot at high school football game; 17-year-old arrested...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/10-teens-shot-high-school-football-game-alabama/story?id=65309106</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A police chief in Alabama said people's "beefs" are "putting people in harm's way" after a shooting at a football game left 10 teens wounded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Droid Welder To Replace Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/technology/meet-robotic-welder-will-soon-be-putting-construction-workers-out-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH AND WAIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/How-Might-Dorian-Compare-Great-Florida-Keys-Labor-Day-Hurricane-1935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Dorian intensifies on its way to The Bahamas and Florida, it’s worth comparing to another famous Labor Day weekend hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST REACTIONS: DARK MASTERPIECE...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/joker-movie-first-reactions-dark-masterpiece/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first reactions to Joker are calling the film a dark, disturbing masterpiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Unleashes Military to Fight Fake News, Disinformation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-unleashes-military-fight-fake-134326896.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Fake news and social media posts are such a threat to U.S. security that the Defense Department is launching a project to repel “large-scale, automated disinformation attacks,” as the top Republican in Congress blocks efforts to protect the integrity of elections.The Defense Advanced Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOAQUIN PHOENIX: I WENT MAD TRANSFORMING INTO JOKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/joaquin-phoenix-on-his-joker-transformation-you-start-to-go-mad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Joker” actor opened up about his shocking turn as the titular supervillain at the Venice Film Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Happiness -- How Close Live To Nature...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/the-closer-you-live-to-nature-the-happier-youll-be-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new study, living within walking distance to an urban green space is associated with improved feelings of happiness, self-worth, and overall life satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too old for president? Health and fitness a better question...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9bb19e782e224fbe948575ce25348645</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Science says age is only a number, not a proxy for physical and mental fitness. But with three Democrats in their 70s vying to challenge the oldest first-term president in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDTWKADU4AIE38E?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Calls for Compromise as East-West Gap Risks Social Fabric...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-calls-compromise-east-west-130133153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chancellor Angela Merkel called for a better exchange of ideas between different parts of Germany as social tensions in the former communist east look set to contribute to bruising electoral losses for the parties in her coalition.Speaking after receiving an honorary degree from a university</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heightened security in Boston for 'pro-straight parade'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/heightened-security-boston-pro-straight-parade-062515220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Boston were gearing up for possible clashes Saturday between "Straight Pride Parade" demonstrators supportive of President Donald Trump and counter-protesters who accuse them of being homophobic and extremist. A group calling itself Super Happy Fun America has organized the controversial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Wealth Hinges on Ability to Borrow Big -- or Else...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-wealth-hinges-ability-borrow-120000587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. economy is consistently ranked among the world’s strongest. But cut off its addiction to debt and exhaust its gold and currency reserves, and a very different picture would emerge.The nation’s health as measured by gross domestic product per capita would plunge into negative territory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hints of factory-driven slowdown in key election states...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-manufacturing-slowdown/hints-of-factory-driven-slowdown-in-key-2020-u-s-election-states-idUSKCN1VK27V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decline in economic activity in the U.S. Midwest, apparent in a little-noticed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China lunar rover finds unexplained 'gel like' substance on Moon dark side...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/unexplained-gel-like-substance-unusual-19112236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space scientists stunned by discovery as China urgently halts all missions of its lunar probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teledildonics users 'sexually assaulted' by hackers 'spying on people having sex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/teledildonics-users-sexually-assaulted-hackers-19023962</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security expert showed how easy it is to hack a butt-plug</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROWING THREAT FOR GEORGIA, CAROLINAS...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2019-08-31-hurricane-dorian-bahamas-florida-georgia-carolinas-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are some key changes in the forecast. Here's what we know right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA Agents Ambush AMTRAK Passengers With Controversial Searches and Seizures...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/08/31/dea-amtrak-passenger-search-albuquerque/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the help of Amtrak and Greyhound informants, agents approach people on thin evidence they are drug couriers — and often take their cash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans fear backlash in suburbs...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/459436-gop-fears-trump-backlash-in-suburbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are growing increasingly worried they will lose the suburbs with President Trump at the top of the ticket in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK assassin Sirhan Sirhan stabbed in prison...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ebe7cfc1b97f4b4e9e56e19a9a697e47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Sirhan Sirhan, imprisoned for more than 50 years for the 1968 assassination of Sen. Robert F. Kennedy, was hospitalized Friday after being stabbed by a fellow inmate at a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico 'Teflon' presidency starting to show wear...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/caaf6e9650224f8cbad01ea50a55a1e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico's drug war has burst into flames again, the economy is flat, the health care system is creaking and President Andrés Manuel López Obrador — facing the wrath of U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters build wall, set fire on main street...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e789a51a2204ce98077ab32889ab263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — A large fire blazed across a main street in Hong Kong on Saturday night, as protesters made a wall out of barricades and set it afire. Hundreds of protesters gathered behind the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM COULD SPARE DIRECT HIT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4f1e25f746ae4406a1792266e44682c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Hurricane Dorian has gained fearsome new muscle as an "extremely dangerous" Category 4 storm, bearing down on the northwestern Bahamas early Saturday en route to Florida's east...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATELLITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.star.nesdis.noaa.gov/GOES/sector_band.php?sat=G16&amp;sector=car&amp;band=GEOCOLOR&amp;length=12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star.nesdis.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's personal assistant fired after comments about family...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/30/trumps-personal-assistant-fired-ivanka-tiffany-1479226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The critical comments happened at an off-the-record dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EDQVw2OWsAEZq8E?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
