<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Burqa ban: Sri Lanka bars wearing face veils...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/sri-lanka-attacks-latest-burqa-ban-face-veil-muslim-women-emergency-law-easter-sunday-bombings-a8890541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines eye crueler ways of making passengers miserable...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/business-economy/2019/04/27/airlines-eye-crueler-ways-of-making-passengers-miserable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Delta’s case, the airline is testing reduced-recline seats on its entire A320 fleet. The idea, Delta insists, isn’t to squeeze more seats into the economy cabin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers making bank ratting out idling drivers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/28/how-new-yorkers-are-making-bank-ratting-out-idling-drivers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dropping a dime on trucks and buses that keep their engines running while parked is paying big bucks to some New Yorkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife arrested after calling cops on cheating husband...</title>
      <link>https://www.montgomeryadvertiser.com/story/news/crime/2019/04/28/millbrook-woman-arrested-for-making-false-report/3608678002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.montgomeryadvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 9 a.m. Wednesday morning, Millbrook police received a call from a woman who reported a burglary in progress at her home.Â There was no burglar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labor union concern over AMAZON move to one-day shipping...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/labor-union-raises-concern-over-amazons-move-to-one-day-shipping-2019-04-28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.’s move toward one-day free shipping may be good news for Prime subscribers, but not necessarily for those who work in Amazon’s warehouses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pill that pings doctors shows promise, pitfalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/business/article/Pill-that-pings-doctors-shows-promise-pitfalls-13802445.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Food and Drug Administration approved in late 2017 a schizophrenia pill that sends a signal to a patient's doctor when ingested, it was seen not only as a major step forward for the disease but as a new frontier of internet-connected medicine.  Patients who have schizophrenia often stop taking their medicine, triggering psychotic episodes that can have severe consequences. So the pill, a 16-year-old medication combined with a tiny microchip, would help doctors intervene before a patient went dangerously off course.  Seventeen months later, few patients use the medication, known as Abilify MyCite. Doctors and insurance companies say it is a case in which real-world limitations, as well as costs, outweigh the innovations that the medical industry can produce.  In the case of schizophrenics, some doctors warn that Abilify MyCite could exacerbate the very delusions that the medication is designed to prevent.  "Patients who have a lot of paranoia might be uncomfortable with the idea of a medicine that is transmitting signals. The patient may be afraid to take it," said Richmond psychiatrist James Levenson. "The science of this one is kind of ahead of the data."  The debate over Abilify MyCite underscores a dilemma American health care will increasingly face as the medical industry and Silicon Valley try to promote innovation. For decades, medicine has been effectively delivered through a few simple mechanisms: a pill, a cream, a nose spray, a needle.  But in the hopes of improving outcomes further, the industry is turning to an array of new technologies against one of the biggest, and most human, challenges in treating disease: getting people to take their medicine in a consistent way.  Companies are producing apps for substance abuse treatment, diabetes management, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>272 Indonesian ballot counters die of exhaustion following election...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/work/1606850/nearly-300-ballot-counters-die-of-exhaustion-in-indonesia-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to 750 million ballots need to be counted in Indonesia—by hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of 'Salvator Mundi', world's most costly painting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20190428/mystery-of-salvator-mundi-the-worlds-most-costly-painting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Later this year, the Louvre in Paris will host an exhibition of masterpieces by the Italian painter Leonardo da Vinci to mark his death 500 years ago in France. But the work that in recent months has been the intense focus of scrutiny by the media and da Vinci specialists, may not be on show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker speech interrupted by van crashing into venue!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article229778754.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Anita Hill In 1998: 'She Was Lying'...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/04/28/joe-biden-on-anita-hill-in-1998-she-was-lying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diver ran out of air at bottom of ocean -- and lived...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20190423-the-man-who-ran-out-of-air-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science tells us the human body can only survive for a few minutes without oxygen. But some people are defying this accepted truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL rookie shot hours after selected...</title>
      <link>https://www.wibw.com/content/news/One-person-dead-following-overnight-shooting-in-Topeka-509179821.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wibw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washburn football player was killed in an overnight shooting in central Topeka that also wounded a former player, according to Washburn University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8956363/model-tales-soares-dies-catwalk-sao-paulo/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MALE model who died after collapsing on the catwalk during Sao Paulo’s Fashion Week may have had an undiagnosed congenital illness, doctors said. Tales Soares, 26, was attended to by parame…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranded dolphin in Florida had plastic bags, balloon in stomach... </title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida/2019/04/28/stranded-dolphin-in-florida-had-plastic-bags-balloon-in-stomach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The female rough-toothed dolphin had to be euthanized after washing up on Fort Myers Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto accuses  White House of dictating FOXNEWS content...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-orourke/democrat-orourke-accuses-trump-white-house-of-dictating-fox-news-content-idUSKCN1S40UN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Democratic presidential candidate Beto O'Rourke attacked the close tie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialists win Spain election...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-election/spanish-voters-put-socialists-in-pole-position-to-regain-power-idUSKCN1S30MB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's Socialist prime minister, Pedro Sanchez, emerged from inconclusive ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Bernie likable enough to become president?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2019/04/28/bernie-sanders-likable-enough-become-president/svONYPDuGqprm1gdD56cXO/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many voters, the Vermont senator’s gruff manner is evidence of his authenticity. But with a record number of women running for the Democratic presidential nomination, some in the party feel he has not been subjected to the same personality-based critiques as female candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewer rushed to hospital for crying uncontrollably...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/a-woman-lands-up-at-the-hospital-after-crying-too-much-watching-the-avengers/articleshow/69081306.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman had to be rushed to the hospital where she was then given oxygen to settle her breathing. According to reports, the woman cried so much that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congregants Tell of Quick Action to Save Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/synagogue-congregants-tell-of-quick-action-to-save-children-amid-chaos-of-attack-11556490153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attack on a synagogue in Poway, Calif., was a chaotic yet short-lived episode in which congregants recognized quickly that a shooter was in their midst and took action. They told how they covered one another and corralled children toward exits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Returns With Tensions Running High...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/congress-returns-with-tensions-running-high-11556449239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers will return this week to a Washington landscape transformed by the unveiling of special counsel Robert Mueller’s report, which has sparked an intensifying fight between Capitol Hill and the White House over Democrats’ push to probe the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, once vaccine skeptic, changes his tune amid measles outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/04/26/trump-vaccinations-measles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They have to get the shots. The vaccinations are so important," President Trump told reporters as he left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialists win Spain election...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-spain-election-no-majority/leftist-bloc-holds-advantage-in-spains-election-with-95-percent-of-votes-counted-idUSKCN1S40SA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leftist political bloc in Spain held the advantage over its rightist rivals ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans women fighting transgender military ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/meet-trans-women-fighting-transgender-military-ban-20190428.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deirdre Hendrick and Alice Ashton, both stationed at Fort Meade in Maryland, knew the ban had been coming since President Donald Trump tweeted about it in July 2017, but with nationwide lawsuits, it wasn’t clear until March 12 that the ban would officially kick in on April 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Feel Little Pressure From Voters to Impeach... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/kids/other/house-democrats-feel-little-pressure-from-voters-to-impeach-trump/ar-BBWnj7y?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAT EPIDEMIC WARNING!</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2019-04-29/obesity-significantly-increases-risk-of-serious-disease-researchers-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Dead, 6 People Shot near Baltimore church... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6970119/Seven-people-shot-near-Baltimore-church.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven people have been shot outside a Maryland church. The shooting occurred close to the Perkins Square Baptist Church in Baltimore at about 5.30pm on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botox and veneers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6970041/How-Joe-Biden-underwent-cosmetic-overhaul-make-appealing-voters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden has altered his hairline, filled in the wrinkles on his face and forehead, and installed dental veneers, according to plastic surgeons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuls struggle with security...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2202481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- Rabbi Yonah Bookstein of Los Angeles' Pico Shul was at home Saturday afternoon, observing the Sabbath, when someone on the synagogue's security team alerted him about the deadly shooting at the Chabad of Poway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese and De Niro look back ahead of 'THE IRISHMAN'... </title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d07f7374825b4d7fa7000229ada13513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ahead of their much-anticipated and most recent collaboration, "The Irishman," Martin Scorsese and Robert De Niro convened at the Tribeca Film Festival to look back on their long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions about immunity in adults...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190428140644-ao7d0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/ (PIX):U.S. measles outbreak raises questions about immunity in adults</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Needs more executioners...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8957769/saudi-arabia-beheadings-execution-jobs/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ruthless Saudi government is beheading so many people it needs to recruit a deadly new squad of sword-wielding executioners. The news comes after it slaughtered 37 people in one bloody day last…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun miraculously jammed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8191b03a1090479f9a305d65c83deb06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on the shooting at a California synagogue (all times local): 2:30 p.m. Rabbi Yisroel Goldstein says the gunman fled after the weapon used in the attack...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady's heir? Patriots draft Stidham...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/patriots/2019/04/27/2019-nfl-draft-patriots-jarrett-stidham-quarterback-tom-brady/3599751002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots' selection of Auburn's Jarrett Stidham in the fourth round of the NFL draft adds some intrigue to their quarterback room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA PUSHED BIDEN NOT TO RUN IN '16</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/politics/the-long-run-biden-and-obamas-odd-couple-relationship-aged-into-family-ties/ar-BBWmF5i?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 85:  JOAN COLLINS SHARES #METOO MOMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6969285/Joan-Collins-says-studio-head-offered-Liz-Taylors-Cleopatra-role-slept-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joan Collins touched on some of the may men in her life, from her love affair with Warren Beatty and on-set romance with Harry Belafonte to her five husbands - whom she ranked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/video/sunday-profile-dynasty-star-joan-collins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the scheming Alexis Carrington on the '80s TV series "Dynasty," British actress Joan Collins was really good at being bad. Mo Rocca talks with Collins about her film and TV career, her five husbands, and her catfights with "Dynasty" co-star Linda Evans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Attorney General Investigates...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/oliver-north-out-as-nra-president-11556376506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York attorney general’s office is investigating potential financial and disclosure problems at the National Rifle Association, amid boardroom turmoil at the group that led Saturday to the departure of NRA President Oliver North after a bruising internal political battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Whistleblower Complaints Emerge against BOEING 737 MAX... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-whistleblower-complaints-emerge-in-boeing-737-max-safety-inquiries-11556418721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are looking into complaints by roughly a dozen purported whistleblowers alleging safety problems with Boeing’s 737 MAX jets, according to officials familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD OF CONDEMNATIONS OF NYT FOR ANTISEMITIC CARTOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/Antisemitism/Flood-of-condemnations-of-NYT-for-anti-Semitic-cartoon-588044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressmen join former ambassador to Israel and journalists in slamming the newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite record diversity, 70-something white men rule 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/despite-record-diversity-70-something-white-men-rule-013121612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats seeking to reclaim the White House are calling for generational change. President Donald Trump is a 72-year-old billionaire, and for many he epitomizes the white male privilege that Democrats often decry. Former vice president Joe Biden, who jumped into the race Thursday, is 76 and has spent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENTS DINNER OPENS WITH DARK SERMON ON TRUMP ENDANGERING JOURNALISTS...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-lieu-comedy-whcd-opens-dark-sermon-trump-endangering-journal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘My son asked me, “Is Donald Trump going to put you in prison?”‘</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AVENGERS' $1.2 BILLION Weekend!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/798efe76562549c687eceb78820838e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — "Avengers: Endgame" has shattered the record for biggest opening weekend with an estimated $350 million in domestic ticket sales and $1.2 billion globally. The Marvel Studios...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation reels from deadly synagogue attack on final day of Passover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14d2196c6d584b1287bc862a0e53c00a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POWAY, Calif. (AP) — The rabbi who led a service on the last day of Passover suffered a gunshot wound to his hands and two others endured shrapnel wounds as political, civic and religious leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8956363/model-tales-soares-dies-catwalk-sao-paulo/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MALE model has died after collapsing on the catwalk during Sao Paulo’s Fashion Week. Tales Soares, 26, was attended to by paramedics in front of horrified onlookers after being taken ill du…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Relaunches as Global Platform...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/04/the-sri-lanka-bombings-were-a-preview-of-isiss-future/588175/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sri Lanka bombings were a preview of the Islamic State’s future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio pioneer emerges as alleged scam artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/sports/2019/04/26/marty-tirrell-kxno-the-jock-troy-aikman-steve-luebke-sports-radio-federal-prosecutors-scam-iowa/3578354002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts native brought his shrill radio voice to Des Moines in 1995; he also allegedly brought a penchant for cheating people out of money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr testimony to House on Mueller in doubt amid dispute...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/06c8721db0b944d192cddef2bfdaa8a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department has informed the House Judiciary Committee that Attorney General William Barr may not attend a Thursday hearing to review special counsel Robert Mueller's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACT CHECK: Unraveling Cow Fart Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2019-04-28/ap-fact-check-unraveling-the-mystery-of-whether-cows-fart</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominate a woman? Dem women not so sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.mynews13.com/fl/orlando/ap-top-news/2019/04/28/nominate-a-woman-some-democratic-women-arent-so-sure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mynews13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democratic women say they&amp;#39;re worried about nominating a woman for president after Hillary Clinton&amp;#39;s loss to Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed while protecting rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/28/us/california-synagogue-shooting-victims/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a gunman opened fire in a synagogue in California, killing one and injuring three others, Lori Kaye jumped between the shooter and the rabbi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Predicts Own Blue 'Wave' In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/rubycramer/bernie-sanders-blue-wave-winning-organizing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"My friends, you are going to see a wave — a wave up and down the Democratic ballot."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How inmates extort families from behind bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2019/04/alabama-inmates-extort-families-beyond-the-walls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department's investigation of Alabama prisons for men uncovered details about prisoners who extort money from other inmates' families. The Alabama Department of Corrections says its Investigations and Intelligence Division has looked into 18 extortion cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone delivers kidney for transplant...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2019/04/earth-shattering-drone-delivers-kidney-for-transplant-over-baltimore/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unmanned aircraft system’s flight last week through the city of Baltimore was less than 3 miles, but it represented a huge first step. See photos and video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record UK stabbing homicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/04/27/knife-crime-britain-wales-national-emergency-record-stabbing-homicides/3470942002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two-hundred and eighty-five people died in knife-related homicides in England and Wales in 2018. It's being call a national crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man on lam after stealing police car while en route to jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/local/sumner/2019/04/27/sumner-sheriffs-looking-man-stole-police-car/3599974002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sumner County Sheriff's Office saidÂ a corrections officer was transportingÂ Dreon Key when Key took control of the jail car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model dies after taking ill on catwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Model-in-Sao-Paulo-dies-after-taking-ill-on-13801184.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) - A model participating in Sao Paulo's Fashion Week has died after getting sick and falling on the catwalk.  A statement from organizers said Tales Soares took ill Saturday while in a parade of fashion brand Ocksa. A medical team attended to him on the catwalk and Soares was later taken to a hospital, where he was pronounced dead.  The statement did not provide more details.  Daily Folha de S. Paulo reported that Soares tripped on his shoelace and fell. According to the paper, people in the crowd initially thought his fall was part of a performance.  A photo in the newspaper showed the model lying face down on the catwalk while paramedics attended to him. The paper reported Soares was 26 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far from glitzy tech hubs, Chinese city bets big on VR...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7dfb8061bc64be182cf9d57fe88e13b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NANCHANG, China (AP) — Liu Zixing craned his neck forward for help with fastening the goggles for his first ever taste of virtual reality. He took a break from the mining ore business to travel to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran foreign minister to visit NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/28/mohammad-javad-zarif-iran-foreign-minister-visit-n/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, says he will visit North Korea as both countries struggle under U.S. sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital cemetery: When FACEBOOK controls human history...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190428-facebook-zuckerberg-dead-orwell-oxford-internet-institute</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Facebook profiles of people who have died may exceed the number of living profiles in just 50 years, according to a new study. As such, the social network could become the keeper of a significant part of humanity’s memory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finders keepers? Police say no way after $30K spills on road...</title>
      <link>https://fox4kc.com/2019/04/27/finders-keepers-michigan-police-say-no-way-after-30k-spills-on-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox4kc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND HAVEN, Mich. -- Police in Michigan are appealing to people to surrender their instant riches after a box with $30,000 fell off the back of a truck. Authorities in Grand Haven say drivers stopped Thursday to pick up cash for themselves. Only $2,500 was immediately recovered and returned to the owner, who had forgotten that a cash box was on the truck's bumper. Traffic was backed up on U.S. 31 after money hit the ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities search for arsonist who set fire outside National Archives...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/authorities-search-arsonist-who-set-fire-outside-national-archives-washington-n999161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Archives houses beloved historical documents such as the Constitution and the Declaration of Independence.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
