<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SINGER TO HONOR KNEELING PROTEST DURING HALFTIME SHOW?</title>
      <link>https://www.bizpacreview.com/2019/02/02/maroon-5-frontman-hints-superbowl-show-will-be-hip-hop-kneeling-fest-fox-news-offers-alternative-for-halftime-720139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bizpacreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proud, flag-loving patriots who hate seeing the American flag be disrespected may have no other option but to tune out of the upcoming Super Bowl halftime show. The show has been mired in controversy because of a concerted effort by radical far-left activists to stop any artist from performing at the event. To them, any …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip from 'concerned citizen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-tip-from-a-concerned-citizen-helps-a-reporter-13585192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reporter who exposed Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam's racist yearbook photo said a "concerned citizen" led him to the story that has prompted widespread outrage and calls for the Democrat's resignation. Patrick Howley, editor in chief of the website Big League Politics, first reported Friday the existence of a photo on Northam's page of his medical-school yearbook depicting a figure in blackface standing next to another person in a Ku Klux Klan hood. "It's very easy to explain," Howley, 29, said in an interview Saturday. "A concerned citizen, not a political opponent, came to us and pointed this out. I was very offended (by the photo) because I don't like racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Bow Wow arrested after fight with woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/crime/2019/02/rapper-bow-wow-arrested-after-fight-with-woman-in-atlanta-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper was booked with misdemeanor battery charges, according to CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party divide could be opening for independent...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/wide-party-divide-could-be-opening-independent-candidate-n966296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1987, only 25 percent said there was “a great deal” of difference in what the Democratic and Republican parties stood for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once red-hot smartphone market sees cooler trend...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190203-once-red-hot-smartphone-market-sees-cooler-trend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once red-hot smartphone market sees cooler trend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel begins construction of new Gaza border barrier...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190203-israel-begins-construction-new-gaza-border-barrier</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel begins construction of new Gaza border barrier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Military intervention an 'option'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/428227-trump-military-intervention-in-venezuela-an-option</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump in an interview broadcast Sunday said U.S. military intervention in crisis-torn Venezuela is an “option.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: 'I would have a hard time' letting son play football...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/428233-trump-i-would-have-a-hard-time-letting-son-play-football</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump said in an interview broadcast Sunday that he would let his son Barron play football if he wanted to, but that he would not steer him into that decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policewoman reprimanded for moonlighting in sex industry...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/crime/yamaguchi-policewoman-resigns-after-being-reprimanded-for-moonlighting-in-sex-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A policewoman in Shimonseki, Yamaguchi Prefecture, has resigned after she was reprimanded for working part-time at a fuzoku (sex industry) establishment. Yamaguchi prefectural police said this week that the officer, whose age and name were withheld, had worked at a commercial sex business in Fukuoka between September and November last year,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life under ISIS led these Muslims to Christ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/life-under-isis-led-these-muslims-christ-n963281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If heaven is made for ISIS and their belief, I would choose hell for myself instead of being again with them in the same place, even if it’s paradise."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAWAIIAN AIR flight returns to LAX three times...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/02/us/hawaiian-flight-33-turn-back/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 200 Hawaiian Airlines passengers aboard Flight 33 said "Aloha" to Los Angeles — and it meant both hello and goodbye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo drugged, raped teens, witness claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/el-chapo-drugged-and-raped-teenage-girls-witness-claims-11199544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK: A witness in the trial of Joaquin "El Chapo" Guzman told the US government the Mexican drug kingpin drugged and raped girls as young as ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez doc wins Sundance audience award...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/428223-ocasio-cortez-campaign-documentary-wins-sundance-film-festival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Audience members at the annual Sundance Film Festival voted Saturday to recognize the documentary "Knock Down the House" with the festival's coveted annual audience award in the documentary category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa caucuses 1 year from today...</title>
      <link>http://www.newspressnow.com/news/local_news/iowans-look-ahead-a-year-to-presidential-caucuses/article_94d6163d-b7c5-5731-a291-98cb82ed3696.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newspressnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank Jimmy Carter, or curse him if you prefer, for the steady stream of presidential candidates visiting Iowa every quadrennium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Some, Tax-Cuts Smaller Than They Once Appeared...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/for-some-companies-tax-cut-gains-are-smaller-than-they-once-appeared-11549195201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With earnings season in full swing, investors are starting to learn which companies were overly optimistic about their tax cuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American anarchist 'John Galton' shot dead in Acapulco...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/3/john-galton-american-anarchist-shot-dead-acapulco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American anarchist who went by the name John Galton was shot dead at his home in the Mexican resort of Acapulco, sending shivers through a tightknit anti-establishment community of expatriates that organizes events in the violence-torn retreat with seminars on topics such as how to make money via cryptocurrencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theresa May vows to 'battle' in Brussels...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/theresa-may-vows-to-battle-in-brussels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust Paradox: Long Lives for Those Who Survived...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2019-01-28/holocaust-health-paradox-survivors-lived-longer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn jail lacks heat, hot water for week...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/2019/02/02/rally-held-at-brooklyn-jail-lacking-heat-hot-water-for-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — A congresswoman who visited a federal detention center in New York City where inmates have been stuck in cold, dark cells for days said Saturday it was "surreal" to hear the inmates banging on the walls. "I am frustrated. This is America. In America, everyone has rights," said Rep. Nydia Velazquez, a Democrat whose district includes the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn. "It's a violation of their human rights to be kept in the cold and not to be able to talk to anyone."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junk Debt Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/junk-debt-is-back-11549142343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Junk-rated bonds and loans are flying off the shelves again, easing recent worries that a credit-market freeze could harm the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran -- where drug addicts outnumber high school students...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/philmatier/article/San-Francisco-where-street-addicts-outnumber-13571702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco has more drug addicts than it has students enrolled in its public high schools, the city Health Department’s latest estimates conclude. There are about 24,500 injection drug users in San Francisco — that’s about 8,500 more people than the nearly 16,000 students enrolled in San Francisco Unified School District’s 15 high schools and illustrates the scope of the problem on the city’s streets. It’s also an increase of about 2,000 serious drug users since 2012, the last time a study was done. “There is an opioid epidemic in this country, and San Francisco is no exception,” Deputy Director of Health Dr. Naveena Bobba said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vivid' memory of blackening face to moonwalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/virginia/government-politics/general-assembly/resisting-calls-to-resign-northam-denies-he-s-in-racist/article_f75d342d-e028-586e-8631-70d52424d604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ralph Northam refused to resign from his office Saturday and instead attempted to ride out a scandal that is threatening to end his political career by denying he was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret plan to evacuate Queen in case of Brexit unrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu-royals/the-queen-to-be-evacuated-in-case-of-brexit-unrest-media-idUSKCN1PS005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British officials have revived Cold War emergency plans to relocate the royal fa...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northam's bizarre press conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/02/ralph-northam-yearbook-1144281</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Virginia governor joins the annals of bizarre political press conferences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coaching Duel: The Legend vs The Next One...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/02/02/guregian-super-coaching-duel-pits-the-legend-vs-the-next-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl pits the game’s most decorated head coach, Bill Belichick, against the NFL’s rising star, Sean McVay. Given their intellectual prowess, it figures to be an exciting chess…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuses to Resign...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/virginia/article_311fc930-26ea-11e9-8adb-8777294eb3d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Virginia governor said Saturday afternoon that he had never seen the yearbook page until the day before when it was brought to his attention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Queens' hidden sex district...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/inside-queens-hidden-sex-district/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s New York City’s Grand Central of illicit sex. A tiny Queens block has become a booming hotbed of hookers operating out of at least eight Chinese massage parlors, The Post found. The slim strip…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' star gets emotional: Attackers won't win...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a926a09b4af04ad19bb154468f53c9f7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HOLLYWOOD, Calif. (AP) — Jussie Smollett was blunt, emotional and defiantly determined Saturday night at a Southern California concert some urged him not to play, telling the crowd before singing a note that he had to go on with the show because he couldn't let his attackers win. "The most important thing I can say is 'thank you so much, and I'm OK," said the "Empire" actor and R&amp;amp;B singer from the stage at the Troubadour in West Hollywood in his first public appearance since he reported to police in Chicago on Tuesday that two masked men had assaulted him and put a rope around his neck while using homophobic and racial slurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA shows signs of decline, even in Trump's America...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/national-rifle-association-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group’s own tax forms show a dip in revenue. And after decades of ever more deadly mass shootings, opponents of gun violence have been on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'BLADE RUNNER' and 'RUNNING MAN' predicted 2019 -- decades ago...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/02/how-blade-runner-and-the-running-man-predicted-our-lives-decades-ago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the future. Two classic science-fiction films — “Blade Runner” and “The Running Man” — are both set in 2019, and although the films envisioned a few details that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Maher Taking Heat for POPEYE'S Chicken Joke to Black Congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/02/02/bill-maher-popeyes-chicken-racist-joke-black-congressman-will-hurd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Maher's at it again: he made yet another joke on his show many people are calling racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt unveils Pharaonic tomb, home to 50 mummies...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/2019/0202/1027143-egypt-pharaoh-tomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian archaeologists have uncovered a tomb related to the Pharaohs containing 50 mummies dating back to the Ptolemaic era, in Minya, south of Cairo, the ministry of antiquities has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kirchner comeback?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-argentina-election-fernandez-exclusiv/exclusive-argentinas-fernandez-plans-election-run-against-macri-sources-idUSKCN1PQ5RB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Argentine President Cristina Fernández de Kirchner intends to run for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA agent commits suicide at Orlando Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/florida/security-issue-at-orlando-airport-halts-flights-officials-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Transportation Security Administration agent was killed Saturday morning after jumping from a hotel balcony into the atrium of Orlando International Airport, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls for resignation build...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/428191-pelosi-calls-on-northam-to-step-aside-photo-is-contrary-to-fundamental</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) called on Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam (D) to "do the right thing" following a photo that surfaced Friday showing a man wearing blackface and another dressed in a Ku Klux Klan robe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto sees stock fall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/428083-beto-orourke-sees-stock-fall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke has seen his stock fall in the last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS, RAMS ready for Super Bowl generation game...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/patriots-rams-ready-super-bowl-generation-game-015749625--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady will chase a record-breaking sixth Super Bowl crown on Sunday as the New England Patriots take on the Los Angeles Rams in a clash of the generations set to rewrite NFL history. Patriots star Brady, 41, will become the oldest quarterback ever to lift the title if he masterminds yet another</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy-plagued halftime show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/super-bowl-liii-halftime-controversy-continues-as-colin-kaepernick-attorney-attacks-adam-levine-1202548192/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy surrounding Super Bowl LIII’s halftime show continues, as Colin Kaepernick’s attorney Mark Geragos called Maroon 5 frontman Adam Levine’s rationalization on his pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northam backtracks after apology...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/northam-backtracks-on-whether-he-is-in-racist-photo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam has said privately he does not think he is in the racist photo from his 1984 medical school yearbook, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considering facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/02/us/politics/ralph-northam-virginia-governor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Northam, increasingly isolated over a yearbook photo showing two people in blackface and Ku Klux Klan robes, was calling fellow Democrats to say he did not think it was him in the photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA GOV NOW SAYS NOT HIM IN PHOTO</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6660879/Democrat-Virginia-Governor-DENIES-hes-racist-yearbook-picture-featuring-blackface-KKK-robe.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Governor Ralph Northam now denies appearing in a racist photograph that he on Friday apologized for Senator Louise Lucas said Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims yearbook mix up?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/02/politics/northam-racist-yearbook-photo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Gov. Ralph Northam has told a source he now believes it is not him in a racist yearbook photo and, despite mounting pressure to resign, that he will not do so, according a top Virginia Democratic source who spoke to the governor on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIXIE DRAMA</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/347ad6bd706c48febcac1903b40dc24c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A Virginia Democrat who has spoken with Gov. Ralph Northam has told The Associated Press that the governor now does not believe he was in a racist picture in his 1984 medical yearbook and has no immediate plans to resign. The official was not authorized to speak on the record to detail a private conversation. The official told the AP on Saturday that Northam plans to address the issue with the public in the afternoon. Northam is calling Virginia Democrats to try and gain support. Nearly his entire political base has called for him to resign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WON'T RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/virginia-democrat-says-gov-northam-wont-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) &amp;mdash; A Virginia Democrat who has spoken with Gov. Ralph Northam has told The Associated Press that the governor now does not believe he was in a racist picture in his 1984 medical yearbook and has no immediate plans to resign. The official was not authorized to speak on the record to detail a private conversation. The official told the AP on Saturday that Northam plans to address the issue with the public in the afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutiny at Central Bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-02-02/mutiny-breaks-out-venezuelas-central-bank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't Resign...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/virginia-democrats-demand-northam-resign-but-add-that-he-does-not-plan-to-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran in 'successful test' of new cruise missile on revolution anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190202-iran-successful-test-new-cruise-missile-revolution-anniversary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran in 'successful test' of new cruise missile on revolution anniversary</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
