<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POLLS:  Le Pen closing gap on Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220329-french-far-right-leader-le-pen-closing-gap-on-macron-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran French far-right leader Marine Le Pen is closing the gap on President Emmanuel Macron ahead of a possible election duel between the two of them next month, two new polls show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not a Ceasefire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-29-22/h_724c88dcb604926363ebcdde88d7e21b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shelling has intensified around the suburbs of Kyiv, and Ukraine's deputy defense minister said Russian forces are attempting to establish a "corridor" around the Ukrainian capital to block supply routes. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US troops in Poland training Ukrainians...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/29/politics/us-troops-poland-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US troops in Poland have been providing Ukrainians with some instruction on how to use the weapons the West has been shipping into Ukraine, sources familiar with the matter tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intentional fire sparks renewed concerns at abandoned New Orleans skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/new-orleans-plaza-towers-intentional-fire/39124441#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent fire sparks renewed concerns at abandoned New Orleans skyscraper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ town sues woman, 82, for 'burdensome' public records requests...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/news/2022/03/nj-town-sues-woman-82-for-voluminous-and-burdensome-public-records-requests.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elouise McDaniel, of Irvington, said she has a “legal right” to know the information she has requested from the town.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Warren cheers Biden billionaires' tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/29/sen-elizabeth-warren-lauds-biden-billionaires-tax-calls-for-even-more-ceo-pay-changes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren praised the Biden administration's renewed effort to introduce a new tax on the country's wealthiest households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gervais mocks meltdown with alopecia joke...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/ricky-gervais-oscars-will-smith-1235121518/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British comedian posted a clip from his U.K. version of 'The Office' poking fun of the Will Smith-Chris Rock drama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 2 In 3 Think He Should Be Charged With Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/poll-will-smith-charged-chris-rock-oscars-slap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new StudyFinds.com poll shows that two in three Americans think Will Smith should be actually be charged for slapping Chris Rock at the Oscars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor survives assassination attempt after he overslept...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukraine-mayor-survives-rocket-assassination-26580942</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian cruise missile struck the Mykolaiv Regional State Administration building, leaving several missing and feared dead, but missed Vitaliy Kim, as he was at home asleep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Aerial Bombing Intensifies!</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2022-03-29/russia-begins-retreat-from-kyiv-in-major-strategy-shift-u-s-general</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with surprising opposition and bogged down supply lines, Russian President Vladimir Putin is repositioning his forces in an attempt to gain a more effective position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN 'WITHDRAWS' TROOPS FROM KYIV...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5001140/putin-withdrawing-troops-kyiv-losing-ukraine-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has said it is to “drastically reduce” forces near the Ukrainian capital Kyiv as its invasion continues to falter. The announcement was made by the Deputy Defence Minister Alexander Fomin an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual defense of war? Patriarch trying...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/spiritual-defense-war-ukraine-putins-090057639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriarch Kirill, a close ally of Vladimir Putin, has lent a spiritual justification for the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-President Asks Putin to Release Dirt on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/trump-asks-putin-to-release-dirt-on-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump called on Russian President Vladimir Putin to release dirt on President Joe Biden amid Russia’s invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly contagious Omicron subvariant now dominant in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/29/health/ba-2-dominant-us/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The highly contagious Omicron subvariant BA.2 is now the dominant strain of Covid-19 in the United States, causing an estimated 54.9% of all new Covid-19 infections last week, according to new data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen shrugs off health issues, attends Philip service...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/queen-elizabeth-ii-covid-entertainment-health-europe-06dd230e64e4cf7418149a428c4ffe1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II walked into Westminster Abbey through a side door Tuesday, making good on her wish to attend a service of thanksgiving for her beloved husband Prince Philip. The monarch entered the church on the arm of her second son, Prince Andrew, then separated from him to walk to her seat alone, easing concerns about her health that had raised questions about whether she would attend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumers still confident, but outlook not as rosy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prices-consumer-confidence-f284d6bbaff12f04ffc872143f659406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SILVER SPRING, Md. (AP) — U.S. consumer confidence bounced back in March and remains high, though consumers' short-term outlook is not quite as rosy. The Conference Board, a business research group, said Tuesday that its consumer confidence index — which takes into account consumers’ assessment of current conditions and their outlook for the future — rose to 107.2 in March from 105.7 in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'TOP GUN: MAVERICK' Trailer Teases Return of Val Kilmer's Iceman...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/top-gun-2-trailer-iceman-val-kilmer-tom-cruise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And he's got a job for his old pal Maverick</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL will require every team to have minority assistant coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/nfl-will-require-every-team-to-have-minority-coach-in-key-offensive-role/ar-AAVAgIN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for Your Toilet Paper Is On...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/the-battle-for-your-toilet-paper-is-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Private Jets Take to Skies, Creating Gridlock on Ground...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/29/more-private-jets-take-to-the-skies-creating-gridlock-on-the-ground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Mike Pellitteri started flying his private plane in 2013, it was easy to find a spot to park it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG probe says evidence suggests Trump Org misstated asset values over decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/29/ny-ag-probe-suggests-trump-business-misstated-asset-values-for-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has criticized the probe of his Trump Organization by New York Attorney General Letitia James as politically motivated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis May Hike Oil Price to Record as War Reroutes Flows...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/saudis-may-hike-oil-price-061748498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Saudi Arabia, the largest oil exporter, will likely boost pricing of its main crude variety to a record as the impact of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine reverberates through markets more than a month after the assault.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Kyiv Seeks Cease-Fire Deal in Russia TalksRoman Abramovich ‘Suffered Symptoms of Suspected Poisoning’ After Ukraine TalksLow-Priced Omega Speedmaster Prompts Global Swatch Store ChaosVanguard Stumbles In Pivot From Cult of Jack Bo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first space hotel to open in 2027 with 'activities you can't do on Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/travel/travel-news/worlds-first-space-hotel-set-26582855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's first space hotel is set to open its doors in 2027 after the Gateway Foundation released plans for the out of the world accommodation around three years ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican headaches grow as infighting roils Senate primaries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/600097-gop-headaches-grow-as-infighting-roils-senate-primaries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican frustrations are growing as multiple GOP Senate primaries have descended into infighting, threatening the party’s chances of retaking the upper chamber in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POSSIBLE COVERUP'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-white-house-logs-given-to-house-show-7-hour-gap-in-trump-calls/ar-AAVCpD9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAN 6 LOGS SHOW 7-HOUR GAP IN TRUMP CALLS</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-calls-seven-hour-gap-january-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House records submitted to the House show a gap in phone logs of calls placed to or by Trump from 11:17 a.m. to 6:54 p.m. on Jan. 6, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leak in Earth's core brings us close to solving mystery of how world formed...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiatoday.in/science/story/leak-in-earth-s-core-provides-clues-to-mystery-around-how-our-world-formed-1930920-2022-03-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiatoday.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have detected Helium-3, a rare primordial gas leaking from Earth's core. This gas is primarily formed in the Nebula as a star comes to life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUDLEY: Fed Has Made Recession Inevitable...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/is-a-recession-coming-the-fed-has-made-it-inevitable</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed Has Made a U.S. Recession Inevitable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott accused of violating Astroworld suits gag order...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travis-scott-entertainment-lawsuits-houston-1d9481be15881ebf69e9703c38c0b163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Attorneys for some of those killed and injured during last year’s deadly Astroworld music festival alleged in court on Monday that rapper Travis Scott has violated a gag order issued in lawsuits they have filed in an effort to influence possible jurors and rebuild his reputation ahead of a potential trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black reparations panel could decide who gets compensation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-legislature-016079ae742956f412cc1b8c32551c8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California’s first-in-the-nation task force on reparations is at a crossroads, with members divided on which Black Americans should be eligible for compensation as atonement for a slave system that officially ended with the Civil War but reverberates to this day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC tried to censor slap. It spread unedited anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/ABC-tried-to-censor-the-Oscars-slap-It-spread-17035264.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sandwiched between presenter Chris Rock's real-time narration of "uh-oh" and then "oh,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police issue first fines for Downing Street pandemic parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/london-police-issue-first-fines-for-downing-street-pandemic-parties/ar-AAVBXEy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to consider rules on humane treatment of pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-to-consider-california-rules-regarding-treatment-of-pigs/ar-AAVAAPU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cronies 'flee to bunkers' in alarming sign might turn nuclear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-cowering-in-bunkers-amid-26579925</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's claimed that Vladimir Putin and his top Kremlin cronies are cowering in top secret rural bunkers while they direct their invasion of Ukraine - an alarming signal the war could be about to escalate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious beams of light in sky spotted around world...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mysterious-beams-light-sky-spotted-210200074.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people spotted a mysterious beam of light in the sky last week. The “red flare”, as many described it, was spotted by people in Houston and other places throughout the world. While the strange red flare might give off extraterrestrial vibes due to its mystery, the phenomenon was most likely nothing quite as extraordinary, … The post Mysterious beams of light in the sky have been spotted around the world appeared first on BGR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Focus on How Trump Tweet Incited Far-Right Groups Before Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/29/new-focus-on-how-a-trump-tweet-incited-far-right-groups-before-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors and congressional investigators have gathered growing evidence of how a tweet by President Donald J. Trump less than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Budget Proposes Billionaires Pay 20% Tax...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-bidens-budget-boost-military-120905285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden on Monday submitted a $5.79 trillion budget plan to Congress that calls for record peacetime military spending and further aid for Ukraine, while raising taxes for billionaires and companies and lowering government deficits. The budget proposal for the fiscal year starting Oct. 1, lays out Biden's priorities, including campaign promises to make the wealthy and companies pay more tax. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said Congress looked forward to working on Biden's "bold fiscal blueprint," even as some fellow Democrats chafed at Biden's pledge to boost military spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCK JOKE NOT ON SCRIPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/movies/movie-news/sources-academy-members-furious-about-will-smith-chris-rock-slapgate-1329031/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say the offending joke was not part of the rehearsals earlier in the week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's troops on the run: Ukraine retakes town near Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10659321/Russian-death-toll-rises-17-000-Putins-forces-fail-make-significant-progress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor said forces had seized back full control of the town which had become one of the main hotspots of fighting after Kremlin soldiers hoped to march on to the capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STERN:  SIGN OF GREAT MENTAL ILLNESS</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/03/28/howard-stern-defends-chris-rock-after-will-smiths-slap/?_ga=2.202822745.977647047.1648428108-2110066361.1618613740</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Hitch” star struck Rock across the face with an open-handed slap for cracking a joke about his wife’s bald head at the 94th Academy Awards on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL will require every team to have minority assistant coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/nfl-will-require-every-team-to-have-minority-coach-in-key-offensive-role/ar-AAVAgIN#:~:text=PALM%20BEACH%2C%20Fla.%20%E2%80%94%20The%20NFL%20enacted%20a,of%20the%20NFL%27s%20two%20Black%20active%20head%20coaches.</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to consider rules on humane treatment of pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/supreme-court-to-consider-california-rules-regarding-treatment-of-pigs/ar-AAVAAPU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52% SAY THEY'VE HAD COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-milestone-majority-say-they-ve-had-covid-even-more-in-gop/ar-AAVAkm0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SMITH APOLOGIZES</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/will-smith-apologizes-chris-rock-slap-oscars-statement-1235216526/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Smith has issued an apology after slapping Chris Rock on the Oscars stage Sunday night. “Violence in all of its forms is poisonous and destructive. My behavior at last night’s Acad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasive ants hit Texas hard  -- now killer fungus is coming for them...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/invasive-ants-hit-texas-hard-190842344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When crazy ants roll into new parts of Texas, the invasive species wipe out local insects and lizards, drive away birds, and even blind baby rabbits by spewing acid in their eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL HE BE ARRESTED?</title>
      <link>https://knewz.com/knewz-analysis-the-lapd-doesnt-need-chris-rock-if-it-wants-to-arrest-will-smith/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knewz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE PEACE NEGOTIATORS 'POISONED'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4994463/roman-abramovich-poisoning-ukraine-russia-chelsea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROMAN Abramovich confirmed tonight he has been the victim of a suspected poisoning – allegedly using chemical weapons. Reports claimed he went blind for several hours and skin peeled off his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SMITH SLAP ON REPORTER 10 YEARS AGO RESURFACES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4995919/will-smith-violent-temper-10-years-slapped-red-carpet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TV presenter who was slapped by Will Smith at a movie premiere a decade ago has slammed the Oscar-winner’s “violent temper”.  Ukrainian reporter-turned-prankster Vitalii Sediuk was pushed an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body language expert:  Will Smith slap was 'choreographed Hollywood display'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/smiths-oscars-slap-choreographed-hollywood-26574442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Oscars 2022 were dominated by one incident - Will Smith storming the stage to smack Chris Rock across the face after he aimed a joke at his wife Jada Pinkett Smith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith and the End of Movie Stars...</title>
      <link>https://theankler.com/p/pod-will-smith-and-the-end-of-movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theankler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen now (52 min) | Publicist: 'This is going to change things for him in a way he won't like'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND LOWEST RATED IN HISTORY...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/2022-oscars-tv-ratings-rise-academy-awards-abc-disney-will-smith-chris-rock-1234989041/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 10:29 AM: If only the Oscars themselves moved as fast as the numbers counters at ABC. Mere minutes after fast-affiliate data for the 94th Academy Awards was out, the Disney-owned net that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massacre at cockfight leaves 20 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/28/mexico-cockfight-shooting-19-dead-michoacan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunmen with assault rifles burst into event in western state of Michoacán long plagued by violence between drug cartels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VP Harris, in toughest hour, keeping tighter circle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/vice-president-kamala-harris-in-her-toughest-hour-is-keeping-a-tighter-circle/ar-AAVzZUy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  PA snow causes massive 50-car pile-up; 3 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/snow-squall-multi-car-crash-in-pennsylvania</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A snow squall in Pennsylvania caused a massive car crash Monday involving dozens of cars and tractor-trailers and leaving at least three people dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Police Set to Issue 20 Fines Over No. 10 Parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-k-police-set-to-issue-at-least-20-fines-over-no-10-parties/ar-AAVBsWC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nun who became ruthless sniper with 40 kills 'captured'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-sniper-with-kill-count-26576503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irina Starikova, code name Baghera, has been captured in by Ukrainian forces after her Russian comrades 'left her for dead'. It is reported she abandoned her faith to become a drug dealer then a feared killer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The looting of Covid relief:  'Biggest fraud in generation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/biggest-fraud-generation-looting-covid-relief-program-known-ppp-n1279664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official in charge of Covid relief tells NBC News' Lester Holt that programs like PPP were structured in ways that were "an invitation" to fraudsters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-list ovation for Smith at VANITY FAIR after-party...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/entertainment-celebrity/it-was-an-a-list-ovation-for-will-smith-at-vanity-fair-s-oscars-after-party/ar-AAVAFT4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARLAMAGNE: Joke 'Very Small Part' of Will's Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/charlamagne-says-chris-rocks-joke-is-a-very-small-part-of-will-smiths-problems-there-is-something-way-deeper-going-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charlamagne tha God offered his take on Will Smith's Oscars meltdown citing the underlying problems that may have caused his outburst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Cawthorn Says D.C. Elite Invited Him to 'Orgy,' Did Cocaine in Front of Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/cawthorn-says-dc-elite-invited-him-orgy-did-cocaine-front-him-1692261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican congressman complained about the "sexual perversion" in the nation's Capitol and suggested the Netflix show House of Cards is largely accurate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists run amid bangs at airport in Cancun resort...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-travel-lifestyle-mexico-media-eda98b3a2b74af491651c23dec797d66</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Tourists were sent scrambling by loud bangs heard at the international airport in the Mexican resort of Cancun Monday. Flights were briefly suspended after authorities received reports of gunshots at the airport, the National Guard said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Length Of Fingers Predicts How Sick You'll Get...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/finger-length-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds finger length displays a link to a person's sex hormone levels, which can influence disease severity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico to rent out unwanted presidential jet for parties...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220328-mexico-to-rent-out-unwanted-presidential-jet-for-parties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Monday that his government would offer to rent out a luxury presidential jet for birthday and wedding parties after failing to find a buyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Says 'Not Walking Anything Back'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-biden-europe-moscow-df6c9f17b04e26611ae5c58a16aa0e78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Monday that he is “not walking anything back” after his weekend comment that Russian President Vladimir Putin “cannot remain in power," although Biden insisted he's not calling for regime change in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Budget Proposes Billionaires Pay 20% in Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/biden-budget-proposes-billionaires-pay-20-percent-income-taxes-1692520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tax proposed in the new budget applies to those with more than $100 million, what the administration estimates is the wealthiest 0.01 percent of Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced to pay on unrealized gains!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/americas-10-richest-people-%E2%80%94-including-elon-musk-and-jeff-bezos-%E2%80%94-would-pay-up-to-dollar215-billion-in-taxes-on-unrealized-stock-gains-under-bidens-new-plan-they-currently-pay-next-to-nothing/ar-AAVAvOD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Infected -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/28/elon-musk-says-he-has-covid-as-tesla-shanghai-faces-health-restrictions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk said he has Covid again, following an earlier bout in November 2020.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
