<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Denver debates civilians be given law-enforcement powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.westword.com/news/homeless-denver-hancock-street-enforcement-team-city-county-12359179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.westword.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Street Enforcement Team will hit the streets in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART worker quits in profanity-laced tirade over loudspeakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/walmart-worker-resigns-over-store-loudspeakers-f-k-this-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walmart worker quit in a profanity-laced tirade over the Louisiana store’s loudspeakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered from virus and traveling to Israel? No test required...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/recovered-from-covid-and-traveling-to-israel-no-pcr-test-required-679867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To qualify, travelers must have tested positive between 11 days and three months prior * Health Ministry drops Mexico from list of red countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of bees kills dozens of endangered penguins...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/world/2021/09/swarm-of-bees-kills-dozens-of-endangered-african-penguins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of bees has killed 63 endangered African penguins on a beach outside Cape Town, the Southern African Foundation for the Conservation of Coastal Birds said on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Fundraising at Record-Breaking Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-fundraising-at-record-breaking-pace-ahead-of-midterms/ar-AAODAZA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Democratic National Committee raised $9.9 million in August bringing its 2021 total to $110 million, both record amounts for a year before an election, according to a person familiar with the party’s fundraising. More than half of the haul in August, traditionally a slow month for raising money, came from small-dollar donors, who gave $5.2 million. So far this year, grassroots contributors have combined to give $58.4 million,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Hanks fights to survive with dog and robot in sci-fi thriller...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/tom-hanks-finch-trailer-1235017014/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hanks is the survivor of an apocalypse with his trusty dog and robot in this Apple TV+ film from director Miguel Sapochnik.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student in Canada had 2 followers. Didn't escape Beijing threats over online activity...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/canada/2021/09/18/a-chinese-student-in-canada-had-two-followers-on-twitter-he-still-didnt-escape-beijings-threats-over-online-activity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitoring of Chinese nationals abroad, and other people of Chinese origin, is posing a challenge that many western countries have been slow to face, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul sets record for most Emmys by Black artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/rupaul-emmy-record-most-wins-black-performer-1235015916/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picking up another Emmy for competition program for 'RuPaul's Drag Race,' the 60-year-old host has surpassed Donald A. Morgan with the most awards from the TV Academy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emmys:  A Thoroughly Modern Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/2021-emmys-were-thoroughly-modern-052449185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Fury/GettyEnd all awards show bits. That’s the lesson.The Emmys winners did the show for them. They were all (mostly) great. There were surprises sprinkled throughout, the kind of fun that shocks TV critics watching alone on their couch with some rosé and makes them stand up reflexively and start clapping about.(That was me, when Mare of Easttown’s Julianne Nicholson deservedly won, Olivia Colman’s Queen Elizabeth reigned over Emma Corrin’s Princess Diana, and Hacks creator/writer/director</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How America Created Gun-Happy Gangster's Paradise in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/america-created-gun-happy-gangster-085834602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Courtesy Jonathan AlpeyrieRIO DE JANEIRO—Thousands of made-in-America weapons are pouring into Brazil and landing straight into the hands of gangsters every day, and the U.S. is failing miserably at stemming the flood.According to the United Nations Office on Drugs and Crimes (UNODC), Brazil is home to roughly 8 million illegal weapons, more than half of which were smuggled from the U.S. The latest U.N.-sponsored report suggests that a little under 20,000 American weapons enter Brazil each year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants quietly buy up dozens of companies a year. Administration is noticing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/09/20/secret-tech-acquisitions-ftc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giants have quietly acquired hundreds of companies over the years without much scrutiny. A new study from the FTC is a step towards changing that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Fundraising at Record-Breaking Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-20/democrats-fundraising-at-record-breaking-pace-ahead-of-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horse owners face ivermectin shortage...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/horse-owners-struggling-buy-ivermectin-152346882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People are self-medicating with ivermectin, which the FDA hasn't approved as a COVID-19 treatment - and it's pricing out horse owners, reports say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States bracing for confusion about booster rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/States-bracing-for-confusion-about-coronavirus-16472711.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State health officials are bracing for confusion as they manage expectations about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Afghanistan's war-torn countryside, America's exit means one thing: Peace...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/in-afghanistans-war-torn-countryside-americas-exit-means-one-thing-peace/article_1f827e58-d8bf-5cf6-86df-9781af8009e3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KULANGAR, Afghanistan — At a tiny, two-pump gas station off the two-lane highway running through Afghanistan's Logar province, Mohammad Farooq, the attendant, was unequivocal in his view of the United</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight bookings plummet amid delta fears...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/aviation/572971-flight-bookings-plummet-amid-delta-variant-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight bookings rapidly declined in August and early September amid a surge in COVID-19 cases fueled by the highly transmissible delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China seeks to extend critical minerals monopoly with help of Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/energy-environment/572932-china-seeks-to-extend-critical-minerals-monopoly-with-help-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The opportunity to seize further control over the world’s supply of rare earth minerals, particularly lithium, is a determining factor in China’s cozying up to the Taliban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says fortune seized in Beverly Hills raid was criminals' loot. Owners say: Where's proof?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fbi-says-fortune-seized-beverly-140035114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI's attempt to confiscate tens of millions of dollars from Beverly Hills safe deposit boxes draws resistance and charges of government misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Zuckerberg Agreed to Push 'State-Sanctioned Conservatism' Under Trump Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/peter-thiel-claimed-mark-zuckerberg-agreed-to-push-state-sanctioned-conservatism-under-trump-deal-book-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Facebook founder allegedly vowed to “avoid fact-checking political speech” if the Trump admin would “lay off on any heavy-handed regulations.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Unvaccinated President Forced to Eat Pizza on Street in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jair-bolsonaro-forced-to-eat-pizza-on-the-street-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diners in the city have to have had at least one coronavirus shot before allowed indoors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER to Pay $809.5 Million to Settle Suit Alleging Dorsey Misled Investors...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/digital/news/twitter-investor-lawsuit-settlement-payment-jack-dorsey-1235068982/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter disclosed a binding agreement to settle a class-action lawsuit, under which the social network will pay $809.5 million to resolve claims it provided misleading engagement info to investors.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lava from Canary Islands volcano flows to sea causing material damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210920-lava-from-canary-islands-volcano-flows-to-sea-causing-material-damage-no-injuries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lava continued to flow slowly from a volcano that erupted in Spain’s Canary Islands off northwest Africa, but the head of the regional government said Monday he expects no injuries to people in the a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITCOIN PUMMELED</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/bitcoin-drops-8percent-to-below-44000-as-risky-assets-tumble-globally-regulatory-concerns-intensify.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of bitcoin dropped sharply Monday as investors began shedding risk amid an equity markets decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Billionaire wants to build utopia in desert. Seems like could go wrong...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/sep/20/a-billionaire-wants-to-build-a-utopia-in-the-us-desert-seems-like-this-could-go-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The architects of the proposed 150,000-acre project are scouting the American south-west. They’re already predicting the first residents can move in by 2030</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King of ring rumbles for Philippine presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210920-pacquiao-king-of-the-ring-rumbles-for-philippine-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacquiao: king of the ring rumbles for Philippine presidency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson suspected in fire at historic Kansas City church...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-fires-crime-kansas-city-missouri-72ce72c62caf9ccd30fb8a824453998e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — Arson is suspected in a fire that damaged the historic Harlem Baptist Church in Kansas City, Missouri. John Ham of the Kansas City office of the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives told the Kansas City Star that authorities have determined that the blaze was intentionally set, making it a federal crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight about gifts broke out at baby shower. Expectant father shot 3 guests, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-fight-about-gifts-broke-out-at-a-Pennsylvania-16472412.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen friends and family members gathered at Kinloch Fire Department's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats against members of Congress skyrocketing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/threats-against-members-of-congress-are-skyrocketing-its-changing-the-job/ar-AAOD2CJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year that kicked off with the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol, threats against Congress members are soaring: 4,135 in just the first three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian pro-Putin party wins big majority after crackdown; foes cry foul...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210920111424-wtsr1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Russian pro-Putin party wins big majority after crackdown; foes cry foul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surging Fertilizer Costs Risk Making Food Even More Expensive...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/surging-fertilizer-costs-risk-making-040100289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most people don’t give fertilizer a second thought -- except maybe when driving through a particularly fragrant agricultural area. But with prices for some synthetic nutrients at their highest levels since the financial crisis, it could mean weaker harvests and bigger grocery bills next year, just as the world’s supply chains start to recover from the pandemic.A perfect storm of events -- from extreme weather and plant shutdowns to new government sanctions -- have hit the chemical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Heart of Nashville, Rolling Parties Rage at Every Stoplight...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/19/in-the-heart-of-nashville-rolling-parties-rage-at-every-stoplight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE — The John Deere tractor pulled onto Broadway and rumbled into the madness. On a Friday night in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief warns China, USA to avoid Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-china-climate-united-states-health-f1186707bee7f8376b0be5523496ddca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — Warning of a potential new Cold War, the head of the United Nations implored China and the United States to repair their “completely dysfunctional” relationship before problems between the two large and deeply influential countries spill over even further into the rest of the planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUDEAU ON BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/20/justin-trudeaus-bid-for-third-term-in-balance-as-canada-goes-to-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Post-vaccination election gamble may not win over a fractured electorate, but result is not expected quickly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash and burn: Intense and fleeting romances of Covid era...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/sep/20/covid-pandemic-dating-relationships-breakups </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/thousands-flee-lava-spewing-volcano-spains-la-palma-island-destroys-houses-2021-09-20/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Canary Islands' first volcanic eruption in 50 years has forced the evacuation of about 5,000 people, including around 500 tourists, and destroyed about 100 houses, officials said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris to Tell Bezos AMAZON Must Pay Fair Share of Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/uk-e2-80-99s-johnson-to-tell-bezos-amazon-must-pay-fair-share-of-taxes/ar-AAOCbik</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson said he will tell Jeff Bezos that Amazon.com Inc. must pay its fair share of taxes in the country when the two meet on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, UK attempt to smooth tensions as France calls sub snub 'crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/us-and-uk-try-to-ease-tensions-with-france-over-submarine-deal-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and the United Kingdom are looking to ease tensions with France after a deal with Australia that Paris described as a "stab in the back."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul sets record for most Emmys by Black artist...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/572960-rupaul-sets-record-for-most-emmys-by-a-black-artist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RuPaul is striking a pose in the history books, setting a record for the most Emmy Award wins by a Black artist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID US death toll on verge of surpassing 1918-19 Spanish Flu pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-us-death-toll-024500236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States' known death toll from COVID-19 will surpass the number of dead from the Spanish Flu within the next day or two, according to the side-by-side numbers — though a direct comparison between the raw numbers doesn’t give the whole story, medical experts and statisticians say. What is clear is that the sheer numbers, given the modern-day tools that combat such illnesses, are a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big gap between PFIZER, MODERNA for preventing hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-gap-between-pfizer-moderna-034719881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna's COVID-19 vaccine does a significantly better job of preventing COVID-19 hospitalizations compared with Pfizer's shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi on Center Stage With Biden's $4 Trillion Agenda at Risk...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/pelosi-on-center-stage-with-bidens-4-trillion-agenda-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earnings Alarm Bells Ringing; Signs of Fatigue...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/earnings-alarm-bells-ringing-market-200000936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An alarming number of companies have warned that profits won’t meet expectations when they report in a month. The group, including PP Industries Inc. and Sherwin-Williams Co., are primarily materials producers that have struggled amid supply-chain disruptions. While just a small part of the S&amp;P 500, their earnings have historically been the most correlated to the index’s of all sectors, a study by Bank of America Corp. found.The profit warnings come as economic growth is slowing,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Haven't Been This Down on Housing Since 1982!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-haven-t-down-housing-174212114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The last time Americans were this turned off by the U.S. housing market, borrowing costs were over five times the current rate. The share of people who think now is a good time to buy a home fell in September to 29%, extending the plunge from March when the proportion was more than twice as high, data from the University of Michigan consumer sentiment survey showed Friday. It’s also the smallest chunk of respondents since 1982.Back then, the average for a 30-year fixed rate mortga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents of Del Rio Feel Impact of Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/20/not-the-same-residents-of-del-rio-feel-the-impact-of-the-migrant-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — On Friday afternoon, Jose Rodriguez stood near a fence that was steps away from the Rio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Supreme Court, Plea to Reveal Secret Surveillance Rulings...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/20/at-the-supreme-court-a-plea-to-reveal-secret-surveillance-rulings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Last year, six months before he was nominated to be attorney general, Judge Merrick B. Garland wrote a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Determined migrants unfazed as deportations begin from Texas border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/determined-migrants-unfazed-as-deportations-begin-from-texas-border/ar-AAOCbZg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reasons they come are complicated and varied. The routes they traverse are dangerous and unpredictable. But what thousands of migrants found on the other side of the Rio Grande was beyond anything they expected when reaching the United States.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW FUTURES TUMBLE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/19/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors fear a contagion sweeping financial markets from the troubled China property market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBAL MARKETS ROCKED</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-worry-builds-key-week-060121984.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA PROPERTY FEARS</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hong-kong-stocks-sink-evergrande-023055601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Growing investor angst about China’s real estate crackdown rippled through markets on Monday, adding pressure on Xi Jinping’s government to prevent financial contagion from destabilizing the world’s second-largest economy.Hong Kong real estate giants including Henderson Land Development Co. suffered the biggest selloff in more than a year as traders speculated China will extend its property clampdown to the financial hub. Intensifying concerns about China Evergrande Group’s debt c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax NFL star offers to buy tickets for UNVACCINATED fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3690546/cole-beasley-buffalo-bills-nfl-unvaccinated-fans-tickets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star and anti-vaxxer Cole Beasley has offered to buy unvaccinated fans tickets to Bills games away from home. Wide receiver Beasley, 32, along with side’s long snapper Reid Ferguson, 27, made t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy satellites could be targeted with giant high-powered lasers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3687396/us-spy-satellites-targeted-lasers-officials-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US intelligence satellites could be targeted with giant high-powered LASERS fired from the sea, officials have claimed. Leading military personnel believe that new technology, developed by foreign …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brass close ranks around embattled general who warned of 'unstable' Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/19/milley-china-contacts-trump-mullen-512752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Having communications with counterparts around the world is routine,” Michael Mullen said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mossad assassinated Iran's chief nuke scientist with remote AI gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/iran-denies-new-york-times-assassination-report-679800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times published a report detailing the assassination of Iran's leading nuclear scientist by a Mossad-operated AI machine gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano blows on Spain's Canary Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10006123/Spanish-island-braces-possible-earthquakes-eruption.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The explosion took place in an area known as Cabeza de Vaca on the western slope of the volcano and comes after the island registered up to 1,000 earthquakes in the past five days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO PLANS TX COMEBACK: RUNNING FOR GOV...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-beto-plans-texas-comeback-governors-race-33a3ae1a-4c58-4e7a-9e44-26342d3128c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;O'Rourke's entry would give Dems a high-profile candidate with a national fundraising network to challenge Greg Abbott.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
