<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Seek to Question Trump Organization Finance Chief...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/prosecutors-seek-to-question-trump-organization-s-finance-chief/17727607/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators in Manhattan have asked to interview Allen Weisselberg, the chief financial officer of the Trump Organization, as part of their investigation into President Donald Trump’s former lawyer Michael D. Cohen, according to two people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Watch Longest 'Blood Moon' Eclipse of Century...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-how-to-see-longest-blood-moon-eclipse-mars-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record-setting lunar eclipse paired with an extra-close Mars will soon have sky-watchers seeing red.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-results-stock/zuckerberg-loses-more-than-15-billion-in-record-facebook-fall-idUSKBN1KG1TN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg's fortune took a more than $15 billion hit on Thursday, as the social media company suffered the biggest one-day wipeout in U.S. stock market history a day after executives forecast years of lower profit margins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE FRIDAY:  'Climate change' supercharging hot and dangerous summer... </title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/environment/index.ssf/2018/07/climate_change_global_warming_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brutal weather has been supercharged by human-induced climate change, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua in 'undeclared state of siege' as hooded gunmen rule streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/world/article215568330.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Ortega claims that he’s restored calm to Nicaragua, but it’s been through the terrifying use of paramilitary gunmen who patrol in masks. His countrymen scurry off the streets at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5%?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-durable-orders-rose-1-0-in-june-1532608467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several forecasters tempered their high expectations for U.S. economic growth in the second quarter—a day before the gross domestic product report is released—due to some underwhelming economic data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUCCI Profit Soars on Surging Demand for Luxury Items...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gucci-profit-soars-on-surging-demand-for-luxury-items-1532630488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating profit at Gucci soared in the first half of the year, as shoppers flocked to the Italian fashion house amid surging global demand for luxury goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN GALACTIC spaceplane smashes altitude record in latest test flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/virgin-galactic-spaceplane-smashes-altitude-record-latest-test-flight-ncna894981 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sleek craft climbs to 32 miles over California’s Mojave Desert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP BLOWOUT?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-investors-cant-remember-the-last-time-a-gdp-report-held-such-import-2018-07-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street investors just traversed a gantlet: the busiest week of corporate quarterly results, fresh developments in global trade relations and a historic stock tumble in Facebook Inc. However, the headliner of this jam-packed week may be GDP, the official scorecard of the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen claims Trump knew in advance of Russian Trump Tower meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/26/politics/michael-cohen-donald-trump-june-2016-meeting-knowledge/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former personal attorney, claims that then-candidate Trump knew in advance about the June 2016 meeting in Trump Tower in which Russians were expected to offer his campaign dirt on Hillary Clinton, sources with knowledge tell CNN. Cohen is willing to make that assertion to special counsel Robert Mueller, the sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight breaks out between pilots at 37,000 feet... </title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-fight-breaks-out-in-cockpit-at-37000-feet-between-iraqi-airways-pilots/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unearthing mysteries of 'Egypt' in dunes of California Coast...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/travel/la-tr-california-guadalupe-dunes-ten-commandments-movie-artifacts-20180726-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artifact is from Hollywood, having been part of the set of the 1923 silent film "The Ten Commandments." It's on display at a little known archaeological center on the central coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO BOMB IRAN?</title>
      <link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-07-27/donald-trump-may-be-prepared-to-strike-iran-sources-say/10037728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior figures in the Turnbull Government say they believe the Trump administration is prepared to bomb Iran's nuclear capability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates hack tablet system, steal $225,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.localnews8.com/news/prison-officials-idaho-inmates-hacked-jpay-tablet-system/773579341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.localnews8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Idaho prison officials say 364 inmates hacked the JPay tablets they use for email, music and games and collectively transferred nearly a quarter million dollars into their own accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest person dead at 117, just after GUINNESS certifies...</title>
      <link>http://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/news/2018/7/oldest-person-title-officially-achieved-by-117-year-old-chiyo-miyako-before-her-d-534017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.guinnessworldrecords.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chiyo Miyako, 117, was the oldest living woman when she passed away on Sunday 22 July</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big stink as thousands of deceased fish blanket Mystic River...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/07/26/nothing-fishy-officials-say-thousands-fish-washed-everett-but-likely-from-natural-causes/w9xdiPhyxyPJKXbQRdL58J/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fish blanketed the shoreline near a Costco store — and customers said the smell was unpleasant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Secret Wars In Africa Rage On...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/26/us-special-operations-africa-green-berets-navy-seals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Operations forces in Africa are supposed to be training and advising, but they keep ending up in situations that are indistinguishable from combat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ORG CFO to Testify Before Federal Grand Jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-organization-finance-chief-called-to-testify-before-federal-grand-jury-1532622947</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg, a longtime financial gatekeeper for President Donald Trump, has been subpoenaed to testify before a federal grand jury in the criminal probe of Mr. Trump’s former personal lawyer, Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$119+ BILLION ROUT BIGGEST LOSS IN HISTORY!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/facebook-on-pace-for-biggest-one-day-loss-in-value-for-any-company-sin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook was on track Thursday to post the largest one-day market cap loss by any company in U.S. stock-market history after releasing a disastrous quarterly report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Bernie Adviser Assisting Special Counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/rubycramer/bernie-sanders-adviser-is-assisting-special-counsel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tad Devine, a top adviser to Sanders’ 2016 campaign, previously worked with Manafort in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Just 13% of Ocean Is Wilderness...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-44970671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have found that only 13% of the world's oceans remain mostly undisturbed by humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal enclaves embrace noncitizen voting...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/26/noncitizen-voting-push-liberal-jurisdictions-draws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget the Russian government — foreign nationals are increasingly gaining the ability to influence American elections more directly. They’re being granted the right to vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11 Victim Identified, Nearly 17 Years Later...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/07/26/632607533/9-11-victim-identified-nearly-17-years-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scott Michael Johnson, identified by the New York City Office of Chief Medical Examiner, was a securities analyst at an investment banking firm. More than 1,100 victims have yet to be identified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN Space Plane Aces Test Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/41295-virgin-galactic-reaches-mesosphere-epic-test.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virgin Galactic's newest space plane took to the skies again today (July 26) for its third rocket-powered test flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: MCDONALD's worker pummels customer who used water cup for free soda...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5994973/McDonalds-worker-beats-customer-free-soda-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight was caught on video by Marie Dayag, who lives in Las Vegas, Nevada, who said that the brawl started when the customer attempted to fill a free water cup with soda from the fountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF HELL: Kids Beaten In 'Dungeon', Child Deprived Of Seeing Cancer Doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.lansingstatejournal.com/story/news/local/2018/07/26/police-lansing-kids-dungeon-whipped-punishment-abuse-child-protective-services-sarah-yenier-conde/828404002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lansingstatejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The kids told Child Protective Services investigators they were routinely beaten and threatened with guns. The parents are charged with child abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Investigates TV Station Owners Over Ad Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/justice-department-investigates-tv-station-owners-over-advertising-sales-1532633979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice is investigating whether television station owners violated antitrust law in ways that inflated local television advertising prices, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States drowning in 'irretrievable' debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/these-american-states-are-drowning-in-irretrievable-debt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Connecticut, New York and California are some of the U.S. states drowning in debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FITBIT data key to finding missing jogger?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/26/us/missing-university-of-iowa-student-mollie-tibbetts/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen FBI agents are part of the search for a missing University of Iowa student, Investigators are looking at her Fitbit and social media accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VOWS TO INVESTIGATE TWITTER 'SHADOW BANNING'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5995209/Trump-warns-Twitter-investigated-SHADOW-BANNING-conservatives.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump entered a contentious battle over online censorship on Thursday, blasting Twitter for allegedly depressing the exposure of messages from its conservaitve users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Mueller Studies Trump Tweets in Wide-Ranging 'Obstruction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/mueller-examining-trump-s-tweets-in-wide-ranging-obstruction-inquiry/17726411/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- For years, President Donald Trump has used Twitter as his go-to public relations weapon, mounting a barrage of attacks on celebrities and then political rivals even after advisers warned he could be creating legal problems for himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plunge drops CEO down billionaire ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebooks-plunge-drops-zuckerberg-down-the-billionaire-ranks----behind-a-guy-many-americans-may-not-know-2018-07-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook lost about $120 billion in market capitalization on Thursday after its latest earnings report showed the social media giant missed expectations on revenue and is experiencing slowing user growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON earnings explode to record profit...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/amazon-earnings-explode-to-record-thanks-to-surprising-e-commerce-profit-stock-gains-2018-07-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. disclosed its biggest quarterly profit total in company history in a Thursday report, thanks to a surprising performance from the core retail business that usually produces razor-thin profit margins if not losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger-Flipping Bot Now Frying Chicken at Dodger Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://la.eater.com/2018/7/26/17617246/flippy-robot-burgers-dodger-stadium-chicken-new</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;la.eater.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flippy is quickly automating the fast food industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON earnings beat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/amazon-earnings-q2-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon is scheduled to report second-quarter earnings on Thursday after the bell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin ordered to pay for gender reassignment surgeries...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/wisconsin-ordered-pay-gender-reassignment-surgeries-180621911.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADISON, Wis. (AP) — A federal judge has ordered Wisconsin to pay for the gender reassignment surgery for two transgender Medicaid recipients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby located across country 24 years after she went missing...</title>
      <link>http://www.azfamily.com/story/38723279/missing-phoenix-girl-found-alive-nearly-24-years-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azfamily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Phoenix girl missing since 1994 has been found. Aleacia Stancil disappeared without a trace nearly 24 years ago, leaving police with few clues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Drop in Foreigners Buying...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/record-drop-in-foreigners-buying-u-s-homes-1532632676</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign purchases of U.S. homes fell a record 21%, posing a fresh challenge to the slumping housing market, which has shown few signs of turning around.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece: 'Serious indications' of arson behind deadly wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-greece-wildfire-arson/greece-says-serious-indications-of-arson-behind-deadly-wildfire-idUSKBN1KG2SD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece has "serious indications" that arson caused a wildfire that soared near Athens on Monday, killing at least 83 people and injuring scores, Citizen Protection Minister Nikos Toskas said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Adversaries Weaponizing Information...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/americas-adversaries-weaponizing-information-nsa-director-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Foreign adversaries have stepped up the use of information warfare to control populations since 2011 and the operations a new threat in the digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC police seize alligator from home...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/local-news/dc-police-seize-alligator-from-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities took a bite out of crime after they seized an alligator from a home in the District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas MAVERICKS Dancers To Cover Up Next Season...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/07/25/mavericks-dancers-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team tells CBS11 this change is part of the Mavs’ effort to revamp its image after a recent sexual harassment scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON Talk Show Coming to HBO...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/lebron-james-barbershop-set-talk-show-picked-up-by-hbo-1130049 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first episode features Jon Stewart, Snoop Dogg, Odell Beckham Jr. and Candace Parker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon opens competition for $10 billion cloud contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pentagon-opens-competition-10-billion-cloud-contract-180122249--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Defense opened the competition for its highly anticipated $10 billion cloud computing services contract on Thursday, an opportunity awaited by bidders that include Amazon, Microsoft Corp and Oracle , among others. The Pentagon's Joint Enterprise Defense Infrastructure, or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of sea turtles wash up dead on FL beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-press.com/story/tech/science/environment/2018/07/25/red-tide-likely-killing-sea-turtles-southwest-florida/827698002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-press.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 turtles have been plucked from Sarasota County waters, and another 66 have been found in Collier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-usa-kalin/erdogan-spokesman-says-united-states-will-not-achieve-results-by-threatening-turkey-idUSKBN1KG2O1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan's spokesman said on Thursday the U.S. administration will not achieve its desired results by threatening Turkey, after U.S. President Donald Trump warned of sanctions unless Ankara freed an American pastor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolinas rip currents 'drowning machines'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/latest-news/article215550280.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How are rip currents caused and how can you spot them? Get info on how riptides form. Use these safety tips when swimming in the oceans of North and South Carolina so you can avoid, get out of and survive one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Pages From Malcolm X Autobiography Turn Up at Auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/26/books/malcolm-x-book-auction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possible existence of three unpublished chapters has been a source of intrigue, and now at least one of them has surfaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing market showing signs of cracking...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/the-anything-goes-list-price-strategy-is-no-longer-working-in-housin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The housing market is slowing down, which means in even some of the hottest markets, bidding wars are less fierce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Mueller Examining Trump Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/26/us/politics/trump-tweets-mueller-obstruction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s public attacks on Jeff Sessions and James Comey, which came as he was also privately pressuring them, are being scrutinized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo accused of painting donkeys to look like zebras...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/zoo-accused-of-painting-donkeys-to-look-like-zebras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Egyptian student too a picture of the alleged zebras at a Cairo zoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT, AP Dig for Dirt on Kavanaugh Wife...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/revealed-nyt-targets-kavanaughs-wife-looking-for-abortion-gun-gay-federalist-emails/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Urban island' heat tests Phoenix, other large cities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe99da5da0d4455eaf2d96842b83b577/'Urban-island'-heat-tests-Phoenix,-other-large-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — When temperatures soar as they have this week in downtown Phoenix, homeless people ride the air-conditioned light rail to avoid a heat so brutal it killed 155 peopl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS 'Strong Solidarity' With CNN After White House Bars Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/da0fca6bfc46433283f8ac5bb1573b93/White-House-bars-CNN-correspondent-from-open-press-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A CNN correspondent was barred from attending an open press event at the White House on Wednesday because of questions she asked President Donald Trump earlier i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona town 'heartbroken' after Sacha Baron Cohen's 'WHO IS AMERICA?' brands them racist...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/arizona-town-heartbroken-sacha-baron-cohens-america-brands-racist-094707751.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A town in Arizona is the latest to kick back against Sacha Baron Cohen and his new TV series Who Is America?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omarosa to Release 'Explosive' Memoir Next Month...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/books/2018/07/26/omarosa-exact-revenge-trump-white-house-tell-all-book/841242002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump White House aide Omarosa Manigault Newman is delivering a tell-all memoir about the White House on Aug. 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rosenstein still standing despite conservative push to impeach...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/26/rosenstein-still-standing-despite-conservative-push-to-impeach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rosenstein Still Standing Despite Conservative Push to Impeach</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE RAT IS A 'TRIPLE THREAT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2018/07/why-michael-cohen-is-a-triple-threat-for-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business deals, affairs, Russia ties—the president's former fixer knows all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After fires, floods hit Greek capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fires-floods-hit-greek-capital-135143109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy rains led to flash flooding Thursday in the north of Athens, three days after devastating wildfires killed scores of people in the region around the Greek capital. Fire services said they received at least 10 calls from motorists whose vehicles were stranded when roads became rivers after storms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DEATH SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/facebook-pays-for-all-its-mistakes-at-once-and-it-is-a-big-bill-2018-07-25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc. appears to be finally paying for the impact of the 2016 elections and user privacy concerns, with the stunning disclosure of a big revenue deceleration in the second half of this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW LOW WILL IT GO?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/FB?p=FB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View the basic FB stock chart on Yahoo Finance. Change the date range, chart type and compare Facebook, Inc. against other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE WATERS CALLS FOR 'STREET' RAGE OVER TRUMP...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/25/maxine-waters-screaming-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRANIAN GENERAL WARNS TRUMP:   WE'LL DESTROY 'EVERYTHING YOU OWN'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5995587/Iranian-special-forces-leader-warns-Trump-war-destroy-own.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The general in charge of Iran's Quds Forces warned Trump that war with the Islamist country would eliminate his entire net worth, suggesting terrorists are prepared to strike his real estate properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti to Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Michael-Avenatti-will-speak-in-Iowa-raising-13107048.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyer for Stormy Daniels announced Thursday that he will speak next month at an annual Democratic dinner in northern Iowa, raising more questions about his presidential ambitions. Michael Avenatti, who rose to prominence this year amid the legal fight between adult film actress Daniels and President Donald Trump, said on Twitter that he will be a speaker at the Iowa Democratic Wing Ding on Aug. 10 in Clear Lake, Iowa. The dinner is known for attracting White House candidates and those contemplating bids to a state that is considered one of the most important presidential proving grounds. Previous speakers include then-candidates Barack Obama, Hillary Clinton and Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDERS DUMPING STOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/26/facebook-insiders-have-sold-4-billion-of-shares-since-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Insiders Have Sold $4 Billion of Shares Since Scandal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ordinary License Plate's Days May Be Numbered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/26/business/digital-license-plates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies are trying out ways to digitize the traditional metal version, eliminating the need for stickers to mark it as up to date. The screen could also be used for advertising or alerts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE LOSES BILLION$ IN MINUTES!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/26/putting-zuckerberg-s-16-8-billion-wipeout-into-perspective#gs.HMhTBl0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Mark Zuckerberg, it’s just about a fifth of his net worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKI WATCH: Ecuador Says Assange Can't Enjoy 'Eternal Asylum'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201807261066703290-ecuador-assange-cannot-stay-in-embassy-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top diplomat's remarks come amid reports that the WikiLeaks founder may soon be stripped of his asylum at the Latin American country's London mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Does L.A.'s creative resistance go too far?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-trump-star-protest-20180725-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artists, pranksters and vandals have hung Trump in effigy, portrayed him nude, and repeatedly vandalized his star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame. The tactics have become a major element of the resistance. But does destroying Trump's star go too far?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned-out millennials quitting lucrative jobs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/25/millennials-are-bailing-on-their-high-paying-jobs-to-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Solomon had a pretty sweet life. The 20-something publicist was always out at fashion events, dinners and parties — and even hung out with John Legend during Fashion Week. “It was definitely …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DEATH SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/us-markets-earnings-trade-ecb-and-data-on-the-agenda.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite and S&amp;P 500 opened lower on Thursday after a sharp decline in Facebook sent tech shares lower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mercury in retrograde': Expect 3 weeks of bad luck?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/07/26/mercury-in-retrograde-should-expect-3-weeks-bad-luck.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're experiencing a spell of bad luck, many people may ask you the same question: is Mercury in retrograde?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5995211/Facebook-shareholders-try-fire-Mark-Zuckerberg-chairman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shareholders are trying to fire Mark Zuckerberg as chairman of Facebook because of the social media giant's 'mishandling' of recent scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL ST STUNNED OVER PROFITABILITY PLUNGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/wall-street-is-stunned-over-facebooks-coming-profitability-plunge-do.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several analysts are downgrading Facebook shares after the company's disappointing sales and profitability forecasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer Snaps Photo Of Mother Duck Swimming -- With 76 Ducklings!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/07/25/mama-duck-76-babies-brent-cizek-new-york-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mama duck in Minnesota has captured hearts across the nation after a Bemidji photographer snapped an image of her leading an astonishing 76 ducklings across a lake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA Customers Find Safety Deposit Boxes Vanished; No Explanations...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/26/safe-boxes-stolen-drilled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman says her bank let her safety deposit box vanish. And she's not the only one. Susan Nomi says when she went to open her Bank of America safe deposit box of 16 years, the entire box was gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betsy DeVos yacht untied from dock, set adrift...</title>
      <link>http://www.toledoblade.com/local/2018/07/25/DeVos-40-million-yacht-vandalized-at-Huron-dock-npr.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occupy ICE Protesters Leave Heaps Of Trash, Human Waste For City To Clean...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/occupy-ice-pdx-protesters-leave-heaps-of-trash-human-waste-for-city-to-clean-at-taxpayers-expense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City leaders say they found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU: AMAZON face ID tool mismatched 28 members of Congress to mugshots...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180726120000-51gft</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON.COM-FACIAL RECOGNITION/ (PIX):Amazon's face ID tool mismatched 28 members of Congress to mugshots: ACLU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Has Just 15 'Perfect' Days A Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/best-day-ever-survey-15-perfect-days-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What makes a day "perfect?" Of course, the answer can be markedly different from person to person, but a recent survey sought to find out common characteristics of an ideal day for the average person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can She Turn Georgia Blue?</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5349541/stacey-abrams-georgia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I am coming for you, Georgia! Help me get there!'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>http://www.newser.com/story/262480/a-harsh-letter-a-168b-loss-and-a-plan-to-fire-zuckerberg.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did you just lose $16.8 billion?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi war threat: Oil tankers bombed; Kingdom bans exports through Red Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/994441/saudi-arabia-news-iran-houthi-movement-oil-tankers-donald-trump-exports-red-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-BACKED Yemeni rebels aligned have launched an attack on two oil tankers passing through the strategically important Red Sea shipping lane of Bab al-Mandeb – prompting Saudi Arabia to announce that was “temporarily halting” all oil shipments along the route.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson wildfire forces entire California town to evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47e6296ea13043c68fcd0147acddc544/Arson-wildfire-forces-entire-California-town-to-evacuate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IDYLLWILD, Calif. (AP) — A fast-moving wildfire — believed to have been sparked by arson — tore through trees, burned five homes and forced evacuation orders for an en</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech blasts snoozing workers with AC...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180726-thats-cold-japan-tech-blasts-snoozing-workers-with-ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence as migrants storm Morocco-Spain border fence...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-5994709/Violence-migrants-storm-Morocco-Spain-border-fence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 400 migrants from sub-Saharan Africa reached Spain Thursday after storming a double barrier between Morocco and the Spanish territory of Ceuta, with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian general warns Trump: 'War will destroy everything you own'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180726094015-595zf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-USA/TRUMP-SOLEIMANI (URGENT):Iranian general warns Trump:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Small bomb set off outside US Embassy in Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/26/us-embassy-incident-beijing/839835002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos posted on Twitter showed a large amount of smoke and what appeared to be police vehicles surrounding the embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO THE HEAVENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/07/26/welcome-to-the-new-space-age#gs.t=jDLaI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the New Space Age</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Outflows Swell as Investors Seek Refuge in Bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/outflows-from-u-s-stocks-swell-as-investors-seek-refuge-in-bonds-1532597401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are fleeing U.S. stocks at a rapid clip as the possibility of a protracted trade dispute between the world’s two largest economies pushes them to seek safety among less risky assets such as U.S. Treasurys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mission to Sample Comet Going 84,000MPH -- and Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/07/26/the-mission-to-sample-a-comet-going-84-000-miles-per-hour-and-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mission to Sample a Comet Going 84,000 Miles Per Hour—and Return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan newspaper closures leave coverage in state's hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-media-coverage/venezuelan-newspaper-closures-leave-coverage-in-states-hands-idUSKBN1KG18G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost three-quarters of Venezuela's newspapers have closed during five years of recession in the once-prosperous OPEC member country, according to the national journalism association, leaving El Nacional as the last independent national daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-shareholders-new-proposal-fire-mark-zuckerberg-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BI PRIME: Facebook investor Trillium Asset Management has drawn up a new proposal to oust Mark Zuckerberg as chairman. Trillium wants to appoint an independent chairman, citing Facebook's 'mishandling' of scandals like Cambridge Analytica.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
