<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kamala meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/15/kamala-harris-campaign-2020-071105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign manager Juan Rodriguez is taking the most heat for the failings, but his defenders point their finger at the candidate's sister, Maya Harris.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purrfect crime: Pet detective seeks lost animals...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/purrfect-crime-chinese-pet-detective-seeks-lost-animals-051212965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private sleuth Sun Jinrong brings heat detectors, tiny surveillance cameras, and a blow dart loaded with a tranquiliser to his search for one desperate client's missing loved one: A cat named Duoduo. Sun often gets calls from anguished pet owners in the middle of the night and rushes to cities and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 sailors injured in 5 hour fire aboard USS Iwo Jima...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2019/11/15/11-sailors-injured-in-5-hour-fire-aboard-amphib-uss-iwo-jima-3rd-warship-damaged-in-fire-during-maintenance-in-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven sailors suffered minor injuries during a fire that broke out late Thursday aboard the amphibious warship USS Iwo Jima (LHD-7), Navy officials told USNI News. “Sailors on board reported smoke in a cargo hold and a subsequent damage control investigation identified the fire and confirmed the fire had not spread to surrounding spaces,” read …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected School Shooter Didn't Fit Profile of Depressed, Angry Teen...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/saugus-high-school-shooter-nathan-berhow-had-girlfriend-honor-roll-track-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 16-year-old Saugus High School student was identified by CBS News as the gunman in the shooting that killed a 16-year-old girl and a 14-year-old boy. Nathan remains in grave condition from a self-inflicted gunshot wound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/horse-found-stabbed-police-say-3-horse-attacks-in-2-weeks/29792322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wyff4.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horse had to be euthanized after it was found stabbed, according to Campobello police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRENNAN WARNS TRUMP:   'May Your Downfall be Swift'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/11/brennan-sends-president-trump-ominous-warning-in-the-middle-of-schiffs-impeachment-show-trial-may-your-downfall-be-swift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS HE WILL DIE IN JAIL... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/report-roger-stone-fears-hell-be-epsteind-in-jail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump confidant scared he will be murdered while in prison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly 'axe attacks' on horses in North and South Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxcarolina.com/investigations/spartanburg-co-official-confirms-another-horse-stabbing-investigation-underway-in/article_a966583e-0702-11ea-9774-cfae5c04498b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxcarolina.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMPOBELLO, SC (FOX Carolina) – Spartanburg County’s Environmental Enforcement Department director confirmed Thursday his team was investigating another incident in Campobello involving a stab wound to a horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces up to 50 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7690103/Roger-Stone-GUILTY-lying-Congress-WikiLeaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone faces years in federal jail after he was found guilty today of lying to Congress about his efforts to procure stolen Democratic Party emails from WikiLeaks to help Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TV RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/myles-garrett-suspended-nfl-thursday-night-football-ratings-rise-fox-greys-anatomy-young-sheldon-1202787177/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blast radius from the chaos of last night’s Thursday Night Football grows as the NFL has fined the Pittsburgh Steelers and the victorious Cleveland Browns and suspended a trio of players for th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea calls Joe Biden 'rabid dog' who should be 'beaten to death with stick'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10354955/north-korea-joe-biden-rabid-dog-beaten-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH Korea has dubbed Donald Trump’s presidential rival Joe Biden a “rabid dog” which needs to be put down for slandering dictator Kim Jong-un.  The official KCNA news agency did not say how Biden…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET BAIER: Trump Just Gave Schiff New Article of Impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/foxs-bret-baier-trump-gave-schiff-a-new-article-of-impeachment-in-real-time-with-twitter-attack-on-yovanovitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dramatic moment during Friday's House Impeachment hearing in which Rep. Adam Schiff (D-CA) read out President Donald Trump's tweet blasting former ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES LIVE:  TRUMP MUST PARDON!</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-alex-jones-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank teller accused of attacking customer in 'reverse bank robbery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bank-teller-accused-of-attacking-customer-in-home-invasion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Maryland have arrested a bank teller accused of a home invasion of a customer who had recently withdrawn a large sum of money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Suspends BROWNS Player Indefinitely, Fines Both Teams $250,000...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/nfl-suspends-myles-garrett-indefinitely-fines-both-steelers-and-browns-250000-also-suspends-maurkice-pouncey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has handed down its punishments for last night’s violence during the end of the Pittsburgh Steelers-Cleveland Browns game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witness tampering, lying to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ad355d2c983e4a7c85bc17e86d8c563f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Roger Stone, a longtime friend and ally of President Donald Trump, was found guilty Friday of witness tampering and lying to Congress about his pursuit of Russian-hacked emails...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VERY INTIMIDATING'</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191115154338-5tai2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV, GRAPHICS):UPDATE 7-'Very intimidating' - Trump launches Twitter attack on witness during impeachment testimony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay employee says salary halved to be even with 'females in office'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/15/gay-employee-salary-halved-even-females-office-new-york-discrimination-lawsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man claims in lawsuit against New York events company that employers sought to degrade him after they learned he was gay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Putting On 'Game Face' Improves Performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/competitive-edge-putting-on-a-game-face-can-improve-performance-stress-recovery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most people consider these gritty stares as nothing more than a side effect of preparing for in-game play, is it possible that putting on a game face actually helps us perform better?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video showing teen with no arms or legs being tackled and pinned by deputy prompts investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Video-showing-teen-with-no-arms-or-legs-being-14837578.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shirtless 15-year-old screams as he lies facedown on the kitchen floor of his group home in Tucson, Arizona. He has no arms or legs, so he can't flee or fight back. A sheriff's deputy at least twice his size is crouching over him and pinning him to the ground, using his body weight to restrain the quadruple amputee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TORCHES WITNESS IN REAL-TIME</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/trump-attacks-marie-yovanovitch-in-real-time-during-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump attacked former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch in real time as she testified in the Trump impeachment inquiry, denigrating her career as a diplomat and asserting h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House releases memo of Trump call with Ukraine Zelenskiy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/15/trump-releases-transcript-of-april-call-with-ukraine-president.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congratulatory phone call was three months before the July 25 call, which sparked the House impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT BANNED FROM PLAYING OLD HITS?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/big-machine-records-denies-taylor-swift-claims-scott-borchetta-scooter-braun-1203406009/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED: In a statement issued early Friday morning, Big Machine Records denied Taylor Swift’s claims that they are blocking the use of her music. Swift had said in social media posts late Thursday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight from London to Sydney breaks 2 world records...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/878650/flight-from-london-sydney-breaks-2-world-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a milestone decades in the making. On Friday, a Qantas airplane loaded with 100 metric tons of jet fuel flew 11,060 miles from London to Sydney, nonstop. The journey lasted 19 hours and 19 minutes, and shattered two records, becoming the longest commercial airline passenger flight for both distance and duration, CNN reports. The new Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner departed from Heathrow Airport at 6 a.m. Thursday morning, and flew over Germany, Russia, Poland, Belarus, Kazakhstan, China, the Philippines, and Indonesia. This was a test flight, and while the plane can hold up to 256 people, there were just 50 on board. All passengers were outfitted with monitors, and researchers from Australia's Charles Perkins Centre will study how sleep patterns, movement, and food consumption on an extremely long flight affect a person's health. The last time Qantas attempted to fly this route without stopping, it was 1989. The airline used a Boeing 747, ripping out most of the seats and loading the plane with as much fuel as possible, even towing it to the runway in order to conserve gas, CNN reports. "Flying nonstop from the east coast of Australia to London and New York is truly the final frontier in aviation, so we're determined to do all the groundwork to get this right," Qantas CEO Alan Joyce said. Qantas is hopeful it can start offering nonstop flights from London to Sydney and vice versa in 2022. Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Faces Probe on Campaign Finance, Lobbying Breaches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/giuliani-faces-u-probe-campaign-000039292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Rudy Giuliani, President Donald Trump’s personal lawyer, is being investigated by federal prosecutors for possible campaign finance violations and a failure to register as a foreign agent as part of an active investigation into his financial dealings, according to three U.S. officials.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fabricating, Manipulating...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/11/15/taylor-swift-big-machine-denies-blocking-ama-performance-lying/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Machine says Taylor Swift's version of things is completely made up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASIK eye surgery should be taken off market, former FDA adviser says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/lasik-eye-surgery-retired-fda-adviser-says-procedure-should-be-taken-off-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An estimated 20 million Americans have undergone the procedure to correct nearsightedness and improve distance vision</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 Children Found Hidden Behind False Wall At Daycare Owner's Home...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/carla-faith-children-found-false-wall-daycare-colorado-springs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials investigating complaints about a daycare in Colorado Springs found more than two dozen children -- all under the age of 3 -- behind a false wall that led to the basement of the owner's home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 2</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f420045618b4106b6fa7419a3d75b8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on President Donald Trump and House impeachment hearings (all times local): 10:10 a.m. President Donald Trump is attacking a witness in House Democrats’...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONGEST SUSPENSION EVER?</title>
      <link> https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/11/15/myles-garrett-cleveland-browns-nfl-discipline-pittsburgh-steelers-mason-rudolph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latin Grammys: Chilean singer exposes her bare chest in political protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/music/2019/11/14/latin-grammys-mon-laferte-exposes-bare-chest-political-protest/4197563002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilean musician Mon Laferte exposed her bare chest at the Latin Grammys Thursday in protest of police brutality in Chile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As smartphones begin using scanned IDs, skeptics cite glitches, misuse, growing surveillance culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/As-smartphones-begin-using-scanned-IDs-skeptics-14837311.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashton Hickey appreciates some of the advanced features on her iPhone 8, like wireless charging and a camera that shoots high-definition 4K video.  But there's one she refuses to use: the fingerprint sensor that lets people access their phones with a single touch. Instead, she continually enters her six-digit passcode.  "I can handle typing that in," said Hickey, a freelance locations coordinator for movies and television shows. And she wouldn't ever consider the facial recognition on the latest iPhones. "Like more and more tech, it's [something] potentially nefarious, disguised as a way to make our life easier."  Hickey is one of a small but passionate group of smartphone owners resisting the recent wave of biometric security features, such as Apple's facial recognition technology and Samsung's iris and facial scans. Instead, they're sticking with passcodes or unlock patterns to access their smartphones even as companies push biometrics as key selling points on the newest thousand-dollar devices.  Avoiding commercial biometric security could be an increasingly difficult feat in the future. Smartphone makers are sticking with the tech and say it is faster and safer to use than a passcode alone. Facial recognition as an ID is already being offered to consumers outside of phones, including at airport check-ins, sports stadiums and concerts.  Computer science experts who study biometrics predict there will only be more options in the coming years, such as voice or heart-rate detection, signature authentication and even devices that can tell who you are by the way you walk. The Pentagon is already working on tools for gait and heartbeat identification.  But the passcode holdouts say they are worried about people gaining access to their phones through faulty fingerprint or face-detection tools. They fret about the security of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants remove dining rooms to speed off-site food frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-fastfood-kitchens/restaurants-remove-dining-rooms-to-speed-off-site-food-frenzy-idUSKBN1XP1A1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants are doing away with dining rooms as consumers increasingly order foo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Plans $100M in Anti-Trump Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/michael-bloomberg-pours-100-million-into-anti-trump-online-ad-campaign-2019-11-15</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg, who is deciding if he will launch a Democratic presidential bid, is not featured in the ad campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hindenburg Omen' and 'Ohama Titanic Syndrome' form in key stock-market index...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/an-ominous-sounding-hindenburg-omen-and-a-ohama-titanic-syndrome-are-forming-in-a-key-stock-market-index-2019-11-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of ominous patterns are forming in the Nasdaq Composite, which could signal that a stock-market climb, fueled by a hoped-for tariff detente between...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?466135-1/impeachment-hearing-ukraine-ambassador-marie-yovanovitch&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intelligence Committee holds an open hearing as part of the ongoing impeachment inquiry. Former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch is slated to testify.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarier than fiction: Climate worry driving 'cli-fi' boom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scarier-fiction-climate-worry-driving-cli-fi-boom-023220739.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a year of devastating extreme weather and worldwide unrest over the emergency posed by climate change, topics that used to belong to the realm of science fiction are finding their way into mainstream storytelling. Back in 2004, Roland Emmerich's disaster flick "The Day After Tomorrow&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-immigrant Sweden Democrats take opinion poll lead...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191115103225-wxg51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWEDEN-POLITICS/SWEDENDEMOCRATS:Anti-immigrant Sweden Democrats take opinion poll lead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, in 3rd Visit in Month, Tries to Boost Republican in Louisiana Governor's Race... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191115022541-uqe0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TRUMP-LOUISIANA (PIX):Trump makes final pitch for Republican challenger in Louisiana governor's race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice hit by another ferocious high tide, flooding city...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-weather-venice-idUSKBN1XP0T5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venice was inundated by exceptionally high water levels on Friday just days afte...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Plans $100M in Anti-Trump Ads...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-plans-100m-anti-trump-121520082.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Former New York City Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg will spend $100 million from his personal fortune for a digital advertising campaign against President Donald Trump ahead of the 2020 election, according to the New York Times.The ads will seek to attack and define Trump in battleground states</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted ambassador to testify...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fabcdf12d10f41eaaeddcccf339d08df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House will hear from a singular witness Friday in the Trump impeachment hearings: Marie Yovanovitch, the former U.S. ambassador to Ukraine who was targeted by the president’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLS FOR JAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/sports/nfl-world-stunned-by-myles-garrett-attack-on-mason-rudolph-calls-for-season-ban-jail-050946065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former NFL players were stunned by the Myles Garrett attack on Mason Rudolph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kissinger warns of 'catastrophic' conflicts between China, USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3037870/kissinger-warns-us-and-china-their-conflicts-will-be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It will be worse than the world wars that ruined European civilisation,’ says former secretary of state and adviser to Richard Nixon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, in 3rd Visit in Month, Tries to Boost Republican in Louisiana Governor's Race... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/trump-goes-after-adam-schiff-at-rally-ostensibly-to-boost-louisiana-governor-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump tried to undermine House Intelligence Chairman Adam B. Schiff during a political rally in Louisiana, saying he has a "small neck."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCORSESE URGES ART OVER ALGORITHM; 'IT'S ALL ILLUSION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/martin-scorsese-urges-commitment-art-algorithms-1255113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honored with the 14th annual Kirk Douglas Award by the Santa Barbara International Film Festival Thursday night, 'The Irishman' filmmaker also opens up on his legendary collaborators and the name on his new trophy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male sex robots to replace men as women leave loveless relationships...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/male-sex-robots-could-see-20841272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The male sex doll market is rapidly growing. Here's how it could impact relationships in the future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He could have killed him'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/nfl-players-react-to-myles-garrett-swinging-helmet-at-steelers-quarterback-mason-rudolph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL world did not have any sympathy for Myles Garrett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete surges ahead of Iowa caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/470565-buttigieg-surges-ahead-of-iowa-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg is surging in the 2020 primary, capitalizing on a Democratic Party wrestling with its political identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELMET ATTACK SHOCKS NFL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9ba79fa26c6c4c55b10a9405d374e4b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — Myles Garrett swung a helmet. The NFL will soon swing back at the Cleveland Browns star. Garrett could be facing an unprecedented league suspension for his violent outburst...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts claim addiction to shopping is mental illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/experts-claim-addiction-to-shopping-is-a-mental-illness-8zptsggjt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addiction to shopping fuelled by online retailing should be classed as a mental health condition, psychiatrists claim. Researchers said that about 5 per cent of adults in developed countries — more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge slams feds over indecision on FBI's McCabe...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/14/andrew-mccabe-prosecution-uncertainty-071028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ongoing uncertainty over the prosecution was unfair to the former deputy FBI director, the federal judge said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Dirt Bike Gang Taunts, Circles Around NYPD Cop At Gas Station... </title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/14/nypd-officer-taunted-by-dirt-bike-riders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD has made an arrest in an incident that some say disrespected the badge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOMELAND SECURITY' CONFIRMS NO NEW BORDER WALL YET...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/14/dhs-confirms-no-new-border-wall-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration still has yet to fence in any new miles of border with President Trump’s wall, a top Homeland Security official acknowledged Thursday — though he said that’s not the right way to look at the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CONWAY SHOW: GEORGE SAYS KELLYANNE IN A 'CULT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/11/kellyanne-caught-in-west-wing-cross-fire-as-george-goes-full-resistance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump complains, and Jared wants her out, as George Conway fires fierce salvos at the president and parties with Kathy Griffin and Paul Krugman. But he still loves Kellyanne, sources say. “He’s going through a tough time,” says one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, in 3rd Visit in Month, Tries to Boost Republican in Louisiana Governor's Race... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/going-louisiana-governors-race-trump-tries-thread-needle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is signaling Saturday's Louisiana governor's race is a harbinger of things to come in 2020. So he's going back there. For a fourth time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX TOPS RATINGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/13-1-million-watched-first-impeachment-hearings-with-fox-news-most-viewed-and-cnn-second-in-demo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Day 1 of the impeachment hearings captured the nation's attention — and blanket coverage across the big three broadcast and cable news networks resulted in a massive daytime audience. Overall, 13</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAYLOR SWIFT BANNED FROM PLAYING OLD HITS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/taylor-swift-american-music-awards-scooter-braun-scott-borchetta-1203405629/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift has taken to social media to tell fans that Scott Borchetta, her former label head at Big Machine Records, and his new partner Scooter Braun are trying to nix her plans for a retrospec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkish media paints White House visit as Erdogan triumph over Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/470559-turkish-media-paints-white-house-visit-as-erdogan-triumph-over-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish media are seizing on President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan’s comments that President Trump had “no reaction” to his returning the American leader’s notorious letter to him, saying it shows a clear victory over Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg apologizes for sexist remarks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/14/bloomberg-apologizes-for-sexist-remarks-as-he-plots-presidential-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg — who is expected to soon declare his candidacy in the Democratic primary, issued a rare apology through a spokesman in a New York Times piece about his lurid statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State slipping back into drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/california/article237368339.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese killer robots sold to Middle East will leave 'every human dead'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-killer-robots-sold-middle-20882729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears that 'fully autonomous' military drones sold by China to Middle East countries could have dire results with the machines able to decide on who lives and dies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE NEWS struggles to add subscribers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/apple-news-has-struggled-to-add-subscribers-since-march-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple signed on 200,000 subscribers to Apple News+ in its first 48 hours in March, but has been stuck in neutral since that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meds pose global environmental risk, experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/medicines-pose-global-environmental-risk-experts-warn-170419416.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residues from billions of doses of antibiotics, painkillers and antidepressants pose a significant risk to freshwater ecosystems and the global food chain, a new analysis said Thursday. There are growing fears that the unchecked use of antibiotics in both medicine and agriculture will have adverse effects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy declares state of emergency in Venice after flood...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-declare-state-emergency-venice-flood-132501344.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy on Thursday declared a state of emergency for Venice after an exceptional tide surged through churches, shops and homes, causing millions of euros worth of damage to the UNESCO city. Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte said the cabinet had approved the state of emergency and ordered the immediate release</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PETITIONS SUPREMES TO SHIELD TAX RETURNS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/019be473afbe4cddbc21aff91f4fa611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is asking the Supreme Court to block a subpoena for his tax returns, in a test of the president’s ability to defy investigations. The filing Thursday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West shatters record with 232 consecutive days of 80 degrees or higher...</title>
      <link>https://accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/this-is-the-land-of-perpetual-summer/627654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stone trial jury ends 1st day of deliberations without verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-stone/jury-in-trial-of-trump-adviser-stone-ends-first-day-of-deliberations-without-verdict-idUSKBN1XO2AS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury in the criminal trial of U.S. President Donald Trump's adviser Rog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Deval could torpedo Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/14/deval-patrick-joe-biden-2020-070915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-Massachusetts governor eyes a path through South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seen Lining Up Military Aircraft For Possible Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/14/779089382/north-korea-seen-lining-up-military-aircraft-for-possible-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images shared exclusively with NPR show North Korean fighters and helicopters massed at a single airbase. It could be another sign of escalating tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Clinton offers advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/14/bill-clinton-offers-donald-trump-impeachment-advic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton, America’s most-recent impeached president, on Thursday offered apparently sincere words of advice for President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anonymous' whistleblower: Medical data of millions at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/nov/14/im-the-google-whistleblower-the-medical-data-of-millions-of-americans-is-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When I learned that Google was acquiring the intimate medical records of 50 million patients, I couldn’t stay silent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds preparing to take over private land in Texas?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/trump-admin-preparing-take-over-private-land-border-wall-n1082316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is preparing court filings to begin taking over private land in Texas to build a border wall as early as this week, say officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP PETITIONS SUPREMES TO SHIELD TAX RETURNS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/trump-asks-supreme-court-to-let-him-keep-his-tax-returns-secret.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case could determine whether any president has blanket criminal immunity while in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlottesville suit seeks to link online talk to violence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47b79d2805754f77af8083c1a3731ad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The white nationalist rally that took a deadly turn in Charlottesville, Virginia, during the summer of 2017 shocked Americans with its front-row view of hatred on the rise. But weeks before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Why not naming whistleblower bad for mainstream media...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/11/14/whistleblower-nyt-impeachment-070887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times will only partially unmask him. The rest of the news media should finish the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States' massive GOOGLE antitrust probe will expand into search...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/14/states-google-antitrust-probe-to-expand-into-search-android-businesses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, the investigation, which is being led by Texas' attorney general, has explicitly focused on Google's advertising business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Student editor in hiding after reporting triggering news...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/daily-northwestern-editor-in-chief-hides-in-office-to-dodge-free-beacon-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily Northwestern editor in chief Troy Closson hid inside his office on Tuesday rather than answer questions from the Washington Free Beacon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-year-old genius to graduate university...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/14/europe/university-graduate-child-genius-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child prodigy from Belgium is on course to gain a bachelor's degree at the tender age of nine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo'Nique Sues NETFLIX Over 'Discriminatory Pay Offer' for Stand-up Special...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/monique-sues-netflix-over-discriminatory-pay-offer-for-stand-up-special/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress and comedian Mo'Nique filed a lawsuit accusing Netflix of pay discrimination based on her race and gender Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein's brother: Epstein didn't kill himself, wasn't trafficking women...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article237242984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX DOMINATES IMPEACHMENT RATINGS</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/impeachment-hearings-tv-ratings-donald-trump-fox-news-cnn-msnbc-1202786141/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was just by a hair, but the debut of the impeachment hearings against Donald Trump yesterday beat Robert Mueller’s testimony before Congress earlier this year …barely. With a grand total o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Tactical edge will shift...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/227149e8403744bf87261f4c9a06f002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s been easy for majority Democrats to keep Republicans from shifting the focus of the House impeachment hearings. Yet GOP leverage to do just that will grow should the battle...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Dead in California High School Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/shooting-reported-high-school-los-angeles-area/story?id=67010044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shooting was reported Thursday morning at a high school in Santa Clarita near Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy says Trump will stay loyal to him -- but jokes he has 'insurance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/14/rudy-giuliani-donald-trump-insurance-loyal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President’s lawyer, a key figure in the impeachment inquiry, speaks to Guardian amid speculation Republicans will seek to paint him as a rogue actor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/11/14/shooting-at-saugus-high-school-prompts-lockdown-of-campus-gunman-sought/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspect has been apprehended after a shooting that left one person dead and several other injured at Saugus High School in Santa Clarita, prompting a massive police response and the temporary lockdown of two entire school districts Thursday morning. The incident began around 7:30 a.m. when deputies responded to a report of shots fired on the campus, located at 21900 Centurion Way, the Los Angeles County Sheriff's Department's Santa Clarita station said in a series of tweets. The agency characterized the incident as an "active shooter situation."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
