<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists hunt for 'Su' who could be mystery 'patient zero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-hunt-patient-su-woman-24217556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelations come after British officials conceded this week that the possibility of a lab leak remains "plausible" - with mysterious "Patient Su" appearing to have been traced close to the Wuhan Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Biden, deeply personal Memorial Day weekend observance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-memorial-day-c3886def81f78c762fd1e920148ef32a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW CASTLE, Del. (AP) — President Joe Biden marked his first Memorial Day weekend as commander in chief by honoring the nation’s sacrifices in a deeply personal manner as he paid tribute Sunday to those lost while remembering his late son Beau, a veteran who died six years ago to the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hat Shop Selling Nazi-Style Jewish Stars Proclaiming 'Not Vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/more-hatmakers-cut-ties-with-nashville-hat-shop-after-controversial-instagram-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday, the owner of hatWRKS hat shop on 8th Ave South in Nashville posted a photo to Instagram with a yellow patch resembling the Star of David along with the words “not vaccinated”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious B.I.G. executed by Nation of Islam convert arranged by Suge Knight, ex-FBI agent claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9634317/Notorious-B-G-executed-Nation-Islam-convert-hit-arranged-Suge-Knight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suge Knight (top right) allegedly paid a hitman to kill Notorious B.I.G. in LA in 1997 as revenge for Tupac Shakur's (bottom right) murder even though the intended target was Sean 'Diddy' Combs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark accused of helping USA spy on Merkel, European officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-57302806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's secret service is accused of helping the US target politicians such as Germany's Angela Merkel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials worry rise in violent crime portends bloody summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/officials-worry-the-rise-in-violent-crime-portends-a-bloody-summer-e2-80-98it-e2-80-99s-trauma-on-top-of-trauma-e2-80-99/ar-AAKxyhR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the nation marks Memorial Day, the unofficial kickoff to summer, many officials are concerned violence could be especially pronounced this season as Americans emerge back into society after a year of coronavirus-related lockdowns and restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Shakeout Stirs Debate on Ether Shot at Usurping Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-shakeout-stirs-debate-on-ether-e2-80-99s-shot-at-usurping-bitcoin/ar-AAKyqGI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The relative resilience of Ether in May’s cryptocurrency rout has put the spotlight back on the idea that the second-largest digital token could one day overtake Bitcoin by market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Moves to Three-Child Policy to Boost Falling Birthrate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-57303592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Census results show China's population grew at its slowest pace in decades last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531094331-qp71v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-REFORMS (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531003534-ol0dn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-JUSTICE/OATHKEEPERS:Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case: court filing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems walk, stop TX sweeping voting restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tx-state-wire-texas-government-and-politics-92d26e25c9db88a32e0fda890773b908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Democrats pulled off a dramatic, last-ditch walkout in the state House of Representatives on Sunday night to block passage of one of the most restrictive voting bills in the U.S., leaving Republicans with no choice but to abandon a midnight deadline and declare the legislative session essentially over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do deficits matter anymore? Biden's first budget signals they don't...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/do-deficits-matter-anymore-biden-s-first-budget-signals-they-don-t/ar-AAKuHYg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s first budget predicts a $1.8 trillion deficit for 2022 and deficits of $1.3 trillion for years to come to fund big investments in education, infrastructure and the social safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shooting at Miami rap concert leaves 2 dead, 20 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/05/30/at-least-20-people-shot-2-killed-at-northwest-miami-dade-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victims were rushed to several hospitals in Miami-Dade and Broward counties after a shooting at a banquet hall, some in their personal vehicles, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS Fan Throws Bottle at Player...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/31/td-garden-fan-water-bottle-kyrie-irving-boston-celtics-brooklyn-nets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Players from both the Celtics and Nets condemned a fan who is now facing charges and a liftetime ban from TD Garden after throwing a water bottle at Nets guard Kyrie Irving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/uptick-in-coronavirus-cases-prompts-chinese-city-to-lock-down-neighborhood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The southern Chinese city of Guangzhou has shut down a neighborhood and ordered residents to stay home for door-to-door coronavirus testing following an upsurge in infections that has rattled authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look inside all of Ellen DeGeneres' homes: Her $450M real estate portfolio!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/a-look-inside-all-of-ellen-degeneres-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres owns $63.3 million in homes and has sold $390 million in houses over the last 17 years, making an estimated $65 million profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Naftali Bennett...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210530163854-syuhk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Netanyahu's grip on power loosens as rival moves to unseat him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops finally admit tear gas used on Lafayette Park protesters in June '20...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/investigations/mpd-admits-it-tear-gassed-protesters-june-2020/65-b91a5d65-b683-4e22-b30a-7a740e9cf61d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Richard Sobiecki explained for the first time why MPD used tear gas against protesters fleeing federal police, though he did not say what exactly was used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indianapolis 500 returns with biggest sports crowd since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indianapolis-500-return-biggest-sporting-011643994.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indianapolis 500 will return with a roar this Memorial Day weekend, as the event expects to host the biggest crowd at a sporting event since the pandemic's start. Bob Donaldson has more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone predicts criminal indictment on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/05/29/roger-stone-predicts-a-donald-trump-criminal-indictment-is-on-the-horizon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stone says it's another "witch hunt" — though many disagree with that assessment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandal hurls concrete slab at LA synagogue...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/investigation-underway-after-vandal-hurls-concrete-slab-at-west-l-a-synagogue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vandal hurled concrete slabs this week at the windows of a West Los Angeles synagogue and a nearby kosher restaurant in the heart of the city’s Jewish community, the latest in a national surge in…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
