<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Boris urges caution as England takes first big step out of lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/28/johnson-urges-caution-as-england-takes-first-big-step-out-of-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outdoor group socialising allowed from Monday but ad campaign stresses Covid risks of indoor meeting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate accused of pandering after he transforms into cowboy for TX congressional run...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/GOP-candidate-accused-of-pandering-after-he-16059538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey boy. Pro wrestler. Republican candidate in Nevada. Dan Rodimer has led many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oil for vaccines,' offers Venezuela's Maduro as Covid bites...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-maduro-proposes-paying-coronavirus-000107796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro on Sunday proposed paying for vaccines against the novel coronavirus with oil, though he provided few details about how such a scheme would work. The crisis-stricken OPEC nation's crude exports have plummeted to their lowest levels in decades since Washington sanctioned state oil company Petroleos de Venezuela in 2019, cutting off Venezuela's exports to the United States and dissuading many other customers from buying Venezuelan oil as well. Maduro said Venezuela was working to pay for vaccines from the World Health Organization's (WHO) COVAX mechanism - which provides vaccine access to poor countries - both through Venezuelan funds frozen in overseas accounts due to sanctions, and through oil shipments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION won't rule out suing Trump next!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/dominion-wont-rule-out-lawsuit-against-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump may yet face a lawsuit from Dominion Voting Systems for spreading election fraud claims about the 2020 contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO GRAND JURIES INVESTIGATING TRUMP IN GA</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-unlikely-team-hunting-team-donald-trump-in-georgia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public integrity unit at the Fulton County District Attorney’s office once had a miserable reputation. Now, a new crew there is investigating the biggest target of them all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>;l;;gmlxzssaw:  US Strategic Command posts bizarre tweet sparking hacking fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2599127/us-strategic-command-bizarre-tweet-fears-memes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BIZARRE tweet from the US Strategic Command has prompted a flurry on Twitter as people try and decipher what it may mean. The government account tweet came around 7:50pm, and began to go viral as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discarded Face Masks Killing Wildlife Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-waste-face-masks-killing-wildlife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers warn that pets are also at risk of accidentally swallowing a face mask, especially dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious disease killing young California bears in Tahoe. One symptom: Fearlessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article250247805.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sickly female cub was covered in ticks when it was captured. What veterinarians discovered about her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis threatens to sue CDC if doesn't lift ban on cruises...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/florida-desantis-lawsuit-threat-cdc-cruise-covid-order-41427821-dff9-44fe-a84f-c1d87c3614b9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say it's "too early" for cruises to resume, given the higher risk of COVID spreading among passengers on ships, per AP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY SOME BOXOFFICE:  'GODZILLA VS KONG' sets pandemic record...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/box-office-coming-back-godzilla-191405637.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros.' 'Godzilla Vs. Kong' debuted to $121.8 million in international markets, while Universal's 'Nobody' was solid in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's true death toll 60% higher than official figure!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2597851/mexico-covid-death-toll-higher-second-wave-brazil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO’S government has acknowledged that the country’s true death toll from the coronavirus pandemic now stands above 321,000, almost 60 per cent more than the official test-confirmed number…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Paid LA Lifeguards Earn Up To $392,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2021/03/27/top-paid-la-lifeguards-earned-up-to-392000-in-2019/?sh=f3f2d0240129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven lifeguards made more than $300,000 and 82 lifeguards had total earnings that exceed $200,000 in 2019, the latest year available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fuels travel boom -- in virtual reality!</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-03-pandemic-fuels-boomin-virtual-reality.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jem Jenkins Jones was stuck at home in Wales for much of the past year amid pandemic lockdowns but managed to fulfill a promise to her 10-year-old daughter to see the northern lights from Iceland and South Africa's game reserves—in virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies after being struck by car while chasing robbery suspects...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/woman-dies-being-struck-car-163306641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman died Friday after she was struck by a car while chasing after two men who might have robbed her in Lancaster, investigators said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Professor Wins Preferred Gender Pronouns Case...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/first-amendment/trump-bush-appeals-court-judges-rule-in-favor-of-professor-of-christian-thought-who-refused-to-call-students-by-their-preferred-gender-pronouns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 6th Circuit on Friday ruled in favor of a "devout Christian" professor who was disciplined because he "refused to refer to students by their 'preferred pronouns.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems could undo Trump policies faster, but they're not. Why?</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/congressional-review-act-why-democrats-are-not-undoing-trump-health-policies-faster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little-used Congressional Review Act allows a new administration and Congress to fast-track the repeal of regulations and other executive actions of the previous administration. But neither law…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chauvin trial represents 'defining moment in America's racial history'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/derek-chauvin-trial-represents-defining-214600581.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Floyd pleading for his life under the knee of a Minneapolis police officer has become a defining moment of our time. What began 10 months ago at the corner of 38th Street and Chicago Avenue has transformed into nothing less than an American reckoning on justice, racial equity, the proper role of law enforcement and the historical wrongs society has perpetrated on Black people. Monday ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Brazilians disregard the pleas to stay at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-brazil-rio-de-janeiro-coronavirus-pandemic-holidays-f7acdacac7446ca40753aacf5c77cb3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Authorities in Sao Paulo and Rio de Janeiro begged the population to stay home, but thousands of Brazilians are traveling to coastal cities and ignoring recommendations on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors face heavy burden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-shootings-trials-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-d89d8aa796d203681a04bef0c1ca5fe7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — One prospective juror's voice quivered as she told attorneys during jury selection that she feared for her family's safety if chosen for the panel that will decide the fate of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris doctors warn of catastrophic overload...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-paris-coronavirus-pandemic-france-emmanuel-macron-f0cb190686641139ffb41e493afd3d2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Critical care doctors in Paris say surging coronavirus infections could soon overwhelm their ability to care for the sick in the French capital's hospitals, possibly forcing them to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network tricked director?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/28/exclusive-cbs-never-told-woody-allen-team-news-interview-would-move-to-pay-service-lied-to-us-month-after-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Lee Cowan interviewed Woody Allen last July for “CBS Sunday Morning,” it was a news segment tied to the release of Allen’s memoir, “Apropos of Nothing.” But the p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic, deadly flooding grips Nashville...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/nashville-inundated-by-life-threatening-flooding-after-severe-storms-tear-across-south/923109</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid another round of severe weather this March across the southern U.S., heavy downpours and flooding became "extremely dangerous and life-threatening" in Tennessee, resulting in four fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb could serve as road map for reparations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/545173-chicago-suburb-could-serve-as-roadmap-for-reparations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago suburb this week passed the nation’s first reparations program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path from Clinton to Biden takes U-turn on debt, trade, more...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/path-clinton-biden-takes-turn-debt-trade-76733195</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Times have changed since the 1990s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Deadly UBER Eats carjacking by teen girls...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/27/graphic-video-shows-deadly-uber-eats-carjacking-by-teen-girls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an Uber Eats driver lay dying on a Washington, DC, sidewalk, the two teen girls who allegedly stun-gunned and carjacked him easily climbed from the wreck — and even tried to run away, grap…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one of America's largest Christian camps enabled abuse...</title>
      <link>https://frenchpress.thedispatch.com/p/they-arent-who-you-think-they-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frenchpress.thedispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inside story of how Kanakuk—one of America’s largest Christian camps—enabled horrific abuse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN downpours flood homes, roads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-thunderstorms-nashville-storms-weather-06b0b257e728b44a3ddecf6105596837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Heavy rain across Tennessee flooded homes and roads late Saturday into early Sunday, prompting officials to rescue many people from houses, apartments and vehicles as a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 killed -- 1 by police -- and 8 others shot in night of chaos at Virginia Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/news/crime/vp-nw-shootings-virginia-beach-oceanfront-20210327-ybziopryevep3ipx5hxv4jl22u-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police think there were three unrelated shootings, but Chief Paul Neudigate said Saturday night, “Unfortunately for us, we don’t have a whole lot of answers.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting rare birds to feed the sex drive of princes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-56419597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A glimpse into the closed world of hunts for houbara bustards, thought by some to be an aphrodisiac.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Care Workers Bragging About Forging Vax Cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/health-care-workers-bragging-tiktok-012240703.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastBefore she wiped her page on Tuesday, TikTok user hann.brooke95 hadn’t been shy about sharing even the most mundane details of her life with her 19,400 followers.She posted TikToks of herself cooking while breastfeeding, the can of beans she was using for nachos, and even the painstaking process of transferring her license as a pharmacy tech from Florida to Illinois: from filling out the application, to affixing a return address label and stamp on the envelope, to dropping it in the mailbox in front of her house.And the stream of everyday minutiae might have continued if she hadn’t also used TikTok to brag about stealing COVID-19 vaccination cards from her job so she and her husband could pass themselves off as vaccinated.“I work at a pharmacy and grabbed blank ones for me and my hubby,” she wrote in the comments of another user’s TikTok about fake vaccination cards.It didn’t take long for fellow users Becca Walker and Savannah Sparks to zoom in on that return address label and match the name and address to public records for Hannah Brooke Hutchinson, 25, who is registered as a pharmacy tech in Illinois. Sparks then reported her to the same Illinois Board of Pharmacy that had just granted her license. The Illinois Board of Pharmacy told The Daily Beast it does not comment on investigations.“I’m pretty sure you’re not supposed to steal from your job. And I’m pretty sure you’re not supposed to steal blank vaccination papers for COVID-19 to falsify information and claim that you and your husband were vaccinated when in actuality you were not,” Walker said in a TikTok she posted to call her out.Women Are Putting Their Abortions on TikTok—but Is It Real?Hutchinson did not respond to multiple phone calls and texts sent to numbers associated with her and her boyfriend. But after Walker and Sparks posted TikToks about her, Hutchinson wiped her TikTok and deleted her Instagram and Facebook accounts. The Daily Beast, however, was able to review the zoomed-in image and independently confirm Hutchinson’s details, including her pharmacy technician license, through public records.Just before she wiped her TikTok, she posted: “Stop hating on me! I don’t care what any of you think. I did what is best for my husband and I.” Hours later she posted another TikTok claiming to be a 16-year-old girl in the U.K. doing an experiment for her dad, who is a filmmaker. But the TikToks, which went back a year, tracked with her husband’s Facebook page, which has also been deleted, where she appeared to be a mom in her twenties.“Very sick people come into pharmacies, so when you have a pharmacy employee lying about being vaccinated, everyone there is at risk,” Sparks, herself a pharmacist in Biloxi, Mississippi, told The Daily Beast. “I don’t want them in the profession.”But Hutchinson is far from the only health-care professional seemingly trying to fake her way into the vaccinated world, a trend that could have huge implications for the vulnerable Americans these employees serve.Since Monday, Walker and Sparks have, combined, posted more than half a dozen TikTok videos calling out health-care workers who’ve talked online about forging or attempting to forge vaccine cards. And they say other users have sent them dozens more tips they haven’t been able to verify.“It’s overwhelming,” Sparks said. And public health experts warn it’s incredibly dangerous.“I’m just sitting here flummoxed, thinking about the implications of it all,” said Dr. William Schaffner, a professor of preventive medicine and infectious disease at Vanderbilt University Medical Center in Nashville. “Anyone who works in the health-care environment obviously contributes to the safety of the environment, which is their own safety, their colleagues’ safety as well as the patients they serve.”He said those caught doing it would likely lose their jobs, if not their careers.“We’re trying to make the whole health-care environment a COVID-free zone and by undermining that in a deliberate fashion, that’s beyond unprofessional. It’s profoundly unethical and contrary to whatever oath a health-care worker took when they accepted their degree. I would imagine there would be implications at the licensing level.”But fear of professional reprisal hasn’t kept some health-care workers from turning the taboo topic of vaccine hesitancy into clout-chasing fodder.Under Hutchinson’s original comment about pinching blank cards, Texas nurse Courtney Long wrote, “Can I pay you to ship a couple to me,” followed by a crying-laughing emoji. Sparks was able to identify Long through the Instagram profile Long included on her TikTok, where she talked about being a nurse, and a linked Facebook profile, under the name Courtney Renee Long, where she also talked about being a nurse. The Texas Board of Nursing’s website identifies a Courtney Renee Long as a Licensed Practical Nurse.“Is this you, Miss LPN?” Sparks said in a TikTok she made calling out Long. “Ah, yeah, the Texas Board of Nursing is gonna see all of this.”Sparks said she reported Long to the Texas Board of Nursing. When contacted by The Daily Beast, the board said it does not comment on investigations. The Daily Beast made a number of attempts to reach Long, through a number associated with family members’ phone numbers and Pinterest, the only social media account in her name that still existed as of Saturday. Calls to a number associated with her name and address were not returned.Sparks and Walker say they have also called out and reported an oncology nurse in Alabama, a trauma nurse at a children’s hospital in Philadelphia, and a receptionist at an asthma clinic.Wisconsin Pharmacist Accused of Spoiling COVID Vaccine Thought It Could Change People’s DNA: CopsIf it seems surprising that vaccine resistance would exist among medical professionals, even those with a strong background in science, Schaffer said it simply highlights how many Americans are still resistant to vaccination, more than three months after the first jabs went into the arms of frontline health-care workers. In February, a survey conducted by experts from Northwestern, Northeastern, Rutgers and Harvard universities found that 21 percent of health-care workers surveyed did not want to be vaccinated. Hesitancy, which indicates skepticism towards the vaccine but not an outright unwillingness to be vaccinated, was 37 percent.“There’s a large number who are not just indifferent but disdainful to the vaccine, they’re just not going to get it. And that’s the remnants of a political approach to COVID under the last administration,” Schaffner said. “It’s hard to unring that bell.”Of course, health-care workers aren’t alone among anti-vaxxers trying to pass as vaccinated and, on Thursday, the Office of the Inspector General warned those who’ve been vaccinated to not post images of their vaccine cards online because of an increase in fake cards.As more Americans get vaccinated, anti-vaxxers have turned to social media to drum up fears of a Biden-governed future in which those without vaccination cards will be turned away from restaurants, hospitals and even Target.“If they're giving out a card to verify you’re vaccinated apparently there’s a reason for it. You might not be able to go shopping, to travel, to buy underwear,” TikTok user truevalor469 posted from a recliner earlier this month. “Hmm. Sounds like the beginning.”The backlash against Walker and Sparks’ crusade to uncover anti-vaxxer health-care workers on TikTok has been harsh. On Wednesday, Sparks changed her phone number after another TikTok user found it and began harassing her. The threats were so bad that on Friday, she had to issue a statement on her business website and shut down the reviews section.So far there are no government requirements to have a vaccination card, and Schaffner said he hasn’t heard of any private companies requiring them for either their employees or customers. Yesterday, Rutgers University in New Jersey became the first college to require students to be vaccinated but Schaffner said fears, widespread as they may be, are for now exaggerated.“By misrepresenting themselves they just avoid a lot of controversy,” he said. “So they’re doing this reprehensible thing to avoid discomfort and having to explain themselves and be responsible for their actions.”Walker said she suspects some of the users may not be as serious about faking their vaccinations as they are about chasing the clout that the taboo topic brings.“If you put up a TikTok saying, ‘Oh, I don't want to get vaccinated. Sell me a vaccine card,’ that’s an automatic 100k views,” Walker told The Daily Beast.Anti-Vaxxers Wage Cruel War on Pregnant Women Who Get COVID ShotOne TikTok user by the name linds3r commented on a viral TikTok about faking vaccination cards, writing, “I got a template if u want it” and, later, “lol I (have) made 8 of them so far front and back.” That user, Lindsey Stauffer, says on Facebook that she is an employee in medical billing at the Department of Veterans Affairs in Lebanon, Pennsylvania. She also makes and sells anti-Biden and pro-Trump shirts from her Facebook page, which includes several of the same images from her TikTok.Reached by The Daily Beast, Stauffer admitted to writing the posts but denied she’d made eight cards.“I didn’t write about making them. I said I know where you can get one. You can go to Google right now and pull up images about it yourself,” Stauffer told The Daily Beast. “I’m not making anything. Anyone can access it.”Stauffer also denied living in Lebanon, though the phone number used to reach her lists that as her address. She denied working at the VA despite listing it as her employer on Facebook. (The federal Department of Veterans Affairs did not immediately respond to requests for comment.) Stauffer also said she had been vaccinated already.“So why would I need to make them?” she told The Daily Beast.But even when medical professionals joke about forging their vaccination, Schaffner said, it can create problems.“When people hear that health-care workers are doing this, it undermines the faith the public has in these institutions and their ability to keep them safe,” Schaffner said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Legislatures Try to Curb Governors' Coronavirus Powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/state-lawmakers-try-to-curb-governors-coronavirus-powers/ar-BB1f28Pf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the pandemic began, the nation’s governors suited up for a new role as state bodyguards, issuing emergency orders to shutter schools, close cinemas and ban indoor dining in an effort to curb a mushrooming threat. But not everyone likes killjoys, no matter how well-intentioned. Now, state legislatures — saying the governors have gone too far — are churning out laws aimed at reining in the power of their executives to respond to the pandemic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film on undercover journalist baiting, exposing ISIS recruiter gets US release...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/03/26/film-on-undercover-journalist-baiting-and-exposing-isis-recruiter-gets-us-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The journalist maintained an ongoing dialogue with a man who had direct ties to Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian newspaper fights on despite threats and attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210328-russian-newspaper-fights-on-despite-threats-and-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian newspaper fights on despite threats and attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope, on Palm Sunday, says devil taking advantage of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210328095442-ps8xc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RELIGION-EASTER/POPE-PALMSUNDAY (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Pope, on Palm Sunday, says devil taking advantage of pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran and China sign 25-year cooperation agreement...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-china-idUSKBN2BJ0AD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China and Iran, both subject to U.S. sanctions, signed a 25-year cooperation agreement on Saturday to strengthen their long-standing economic and political alliance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taste and smell gone forever? The anguish of Covid survivors...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210328-taste-and-smell-gone-forever-the-anguish-of-covid-survivors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taste and smell gone forever? The anguish of Covid survivors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th Stimulus? Over 60 Lawmakers Now Support Further Direct Payments...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/fourth-stimulus-check-over-60-lawmakers-now-support-further-direct-payments-americans-1579286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House and Senate Democrats have pushed Biden for more direct payments, but the possible measure would face a legislative challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas numbers fall for 17th consecutive day following 100% reopening...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9410481/Texas-COVID-numbers-fall-17th-consecutive-day-following-reopening.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations continue to see a downward trend more than two weeks after the state scrapped its mask mandate and allowed businesses to reopen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant girls start arriving at San Diego Convention Center shelter...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/news/local-news/officials-share-update-from-newly-opened-migrant-shelter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials unveiled the San Diego Convention Center’s new migrant shelter Saturday, where 500 unaccompanied kids seeking asylum in the U.S. will have arrived by the end of the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma jail inmate shot, killed after hostage situation...</title>
      <link>https://www.oklahoman.com/story/news/2021/03/27/detention-officer-taken-hostage-at-oklahoma-county-jail/7032275002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oklahoman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A detention officer was taken hostage Saturday at the Oklahoma County jail, according to multiple reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK freezes Maduro's page for 'COVID misinformation'...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comaljazeera.com/news/2021/3/27/facebook-freezes-maduro-page-over-covid-misinformation-venezuela</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comaljazeera.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58 minutes of terror: How the Boulder shooting unfolded...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/03/27/boulder-shooting-king-soopers-58-minutes-how-unfolded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In just under an hour, a gunman terrorized the large Boulder grocery store, killing 10 people and shattering both a tight-knit workplace and a larger community’s sense of security around an e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused gunman Ahmad Al Aliwi Alissa was 'laughing' during massacre...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/27/ahmad-al-aliwi-alissa-was-laughing-during-boulder-shooting-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accused gunman in Monday’s mass shooting in Boulder was “laughing” as he murdered 10 people and terrorized shoppers inside a King Soopers grocery store, police and a witness said.  “We cou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccines haven't cured loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-new-york-coronavirus-pandemic-herkimer-medicaid-5e3ba59ec814a94b55cf86b56e84c54c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HERKIMER, N.Y. (AP) — Vaccines have begun saving lives in New York's nursing homes, but they haven't yet cured another crisis caused by the pandemic: loneliness. Persistently high rates of...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
