<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Buckingham Palace banned ethnic minorities from office roles, papers reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/jun/02/buckingham-palace-banned-ethnic-minorities-from-office-roles-papers-reveal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Documents also shed light on Queen’s ongoing exemption from race and sex discrimination laws</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Stock Craze Reaches New Heights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/meme-stock-amc-is-offering-its-investors-popcorn-how-fitting/ar-AAKFDVb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There could be no better gift to shareholders than the alluring kernels of puffed-up nothingness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/lapid-tells-rivlin-new-government-ready-669937</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bennett, Abbas finalize coalition deal * New governing coalition has been formed and is prepared to replace Netanyahu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISLAMIST LEADER OUSTS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210603082133-ag1u1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ISLAMIST-ABBAS (PIX):Arab Islamist helps clinch Israel's new anti-Netanyahu government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE AGAINST CLOCK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-health-coronavirus-pandemic-e96cc15e2474658e271e373cd4d6aeda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s opponents pushed Thursday for a quick parliament vote to formally end his lengthy rule, hoping to head off any last-minute attempts to derail their newly announced coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU plans digital ID wallet for bloc's post-pandemic life...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-travel-73f90d18909c595da463994e16e17348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The European Union unveiled plans Thursday for a digital ID wallet that residents could use to access services across the 27-nation bloc, part of a post-pandemic recovery strategy that involves accelerating the shift to an online world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafts may be coming from sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3008383/ufos-coming-from-space-sea-aliens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UFOs may not be coming from space – but rather from beneath the sea amid a string of strange encounters involving US warships, a former cop turned investigator has claimed. Gary Heseltine is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter Braun Hit With $200M Fraud Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/scooter-braun-hit-with-fraud-suit-private-equity-firm-1234962451/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scooter Braun, the music industry megastar who launched Justin Bieber’s career, is now afflicted with a significant legal dispute over actions in getting a new private equity fund off the gro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Favorite Pole-Dancing Studio Undone by Emotional Exploitation, Racial Insensitivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywood-pole-dancing-studio-s-factor-allegations-1234961498/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nadia Mitri says it was her experience on the dance floor in a Hawaii hotel ballroom with a veteran Hollywood actress that led to the darkest interlude of her life. In 2015, at a wellness retreat i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Anderson, Sean Penn to headline Cannes return...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-filmfestival-cannes-selection/wes-anderson-sean-penn-to-headline-cannes-return-idUSKCN2DF166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wes Anderson's "The French Dispatch" and Sean Penn's latest outing will be among movies vying for the top award at the Cannes Film Festival in July, as the cinema showcase plots a red carpet revival and coronavirus restrictions ease up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ investigating consulting firm tied to Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/03/blue-star-burisma-justice-department-investigation-491681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice is looking at whether Blue Star Strategies illegally lobbied on behalf of a Ukrainian company that counted Hunter Biden as a board member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying spheres spotted hurtling past ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/perfectly-spherical-ufos-mechanical-lighting-24239714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple glowing "orbs" appeared on the ISS camera and moved at a great speed in space. Graham, who recorded the footage, said it was a very "compelling" UFO sighting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'MONOPOLY' Leads To Most Fights On Game Nights...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/game-night-monopoly-banned-causes-most-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-two percent have banned certain games and another 22 percent have had to ban a particular player from their game nights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist Sells Invisible Sculpture for $18,000...</title>
      <link>https://hypebeast.com/2021/6/salvatore-garau-lo-sono-invisible-sculpture-18k-usd-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hypebeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Made from "air and spirit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOND Writer Fears Bezos Will Ruin Franchise: 007 Not 'Mere Commodity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/james-bond-writer-fears-amazon-will-ruin-the-franchise-007/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Logan, who wrote the James Bond movies Skyfall and Spectre, is worried about the future of the franchise in the wake of Amazon’s purchase of MGM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George P. Bush launches run for TX attorney general...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/02/politics/george-p-bush-texas-attorney-general/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Land Commissioner George P. Bush announced Wednesday night that he's running for attorney general in Texas, setting up a GOP showdown with one of the most high-profile Republican attorneys general in the country, Ken Paxton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why now?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/why-are-we-all-talking-about-u-f-o-s-right-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When spooky things appear in the sky, witnesses have often been reluctant to report them for fear of mockery by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10,000 volunteers drop out; Tokyo Olympics open in 50 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-health-coronavirus-pandemic-olympic-games-2020-tokyo-olympics-e7350e3562f420ef35f51b71b558aa8e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The countdown clock for the Tokyo Olympics hit 50-days-to-go on Thursday, and the day also brought another problem for the delayed games. About 10,000 of 80,000 unpaid volunteers for the Tokyo Olympics and Paralympics have told organizers they will not participate when the games open on July 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uyghur exiles describe forced abortions, torture in Xinjiang...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-middle-east-europe-government-and-politics-76acafd6547fb7cc9ef03c0dd0156eab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Three Uyghurs who fled from China to Turkey have described forced abortions and torture by Chinese authorities in China’s far western Xinjiang region, ahead of giving testimony to a people’s tribunal in London that is investigating if Beijing’s actions against ethnic Uyghurs amount to genocide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming UFO report to Congress creating lots of buzz...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/upcoming-ufo-report-congress-creating-lots-buzz/story?id=78017649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly-anticipated U.S. government report on UFOs is set to come out later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds investigating obstruction as part of Gaetz probe, sources say...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/03/politics/feds-investigating-obstruction-gaetz-probe/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is investigating potential obstruction of justice connected to the ongoing probe of Rep. Matt Gaetz and his alleged sexual relationship with a minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundy Gov Run Has Some Bracing for Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/far-right-vigilante-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98alarming-e2-80-99-gubernatorial-run-has-some-bracing-for-chaos/ar-AAKF2Ei </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MEAT HACK SHAKES GLOBE...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jbs-plants-limp-back-hack-223525704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- JBS SA workers returning to a meat-processing plant in Texas on Wednesday afternoon were told to be ready to do things a bit differently than normal: Work by hand.With everything from knife sharpening to production-line speed controls relying on automation, coming back from a cyberattack that forced the world’s largest meat producer to halt operations across the globe is set to be a bumpy ride. Because the plants are coming back online without some of their systems in service, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Wants to Bring Back Supersonic Air Travel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/united-airlines-wants-to-bring-back-supersonic-air-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The era of supersonic commercial flights came to an end when the Concorde completed its last trip between New York</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought ravages CA reservoirs ahead of hot summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/california-droughts-government-and-politics-science-business-76709d5854394905e0f46880ed6dab9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OROVILLE, Calif. (AP) — Each year Lake Oroville helps water a quarter of the nation’s crops, sustain endangered salmon beneath its massive earthen dam and anchor the tourism economy of a Northern California county that must rebuild seemingly every year after unrelenting wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report examines misinformation on Miami Spanish talk radio...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/up-is-down-and-down-is-up-report-examines-misinformation-on-miami-spanish-talk-radio/ar-AAKDYlb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Thousands of dead people and noncitizens voted in the 2020 presidential election. There were more votes cast than registered voters. Black Lives Matter and Antifa infiltrated the deadly storming of the U.S. Capitol. Doctors Without Borders, which closed its COVID-19 treatment center last year after three months because of low use, said it has not decided whether to reopen. Those are ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging herd of elephants cause chaos as they plough through city of 7 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9647679/Rampaging-herd-15-elephants-cause-chaos-plough-Chinese-city-7-million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rampaging herd of 15 elephants have reached the outskirts of Kunming, the capital of the Yunnan province, after breaking out of a nature reserve in Xishuangbanna Dai prefecture on April 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Stock Craze Reaches New Heights...</title>
      <link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/markets/amc-stock-extends-surge-as-reddit-s-retail-frenzy-reaches-new-heights-121060300697_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie-theater chain has a market value of more than $30 billion, making it more valuable than at least half of the companies in the S&amp;P 500 Index.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Prices Decade High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/global-food-prices-surge-highest-080152199.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global food prices extended their rally to the highest in almost a decade, heightening concerns over bulging grocery bills as economies struggle to exit the Covid-19 crisis.A United Nations gauge of world food costs climbed for a 12th straight month in May, its longest stretch in a decade. The continued advance risks accelerating broader inflation, complicating central banks efforts to provide more stimulus.Drought in key Brazilian growing regions is crippling crops from corn to c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR Therapy Plunges Patients Back Into Trauma. Some Swear by It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/03/virtual-reality-therapy-plunges-patients-back-into-trauma-here-is-why-some-swear-by-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a Veterans Affairs therapist first suggested that Chris Merkle try a virtual reality simulation that would mimic his days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's largest warship catches fire, sinks in Gulf of Oman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-tensions-middle-east-iran-business-evacuations-f3e8126a8603326e1abc4705c6629fcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — The largest warship in the Iranian navy caught fire and later sank Wednesday in the Gulf of Oman under unclear circumstances, the latest calamity to strike one of the country’s vessels in recent years amid tensions with the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Covid shock has radicalized Generation Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/02/how-the-covid-shock-has-radicalised-generation-z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: young people’s testimonies show they are ready to draw systemic conclusions from the handling of the pandemic by political elites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microwave weapons that could cause Havana Syndrome exist, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/02/microwave-weapons-havana-syndrome-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia and possibly China have developed technology capable of injuring brain and a US company made a prototype in 2004</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ends blog after 29 days, infuriated by measly readershipy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ends-blog-after-29-days-infuriated-by-measly-readership/ar-AAKDOuj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infuriated by reports highlighting its measly viewership, Trump ordered his team Tuesday to put the blog out of its misery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure mounts on Manchin as 'panic' sets in among Dems over voting rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pressure-mounts-on-Manchin-over-voting-rights-16218859.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Democratic leaders and activists are urgently stepping up pressure on Sen....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York subway system was targeted...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/556598-new-york-subway-system-was-targeted-by-chinese-linked-hackers-in-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s subway system was targeted by hackers with links to the Chinese government in April, according to an MTA document</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD HIGH:  Pot Producers Pushing to Clamp Down on Delta-8 THC...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/pot-producers-are-pushing-to-clamp-down-on-delta-8-thc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A little-known substance derived from hemp is flying off the shelves of U.S. gas stations and smoke shops. Delta-8, almost chemically identical to federally outlawed forms of marijuana, has escaped widespread scrutiny thanks to ambiguity in U.S. law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden targets crypto tax evaders in global data-sharing pitch...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-tax-report/biden-targets-crypto-tax-evaders-in-global-data-sharing-pitch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has proposed requiring the collection of data on foreign cryptocurrency investors active in the U.S., aiming to bolster international cooperation to help in a broader crackdown on tax evasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA will launch 2 new missions to Venus by 2030...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/nasa-unveils-2-venus-missions-veritas-davinci</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After decades without a NASA mission, it's Venus' time to shine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 2 Apples A Day Keeps Diabetes Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/2-servings-of-fruit-diabetes-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People consuming 2 servings of fruit daily display higher levels of insulin sensitivity in comparison to those eating less than half a serving each day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. troops mistakenly stormed olive oil factory in Bulgaria...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/u-s-troops-mistakenly-stormed-cooking-oil-factory-in-bulgaria/ar-AAKE4nM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They cooked up an international incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC could wait weeks for mayoral primary results...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/york-city-wait-weeks-ranked-choice-mayoral-primary/story?id=78029551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baffert banned from Churchill Downs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/02/churchill-downs-suspends-bob-baffert-for-2-years-as-kentucky-derby-winner-medina-spirit-fails-2nd-drug-test.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to teach university course on Mueller investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mueller-university-course-investigation-uva-trump-1f267e6e-ff90-4610-80c0-edee4d30f74b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller will be involved in the course alongside others who worked with him during the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Nearly Half Of Americans Think Dinosaurs STILL Roam Earth!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/half-americans-think-dinosaurs-still-on-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-four percent also believe all dinosaurs only lived in Africa and North America – unaware that scientists have unearthed their bones all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fink Sees for 'Big Shock' From Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/economy/blackrock-ceo-larry-fink-sees-potential-for-big-shock-from-inflation-2521528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BlackRock CEO Larry Fink Sees Potential for ‘Big Shock’ From Inflation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha's Vineyard route disrupted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/02/business/steamship-authority-ransomware-attack/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ransomware attack has disrupted ferry services in Cape Cod, Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE diversity chief said Jews have 'insatiable appetite for war'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/google-pr-flack-flags-diversity-chiefs-private-apology-for-anti-semitic-remarks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google’s global diversity leader apologized privately on Tuesday night to the company's Jewish employees for a blog post in which he argued that Jews have an “insatiable appetite for war," but the tech company remains mum on the controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CITIZEN: The public safety app pushing surveillance boundaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/citizen-public-safety-app-pushing-surveillance-boundaries-rcna1058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The smartphone app Citizen describes itself in simple terms: a safety network that sends alerts about nearby incidents including crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would-be Reagan killer rebrands himself as singer-songwriter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/02/would-be-reagan-killer-john-hinckley-rebrands-self-as-singer-songwriter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Hinckley won a lengthy court battle last year, freeing him to publicly display his music, writings and other art, and potentially make a living in the recording industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King County, WA first in country to ban facial recognition software...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/king-county-is-first-in-the-country-to-ban-facial-recognition-software</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King County became the first county in the country to ban government use of facial recognition software. Supporters applaud the newly approved ban on facial recognition software. They said this is a big win for civil rights and privacy. Those worried about facial recognition software say Blacks, Asians, and Latinos are often misidentified by the software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools falling into disrepair...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/america-s-schools-are-falling-disrepair-no-solution-sight-experts-n1269261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It really is a national tragedy when you start looking at these schools and understand what kids are subjected to," said an environmental engineer for the Philadelphia teachers union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High vitamin D levels do NOT protect against virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210602171255-5nuat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHICS):COVID SCIENCE-Virus does not threaten U.S. blood supply; high vitamin D levels do not protect against COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privately tells lawmakers not to expect much on reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/02/biden-reparations-tulsa-491607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president weighed in on race relations more bluntly than any of his predecessors during his speech Tuesday. But he also set expectations low for congressional action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary DUKE coach Krzyzewski retiring...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mens-college-basketball/story/_/id/31553654/duke-blue-devils-coach-mike-krzyzewski-plans-leave-season-leave-next-season-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hall of Fame coach Mike Krzyzewski, who has led Duke to five national titles in his 40 seasons with the Blue Devils, plans to retire after the 2021-2022 men's college basketball season, sources confirmed to ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In tit-for-tat move, Germany blocks Russian airlines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/germany-russia-europe-airlines-business-4647a2173775262d17e0dc2fca15b064</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany has denied Russian airlines permission to use its airspace after Moscow failed to approve a Lufthansa flight to Russia, German officials said Wednesday. In a statement, Germany’s Transport Ministry said the decision was based on the practice of reciprocal approval of flights, and affected connections operated by Aeroflot and budget carrier S7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Pandemic turned us into barbarians...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/culture/sports/1001080/the-pandemic-turned-us-into-barbarians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER Hit with Fine from FEC over Buying and Killing Story from Mistress...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/01/national-enquirer-hit-with-187k-fine-from-federal-election-commission-over-buying-and-killing-story-from-trump-mistress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember when the National Enquirer was doing Donald Trump’s dirty work? Well, they’ve just been fined $187,000 by the Federal Election Commission for buying and killing a tell all by f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts ferry operator hit by ransomware attack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/local/mass-steamship-authority-delayed-due-to-cyber-attack/2477951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ransomware attack on the Steamship Authority of Massachusetts hampered operations Wednesday morning. The largest ferry service to the islands of Martha’s Vineyard and Nantucket, the Steamship Authority issued a statement warning that traveling customers may be delayed as a result. A “team of IT professionals” is working to assess the impact of the cyber attack, according to the Authority. No further information…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China threatens USA with 'intense nuclear showdown'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15140218/china-threatens-us-intense-nuclear-showdown-atomic-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has threatened the United States with an “intense nuclear showdown” as it ramps up its atomic program. The Chinese Communist Party’s mouthpiece newspaper launched a blisteri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Greenwald 'New Master of Right-Wing Media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/is-glenn-greenwald-the-new-master-of-right-wing-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leftist scribe has become “a practitioner of manufactured controversy” for outlets like Fox News, say his stunned former colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3-year-old piano prodigy to perform at Carnegie Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/piano-prodigy-practices-for-carnegie-hall-performance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brigitte Xie's piano talent has earned her a spot on stage at Carnegie Hall this fall. She will likely be the youngest person on stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proof of aliens would lead to new religions and massive military spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/proof-aliens-lead-new-religions-24235493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former US president says many people’s religious beliefs will change if it’s ever proved alien life does exist – and there’ll be calls for huge amounts to be spent on arming ourselves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CITIZEN: The public safety app pushing surveillance boundaries...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/E241fA5UcAAGMLd?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Vows One Last Film!</title>
      <link>https://moviemaker.com/quentin-tarantino-most-directors-have-horrible-last-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino has long promised that his tenth movie will be his last, and he said in a podcast released Tuesday that he hopes to avoid the common director curse of going out with a “horrible” film. In an interview on Tuesday’s episode of the Pure Cinema Podcast with Elric Kane and Brian Saur, the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Stand your ground' defense rejected in iguana killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/stand-your-ground-defense-rejected-in-iguana-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has rejected the “stand your ground” defense of a Florida man who said he beat an iguana to death only after it attacked him, biting him on the arm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod shark detections surging as researchers tag more: 118 great whites!</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2021/05/31/cape-cod-shark-detections-rising-as-researchers-tag-more-118-great-whites-detected-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of great white sharks detected along the Cape has ballooned over the last few years as researchers continue to tag more of the apex predators each summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC 5TH ELECTION?!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-change-government-deadline-oust-netanyahu-cf0fd3c2-9b4d-448d-b165-8fae8afc55aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel hasn't had a new prime minister since 2009.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
