<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Race-Based Tax Rates the Next Step?</title>
      <link>https://www.nysun.com/new-york/could-tax-code-be-used-to-make-us-reparations/91467/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nysun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could a racial priority for getting a Covid-19 vaccine turn out to be just the first stop on the way to race-based tax rates? A tax bill that varies depending on the taxpayer's race might strike readers as some law professor's remote fantasy, far from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Tragic Mediocrity of U.S. Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/04/09/congress-mediocrity-politics-480472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leaders and reprobates in Congress might get the headlines, but the real story lies in its boring, unimpressive middle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slots Go Unused in Mississippi and Other States...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/vaccine-slots-go-unused-in-mississippi-and-other-states/ar-BB1fsP7g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Correction: April 8, 2021 This article has been revised to reflect the following correction: An earlier version of this article misspelled the surname of a former director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. He is Dr. Thomas Frieden, no Friedan. When it comes to getting the coronavirus vaccine, Mississippi residents have an abundance of options. On Thursday, there were more than 73,000 slots to be had on the state’s scheduling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYPILLOW Lindell Claims He Has Private Investigators Looking at FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/mypillow-ceo-mike-lindell-claims-he-has-private-investigators-looking-at-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MyPillow CEO Mike Lindell claimed Friday he has hired private investigators looking at "everything," including who's behind "the bots and trolls" and even Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deshaun Watson DID have sex with massage therapists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9455315/Deshaun-Watson-DID-sex-massage-therapists-attorney-says-consensual.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deshaun Watson did have sexual encounters with some of his massage therapists, but they were all consensual, his attorney said as his client faces sexual misconduct lawsuits from 22 different women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA considering cash payments to Central America to stem migration...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-immigration-border/exclusive-us-considering-cash-payments-to-central-america-to-stem-migration-idUSL1N2M22DY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is considering a conditional cash transfer program to help address economic woes that lead migrants from certain Central American countries to trek north, as well as sending COVID-19 vaccines to those countries, a senior White House official told Reuters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ash five miles high...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/04/09/st-vincent-volcano-la-soufriere-erupts-as-caribbean-island-evacuated-14384326/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The volcano has now moved into an 'explosive state', with thousands of lives at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive eruption rocks volcano on Caribbean island... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/puerto-rico-caribbean-volcanic-eruptions-latin-america-evacuations-1430a41cbaa02f20222b6b3e37dc2c05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico (AP) — An explosive eruption rocked La Soufriere volcano on the eastern Caribbean island of St. Vincent on Friday after the government ordered thousands to evacuate their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands forced into prostitution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-global-trade-mexico-coronavirus-pandemic-caribbean-69ed9611a08b8973e59841c7120cc9e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Hardships caused by the coronavirus pandemic have forced former sex workers in Mexico back into the trade years after they left, made it more dangerous and reduced some to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime reporter's murder shocks Greece...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210409-crime-reporter-s-murder-shocks-greece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crime reporter's murder shocks Greece</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsrooms facing mental health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/journalism-burnout-mental-health-crisis-2021-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As some journalists head for the exits, citing burnout, newsroom leaders are attempting to put in place mental health safeguards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA trial opens window on secretive leader's life and work...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-dallas-trials-bahamas-gun-politics-6961ee94222eb28e788030d4f9461f61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — Wayne LaPierre flies exclusively on private jets, he sailed around the Bahamas for “security” and he never sends emails or texts in the course of his work running the nation's most...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who coughed on cancer patient gets 30 days in jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/florida-woman-who-coughed-cancer-patient-gets-30-days-jail-n1263627</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge in Jacksonville ordered Debra Hunter to pay a $500 fine, serve six months probation and participate in a mental health evaluation along with anger management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's homicides soar. Police use socials to plead for calm...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/think-before-you-shoot-atlanta-police-turn-to-social-media-as-gun-violence-surges/BWMSPUX2SRHIDGGNXADB6JFYBM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Atlanta’s homicide cases mount, the police department has taken a unique approach in its effort to curb gun violence across the city: pleading with residents not to shoot anyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House inches closer to enacting slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/9/house-inches-closer-enacting-slavery-reparations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill that could lead to slavery reparations took a major step forward Friday when the House Judiciary Committee scheduled it for a debate and vote next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY Has Now Deleted 42 Episodes of 'JOE ROGAN EXPERIENCE' Podcast...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/spotify-deletes-joe-rogan-podcast-episodes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spotify has now deleted more than 40 podcast episodes of "The Joe Rogan Experience" after recently removing two more from its service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER requests clearance to jab 12-year-olds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/pfizer-requests-fda-clearance-vaccine-kids-ages-12-15-n1263649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move would make Pfizer's vaccine available to the widest age range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon cop charged with murder after killing 2...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/montgomery-county/2021/04/pentagon-officer-charged-with-murder-in-takoma-park-shooting-that-left-2-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Takoma Park police have arrested and charged the off-duty Pentagon Force Protection Agency officer they say shot and killed two men Wednesday morning in Montgomery County, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Using Facial Recognition More Than Previously Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/04/09/cops-are-using-facial-recognition-technology-more-than-previously-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surveillance state is available as a plug-and-play solution for any cop interested in a free trial period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NFL star had meds taken away  before killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2666277/nfl-phillip-adams-meds-cut-off-killing-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EX-NFL star Phillip Adams had reportedly just had his meds taken away by his doctor victim before going on a killing spree that left five dead. Adams fatally shot Dr Robert Lesslie, 70, his wife, B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING 737 MAX Jets Grounded Again!</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/04/09/boeing-737-max-electrical-issue-grounds-planes-american-southwest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a little like déjà vu, on Friday Boeing recommended that more than one-dozen of its customers take some of their planes out of service because of a potential electrical issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hip-hop icon had 5 #1s...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/dmx-dead-hip-hop-legend-belly-exit-wounds-actor-1234731131/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DMX, the first hip-hop artist ever to top the charts with his initial five albums and almost his sixth, has died. He was 50. Born Earl Simmons, the rapper and actor suffered a heart attack on April…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Timberlake To Play Chuck Barris In TV Series...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/justin-timberlake-chuck-barris-apple-tv-series-auction-gong-show-host-cia-assassin-confessions-of-a-dangerous-mind-1234731030/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Eager to bring Justin Timberlake back into the Apple TV + fold after the strong results of the Fisher Stevens-directed dramatic film Palmer in January, Apple won an auction and acquired …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don has NO plans for presidential library...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/politics/trump-presidential-library/2021/04/05/id/1016333/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is spending his first months as an ex-president trying to ensure that he's remembered the way he wants - but he's holding off on plans to establish a library that would enshrine his version of his presidency...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major win for e-commerce giant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/amazon-appears-to-have-the-votes-to-overcome-union-effort-a-major-win-for-the-e-commerce-giant/ar-BB1ftCv5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The closely watched vote, which involved thousands of workers at a Bessemer, Ala., warehouse, will probably face challenges at the National Labor Relations Board and in court that could delay the final outcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How California snared 2 elite hunters posting kills on social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/how-california-snared-2-elite-hunters-posting-kills-on-social-media/ar-BB1fs3yX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — Joe Frater and Chris Stone were on their way to social media stardom in the elite world of trophy deer hunting. The two law enforcement officers — Frater is a corrections officer at a local prison; Stone is an investigator for the Amador County district attorney — regularly showed off their trophies from just a few years of hunting with bows and arrows in the Sierra ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pair of interstate truckers accused of kidnapping women...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/truckers-accused-of-kidnapping-women-along-i-95-in-nj-other-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Agents with the Federal Bureau of Investigation say two truckers have been arrested for kidnapping and physically assaulting women in Georgia and New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 3,600 US health workers died in covid first year...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/us-health-workers-deaths-covid-lost-on-the-frontline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lost on the Frontline, a yearlong investigation by The Guardian and KHN to count health care worker deaths, ends today. This is what we learned in a year of tracing the lives of those who made the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Bowl Sets July Reopening!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/hollywood-bowl-reopening-july-covid-concerts-1234731070/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For fans of the Hollywood Bowl, the lack-of-shell shock is nearly over. After being closed for more than a year, the storied venue said today that it will reopen in July for 14 weeks of concerts wi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NFL star had meds taken away  before killing spree...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2666277/nfl-phillip-adams-meds-cut-off-killing-spree/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EX-NFL star Phillip Adams had reportedly just had his meds taken away by his doctor victim before going on a killing spree that left five dead. Adams fatally shot Dr Robert Lesslie, 70, his wife, B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought he was in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/golf/2021/04/08/tiger-woods-crash-report-reveals-clues-his-condition-day/7151217002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods thought he was in Florida when interviewed by a deputy at a Los Angeles County hospital right after his crash in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Heart Failure, Stroke Cases On Rise In Men Under 40...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/heart-failure-stroke-men-under-40/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research also discovered a link between higher rates of cardiovascular disease and obesity or low fitness levels as a teenager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: DISNEY makes pick for next ABCNEWS president...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/disney-makes-its-pick-next-abc-news-president-n1263584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Godwin, the executive vice president of CBS News, looks set to become the first Black woman to lead a broadcast news division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: NASA prepares for first helicopter flight on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/09/nasa-helicopter-mars-479768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's plan to launch the Ingenuity on Sunday has been decades in the making, says Robert Hogg, the deputy surface mission manager for the Mars 2020 program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant Devastating Brazil Spreading in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9453651/Brazil-coronavirus-variant-second-common-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now at least 434 cases of Brazil's P1 variant, which is capable of reinfecting COVID-19 survivors, in the U.S., according to Centers for Disease Control and Prevention tracking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Pelosi's war with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/politics/2021/04/09/bracing-battle-inside-nancy-pelosis-war-donald-trump/7053833002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The election she thought would be the end of her career became the beginning of its most consequential chapter: Defying a 'scary' president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's biggest boom since 1946?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/global-economy-boom-growth-100e317f-2c0e-4465-8c18-2b13c2c1353d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The years-long economic boom is likely to be a global phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA hitting vaccine wall?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-coronavirus-vaccines-republicans-rural-states-34755cbf-384e-4539-bb45-68a775581f6f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people who are eager for a vaccine is shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top court orders probe of Bolsonaro pandemic steps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-brazil-judiciary-coronavirus-pandemic-sao-paulo-31decb098c1058ca0862b1894270ca90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO (AP) — A Brazilian Supreme Court justice ordered the Senate on Thursday to investigate the government's handling of the coronavirus crisis and the full court ruled that churches can be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US warships to deploy in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-usa-turkey/turkey-says-u-s-warships-to-deploy-in-black-sea-until-may-4-idUSKBN2BW1HV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has informed Turkey that two of its warships will pass through Turkish straits to be deployed in the Black Sea until May 4, Ankara said on Friday, as Russia has bulked up its military forces on Ukraine's eastern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans next...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/09/elon-musks-neuralink-shows-video-of-monkey-using-mind-to-play-pong.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neuralink, the brain machine interface company founded by Tesla CEO Elon Musk, has published a video of a monkey playing the video game Pong with its mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Attacks DUNKIN' Clerk With Tip Jar When Asked To Cover Face...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/04/08/dunkin-employee-attacked-tip-jar-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dunkin’ store served up a chaotic scene recently when police said a customer attacked a worker after being asked to put on a face mask.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Americans Infected With Variant Devastating Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/brazilian-p1-coronavirus-variant-has-infected-hundreds-of-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The P1 variant that was first identified in Brazil is now the second most prevalent in the United States, with at least 434 people having been infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How monkeys made more friends after their island was devastated by hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/offbeat/puerto-rico-exeter-pennsylvania-hurricane-maria-exeter-university-b1828619</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rhesus macaques living in Cayo Santiago also became more tolerant of each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Warns Risk of Broader Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/kremlin-says-ukraine-s-actions-raise-risk-of-broader-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin Warns of Risk of Broader War in Ukraine Conflict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE PHILIP DEAD AT WINDSOR CASTLE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14207808/prince-philip-dead-duke-edinburgh-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Philip has died aged 99, Buckingham Palace announced today. The Duke of Edinburgh, who had been married to the Queen for 73 years and described as her constant strength, passed away “p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Migration: Moving to Cities While Others Flee...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/09/reverse-migration-moving-to-cities-while-others-flee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly Shoul and Alex White spent years trying to get out of their house in York, Pa., only to be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Your Illegal Drugs Pure? New Zealand Will Check for You...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/09/are-your-illegal-drugs-pure-new-zealand-will-check-them-for-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand — New Zealand has enshrined into law a one-year experiment allowing drug users to have illegal substances</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New footage captures 'pyramid UFOs swarming Navy destroyer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/astonishing-new-footage-captures-pyramid-23882803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amazing video and collection of photos of a "spherical" craft swarming a US Navy destroyer were allegedly part of a classified briefing conducted to "de-stigmatise the UAP problem"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch monkey with Musk's brain chip play video games with mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/elon-musks-neuralink-reveals-monkey-playing-pong-with-brain-implant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Neuralink video shows nine-year-old Macaque playing the classic video game... using a brain-implant device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will take plea deal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/matt-gaetz-associate-to-take-plea-deal-in-sex-trafficking-case-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg, an associate of embattled GOP Congressman Matt Gaetz, is expected to take a plea deal in his own sex-trafficking case — and cooperate with federal authorities, according to re…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST:  Gaetz Paid Accused Sex Trafficker, Who Then Venmo'd Teen...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gaetz-paid-accused-sex-trafficker-who-then-venmod-teen?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>56%  Say Pandemic Ruined Their Sex Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/2020-pandemic-stress-ruined-sex-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;56 percent experienced performance anxiety or concerns their sexual performance might not meet their partners wants, needs, or expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DICK VAN DYKE AT 95:  I DON'T KNOW HOW I DID IT!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/04/08/exclusive-dick-van-dyke-95-on-his-kennedy-center-honor-i-never-thought-id-live-this-long-i-dont-know-how-i-did-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dick van Dyke — of the towering performers of our lives — is thrilled and surprised to receive a Kennedy Center honor this June. He’s only 95. (It should have been 20 years ago at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Bar Slammed After Requiring Proof Of Vaccination...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/07/denver-bar-max-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bar Max in Denver is now open after being closed for much of the pandemic. Patrons can enjoy a cocktail inside only if they provide proof of vaccination.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
