<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New genetic data bodes well for comeback condors...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210513-new-genetic-data-bodes-well-for-california-s-comeback-condors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New genetic data bodes well for California's comeback condors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTAGE FOR WEEKS</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/05/12/colonial-pipeline-hack-shutdown-gas-outages-refuel/5065013001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial Pipeline will likely resume over the next two days, but consumers may have to wait longer in line, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists bring to life 100 baby sharks through artificial insemination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/13/world/baby-sharks-artificial-insemination-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists were able to use artificial insemination to bring 97 baby sharks to life, according to a new study, in what its release describes as the "largest-ever effort to artificially inseminate sharks."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTAGE CONTINUES</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2021/05/gas-shortage-continues-as-colonial-restarts-pipeline-operations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that Colonial has restarted its pipeline operations after a cybersecurity attack, it will be a few days before things return to normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD Wants Billboards to Beam Distracting Ads to Screens Inside Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7bnz7/ford-wants-billboards-to-beam-distracting-ads-to-screens-inside-your-car</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company's recently-patented idea for in-car advertising sounds like a disaster waiting to happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Surveilling Americans Without a Warrant, Senator Reveals...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88ng8x/pentagon-americans-surveillance-without-warrant-internet-browsing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A letter obtained by Motherboard discusses internet browsing, location, and other forms of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF calls up reservists...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/israeli-ground-offensive-in-gaza-on-table-as-rocket-barrages-continue-668048</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocket barrage comes as IDF prepares for possible ground invasion of the Gaza Strip. Plans are to be presented on Thursday to Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress auctioning NFT about her vagina...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/cara-delevingne-vagina-nft-1234952715/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cara Delevingne is … well … there’s no other way to phrase it. Yes, the Suicide Squad and Carnival Row actress-model is taking the burgeoning NFT content marketplace to someplace …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$7 A GALLON IN VA</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-hits-7-in-virginia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers were shocked when they got to the pump at a gas station in Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic tremors hit White House at crucial moment for  policy agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/economic-tremors-hit-white-house-at-crucial-moment-for-biden-policy-agenda/ar-B1gE8bD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine Major detained for participating in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/13/capitol-riot-us-marine-major-warnagiris-arrested-for-role-in-trump-mob.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine is the latest person charged in the U.S. Capitol riot on Jan. 6, which occurred after President Donald Trump urged supporters to march to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is 'Black Fungus' Spreading Among India's Patients?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2021/05/13/996488271/what-is-black-fungus-and-why-is-it-spreading-among-indias-covid-patients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors say India's battle with COVID-19 has led to an unprecedented rise in mucormycosis, a rare but dangerous fungal infection that preys on people with weakened immune systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC To Ease Indoor Mask-Wearing Guidance For Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/05/13/cdc-ease-indoor-mask-wearing-guidance-fully-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on Thursday will ease indoor mask-wearing guidance for fully vaccinated people, allowing them to safely stop wearing masks inside in most places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK 'anxious' over rise of variant...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-health-b78232d5f4081d37ff7fe2bb2dce7f17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson said Thursday he was “anxious” about a rise in the U.K. of the coronavirus variant first identified in India, after a closely-monitored study of infections in England found the variant is becoming more prevalent just ahead of the next big easing of lockdown restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz associate expected to plead guilty in case that spawned sex-trafficking investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/matt-gaetz-associate-expected-plead-guilty-case-spawned-sex-trafficking-n1267258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plea change indicates the associate, Joel Greenberg, is going to cooperate with the government, but it's unclear what that means for the investigation of Gaetz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FRIENDS' reunion releases teaser trailer; Gaga, Bieber to guest star...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/friends-reunion-trailer-hbo-1234952671/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first trailer for the Friends reunion special is here. Below is the first footage from HBO Max’s long-awaited reunion of the cast of the iconic NBC comedy series, along with a premiere da…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online, mug shots are forever. Some states want to change that...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/online-mug-shots-forever-states-181700675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;May 10—After a weekend in the Burleigh County, North Dakota, detention center last summer, Dustin Gawrylow was relieved when the state's attorney decided not to press charges against him. Gawrylow, 38, had been in a fistfight with his brother—a "brotherly scuffle," he called it—and was surprised to be arrested after going to the police to explain what happened. But even though his charges ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army releases recruitment advertisement featuring lesbian wedding...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/army-releases-recruitment-advertisement-featuring-lesbian-wedding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army released an animated advertisement featuring a girl raised by two mothers, who marched in pride parades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia mayor reelected 2 days after arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/west-virginia-mayor-reelected-2-days-after-arrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A southern West Virginia mayor has been reelected despite facing criminal charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic tremors hit White House at crucial moment for  policy agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/economic-tremors-hit-white-house-at-crucial-moment-for-biden-policy-agenda/ar-BB1gE8bD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration and Federal Reserve have waved off fears of out-of-control inflation, saying that bumps in prices will be temporary and won’t pulse through the whole economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Taxes, Spending, and Deficit Continue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-taxes-spending-and-deficit-all-set-records-through-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal taxes, spending and the federal deficit all set records through the first seven months of fiscal 2021 (October through April), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish, Arab Neighbors Turn On Each Other...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/israel-palestine-hamas-religious-violence-streets-2021-05-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As tit-for-tat bombing by Israel's military and Palestinian militants in Gaza takes a mounting toll, violence is also flaring up in Israeli cities in a way that's new, and worrying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami News Crew Attacked -- While Covering Rise In South Beach Violence!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/05/12/cbs4-crew-attacked-south-beach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortunately, CBS4 Reporter Bobeth Yates and Photojournalist Ebenezer Mends are OK.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Facing White-Knuckle Summer With Power in Short Supply...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-west-facing-white-knuckle-111527363.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- First they struck California, then Texas. Now blackouts are threatening the entire U.S. West as nearly a dozen states head into summer with too little electricity.From New Mexico to Washington, power grids are being strained by forces years in the making — some of them fueled by climate change, others by the fight against it. If a heat wave strikes the whole region at once, the rolling outages that darkened Southern California and Silicon Valley last August will have been previews, not flukes.“It’s really the same case in different parts of the West,” said Elliot Mainzer, chief executive officer of the California Independent System Operator, which runs most of the state’s grid. “It’s revealed competition for scarce resources that we haven’t seen for some time.”The specter of blackouts highlights a paradox of the clean-energy transition: Extreme weather fueled by climate change is exposing cracks in society’s move away from fossil fuels, even as that shift is supposed to rein in the worst of global warming. States shuttering coal and gas-fired power plants simply aren’t replacing them fast enough to keep pace with the vagaries of an unstable climate, and the region’s existing power infrastructure is woefully vulnerable to wildfires (which threaten transmission lines), drought (which saps once-abundant hydropower resources) and heat waves (which play havoc with demand).On Wednesday, California's grid managers warned that while they're better positioned than last summer, the risk of power shortages during extreme heat remains a clear possibility. For many, California’s power crisis in 2020 was the first indication of how serious the regional power shortfall had become. While the blackouts highlighted the state’s reliance on solar power — a resource that ebbs in the evening just as demand picks up — an equally significant problem was California’s dependence on imported electricity. Utilities routinely source power supplies from out of state, drawing electricity across high-voltage transmission lines to wherever it’s needed. But last summer, neighboring states coping with the same heat wave as California were straining to keep their own lights on, and imports were hard to come by.This year, that dynamic is playing out on a larger scale. Across the West, states have grown dependent on importing power from one another. That works fine in temperate weather, when electricity demand is relatively low. But it's a problem when a widespread heatwave blankets the entire region. The Western Electricity Coordinating Council, which oversees electricity grids throughout the western U.S. and Canada, estimates that without imports, Nevada, Utah and Colorado could be short of power during hundreds of hours this year, or the equivalent of 34 days. Arizona and New Mexico could be short for enough hours to total 17 days, according to a report by the organization that looked at worst-case scenarios to help states develop plans to head off potential outages.“It’s no longer necessarily a California problem or a Phoenix problem,” said Jordan White, vice president of strategic engagement for the group, known as WECC. “Everyone is chasing the same number of megawatts.” While blackouts aren’t a guarantee in any region, traders are already betting on supply shortages and sending power prices soaring throughout the West. At the heavily traded Palo Verde hub in Arizona, prices have nearly quadrupled since last summer’s outages, while the Pacific Northwest’s Mid-Columbia hub has tripled.“We are already seeing record-breaking prices across the West, some of which can be attributed to a fear factor being priced in,” said JP McMahon, a market associate for Wood Mackenzie. “Last year was a bit of a wake-up call.”The reasons behind the shortfall are two-fold: Climate change is making it harder to forecast demand for electricity while the shift to clean energy is straining power supplies.Where utilities and grid managers were once able to rely on predictable consumption patterns season to season — more air conditioner use in August, less in October — they’re now reckoning with record-hot summers and historic winter storms that cause great, unexpected surges in demand.“It’s becoming challenging to take out the crystal ball to know with any level of certainty how hot it it’s going to be,” White said.At the same time, older coal and gas plants capable of providing power 24 hours a day are being pushed out by climate change regulations and their own dwindling profitability. In the West, power generation from such plants slipped 6% from 2010 through 2018, according to WECC. While wind and solar capacity have more than tripled in the region, the output from those resources varies by the hour, making them harder to rely on during an unexpected demand crunch. Massive batteries can help make up the difference, but their installation is just beginning.It’s a global phenomenon. Sweden this summer is bracing for power outages and curbing electricity exports after nuclear retirements have left the country with too little spare capacity to balance big swings in demand. In China last winter, even a surplus of coal plants couldn’t keep the lights on during a severe cold blast.At this point, no subregion in WECC’s coverage area generates enough electricity to meet its own needs during periods of high demand; they all rely on imports to avoid outages.In the aftermath of the California crisis, utilities have been signing up contracts for more emergency power supplies and are trying to make sure they aren’t relying on the same suppliers as everyone else. Some entities, including the Imperial Irrigation District of Southern California are working to curb their reliance on imports. But it’s not clear that all utilities in the highest-risk areas plan to do much differently. The situation is, if not dire, getting close. Temperatures in the West are expected to be above average through the summer, with the worst heat slamming the Southwest. More than 84% of land in the 11 Western states is gripped by drought.Following last summer’s outages, California is among the best positioned going into summer. The state is plugging roughly 1,500 megawatts of batteries into the grid, has postponed the retirement of several aging gas plants and raised the price cap on power trades to incentivize imports if outside supplies are necessary and available. Even if imports are readily available for those that need them, there’s no guarantee that transmission lines will be able to carry those electrons where they need to go. Extreme weather can take out the high-voltage conduits that stitch the Western states together, and wildfires are notorious for knocking out transmission lines. Although it received little attention at the time, a major transmission line in the Pacific Northwest that suffered damage in a storm last spring limited power flows into California throughout the summer energy crisis.Energy consultant Mike Florio, who used to sit on the board of California’s grid operator, said other states can learn from the West’s dilemma. They should keep a variety of resources as they decarbonize, learning how to balance the daily rhythms of solar and wind, and not move too quickly to shutter old gas-burning plants that can provide power in a pinch.“We forget that we’re still learning a lot about how to run a system like this,” Florio said. “We probably want to keep our existing gas capacity, at least in reserve. It may be used less, but something that’s already built is cheap insurance.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops massing on Gaza border...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14940373/forces-neutralise-hamas-terror-group-rockets-bomb-israel/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL has deployed tanks and troops to the Gaza border and is threatening to INVADE after rejecting Hamas’ calls for a ceasefire. Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has dismissed the calls fo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Floridians prosecuted for bareface will be PARDONED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2878069/florida-residents-prosecuted-not-covid-masks-pardoned-desantis/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOVERNOR Ron DeSantis will pardon all Floridians that have been prosecuted for failing to wear a face covering or socially distance, he announced last night. The Republican appeared on Fox News’ &amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeGeneres says instincts, not controversy, driving decision to end talk show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/tv/ellen-degeneres-says-instincts-not-controversy-driving-her-decision-end-n1267188</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If it was why I was quitting, I would have not come back this year," she said of allegations last year of a toxic workplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once again finds herself at center of cultural change...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/ellen-degeneres-departing-syndicated-tv-once-again-finds-herself-center-n1267168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: The talk show host symbolized important social shifts in the 1990s. She’s now a key figure in changes sweeping business and society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Israel reaching tipping point with internal clashes?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/is-israel-reaching-a-tipping-point-with-internal-clashes-668031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The explosion of violence appears to have come from nowhere but has deep roots in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar over proposed homeless camp sites at L.A. beaches...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/mike-bonin-temporary-homeless-camping-beaches-parks-los-angeles-1234755193/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday a Los Angeles Times investigation revealed that, among other things, fires related to homeless encampments have nearly tripled. According to the paper, in the first four months of this…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach preparing for possible Trump indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/palm-beach-police-have-reportedly-discussed-trumps-possible-extradition-if-hes-indicted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law enforcement officials in Palm Beach County, Florida are reportedly developing a plan in case Donald Trump is ever indicted by Manhattan DA Cyrus Vance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,600 rockets fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.dpa-international.com/topic/gaza-shot-1600-rockets-israel-80-palestinians-killed-urn%3Anewsml%3Adpa.com%3A20090101%3A210513-99-584565</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Stories from around the globe brought to you by dpa International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French techno musician rocks Swiss mountain tops...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210513125228-qxx94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWISS-DJ/MOUNTAIN (PIX, TV):French techno musician rocks Swiss mountain tops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Brett Kavanaugh Out for Revenge?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2021/06/brett-kavanaugh-supreme-court/618717/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three years after his polarizing confirmation hearings, the Supreme Court’s 114th justice remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani hires attorneys who defended Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/553318-giuliani-hires-attorneys-who-defended-harvey-weinstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Trump attorney Rudy Giuliani in the case related to the FBI raid of his apartment last month has hired two lawyers who worked on disgraced film producer Harvey Weinstein’s defense team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree poaching hits Canada amid lumber shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/may/13/tree-poaching-hits-canada-amid-lumber-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials on Vancouver Island say at least 100 trees have been illegally chopped down, leaving one stump with a face carved into it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Exodus? 1 In 3 Ready To Nix Over Lackluster Content...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/netflix-hulu-streaming-services-overrated-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, not all the shows and streaming services are living up to their hype, leaving many people ready to cut their subscriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTAGES SPREAD</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gas-stations-await-relief-from-panic-buyers-while-colonial-pipeline-restores-service/ar-BB1gGR1u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may take a few days to recover from the fuel runs and shortages that cleaned out more than half the stations in Virginia, Georgia and the Carolinas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many in Hollywood cheering hiatus for GLOBES. Those who count dollars less sure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/many-in-hollywood-are-cheering-a-hiatus-for-the-golden-globes-those-who-count-the-dollars-are-less-sure/ar-BB1gGZ9y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washington Post analysis found that over the past 15 years, winning a Golden Globes award for best dramatic film brought in an additional $6 million in box office receipts the weekend after the Globes, compared with the previous weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Facing White-Knuckle Summer With Power in Short Supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/u-s-west-facing-white-knuckle-summer-with-power-in-short-supply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. West Facing White-Knuckle Summer With Power in Short Supply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided nation flocks to partisan brands...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/brands-politics-patagonia-trump-mypillow-4391077e-f74e-4b97-a509-384730349aae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Politics can help a company's reputation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning shows extend day to cope with viewer erosion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-arts-and-entertainment-f7744cafb99f497453bc273310f90715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A recent job promotion came with what seems to be a counterintuitive mandate for NBC News senior vice president Libby Leist: Drum up interest in the “Today” show anytime other than the mornings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judy Sheindlin on Ending 'JUDGE JUDY,' Her New Show and Legal System's Biggest Flaw...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/judge-sheindlin-ending-judge-judy-1234950880/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 25 years, TV’s highest-paid host is walking away from the show that made her an icon, but she has no plans to put the gavel down any time soonBy Mikey O’ConnellPhotographed byJeff…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IDOL' finalist out after KKK-themed video surfaces...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/12/american-idol-finalist-caleb-kennedy-out-after-video-surfaces/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A representative for the show confirmed to The Post that he will no longer be moving forward in the competition after a video surfaced showing him next to someone wearing what appears to be a Ku Kl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry Scorches Joe Rogan Over Vax Remarks: 'Careful What Comes Out Of Mouth'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/prince-harry-joe-rogan-coronavirus-vaccination-armchair-expert-1234755386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry has joined the chorus of backlash against Joe Rogan’s remarks about the coronavirus vaccine, arguing that the influential podcast star should have chosen his words more carefully…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears mount of irreparable damage to society...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/as-rival-gangs-of-jews-and-arabs-clash-on-streets-fears-mount-of-irreparable-damage-to-israeli-society/ar-BB1gGZ4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While there will be an eventual cease-fire between Israel and Hamas, it will be harder to stop the communal violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAZA GROUND WAR IMMINENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9574147/Netanyahu-rejects-Hamas-ceasefire-plea-nine-commanders-neutralised.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamas offered truce last night via the Russian foreign ministry, requesting ceasefire on a 'mutual basis' after they launched more than 1,000 rockets since Monday, killing seven Israeli civilians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S boost pay to lure new workers...</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/mcdonalds-owned-u-restaurants-boost-121052726.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's Corp announced on Thursday a 10% average hourly pay raise at the nearly 660 U.S. restaurants it operates, joining the industry's scramble to lure workers back into kitchens and dining rooms as pandemic restrictions ease. The wage increases do not apply to employees at the roughly 13,025 U.S. McDonald's restaurants owned and operated by franchisees. McDonald's said the pay hikes for more than 36,500 hourly restaurant workers had already begun and would continue over several weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities see surge in deadly street racing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-coronavirus-pandemic-pandemics-health-business-71278d5eba8a9e71df2d5ef135168af3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaye Sanford, a 52-year-old mother of two, was driving home in suburban Atlanta on Nov. 21 when a man in a Dodge Challenger muscle car who was allegedly street racing crashed into her head-on, killing her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many experts think Americans can ditch masks soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210513-why-many-covid-experts-think-americans-can-ditch-their-masks-soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why many Covid experts think Americans can ditch their masks soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang sits atop mayoral field vying to revive battered NYC...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210513085243-ov3bq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-ELECTION/MAYOR (PIX):Yang sits atop mayoral field vying to revive a battered New York City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges pushed anew for reparations for slavery, racism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ma-state-wire-philanthropy-slavery-race-and-ethnicity-education-bff4488c36de6c7beb3f7696da07d77d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — For Brown University students, the Ivy League college's next step in its yearslong quest to atone for its legacy of slavery is clear: Pay up. Nearly two decades after the Providence, Rhode Island, institution launched its much-lauded reckoning, undergraduate students this spring &lt;a href="https://www...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palm Beach preparing for possible Trump indictment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2021/05/13/how-palm-beach-is-preparing-for-a-possible-trump-indictment-492836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And a meeting today will tell us how far apart the parties are on infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communal violence erupts in cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/12/middleeast/israel-palestine-violence-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Israeli military and Palestinian militants in Gaza exchange deadly airstrikes and rocket bombardments, rioting and violent clashes have also swept through several Israeli cities between Arab and Jewish citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Greene aggressively confronts Ocasio-Cortez, causing congresswoman to raise security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rep-greene-aggressively-confronts-rep-ocasio-cortez-causing-new-york-congresswoman-to-raise-security-concerns/ar-BB1gG3bZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene (Ga.) followed Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) off the House floor and accused her of supporting “terrorists and antifa.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$365 BILLION WIPED OFF CRYPTO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/13/bitcoin-btc-price-falls-after-tesla-stops-car-purchases-with-crypto.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk said Tesla would suspend car purchases using bitcoin, wiping off billions of dollars of value from the cryptocurrency market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguay, once a corona model, struggles...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/uruguay-once-a-coronavirus-model-struggles-against-a-deadly-wave/ar-BB1gFfjG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South America leads the world in new cases and deaths per capita. Uruguay leads South America in both.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE passenger who blew nose into blanket faces $10,500 fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-maskless-airline-passenger-blew-his-nose-into-a-blanket-he-now-faces-a-2410500-fine/ar-BB1gFnid?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest fines come under the Federal Aviation Administration's "zero-tolerance policy" for passengers who disobey flight crew instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI learns to type on phone like humans...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2021-05-ai-humans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Touchscreens are notoriously difficult to type on. Since we can't feel the keys, we rely on the sense of sight to move our fingers to the right places and check for errors, a combination of tasks that is difficult to accomplish simultaneously. To really understand how people type on touchscreens, researchers at Aalto University and the Finnish Center for Artificial Intelligence (FCAI) have created the first artificial intelligence model that predicts how people move their eyes and fingers while typing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O opens up about coping with depression: 'Don't wallow in your low'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/michelle-obama-opens-coping-depression-171708137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On 'The Late Show With Stephen Colbert,' former First Lady Michelle Obama talked about how she has dealt with anxiety and depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL NOT PAY RANSOM</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210512195700-2wvda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PRODUCTS/COLONIALPIPELINE-RANSOM (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Colonial Pipeline has no plan to pay ransom to hackers -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 rockets fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/latest-news/around-1500-rockets-fired-towards-israel-from-gaza-army/news-story/cb3d411ca736192a9b398d6d6a0eb086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theaustralian.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 1,500 rockets have been fired from Gaza into Israeli cities since hostilities escalated between Hamas militants and Israel earlier in the week, Israels army said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA BAILS ON BITCOIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/elon-musk-tesla-bitcoin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The problem is the cryptocurrency's environmental impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brawl Over Line-Cutting...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article251353113.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video of the fight has made international news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob 'lynching of Arab' aired live on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mob-lynching-of-arab-aired-live-on-israeli-tv/ar-BB1gFrB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of a far-right Israeli mob attacking a man near Tel Aviv they believed to be an Arab was aired live on television Wednesday night, as the Israel-Palestinian conflict raged on. Demonstrations by far-right activists broke out Wednesday night in several cities, leading to clashes with police and sometimes Arab Israelis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governor Announces Million Dollar Lottery For Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ohio-governor-announces-a-million-dollar-lottery-for-adults-who-have-gotten-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio Governor Mike DeWine announced a million-dollar lottery for people who have gotten vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeGeneres to End Daytime Talk After 19 Years...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/ellen-degeneres-ending-daytime-talk-show-1234971355/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres is ending her long-running daytime talk show, Variety has confirmed. “The Ellen DeGeneres Show” will officially end after the upcoming 2021-22 season. DeGeneres has host…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL, GAZA VIOLENCE ESCALATES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-africa-gaza-middle-east-violence-cb885f54369c7f4799aff0d8e421212c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israel on Wednesday pressed ahead with a fierce military offensive in the Gaza Strip, killing as many as 10 senior Hamas military figures and toppling a pair of high-rise towers housing Hamas facilities in a series of airstrikes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Ailments Said to Be More Widespread Among U.S. Personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/12/us/politics/havana-syndrome.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has begun more aggressively investigating episodes that left spies, diplomats, soldiers and others with brain injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE RESTARTS AFTER HACK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/colonial-pipeline-restarts-after-hack-but-supply-chain-wont-return-to-normal-for-a-few-days.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says 28 blood clot cases, 3 deaths may be linked to J&amp;J...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/12/cdc-says-28-blood-clot-cases-3-deaths-may-be-linked-to-jj-covid-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women who were 30- to 39-years old accounted for the biggest risk group who developed rare blood clots following J&amp;J's Covid vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kerry Admits Slave Labor Fuels China's Green Energy Supply Chain...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/kerry-admits-slave-labor-fuels-chinas-green-energy-supply-chain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden administration climate envoy John Kerry admitted before Congress on Wednesday that slave labor plagues the globe's green energy supply chain, potentially complicating the administration's efforts to source materials from top human rights abusers like China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE WILL NOT PAY RANSOM</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/joewalsh/2021/05/12/colonial-pipeline-reportedly-wont-pay-hacker-ransom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial, which normally carries almost half of the East Coast’s gasoline supply, hopes to restore data from a backup instead of paying off hackers, the Washington Post reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost of Dying: $20,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/dying-america-funerals-cost-5bb4dc9e-797d-4ffd-94a5-39b8ac953bb9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average cost of funerals and end-of-life care is nearly $20,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady 'fearful' of what comes after football...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/11/tom-brady-a-little-fearful-of-what-comes-after-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-time Super Bowl champion, in a new podcast interview, discussed the latter half of his football career, and what lies ahead when he finally decides to walk away from the game for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Docs Show Police Charged Thousands For Petty Violations...</title>
      <link>https://mtracey.substack.com/p/new-documents-show-police-charged</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mtracey.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In March and April of last year, drastic emergency measures were imposed by federal, state, and local government authorities for the stated purpose of curbing the spread of COVID-19. By March 16, 2020, all states had declared a State of Emergency, and by April 7 all states except four had imposed a “Stay at Home” order of some kind. Counties and municipalities also decreed their own separate COVID-related orders. As usual in the US, the details greatly varied by jurisdiction — some measures were far more stringent than others. But in general, a new legal regimen had taken hold across the country, in the name of combatting what was described as a once-in-a-lifetime public health crisis.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
