<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GANNETT making deep cuts, furloughing staff... </title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gannett-announces-pay-cuts-and-furloughs-across-entire-media-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mass-media company, which owns many large newspapers including USA Today, announced Monday that the coronavirus downturn has forced the company to make deep cuts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Warn Virus Persists 8 Days --  After Symptoms Disappear!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/coronavirus-persists-in-many-patients-even-after-symptoms-disappear-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds many patients will still be contagious and house coronavirus in their bodies for up to eight days even after their symptoms disappear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S to lay off 130,000 employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-macy-s-layoff/macys-to-furlough-most-of-130000-employees-as-stores-stay-shut-idUSKBN21H2I7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macy's Inc said on Monday it would furlough most of its 130,000-strong workforce starting this week as all stores of the department chain operator have been temporarily shut due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamptons Houses Now Luxury Bunkers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/realestate/hamptons-houses-are-now-luxury-coronavirus-bunkers/ar-BB11VhKb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Coronavirus could have spread among humans for years or even decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/coronavirus-could-spread-among-humans-21777358</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of experts have analysed the coronavirus Covid-19 outbreak that is claiming the lives of thousands around the world - and they believe animals may have played a role in spreading the disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Clashes at Epicenter Show Risks Facing Xi...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-clashes-virus-epicenter-show-110613727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- China’s leaders normally spend a lot of time and money on keeping the country’s 1.4 billion people in line -- and that was before a global pandemic ravaging the world economy threatened to put millions out of work.A rare street clash over the weekend on the border of virus-stricken Hubei</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Field hospital set up in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200330143752-x6an9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-New York mayor pleads for help as U.S. coronavirus toll mounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi king offers to pay for patients' treatment...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200330133135-xkcdx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SAUDI:Saudi king offers to pay for coronavirus patients' treatment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting odds surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/2020-odds-cuomo-surges-third-behind-trump-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo, a 2020 presidential afterthought before his popular performance fighting the coronavirus, has surged ahead of Sen. Bernie Sanders to become the third top bet to win the presidency, according to oddsmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS orders office evacuation, affecting most agency employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/30/irs-orders-office-evacuation-affecting-most-agency-employees-155502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The directions include employees who don’t have a telework agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1918 public health order from Spanish flu sounds a lot like now...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/coronavirus/article241614086.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas Lawyer and an Open Secret: How Harvey Weinstein's Charity Fraud Led to His Downfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-harvey-weinsteins-charity-fraud-led-his-downfall-1286557</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, attorney Tom Ajamie opens up about his pro bono investigation into questionable practices at amfAR that led to the disgraced movie mogul's demise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number of 911 calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/sirens-a-constant-as-nyc-nears-700-coronavirus-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers are hearing a constant wail of sirens as weary ambulance crews respond to a record volume of 911 calls, many from people experiencing symptoms of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI RIPS TRUMP:  'As the President fiddles, people are dying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/29/politics/nancy-pelosi-coronavirus-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi on Sunday criticized President Donald Trump's response to the coronavirus pandemic, saying "his denial at the beginning was deadly" and that as he "fiddles, people are dying."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GREAT WAIT</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-america-waiting-8e474434-5736-49eb-ad74-025305c031f8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's going to be a maddening few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICA'S GRIMMEST MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-coronavirus-april-trump-9c611279-070a-4be7-9c4a-c6d3c4db2dbf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus outbreak is about to get much worse before it gets better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Birth In Time Of Pandemic 'Absolutely Terrifying'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/03/28/coronavirus-pregnant-mothers-forced-change-birth-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two local women have had to adjust their birth plans due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Orban gets sweeping new powers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hungarys-orban-seeks-sweeping-powers-virus-fight-022138638.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary's parliament endorsed a bill on Monday giving nationalist premier Viktor Orban sweeping new powers he says he needs to fight the new coronavirus pandemic. Critics at home and abroad have condemned the "anti-coronavirus defence law", saying it gives Orban unnecessary and unlimited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Break Up Funeral In Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/03/29/police-break-up-church-gathering-of-40-to-60-people-on-northwest-side-amid-stay-at-home-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police on Sunday broke up a large funeral at a church on the city’s Northwest Side for violating the Illinois stay-at-home order during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Cursed' Horror Movies That Resulted in Real-Life Death and Tragedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-cursed-horror-movies-that-resulted-in-real-life-death-and-tragedy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Shudder docuseries “Cursed Films” explores the horror-movie productions (“Poltergeist,” “The Omen”) that people have deemed “cursed” for all the death surrounding them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Benedict 'plotting downfall of Francis' in Vatican coup...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1262248/christian-news-pope-benedict-pope-francis-vatican-coup-latest-catholic-religion-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE BENEDICT is "plotting the downfall of Pope Francis," a panicked expert has warned after admitting Francis has been unable to push through vital changes to Catholicism in the hope of modernising the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Gogh painting stolen from museum in raid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e635b833e60dfcb01351752976d818df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — A Dutch museum that is currently closed to prevent the spread of the coronavirus said Monday a painting by Vincent van Gogh on loan for an exhibition was stolen in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI PROJECTS '100,000-200,000' DEAD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/64ac08d62c3621f2b888785e02c7f6b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The coronavirus outbreak could kill 100,000 to 200,000 Americans, the U.S. government's top infectious-disease expert warned on Sunday as family members described wrenching...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Virus could wipe us out': Indigenous South Americans blockade villages...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/30/south-america-indigenous-groups-coronavirus-brazil-colombia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Groups in Brazil, Colombia, Ecuador and Peru withdraw into homes as physicians highlight history of diseases ‘decimating’ communities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead bodies loaded into refrigerated truck...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8167283/Horrifying-moment-dead-bodies-loaded-refrigerated-truck-forklift.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage has emerged of dead bodies being loaded onto a truck with a forklift outside a Brooklyn hospital the same day a nurse shared a harrowing image of corpses lining the inside of another lorry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of 17 infected at funeral of COVID-19 victim...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/family-caught-coronavirus-at-funeral-104418679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheila Brooks' family attended her funeral before movement restrictions were imposed. Her niece died just a few days later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Hoarding Cash at Fastest Pace Since Y2K...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/dailyshot/2020/03/30/the-daily-shot-americans-hoarding-cash-at-the-fastest-pace-since-y2k/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counties without coronavirus mostly rural, poor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adef9109ed81e8d48631aea8c6524394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — As the coronavirus rages across the United States, mainly in large urban areas, more than a third of U.S. counties have yet to report a single positive test result for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elderly woman dies after smacked for not social distancing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/29/elderly-woman-dies-after-being-shoved-for-not-social-distancing-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 86-year-old woman awaiting treatment for bowel blockage at a Brooklyn hospital yesterday died after being punched by a fellow patient — for not engaging in “social distancing” amid the coronavir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Shares Cautionary Tale: 'I Was Alone. Crying. Suffocating. Gasping For Air'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/29/coronavirus-young-healthy-patient-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When her symptoms worsened Friday, it was time to go to the emergency room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'President Cuomo' new daydream for those fretting over Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/president-cuomo-daydream-those-fretting-100000517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- While Americans are stuck at home, the Democrat dominating the airwaves to counter President Donald Trump’s messaging about the coronavirus is not the one seeking to replace him in the Oval Office -- it’s New York Governor Andrew Cuomo.And that’s causing some daydreaming for political</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER removes Bolsonaro tweets questioning quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-economy-cant-stop-coronavirus-bolsonaro-233240524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two tweets by Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro in which he questioned quarantine measures aimed at containing the novel coronavirus were removed Sunday, on the grounds that they violated the social network's rules. Twitter explained in a statement that it had recently expanded its global rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu self-isolating after aide tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200330110528-z7cq1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-NETANYAHU (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Netanyahu self-isolating after aide tests positive for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rampaging monkeys launching attacks sign of biblical plague, claims rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/rampaging-monkeys-launching-attacks-sign-21774648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rabbi Yosef Mizrahi refers to Deuteronomy 7:22, which states those who follow God’s laws are blessed – while there is a plague promised for those who break them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist 'saw' demon with no eyes mimicking possessed teen in ritual...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/exorcist-saw-demon-no-eyes-21752934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exorcist claimed to see a vile-looking demon which had taken control of a 17-year-old girl and made her swear and hurl abuse at her family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia primed to feast on Italy's devastation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mafia-primed-feast-italys-virus-devastation-103659112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Italy mourns thousands of coronavirus dead, and survivors brace for life in an economic wasteland, one rung of society looks to win big: organised crime. "The Italian mafia can turn threats into opportunities," top government anti-mafia investigator Giuseppe Governale told AFP. Over 10,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses Die, Doctors Fall Sick, Panic Rises on Front Lines...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/30/nurses-die-doctors-fall-sick-and-panic-rises-on-virus-front-lines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A supervisor urged surgeons at Columbia University Irving Medical Center in Manhattan to volunteer for the front lines because half</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Already Too Diseased to Go Back to Work Right Now...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/30/americans-are-already-too-diseased-to-go-back-to-work-right-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health measures to slow the spread of Covid-19 have already taken a staggering toll on the economy, with the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandma is gone: Coronavirus keeps kids from older family...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f295c91756b2625ab83f339d3e92fdd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A few weeks ago, Debbie Cameron saw her grandsons most days, playing the piano, making after-school snacks or singing nursery rhymes with the baby in her Chandler, Arizona,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo infection spike AFTER Olympic delay sparks questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c346402f4a0ef8796c6eb0afebe342f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Before the Olympics were postponed, Japan looked like it had coronavirus infections contained, even as they spread in neighboring countries. Now that the games have been pushed to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blissful ignorance? Submariners likely unaware of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/82739c3cf06b8acc415b71fd3c950aa1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LE PECQ, France (AP) — Of a world in coronavirus turmoil, they may know little or nothing. Submariners stealthily cruising the ocean deeps, purposefully shielded from worldly worries to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to run daily temp checks on workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/608338/amazon-temperature-checks-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has said it will start taking daily temperatures of its employees after reports that at least 17 company locations have had employees test positive for the coronavirus. The retail giant will…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers who break distancing rules face fines of $500...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/albany/story/2020/03/29/new-yorkers-who-break-social-distancing-rules-will-now-face-fines-up-to-500-1269545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fines will be a last resort, but de Blasio has authorized police officers to give them out to people who are ordered to disperse but fail to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurches Still Packing In Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-megachurches-are-still-packing-in-crowds/ar-BB11SBxU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Social Distancing Looked Like in 1666...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/what-social-distancing-looked-like-in-1666/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of English people believed 1666 would be the year of the apocalypse. You can’t really blame them. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hosts party, gets arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article241605346.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugs, Kisses, Dining Out During Virus Raise Fear in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/hugs-kisses-dining-out-during-virus-raise-fear-in-mexico/ar-BB11SinY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CITY WILL BE SPARED</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/dr-deborah-birx-issues-coronavirus-warning-we-dont-think-any-city-will-be-spared</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump sought to keep the public safe Saturday when he said he was considering a mandatory quarantine for the New York City metro area, a key member of his Coronavirus Task Force said Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Armed 'vigilantes' in Maine cut down tree to quarantine men from New Jersey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165415/Armed-vigilantes-cut-tree-use-roadblock-quarantine-workers-New-Jersey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they were called on Friday afternoon to the island of Vinalhaven to reports of  several people with guns threatening a man who had left his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON LOCKDOWN COULD GO MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165169/Coronavirus-lockdown-SIX-MONTHS-says-Dr-Jenny-Harries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Jenny Harries told a Downing Street press conference that people should not be viewing the coronavirus crisis as something that will blow over soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vaunts his TV ratings amid pandemic..</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-vaunts-tv-ratings-amid-virus-pandemic-201026555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Sunday to vaunt the television ratings of his daily briefings on the coronavirus pandemic gripping the United States. "Because the 'Ratings' of my News Conferences etc. are so high... the Lamestream Media is going CRAZY," the president tweeted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Orders All Residents to Stay Home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moscow-mayor-orders-residents-stay-home-192601827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow's mayor announced strict isolation rules for the city from Monday, the latest in a series of measures introduced in Russia to fight the spread of the coronavirus. The new restrictions would apply to all the city's residents, regardless of age, mayor Sergei Sobyanin said in a statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field hospital set up in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/field-hospital-set-yorks-central-park-202813283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York's Central Park on Sunday, a field hospital was going up. Samaritan's Purse, a US-based Christian global relief agency, is setting up the hospital on the park's East Meadow lawn, where workers in face masks unloaded a white tarp and other equipment on the grass. The site is right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing, testing, testing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d851c87c07a7e0f67c245abe0d86e56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As President Donald Trump looks for ways to restore normalcy in parts of the U.S., his foremost infection disease expert says the country could experience more than 100,000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Why Second Wave of 1918 Spanish Flu Was So Deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.history.com/news/spanish-flu-second-wave-resurgence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.history.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first strain of the Spanish flu wasn’t particularly deadly. Then it came back in the fall with a vengeance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Tried to Build New Fleet of Ventilators. Mission Failed...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/the-u-s-tried-to-build-a-new-fleet-of-ventilators-the-mission-failed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen years ago, a group of U.S. public health officials came up with a plan to address what they regarded</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
