<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hopefuls hesitate to define 'Green New Deal' meaning...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2019/01/29/hopefuls-hesitate-define-meaning-green-new-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They love to talk about a landmark climate deal but are short on specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gwyneth Paltrow sued for 'hit and run' ski accident; 'Brain injury, broken ribs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/01/29/utah-man-is-suing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Utah man is suing actress Gwyneth Paltrow for a “hit-and-run ski crash” on the slopes at Deer Valley — alleging she hit him and then skied away as he lay in the snow with serious injuries. And he’s asking for damages in excess of $3.1 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too much sex on famous nudist beach causing massive damage, say furious environmentalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/travel/world-travel/europe/sex-on-ibizas-famous-sand-dunes-is-ruining-the-environment/news-story/e0d5cb26a4aa386b2829742e39f84723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Randy tourists having sex on Ibiza’s most famous nudist beach are causing massive damage to the island’s protected sand dunes, say furious environmentalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXELROD: Beto counter-narrative driving political class nuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/29/opinions/beto-orourke-is-driving-the-political-class-nuts-axelrod/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether or not the Texan -- blogging from a road trip at the moment -- runs in 2020, others could learn something from him about shattering old political shibboleths; about genuinely listening, empathy and the need for an authentic, connecting narrative that can help lift our divided country, writes David Axelrod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musician finds migrants hiding in tour bus to cross UK border...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-01-29/amy-shark-finds-stowaways-on-tour-bus/10757260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shark's crew discovers the pair in the luggage compartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Wants to Be Big in Entertainment. First, A $49 Billion Problem to Fix...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-t-wants-to-be-big-in-entertainment-first-it-has-a-49-billion-problem-to-fix-11548777413</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The telecom giant is attempting to expand its footprint in a media industry currently in a state of flux. But since acquiring DirecTV in 2015, the satellite pay-TV service has become a drag on AT&amp;T’s business and public image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First quarterly decline in revenue and profit in over decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-posts-drop-in-quarterly-revenue-and-profit-11548797780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. posted a quarterly decline in both revenue and profit, the first time in more than a decade for the December quarter, underlining its need to reignite slowing iPhone sales and get more growth from services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare fruit selling for $1,343 each!</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/se-asia/rare-durian-on-sale-in-indonesia-for-1343-each</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAKARTA (DPA) - A rare variety of durian is being sold for 14 million rupiah (S$1,343) each at a shopping mall in an Indonesian town. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Services Business Jumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/apple-services-business-grows-19-percent-weak-iphone-sales-1180902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEO Tim Cook had warned investors that the quarter would be a disappointing one due to soft iPhone sales an a weakening economy in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASH PILE GROWS TO $245,000,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/29/apple-now-has-tk-cash-on-hand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple disclosed its cash pile in its first-quarter 2019 earnings report on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE opens new chapter as iPhone sales fall, stock sinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c281923e5ab14348a7dd673cee7e661e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Apple hoped to offset slowing demand for iPhones by raising the prices of its most important product, but that strategy seems to have backfired after sales sagged during the holiday shopping season. Now, CEO Tim Cook is grappling with his toughest challenge since replacing co-founder Steve Jobs 7 ½ years ago. Even as he tries to boost iPhone sales, Cook also must prove that Apple can still thrive even if demand doesn't rebound. It figures to be an uphill battle, given Apple's stock has lost one-third of its value in less than four months, erasing about $370 billion in shareholder wealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Dog Stuck In Drainage Ditch For 5 MONTHS Rescued...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/01/28/coco-dog-stuck-drain-ditch-five-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dog is safe tonight after spending the last five months trapped in a drainage ditch in South Sacramento.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo defense rests after just 30 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6645135/El-Chapos-defense-case-rests-just-30-minutes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for Joaquin 'El Chapo' Guzman called just one witness and put one document into the record on Tuesday before resting the case at his U.S. drug-trafficking trial in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Mocks 'Billionaire'...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/dc/elizabeth-warren-mocks-howard-schultz-electability</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) took a shot Tuesday at former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz&amp;#8217;s chances of mounting a serious presidential campaign,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE earnings raise Wall St. nerves... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/news/stocks/apple-stock-price-earnings-pros-weigh-in-2019-1-1027905964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound bombs explode in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-security-blast/sound-bombs-explode-in-southeast-iran-police-officers-wounded-idUSKCN1PN2HR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sound bombs exploded in front of a police station in the city of Zahedan in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-deal Brexit voted down...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/uk-britain-eu/british-lawmakers-vote-down-bid-to-prevent-no-deal-brexit-idUSKCN1PN007</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British lawmakers voted on Tuesday against a bid to prevent a potentially disord...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abrams to deliver Dems' State of Union response...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/abrams-deliver-dems-state-the-union-response/2Oo3TTBaQB8OMaRNhBoc9L/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stacey Abrams will deliver the Democratic response to President Donald Trump’s State of the Un...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel chiefs contradict president on NKorea, ISIS threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bb33704147f4951a040dcb53d709586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Directly contradicting President Donald Trump, U.S. intelligence agencies told Congress on Tuesday that North Korea is unlikely to dismantle its nuclear arsenal, that the Islamic State group remains a threat and that the Iran nuclear deal is working. The chiefs made no mention of a crisis at the U.S.-Mexican border for which Trump has considered declaring a national emergency. Their analysis stands in sharp contrast to Trump's almost singular focus on security gaps at the border as the biggest threat facing the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White gold: Unstoppable rise of alternative milks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2019/jan/29/white-gold-the-unstoppable-rise-of-alternative-milks-oat-soy-rice-coconut-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long read: How wellness upstarts spoiled milk’s healthy reputation – and built a billion-dollar industry from juicing oats and nuts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI final report finds no motive for Vegas shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/shootings/fbi-final-report-finds-no-motive-for-las-vegas-shooting-1584677/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly 16 months, the agency said it cannot determine why gunman Stephen Paddock killed 58 people and injured nearly 900 others in October 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 kids kidnapped, killed for body parts...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/ten-children-in-tanzania-kidnapped-and-killed-for-their-body-parts-authorities-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanzanian authorities say that 10 children who were kidnapped in December were found dead were killed for their body parts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS:  Tax Cuts 'Accelerated' Wage Increases...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/starbucks-gop-tax-cuts-accelerated-wage-and-benefit-increases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antifa leader arrested for 'terroristic threats'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/29/antifa-leader-marines-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheDCNF's reporting led to Joseph Alcoff's arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tracking 3 migrant caravans...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/29/us-tracking-three-migrant-caravans-one-12000-peopl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government is tracking three separate migrant caravans, one of them estimated to be more than 12,000 people in size, heading north toward the U.S., a top Pentagon official said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital let woman pull plug on wrong man...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Hospital-let-woman-pull-the-plug-on-wrong-man-13570102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was told her brother was dying, so Shirell Powell hurried to St. Barnabas Hospital in the Bronx last July. The prognosis was bad, Powell was told, she claims in a recently filed lawsuit. Her brother, Frederick Williams, was unconscious from an apparent drug overdose and had suffered severe brain damage. Doctors didn't believe he was going to make it, she said she was told. She sat at his bedside, looking at the 40-year-old man on life support, tubes obscuring his face, and cried. Soon, she called his family in Virginia, including two teen daughters, she told the New York Post, and told them they needed to drive up to say their goodbyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon sending thousands more troops to Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0e34832e77f945c0bd8aefdb1facb1af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Acting Defense Secretary Pat Shanahan says the U.S. will be sending "several thousand" more American troops to the southern border to provide additional support to Homeland Security. He says the troops will mainly be used to install additional wire barriers and provide increased surveillance of the area. Plans call for about 150 more miles of concertina wire. The Pentagon has approved an extended U.S. deployment to the border through the end of September. Officials have been working out how many forces are needed and which ones should be tapped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI doesn't find motive for Vegas mass shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00b90ac3e97a41c3b3c078855b32d75f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — A high-stakes gambler who rained down a hail of gunfire, killing 58 people from his high-rise casino suite in Las Vegas wanted infamy and mass destruction, the FBI told the Associated Press Tuesday, but took whatever motive might stretch beyond that to his grave. "It wasn't about MGM, Mandalay Bay or a specific casino or venue," said Aaron Rouse, the special agent in charge of the FBI's Las Vegas office. "It was all about doing the maximum amount of damage and him obtaining some form of infamy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodell-Critical Outlet Banned, Threatened Arrest Over Fake Passes...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/29/barstool-sports-pft-commenter-arrested-at-super-bowl-media-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Portnoy was not arrested, but instead banned from the Super Bowl after he was caught with a fake pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Begs Users to Stop Calling Serial Killer Ted Bundy 'Hot'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/netflix-begs-people-to-stop-calling-serial-killer-ted-bundy-hot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are literally THOUSANDS of hot men on the service -- almost all of whom are not convicted serial murderers," streaming service tweets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot owners swap used parts on forum...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8305623/sex-robots-used-second-hand-buy-doll-forum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX ROBOT owners are swapping “used” parts and selling “bruised, battered” dolls on a creepy online forum. Randy bot-bonkers flog their second-hand dolls to each other – som…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Belichick beat league built for parity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jan/29/bill-belichick-new-england-patriots-strategy-nfl-super-bowl-liii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots head coach is an economics major, and his exploitation of market inefficiency has helped him dominate the NFL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Kellyanne Leaked While Aide Drafted Statement Denying She Leaked...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6640749/Kellyanne-Conways-White-House-leaking-worst-kept-secret-town-says-former-aide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House aide Cliff Sims on Monday claimed Kellyanne Conway's leaking about President Donald Trump to reporters was 'the worst-kept secret in town.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Confidence Falls Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/01/29/consumer-confidence-falls-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confidence fell for the third consecutive month but remains quite high by historical standards. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway slams Trump: 'Your stupidity knows no bounds'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/427445-george-conway-slams-trump-your-stupidity-knows-no-bounds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway and a frequent critic of President Trump, blasted him on Tuesday, saying his “stupidity knows no bounds” after Trump ripped into former aide Cliff Sims for h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Star Recovering from Homophobic Attack, Chemical Substance Used...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/empire-star-jussie-smollett-homophobic-attack-chicago-chemical-substance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some journalists wonder if profession is tweet-crazy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd0b37f7e04d48fdae04451459f72703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — If Twitter is the town square for journalists, some are ready to step away. That's happening this week at the online news site Insider — by order of the boss. Reporters have been told to take a week off from tweeting at work and to keep TweetDeck off their computer screens. The idea of disengaging is to kick away a crutch for the journalists and escape from the echo chamber, said Julie Zeveloff West, Insider's editor-in-chief for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign threatens to sue ex-staffer for tell-all...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6644447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has lashed out at authors in the past – most notably journalist Michael Wolff, who he called 'a total loser who made up stories.' The book quickly became an Amazon best-seller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slams Kamala Plan to Abolish Private Insurance...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/video/howard-schultz-blasts-kamala-harris-plan-to-abolish-private-insurance-thats-not-american/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What industry are we going to abolish next? The coffee industry?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Brady Conquered His Greatest Opponent: Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-tom-brady-conquered-his-greatest-opponent-age-11548767181</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady throws short passes. He gets rid of the ball quickly. He never gets hit. And it’s how he’s in his ninth Super Bowl at 41 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby Targeted by Drone Camera in Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/29/bill-cosby-prison-drone-camera-photo-lockdown-sci-phoenix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's an eye in the sky over Bill Cosby, and Pennsylvania Prison officials are pissed about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Vatican priest resigns over advances to nun...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20190129/senior-vatican-priest-resigns-over-advances-to-nun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Vatican priest accused of making advances towards a nun during confession has resigned, the Vatican said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DON'T GO OUTSIDE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/weather/ct-met-chicago-weather-dangerous-cold-outlook-20190128-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the coldest air masses in years will drop temperatures to around 23 below zero by Tuesday night, according to the National Weather Service, with a daytime high of about minus 14 on Wednesday and another plunge to minus 25 overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animals face fight for survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/weather/ct-met-chicago-cold-weather-wild-animals-20190128-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wild and feral animals that live outdoors in Chicago could be fighting for their lives Wednesday and Thursday when the polar vortex brings temperatures expected to dip more than 20 degrees below zero.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign preparing to sue ex-staffer...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/427417-top-official-says-trump-campaign-preparing-to-sue-ex-staffer-who-wrote-tell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top official for President Trump's 2020 campaign said Tuesday that the campaign was preparing to file a lawsuit against former White House communications aide Cliff Sims for violating a non-disclosure agreement (NDA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexander the Great 'buried alive after disease paralyzed him for six days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8303195/alexander-the-great-was-alive-while-body-was-prepared-for-burial-after-rare-disease-left-him-paralysed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE mystery over the death of Alexander the Great may have finally been solved – and his passing was grislier than historians had ever imagined. The fearsome military genius succumbed to a rare dis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked men, drugs, karmic baths: What it's like at greatest spiritual gathering on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/india/articles/kumbh-mela-india/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane passenger meltdown after seated between 'two fat pigs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/plane-passenger-meltdown-because-shes-13920671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed passenger was later ejected from the flight because of her abusive comments on the United Airlines flight from Las Vegas to New Jersey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEED A MIRACLE: Marianne Williamson launches campaign...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/427394-author-marianne-williamson-running-for-2020-dem-nomination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author and activist Marianne Williamson has announced a bid for the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination, joining a crowded field of candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Revolution: Part Deux...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-01-28/french-revolution-part-deux</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte's Crime War, Which Has Killed Thousands, Turns Toward Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/dutertes-crime-war-which-has-killed-thousands-turns-toward-children-11548763638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine strongman Rodrigo Duterte is widening his crackdown on drugs and crime by lowering the country’s legal age of responsibility, a move opponents say risks sweeping children up as criminals in violence that has killed thousands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans in Texas sounding alarm about 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/texas-republicans-fear-trump-could-lose-the-state-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Republicans in Texas are sounding the alarm about 2020, warning President Trump could lose the usually reliably red state unless he devotes resources and attention to it typically reserved for electoral battlegrounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of migrants cross Arizona border after 'busloads' dropped off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/28/politics/migrants-arizona-arrests/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the early morning hours Thursday, several busloads of migrants were dropped off on Highway 2 in Mexico, just south of the Arizona border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashless experience coming? VISA says yes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/01/29/cashless-super-bowl-coming-visa-says-yes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — So you’re headed to the Super Bowl some year in the future, and you’re wondering how much cash you’ll need for the big game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump could be new Clinton if Dems impeach: Sympathetic and stronger than ever...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/427329-trump-could-be-the-new-clinton-if-democrats-impeach-sympathetic-and-stronger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rehabilitated Trump could then be even more formidable than incumbent presidents seeking re-election already are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists test shark bite-resistant wetsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.surfertoday.com/surfing/14838-scientists-test-a-shark-bite-resistant-wetsuit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.surfertoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By using a special material similar to Kevlar, researchers from Flinders University, in Australia, hope to reduce the blood loss in shark attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second fuel pipeline explodes in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://punchng.com/second-fuel-pipeline-explodes-in-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;punchng.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pipeline in Mexico exploded while people were stealing fuel from it, near where a similar blast this month left 115 dead, an official said. The new blast struck Monday in the central state of ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Egypt, stray dogs pose growing urban challenge...</title>
      <link>https://aawsat.com/english/home/article/1566966/egypt-stray-dogs-pose-growing-urban-challenge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;aawsat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alaa Hilal was out shopping in Cairo when she was attacked by a stray dog in broad daylight -- an increasing problem of daily life in Egypt which is stirring debate. "I got out of my car and saw an exceptionally large street dog," the 38-year-old hou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu's toughest ballot rival, ex-general Gantz, to break silence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190129085435-w1gtu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/GANTZ (PIX, TV):Netanyahu's toughest ballot rival, ex-general Gantz, to break silence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Govt Seen as Most Corrupt in Seven Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-leads-plunge-lower-by-populists-in-annual-corruption-index#gs.lneflmVF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trumpâ€™s U.S.A dropped six places to 22nd globally in the 2018 corruption-perception index published by Transparency International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems float idea of primary challenge for Ocasio-Cortez...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/427364-some-dems-float-idea-of-primary-challenge-for-ocasio-cortez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (D-N.Y.) has infuriated colleagues by aligning with a progressive outside group that’s threatening to primary entrenched Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE scrambles...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-bug-enables-eavesdropping-on-facetime-users-11548741057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple scrambled to fix a bug in its FaceTime video-chat system that lets callers eavesdrop on users of iPhones, iPads, and Macs, an embarrassing setback for a company that has touted its commitment to privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicines set to be prioritized over food in crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/doomsday-no-deal-brexit-will-13919871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Medicines are set to be prioritised over food, the Government has declared, as ministers think forward to potentially desperate scenarios resulting from a chaotic crash out of the EU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENERATION OF WEB ADDICTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6642161/Generation-web-addicts-Children-spend-time-YouTube-friends.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shocking scale of UK children's internet obsession has been revealed by a new Ofcom study of 2,000 people as parents admit to 'losing control' of their children's browsing habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro seeks talks with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/venezuelas-maduro-seeks-talks-trump-us-plans-empower/story?id=60677368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's Nicolas Maduro is reaching out to the U.S. after it recognized his opponent as the country's real president and is now moving to empower him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV Status of More Than 14,000 People Leaked in Data Breach...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190129041314-jbm46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE-HEALTH/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. citizen leaks data on 14,200 people in Singapore with HIV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge to allow controversial evidence in ROUNDUP cancer trials...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190128212106-pmd7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAYER-GLYPHOSATE/LAWSUIT (PIX):U.S. judge to allow controversial evidence in Roundup cancer trials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese activist jailed for five years...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/chinese-activist-jailed-five-years-rights-groups-032700084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founder of a prominent Chinese civil and human rights website was sentenced to five years in prison on Tuesday for inciting state subversion, according to human rights organisations. Liu Feiyue created and ran the Civil Rights and Livelihood Watch website, which covers a range of civil and human</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental radar aims to stop drones at game...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/28/super-bowl-drones-radar-start-up-experiment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After rogue drone sightings halt flights, startup seeks permission to test tracking system at Sunday’s game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He broke Rand Paul's ribs. Now jury will decide how much he should pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/politics-government/article225167965.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trial in which Republican U.S. Sen. Rand Paul is seeking up to $1.5 million in damages from a neighbor who attacked him and broke his ribs is scheduled to get underway Monday in Bowling Green.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Kellyanne Leaked While Aide Drafted Statement Denying Leaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2019/01/28/ex-wh-aide-cliff-sims-kellyanne-conway-was-leaking-while-i-was-writing-a-statement-denying-she-was-leaking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday on ABC's "The View," former White House aide Cliff Sims, author of the soon-to-be-released "Team of Vipers," said at the same time he was writing a | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrests hundreds of opponents...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dfb50cee83c84ccc9992df12eb13299c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — More than 700 opponents of President Nicolas Maduro have been arrested during the latest push by Venezuela's opposition to oust the socialist leader. But there's one anti-government activist security forces notably haven't touched: Juan Guaido, the lawmaker who declared himself interim president in a direct challenge to Maduro's rule. Maduro's refusal, at least so far, to order Guaido's arrest reflects mistrust in his own security forces as well as the Trump administration's warning that any harm to the man the U.S. recognizes as Venezuela's legitimate leader would be crossing a dangerous red line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams ace taunts Brady over age ahead of Super Bowl... </title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/rams-ace-taunts-brady-over-age-ahead-super-215510280--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Rams cornerback Nickell Robey-Coleman has risked the wrath of Tom Brady after claiming age had finally caught up with the New England Patriots quarterback. Brady, 41, will overtake Peyton Manning as the oldest quarterback to win a Super Bowl on Sunday if he guides the Patriots to victory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit plots and passions split UK parliament...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/brexit-plots-passions-split-uk-parliament-025816348.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's bickering parliament has splintered into rival factions with their own remedies for Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit deal. Here is what the political lay of the land will look like when the House of Commons holds votes that could alter the course of Britain's planned split from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How He Could Actually Win...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/rogerlsimon/howard-schultz-could-actually-win-the-presidency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't laugh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Screen time delaying children's development... </title>
      <link>https://fox17.com/news/local/study-increased-screen-time-in-young-children-associated-with-developmental-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox17.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from psychologists and doctors in Canada found increased screen time in young children can cause issues with children reaching developmental milestones. Researchers studied 2,441 mothers and children with higher levels of screen time for children aged 24 and 36-months-old. Researchers then examined developmental milestone test results in the same children at 36 and 60-months-old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHULTZ ROCKS 2020...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0a2b5a89587e44568481c133356f262c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some of the most influential forces in Democratic politics revolted Monday against former Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz's prospective presidential bid, insisting that an independent run would unintentionally help President Donald Trump win another four years in office. The critics included the Democratic chairman of Schultz's home state, another billionaire businessman who long flirted with an independent run of his own, former President Barack Obama's chief strategist, and the most powerful super PAC in Democratic politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mugged by macaques: Urban monkey gangs of Kuala Lumpur...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/cities/2019/jan/28/mugged-by-macaques-the-urban-monkey-gangs-of-kuala-lumpur</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next 15 megacities #10: As Malaysia’s ever-expanding capital swallows up their rainforest habitat, the macaques are turning to guerrilla warfare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment cries cloud Dem vow to leave Special Counsel alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/28/impeachment-cries-democrats-leave-mueller-alone-1132807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possible clashes will be on display Tuesday morning when the new Democratic House caucus meets for the first time this year to discuss Mueller’s investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Eyes Tiny Nuclear Reactors for Deployed Troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2019/01/us-military-eyes-tiny-nuclear-reactors-deployed-troops/154406/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Strategic Capabilities Office wants to fund prototypes, picking up on decades of intermittent research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE bug lets you listen in on people you call, even if haven't picked up! </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/28/apple-facetime-bug-lets-you-listen-even-if-someone-doesnt-answer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FaceTime bug lets you listen to someone you're trying to call even if they haven't picked up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech giants face critical earnings week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/apple-facebook-amazon-microsoft-and-other-tech-giants-face-critical-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-tech industry in the spotlight this week as investors look for signs that growth is holding up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol wives invite Pelosi to see why want wall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/427366-border-patrol-wives-invite-pelosi-to-border-to-see-why-they-want-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of women whose husbands work as Border Patrol officers are inviting Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) to come to McAllen, Texas, to see what's taking place at the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heckled Within Seconds At First Public Event...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-howard-schultz-heckled-within-seconds-first-campaign-appeara</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Go back to Davos with the other billionaires!'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort Sentencing Delay...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/Politics/sentencing-delayed-president-donald-trump-campaign-chairman-paul/story?id=60687209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dispute between special counsel Robert Mueller and President Donald Trump’s campaign chairman Paul Manafort has led a federal judge to postpone his sentencing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 cyber criminal groups behind $1 Billion in crypto theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/two-groups-account-for-1-billion-in-cryptocurrency-hacks-new-report-says-11548676800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Chainalysis, the two entities, which are likely still active, employed an extensive network of digital wallets to hide their tracks and later converted the money to physical cash through online exchanges and individual transactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'5,000 troops to Colombia' written on Bolton notepad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8301494/us-invade-venezuela-colombia-john-bolton-troops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE threat of a US invasion of Venezuela to oust socialist President Nicolas Maduro has been raised after Donald Trump’s security adviser flashed a note about sending “5,000 troops to C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Plan To Sell Phone Location Data...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/01/28/google-alphabet-sidewalk-labs-replica-cellphone-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's sibling company Sidewalk Labs offers planning agencies the ability to model an entire city's patterns of movement.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
