<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Climber saved by 'FREE SOLO' star after El Capitan fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article237804629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says hundreds of banks torched in 'vast' unrest plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gasoline-protests-minister/iran-says-hundreds-of-banks-were-torched-in-vast-unrest-plot-idUSKBN1Y10GY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's top leader on Wednesday denounced an outbreak of deadly unrest as a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French farmers clog highways to protest at 'agri-bashing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-farmers/french-farmers-clog-highways-to-protest-at-agri-bashing-idUSKBN1Y10MQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French farmers angered by government policies that they say threaten their livel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI mind-reading tool produces video of human thoughts in real-time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ai-mind-reading-tool-produces-20971379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling footage shows an AI created by Russian researchers using the brainwaves of human participants to accurately guess their thoughts in real-time through video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Climate anxiety' churns up psychological storm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-climate-anxiety-churns-psychological-storm-012205399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears about climate change are prompting worldwide action, but one knock-on effect in the United States is mounting anxiety about everything from plastics to class-based environmental disparities. Schapira, a 40-year-old senior lecturer in the English department at Brown University, is addressing that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO grandmaster quits saying computers 'cannot be defeated'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/grandmaster-says-computers-cannot-defeated-104015667.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only human ever to beat Google's computer algorithm at the ancient Chinese strategy game Go decided to retire because he is convinced machines "cannot be defeated", a report said Wednesday. South Korean Lee Se-Dol's five-match showdown with Google's artificial intelligence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's AfD plots new course with radicals on rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-afd-plots-course-radicals-rise-025153180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's far right AfD party is choosing new leaders on Saturday in a vote shaped by an increasingly powerful radical wing which wants a rethink of the country's culture of atonement for Nazi crimes. The anti-migrant party's radicals have the upper hand following a series of electoral gains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight leaves voters cold in contested Wisconsin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed75f30906384abaad31b7b69a49d163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RACINE, Wis. (AP) — There’s not a lot that Republicans and Democrats in this political battlefield agree on, but the impeachment probe into President Donald Trump may have surfaced one: The public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Thanksgiving menu: Turkey, with side of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/deb5250314a44feea5aaa36150b479fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — Some people heading to Thanksgiving gatherings predict it’s not just the turkey that will get roasted. Already polarized over Republican Donald Trump’s presidency,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility Rate Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/us-fertility-rate-hits-record-low-after-four-consecutive-years-of-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were just over 59 births for every 1,000 women of childbearing age last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence erupts again in Colombia ahead of nationwide protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/violence-erupts-again-in-colombia-ahead-of-nationwide-protests/article_51d827c6-18f8-56df-a4c0-a3a3db72d51d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia — Violent protests erupted in Colombia on Tuesday ahead of nationwide marches that have been called for the second time in the span of a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo on rocky terrain...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/472181-pompeo-trump-relationship-tested-by-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo is on rocky terrain with President Trump and members of the State Department following critical testimony by diplomatic officials in the public impeachment hearings led by House Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL RETURNS TO 405...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/video/4222753-watch-traffic-jammed-on-405-freeway-ahead-of-thanksgiving-getaway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the 405 is never easy driving through West L.A., it was all brake lights Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wintry weather to snarl holiday travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0b05febb6b84aaebad59ca58a6841d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A storm packing heavy snow and high winds that wreaked havoc as it whipped through Colorado, Wyoming and Nebraska marched into the upper Midwest on Wednesday as anxious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant explosion in Texas blows windows from homes miles away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98a09d85392e4cdfbc617fb7caf1e8bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT NECHES, Texas (AP) — A chemical company says three people were injured in an explosion at its plant in East Texas. The powerful blast blew out the windows of homes and sent a chemical plume...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb chef dies at 59...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5428beca21da4296bb49563256ee47a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Celebrity chef Gary Rhodes, who helped transform the stodgy reputation of British food, has died aged 59 with his wife Jennie by his side, his family said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg to visit church in NC... </title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article237748079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Haitian LGBTQ activist found dead amid suspicious circumstances...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonblade.com/2019/11/25/prominent-haitian-lgbtq-activist-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports indicate Charlot Jeudy may have been poisoned at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has 700 tapeworms in brain and chest from undercooked pork...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10430920/more-than-700-tapeworms-found-in-mans-brain-and-chest-after-he-ate-undercooked-pork/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOCTORS were left stunned when they examined a scan showing their patient’s brain and chest was riddled with more than 700 worms. Zhu Zhongfa, 43, is believed to have ingested eggs of the parasite …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg tol visit church in NC... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/suicides-and-overdoses-among-factors-fueling-drop-in-us-life-expectancy/ar-BBXmQcB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUAWEI phone rated higher than IPHONE, SAMSUNG...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2019/11/24/huawei-beats-apple-iphone-11-pro-max-samsung-galaxy-s10-in-new-rating/#61b35ff732e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of nowhere, Huawei has just won an award for outstanding audio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX Threatened By NYC Mayor After Unauthorized Delivery Robot Roams Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90436843/even-the-mere-appearance-of-a-fedex-delivery-robot-freaks-out-the-mayor-of-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials were quick to tell FedEx to screw off, even though the robot’s appearance was just a marketing stunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Denies Sending Rudy to Ukraine for Biden Dirt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-denies-sending-rudy-giuliani-223426705.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump denied directing Rudy Giuliani to go to Ukraine to look for dirt on his political rivals, in an interview with former Fox News host Bill O’Reilly.“No, I didn’t direct him, but he is a warrior, he is a warrior,” Trump told O’Reilly in an interview streamed on the internet on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEAK TOO SOON?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/buttigieg-claims-2nd-warren-sinks-us-2020-poll-213929575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political wunderkind Pete Buttigieg rocketed into second place in the Democratic presidential nomination race, polling showed Tuesday, with support for progressive ex-frontrunner Elizabeth Warren sliding as voters sour on her universal health care proposal. Buttigieg, the moderate millennial mayor of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE says recent changes improve user privacy, but lawmakers see them as an effort to edge out rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/apple-says-recent-changes-improve-user-privacy-but-some-lawmakers-see-them-as-an-effort-to-edge-out-rivals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has made strengthening privacy protections a central part of its brand. Critics increasingly warn that the iPhone maker may be using privacy as a guise for anti-competitive behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court's desire to be seen as neutral arbiter to be tested... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/national/as-trump-cases-arrive-supreme-court-s-desire-to-be-seen-as-neutral-arbiter-will-be-tested/ar-BBXnTnd?li=BBnbfcN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newborn offered for sale on CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article237751089.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage After Video Shows Horse Being Pulled By Truck On Snowy Road...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/25/horse-tied-pickup-truck-colorado-grand-county-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video posted on Facebook showing a horse tied to the back of a pickup truck and being pulled has sparked outrage across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign attacks GOOGLE's new ad policy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a730d4aa93d143f6a42e21e0420a65f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s reelection campaign and other Republican election groups criticized tech giant Google on Tuesday for making it harder for political advertisers to target...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accelerate impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/160472d13671476584be900f818a76aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Judiciary Committee is set to take over the impeachment probe of President Donald Trump, Democrats announced Tuesday, scheduling a hearing for next week as they push...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine -- Might Help Alcoholics...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/26/782066337/a-single-dose-of-ketamine-might-help-heavy-drinkers-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants in the U.K. experimental study dramatically reduced their average alcohol intake for months after the initial dose. Ketamine has also been used to treat severe depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influential neo-Nazi eats at soup kitchens, lives in govt housing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/influential-neo-nazi-eats-soup-kitchens-lives-government-housing-n1091681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his writings, James Mason advocates waging war against "the system." But at 67 and living in Denver, he's now dependent on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Robbins starts legal actions against BUZZFEED -- in Ireland...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/tony-robbins-starts-legal-actions-against-buzzfeed-over-sexual-assault-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed self-help guru Tony Robbins filed a summons against BuzzFeed News in Ireland Tuesday after the digital news outlet published a report about an alleged sexual assault by Robbins that took place decades ago -- but the news organization said it stands by its reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary hearings next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/26/judiciary-committee-to-hold-first-impeachment-hearing-next-week-073991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are also giving Trump the option to let White House lawyers participate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANONYMOUS' to answer public questions -- anonymously...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/26/anonymous-trump-official-reddit-ama-074040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious author of the famous op-ed and new book will answer questions for the first time in a Reddit AMA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN WIPEOUT? Poll shows plummeting support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/quinnipiac-poll-half-of-warrens-supporters-have-abandoned-her-in-one-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest national poll of the Democratic primary conducted by Quinnipiac shows support for Elizabeth Warren plummeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans dying young at alarming rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/theres-something-terribly-wrong-americans-are-dying-young-at-alarming-rates/ar-BBXmP82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to Participate?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-invited-to-participate-in-impeachment-hearing-next-week/ar-BBXnC97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow scores 100th record close under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/stocks-point-upwards-after-possible-us-china-trade-war-breakthrough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks continue to march higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Admits Giving Wrong Person Kidney Transplant...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/exclusive-lourdes-hospital-transplant-center-admits-giving-wrong-person-kidney-transplant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two patients have the same name and are around the same age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US workforce dying faster than any other wealthy country...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/26/us-life-expectancy-downward-spiral-study/4303700002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study shows a decline in life expectancy in the U.S. is driven by increased mortality among working-age people 25-64 , a danger sign for the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordanian Army Conducts Simulated Military Battle With Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.memri.org/reports/jordanian-army-conducts-maneuvers-simulating-military-battle-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.memri.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yesterday, November 25, 2019, the Jordanian Army conducted military maneuvers named "Swords of Karama," named for Israel's 1968 military operation against Fatah that took place near the village of Karama, and in which the Jordanian Army fought alongside Fatah. The maneuvers took place in the presence of King Abdullah II and appear to be a message addressed to Israel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid hold came same day as President's call...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/26/politics/ukraine-aid-trump-call-omb/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House budget office's first official action to withhold $250 million in Pentagon aid to Ukraine came on the evening of July 25, the same day President Donald Trump and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky spoke on the phone, according to a House Budget Committee summary of the office's documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  White House lockdown possibly caused by birds on radar...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/white-house-reportedly-on-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A White House lock down was lifted shortly after a reported D. C. airspace violation Tuesday morning. An evacuation was ordered for the United States Capitol, as well. That lasted about 30 minutes. Apparently, though, it was a false alarm. Shortly before 2 p. m. , NORAD confirmed that there was no airspace violation. The security scare may have been caused by a flock of birds appearing on radar, ABC7's Sam Sweeney reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton: U.S. National Security 'Under Attack From Within'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/26/john-bolton-national-security-attack-within/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton said that the United States' commitments to national security are &amp;quot;under attack from within&amp;quot; in a tweet Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton strategist Mark Penn giving Oval Office advice...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Clinton-strategist-Mark-Penn-counsels-Trump-on-14864302.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As President Donald Trump's White House battles impeachment, he turned to a familiar face last week: Mark Penn, one of President Bill Clinton's top strategists.  Penn came to the Oval Office for more than an hour last Monday, three people familiar with the meeting said, and brought polling data and impeachment advice for the president. Penn reassured Trump that he wouldn't be removed from office, according to people familiar with the meeting, and encouraged him to travel the country like Clinton did when he was fighting impeachment over 20 years ago, officials said.  Vice President Mike Pence and counselor Kellyanne Conway were also present for the meeting, where Diet Cokes were served. Penn was escorted by Andrew Stein, a longtime Trump friend from New York who recently penned a Wall Street Journal op-ed calling for Nikki Haley to replace Pence on the ticket.  Penn recommended that Trump "stay focused on the substance" of the allegations surrounding trading access and aid for political favors from Ukraine, according to Stein, "and not respond to everything."  Trump has sent dozens of tweets attacking Democrats for waging an unfair battle against him and has regularly fixated on the impeachment process, according to current and former aides, while attacking his opponents as "DO NOTHING DEMOCRATS."  "You've got to govern," Penn told Trump of how Clinton handled the impeachment process, according to another person with knowledge of the meeting.  Penn's visit suggests the president is seeking information from a wide variety of sources as Congress' impeachment battle heats up and a possible vote by the House nears in mid-December. Officials say Trump has called a variety of TV personalities, lawmakers and longtime New York and Palm Beach friends to poll advisers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moms binge drinking more...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/womens-health/moms-are-binge-drinking-more-so-are-all-women-study-n1091806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's been a lot of media attention on the "mommy drinking phenomenon," but research shows it isn't substantiated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bomb cyclone' could break records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/bomb-cyclone-could-break-records-as-it-slams-into-the-west-coast-bringing-100-mph-winds-and-blizzard-conditions/ar-BBXmmRg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN WIPEOUT? Poll shows plummeting support...</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/national/release-detail?ReleaseID=3650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Retakes Lead As Warren Plunges, Buttigieg Rises, Quinnipiac University National Poll Finds; Voters Not Swayed By Impeachment Hearings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deval Patrick Calls His Sister's Rape a 'Relapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.insidesources.com/deval-patrick-calls-his-sisters-rape-a-relapse-during-nh-campaign-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insidesources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt moving jobs out of DC -- and cutting pay...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/472074-relocated-blm-staff-face-salary-cuts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new internal Bureau of Land Management (BLM) website designed to answer employees’ questions about the agency’s upcoming relocation out West says staffers should expect a drop in their overall pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Bloomberg's $3,000-a-minute ad campaign...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mike-bloomberg-35-million-spending-tv-ads-184729122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data offers detail into Mike Bloomberg’s splashy entrance into the 2020 presidential contest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Grace leaving CNN for FOX NATION streaming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/05e14429f40f4eefaca812e03ec74af9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former CNN mainstay Nancy Grace is signing up for a crime show on Fox Nation, an illustration of how Fox News’ streaming service has evolved counter to expectations one year into...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top French actress files abuse charge against director...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-french-actress-files-abuse-charge-against-director-165110091.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French star Adele Haenel lodged a formal complaint on Tuesday against a film director she claims sexually harassed her between the ages of 12 and 15, her lawyers said. The actress shook the French film industry earlier this month with accusations about being repeatedly touched and kissed by Christophe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado National Guard  On Standby As Storm Wallops...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/colorado-national-guard-snow-response-winter-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado National Guard is standing by to help first responders if needed. The troops staged their gear on Monday night when the snow started to fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fifth Avenue Wraps Empty Storefronts in Holiday Cheer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/11/26/nyregion/Fifth-Avenue-holiday-windows.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail in Midtown is struggling. Short term, this means more window displays. Long term? Hmm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redford Says 'Monarchy in Disguise' Must End...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/robert-redford-says-trumps-monarchy-disguise-end-1258090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Leaders on both sides lack the fundamental courage to cross political aisles on behalf of what is good for the American people," the actor writes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  50% WANT REMOVAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/26/politics/cnn-poll-impeachment-views/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After five days of public hearings in House Democrats' impeachment inquiry into Donald Trump, public opinion over whether the President ought to be impeached and removed from office remains exactly the same as it was in October, according to a new CNN poll conducted by SSRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol K-9 to Retire After 10 Years, 2.5 Tons of Drugs Seized...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/11/26/border-patrol-k-9-to-retire-after-10-years-2-5-tons-of-drugs-seized/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her retirement concludes more than 10 years with the Border Patrol and the interdiction of approximately 2.5 tons of drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK SUPERMAN?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/dc-comics-superman-michael-b-jordan-green-lantern-aquaman-birds-of-prey-1203415757/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DC Films appears to have hit its stride, rebounding from the commercial failure of “Justice League” and the critical drubbing of “Batman v. Superman: Dawn of Justice” with a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg campaign chief:  President winning 2020 right now...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/471950-bloomberg-campaign-chief-trump-is-winning-2020-election-right-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Mike Bloomberg’s 2020 campaign chief Kevin Sheekey defended the former New York City mayor’s decision to skip early nominating states after his late entry into the crowded primary f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Niro Pounds Trump:  'Jerk-off in chief" and a "f------ fool'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/472059-de-niro-life-for-americans-during-the-trump-presidency-is-like</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert De Niro says life for Americans during the Trump presidency is like "living in an abusive household." "It's a really, really serious situation we're in," the "Irishman" star said in a Monday interview on CBS's "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>82-Year-Old Bodybuilding Grandma Takes Down Burglar...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/11/25/he-picked-the-wrong-house-powerlifting-82-year-old-grandma-takes-down-home-intruder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 82-year-old female bodybuilder fought back against a man who broke through the door into her home, holding him down until police officers arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment cloud darkens Thanksgiving break...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/impeachment-cloud-darkens-trumps-florida-thanksgiving-break-143107297.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump branded his political enemies "wolves" on Tuesday ahead of leaving Washington for a campaign rally and Thanksgiving break at his Florida home already being spoiled by the growing threat of impeachment. Politics watchers, however, were less interested in the fates of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire threatens homes in Santa Barbara County amid strong winds...</title>
      <link>https://keyt.com/news/fire/2019/11/25/fire-breaks-out-along-painted-cave-east-camino-cielo-above-santa-barbara/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;keyt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire broke out in the mountains above Santa Barbara Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wintry weather threatens to snarl holiday travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6cfd24e3192347d8b0fb593dfa0d135a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — A storm that dumped heavy snow in Colorado and Wyoming forced airlines to cancel hundreds of flights in Denver on Tuesday and has made driving impossible in some parts of the two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu steps up campaign against indictment with rally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30b82e2350674150888ace4bc2e62cc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Ramping up his attack on the state institutions responsible for his corruption indictment, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is looking for a show of strength in a public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado National Guard Snow Response Team On Standby As Storm Wallops...</title>
      <link>ttps://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/colorado-national-guard-snow-response-winter-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students say it's not okay to celebrate Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/video-students-say-its-not-okay-to-celebrate-thanksgiving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based off of the genocide of indigenous people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Return of Jerry Nadler...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/11/jerry-nadler-trump-impeachment/602638/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Judiciary Committee, which he chairs, is fractious and unruly. And it’s about to take over impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: Giuliani lobbied DOJ on behalf of wealthy Venezuelan who aided Ukraine effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-wealthy-venezuelan-hosted-giuliani-as-he-pursued-ukraine-campaign-then-giuliani-lobbied-the-justice-department-on-his-behalf/ar-BBXmE7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newborn baby offered for sale on CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article237751089.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Scorsese brought together three septuagenarians for mobster film decade in making...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/making-irishman-robert-de-niro-al-pacino-bring-scorseses-career-experiment-big-screen-1257256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese brings together (and de-ages) three septuagenarian legends — De Niro, Pacino and Joe Pesci — for the film that started as much more traditional genre piece and transformed into a different type of mob movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia launches mysterious military satellite with secret payload...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-launches-mysterious-military-satellite-20961673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin's military launched the rocket into orbit last night, but little is known about what's on board</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: 'GODFATHER' horse-head mansion enters bankruptcy protection...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/business/property/godfather-horse-head-mansion-enters-protection-programme-1.68091712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storied $125 million mansion in Beverly Hills is in bankruptcy protection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
PAPER: ESPN DROPS THE BALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/nov/26/monday-night-football-espn-booger-mcfarland-joe-tessitore-nfl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overblown announcing, incoherent analysis and bizarre graphics: ESPN’s broadcast checks every box when it comes to bad TV</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ moves to halt judge's ruling that McGahn must testify...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/26/doj-moves-to-halt-judges-ruling-that-mcgahn-must-testify-073923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The planned appeal means impeachment investigators won’t likely hear from McGahn anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Moontopia! Homes in lava-tubes and fake meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/welcome-moontopia-scientist-predicts-what-20963472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Lewis Dartnell has revealed what he thinks the lunar cities could look like in the next 150 years, in a project dubbed ‘Moontopia’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA: BIDEN 'DOESN'T HAVE IT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/obama-reportedly-told-a-dem-candidate-that-joe-biden-really-doesnt-have-bond-with-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new profile on former President Barack Obama suggests the former president doesn't have faith in Joe Biden's chances to connect with voters and win the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA expanding facial recognition technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.king5.com/article/news/local/facial-recognition-delta-airlines-seatac-airport/281-28a08e17-607b-47ec-8c32-caeb29e68fe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.king5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology should be in place at Sea-Tac by the end of the year and it will be optional for passengers, Delta said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer confidence falls fourth consecutive month...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/26/us-consumer-confidence-for-november-comes-in-at-125point5-vs-126point6-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer confidence dipped for a fourth straight month in November as economic conditions weaken toward the end of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filmmaker warns Russia wants Ukraine on its knees...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/filmmaker-warns-russia-wants-ukraine-knees-133303595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian filmmaker Oleg Sentsov, receiving a human rights prize from the European Parliament, warned Tuesday against attempts to thaw ties with Russia. Sentsov was held in a Russian jail for the first five years of a 20-year sentence for allegedly planning attacks in Moscow-occupied Crimea. "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stray Dog Found Warming Abandoned Kittens On Side Of Snowy Road...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/11/25/stray-dog-found-warming-five-abandoned-kittens-on-side-of-snowy-road/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dog found keeping five kittens warm on the side of a road on a cold night in Canada was rescued and will soon be available for adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK FRIDAY: 48 Million Americans Still Have Debt From LAST YEAR...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/black-friday-is-coming-and-48-million-americans-still-have-holiday-debt-from-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest shopping day of the year is almost here, and marketers are working hard trying to extract as much money from U.S. consumers as possible.  Unfortunately, it is becoming increasingly difficult to get consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Gestures, Big Impact: Feeling Loved Increases Well-Being...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/small-gestures-big-impact-feeling-loved-increases-well-being-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that brief, seemingly mundane moments of love can make all the difference when it comes to feelings of self-worth and positive well-being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cave fire threatens homes in Santa Barbara County amid strong winds...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-25/fire-los-padres-national-forest-santa-barbara</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around midnight, parts of southern Santa Barbara County were experiencing power outages due to the fire that has spent hours chewing through the hillside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Colombia anti-govt protests intensify...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/colombia-protests-government-crackdown-latin-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mass anti-government protests that have arisen in several Latin American countries have boiled over into Colombia as thousands took to the streets in recent days, sparking fear and violence throughout the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House briefly on lockdown due to airspace violation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/26/white-house-on-lockdown-due-to-airspace-violation-fighter-jets-scrambled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Tuesday was briefly put on lockdown, as fighter jets were scrambled in Washington following an airspace violation, law enforcement officials told NBC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVP? RAVENS 22-Year-Old QB Sets NFL Record...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/11/25/baltimore-ravens-crush-rams-with-45-6-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 9-2, the Ravens have matched their best start since 2012, which ended in their second Super Bowl championship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed by feral hogs outside home: 'One of worst things I've ever seen'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/26/texas-woman-killed-feral-hogs-outside-home-she-worked-caretaker/4305584002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chambers County Sheriff Brian Hawthorne said Christine Rollins, 59, was found outside an elderly couple's home where she worked as a caretaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What It's Like To Drive 300 MPH -- From the Guy Who Did It...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/what-it-s-like-to-drive-300-miles-per-hour-from-the-guy-who-did-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What Itâ€™s Like To Drive 300 Miles Per Hour, From the Guy Who Did It</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer crocodiles: Why are more humans being attacked?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/killer-crocodiles-why-more-humans-being-attacked-east-042404566.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mario Da Cruz could only watch in horror as a small army of crocodiles killed a child on an East Timor beach -- another victim of the tiny nation's soaring rate of attacks. Such incidents have jumped more than 20-fold over the past two decades with an average of one person a month falling prey to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google tensions deepen over firings of 'Thanksgiving Four'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/google-tensions-deepen-over-firings-thanksgiving-four-112350895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google on Monday fired four employees on the grounds they had violated data security policies, but the tech titan was accused of persecuting them for trying to unionize staff. Google, the money-making engine of parent company Alphabet, confirmed a copy of the note published by Bloomberg News but declined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Loneliness of a Highbrow Teenage Songwriting Robot...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/loneliness-highbrow-teenage-songwriting-robot-111500888.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Meet Yona. She loves reading Margaret Atwood and articles about teenage life and sings about loneliness and relationships on her newly released track.If this sounds a bit scripted, that’s because it is: Yona’s not human.Yona has been created by London-based company Auxuman and trained</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful quake kills in Albania as buildings bury residents...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191126115656-cfuoi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANIA-QUAKE/USGS (UPDATE 10, PIX, TV):UPDATE 10-Powerful quake kills 13 in Albania as buildings bury residents</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
