<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AOC repeats 'f**king bitch' while accusing GOP Rep during wild House floor speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1187511/ocasio-cortez-repeats-gop-lawmaker-insult-house-floor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA Ocasio-Cortez repeated the Republican lawmaker’s “f***ing b**ch” insult in a wild House floor speech. Speaking on the House floor on Thursday morning, the 30-year-old Democra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX unveil jumbo Black Lives Matter mural at Fenway...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1186459/black-lives-matter-boston-red-sox-fenway-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Boston Red Sox unveiled a massive Black Lives Matter mural at Fenway Park on Wednesday ahead of Opening Day this week. The team revealed the 250-foot black and white billboard, which features t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PURPLE BOLTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1180883/east-coast-storm-gale-statue-liberty-world-trade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE World Trade Center and Statue of Liberty were struck by lightning as severe thunderstorms with 75mph gales savaged the East Coast on Wednesday evening. Dramatic photos captured the moment purpl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift Dropping Surprise Album TONIGHT; Going Head to Head With Kanye...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/23/taylor-swift-is-dropping-a-surprise-album-tonight-called-folklore-which-ironically-will-knock-kanye-west-off-the-headlines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taylor Swift has just dealt Kanye West a real blow. She’s surprise dropping a new album at the same time his “Donda” is supposed to be coming out. Could she have known under the U…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State reports most deaths in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article244430452.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would happen if Trump refused to accept loss?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-s-assault-on-election-integrity-forces-15426993.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's relentless efforts to sow doubts about the legitimacy of this year's election are forcing both parties to reckon with the possibility that he may dispute the result in November if he loses - leading to an unprecedented test of American democracy.  With less than four months before the election, Trump's escalating attacks on the security of mail-in ballots and his refusal again this week to reassure the country that he would abide by the voters' will have added urgency to long-simmering concerns among scholars and his critics about the lengths he could go to hold on to power.  "What the president is doing is willfully and wantonly undermining confidence in the most basic democratic process we have," said William Galston, chair of the Brookings Institution's Governance Studies Program. "Words almost fail me - it's so deeply irresponsible. He's arousing his core supporters for a truly damaging crisis in the days and weeks after the November election."  Most legal experts said it is hard to envision that Trump would actually try to remain in office after a clear defeat by former vice president Joe Biden, considering the uproar that would follow such a challenge to U.S. democratic norms. Trump has previously said he offers up inflammatory ideas to provoke the media and his critics.  But his unwillingness to commit to a smooth transition of power has forced academics and political leaders - including, privately, some GOP lawmakers - to contemplate possible scenarios.  The resulting turmoil could surpass the contention over the outcome of the 2000 presidential election, confounding the legal system, Congress and the public's faith in how the country picks its leaders. Such a crisis could also have long-lasting consequences for a nation that has already been rocked this year by the coronavirus pandemic,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Nuns At Michigan Convent Die Of Covid: 'It Went Through Like Wildfire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-convent-detroit-michigan-13-nuns-die-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nuns, who ranged in age from 69 to 99, included teachers, an author and a secretary in the Vatican Secretariat of State.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tea Party' rises up against ANOTHER $1 trillion bailout...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/508623-tea-party-rises-up-against-mcconnells-1-trillion-relief-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate over the size of the next coronavirus relief bill is reopening the same divisions within the Republican Party that spawned the Tea Party movement more than a decade ago, putting Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) in a delicate spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIDGE: I'd Resign Before Letting Federal Agents Invade Cities...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/07/22/tom-ridge-says-he-would-likely-resign-before-letting-federal-agents-into-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $135 million underwater lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90531142/see-the-135-million-underwater-lab-designed-by-fabien-cousteau-and-yves-behar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four times larger than any underwater lab to date, it could change underwater research forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans scrap Trump demand for payroll tax cut in relief bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/senate-republicans-tossing-out-payroll-tax-cut-trump-stimulus-checks-2020-7/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump had insisted on including the payroll tax cut in the GOP coronavirus relief bill. The development marks a dramatic reversal for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell's Bid for Gag Order in Case Denied by Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-23/ghislaine-maxwell-s-bid-for-gag-order-in-case-denied-by-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal judge presiding over Ghislaine Maxwell’s sex-trafficking trial rejected a request by her defense lawyers to impose a gag order preventing prosecutors, federal agents and lawyers for the alleged victims from discussing the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State reports record one-day increase in deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723135400-1okio</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida reports record one-day increase in COVID-19 deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans scrap Trump demand for payroll tax cut as they draft coronavirus bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2020/07/23/congress-stimulus-coronavirus-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leah Remini Wants to Expose Tom Cruise Dark Side...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/leah-remini-wants-to-expose-tom-cruises-dark-side</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “King of Queens” actress and ex-Scientologist, along with fellow whistleblower Mike Rinder, open up about Scientology’s most famous member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bragged About 'Pal' Jeff Bezos...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ghislaine-maxwell-bragged-about-pal-jeff-bezos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeffrey Epstein’s jail stint, his alleged madam tried to reinvent herself and get back in high society—and she made Silicon Valley money her ultimate target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah Dept of Agriculture investigates mysterious seeds sent from China...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox13now.com/news/local-news/utah-department-of-agriculture-investigates-mysterious-seeds-sent-from-china-to-tooele</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past few weeks, people in Utah have been reporting mysterious packages they’ve been receiving in the mail from China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots 'give TINDER run for money' as humans swapped for dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-give-tinder-run-22403340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to RealDoll's production manager, Mike Wilson, sex robots are on the cusp of rivalling popular dating app Tinder as the coronavirus pandemic forces people to seek alternatives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man seized by Secret Service outside Ivanka home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8552883/Man-seized-Secret-Service-outside-Ivanka-Trumps-house-early-morning-confrontation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was taken into Secret Service custody Thursday morning outside of Ivanka Trump's Washington, DC, home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59% don't plan to renew gym memberships...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/23/many-dont-plan-to-renew-their-gym-memberships-post-pandemic-survey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new TD Ameritrade survey, 59% of Americans say they have found more affordable ways to work out during the pandemic and don't plan on renewing their memberships when gyms reopen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas GOP infighting gives Dems hope of nabbing Senate seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/kansas-gop-infighting-gives-democrats-hope-of-nabbing-senate-seat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are suddenly more bullish about their chances of flipping the Republican-held Senate seat representing Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept Insiders Ask: What Is Susan Pompeo Really Up To?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/23/susan-pompeo-state-mike-378073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wife of Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has been integral to his meteoric rise. But her close involvement in his career has attracted unwelcome scrutiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tallest swing opens on  edge of 2,300ft cliff...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8552483/Worlds-tallest-swing-height-30-storey-building-opens-edge-Chinese-cliff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage shows thrill-seekers screaming as they were bound to a harness horizontally and flung out at a top speed of 80mph at the attraction's grand opening today in Chongqing, China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning Strikes Statue of Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://www.radio.com/articles/watch-massive-lightning-bolt-strikes-statue-of-liberty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video shared on social media captured the moment the Statue of Liberty was struck by a massive lighting bolt on Wednesday as a storm passed over NYC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices in Hamptons hit record as wealthy New Yorkers flee to beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/23/coronavirus-home-prices-in-hamptons-hit-record-as-wealthy-new-yorkers-flee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The median price of a single-family home in the Hamptons reached $1.1 million in the second quarter, marking a new record and an increase of 25% over last year's second quarter, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diets rich in beans, lentils, nuts linked to lower risk of early death...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/diets-rich-beans-lentils-nuts-223000851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources of plant protein include beans, lentils, chickpeas, edamame beans, nuts and quinoa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge to decide if newly imprisoned Michael Cohen can go home again...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723101315-nvvqz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/COHEN (PIX):U.S. judge to decide if newly imprisoned Michael Cohen can go home again</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazi guard convicted in Germany's 'last' Holocaust trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/nazi-holocaust-stutthof-trial/a-54274225</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 93-year-old former SS Nazi concentration camp guard has been found guilty of accessory to murder and handed a suspended sentence of two years. This may be the last verdict on a Holocaust perpetrator in a German court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,600 new cases every hour...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723091312-956hb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CASES (PIX, GRAPHIC):U.S. records 2,600 new coronavirus cases every hour as total approaches 4 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,100 deaths for second day in row...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723031027-ka4xd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CASUALTIES (UPDATE 1, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-U.S. records over 1,100 new coronavirus deaths for a second day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China blasts Houston consulate shutdown as Trump election gambit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723013254-mli2m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-CHINA/CONSULATE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China state media blasts Houston consulate shutdown as Trump election gambit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Very few Americans back full school reopenings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b133f482b2eba88f8bd733e2d15d13ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Virtual instruction. Mandated masks. Physical distancing. The start of school will look very different this year because of the coronavirus — and that’s OK with the vast majority of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labs buckle amid testing surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/969fbbf44dd2ba1acea130f95b21ef62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Laboratories across the U.S. are buckling under a surge of coronavirus tests, creating long processing delays that experts say are undercutting the pandemic response. With...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA orders China to shut Houston consulate in 'unprecedented escalation'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ffc84d09363ba0a1a0e6db3c05bb8322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States ordered China to close its consulate in Houston, escalating tensions between the world’s largest economies as President Donald Trump ramps up punitive measures...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls Trump the country's 'first' racist president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/323bba8b134eaedd188cf73122036a93</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden said Wednesday that President Donald Trump was the country's “first” racist president. The presumptive Democratic presidential nominee’s comments came during a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE CAFETERIA SHUT AFTER INFECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1184560/white-house-cafeteria-closed-coronavirus-worker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE White House office cafeteria has been closed after a worker contracted coronavirus. Three Trump administration officials confirmed the news to NBC, just hours before the president said that a d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group sues UT-Austin on behalf of white students who say they were unfairly denied admission...</title>
      <link>https://www.statesman.com/news/20200722/group-sues-ut-austin-on-behalf-of-white-students-who-say-they--were-unfairly-denied-admission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A national organization has filed a suit in federal court on behalf of two white members who claim the University of Texas did not give them a fair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 brothers, woman arrested in murder of 3 friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/arrests-massacre-3-friends-fishing-trip-polk-county-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the suspects, Tony "TJ" Wiggins, 26, had previously been charged with 230 felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Pays Above Face Value For Coins Amid Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/wisconsin-bank-pays-above-face-value-coins-amid-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate poised to defy veto with directive to change base names... </title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/world/americas/300063912/us-senate-poised-to-defy-trumps-veto-with-directive-to-change-military-base-names</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the Black Lives Matter movement, lawmakers chart collision course with US president who threated to veto any move to change the names of armed forces bases that commermorated Confederate generals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: All Mammals, Including Humans, Share Equal Brain Connectivity...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mri-study-reveals-all-mammals-including-humans-share-equal-brain-connectivity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After examining and comparing brain connectivity across 130 different mammals (including humans), a new study conclude that brain connectivity is equal among all mammals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worries about Trump and bloodbath at polls this fall stokes Republican feuding...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Worries-about-Trump-and-a-bloodbath-at-the-polls-15427337.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Tensions among congressional Republicans fueled by the party's diminishing electoral fortunes broke out into the open this week - as GOP lawmakers sparred over the shape of the next coronavirus aid package, how vigorously to stand behind President Donald Trump and which primaries to wade into that could help determine control of the Senate in November.  In the Senate, GOP senators continued to struggle to find consensus on a massive spending bill aimed at mitigating the pandemic and softening its economic impact - a task complicated by the president's insistence on a payroll tax cut that few in his own party want, intraparty feuding over the cost of the package and disagreements over exactly how the money should be spent.  Across the dome in the House, some of the Trump's closest allies launched a surprising attack against Rep. Liz Cheney, R-Wyo., the highest-ranking Republican woman on Capitol Hill, charging her with disloyalty to the president because she has bucked him on national security issues and embraced public health advice and officials whom Trump has dismissed.  And on Wednesday, allies of Senate Republican leaders formally threw their support behind the establishment choice in a heated GOP primary in Kansas, pitting themselves against a strong supporter of the president who was an early advocate of his immigration policies.  The battles this week were a microcosm of the broader reckoning over the party's future and how strong the populist tenets of Trumpism will hold after the president leaves office. The fractures are emerging now because of worries that the party faces doom at the polls this fall owing to Trump's handling of the pandemic and his resulting falling poll numbers against presumptive Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden.  Trump came from nowhere five years ago to effectively...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT INVESTIGATED FOR VIOLATION</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/President-Trump-was-maskless-in-the-lobby-of-his-15426603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The president's maskless appearance at Trump International Hotel this week -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon asks for restraining order...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/22/judge-oregon-request-restrain-federal-agents-378315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state's lawsuit is part of a growing pushback against the Trump administration's use of federal agents against protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Cardinal Ran 'Sex Cabal' at NJ Beach House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/crime/2020/07/former-cardinal-mccarrick-accused-of-participating-in-beach-house-sex-ring-lawyers-allege.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victim charges he and others were groomed and manipulated as teenagers when they visited New Jersey beach house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rare Area 51 pictures show giant hangar vanished...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/rare-area-51-pictures-shows-22399916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New long-range photographs of the top-secret military base deep in the Nevada Desert show a giant hangar previously pictured at the site is nowhere to be seen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 98 Californians infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/1-in-98-californians-infected-with-coronavirus-hospitalizations-at-all-time-high/article_d149c7ff-57b9-5cee-980e-eba2698f25a9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — More than 400,700 Californians — about 1 in 98 state residents — have been infected by the coronavirus. Of those, 7,755 have died as of Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARS IN 4 K:  RED PLANET LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SEEN IT BEFORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8549745/Incredible-images-captured-Mars-remastered-ultra-HD.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British YouTubers ElderFox Documentaries have taken thousands of pictures and converted them into ultra high definition for a 'world first' view of the Red Planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK DOES IT AGAIN: TESLA fourth straight quarter of profits...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/tesla-tsla-earnings-q2-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the period ending June 30, 2020, Tesla grappled with the effects of the Covid-19 pandemic and widespread civil rights protests on its employees, customers and U.S. factory operations, especially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil sets daily record of corona cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/brazil-sets-daily-record-of-new-coronavirus-cases-01595456404?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil recorded a new daily record of coronavirus cases Wednesday with nearly 68,000 infections, a sign COVID-19 is still far from being brought under control in the hard-hit country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDATORY WHEN LEAVING HOME</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/bowser-masks-mandatory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Face coverings will now be mandatory for any D. C. resident leaving their homes, D. C. Mayor Muriel Bowser announced during a Wednesday press conference. Bowser says this means a mask must be worn when ordering food at a restaurant, waiting for a bus, sitting in a cubicle in an open office space, and walking your dog, just to name a few examples. We know that without a vaccine or a cure for COVID, we have to continue to take precautions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 FINE FOR NOT WEARING MASKS IN DC</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/508526-dc-mayor-issues-order-requiring-masks-outside-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Mayor Muriel Bowser (D) issued an executive order Wednesday requiring residents to wear masks outside of the home as the city battles rising coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating chocolate 'wards off heart disease'...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/chocolate-heart-disease-coronary-artery-disease-231536646.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The indulgence could keep arteries healthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLS ANGELS Accused of Killing Leader of Rival Gang...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/22/hells-angels-accused-of-killing-leader-of-rival-biker-gang/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two members of the Hells Angels motorcycle gang and a third man were charged on Wednesday with carrying out the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Narcissists, Psychopaths Less Likely to Wear Masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/narcissists-psychopaths-face-mask-requirement-mandate-social-distancing-covid-19-coronavirus-1519732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS megadeal bucks conventional economic wisdom...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Dodgers-working-on-megadeal-for-Mookie-Betts-15426708.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of baseball's regular season opener, amid a global pandemic that makes projecting the sport's economic future difficult if not impossible, the Los Angeles Dodgers nonetheless were believed to be nearing a mammoth contract extension for new right fielder Mookie Betts that would make him among the sport's highest paid players.  Various reports and industry speculation pegged the prospective deal as being in the neighborhood of 10 to 13 years, with a value of between $350 million and $400 million. Boston radio station WEEI first reported the news that an extension was close with Betts, whose résumé includes an MVP award (2018), a World Series title (2018) and the type of production matched or exceeded by only a handful of players over the past few seasons.  Mike Trout's 12-year $426.5 million extension with the Los Angeles Angels remains the largest in the sport's history, and Gerrit Cole, Bryce Harper, Manny Machado and Giancarlo Stanton are also currently on deals worth north of $300 million. Cole's $36 million average annual salary is tops in the game on a per-year basis.  At one time, when the 2020 season hung in the balance due to both the coronavirus and the inability of Major League Baseball and its players' union to strike an economic deal, it appeared Betts would never play a meaningful game in a Dodgers uniform.  Traded to Los Angeles by the Boston Red Sox in exchange for three younger players in February - prior to what would be his final season before reaching free agency - Betts, 27, could have taken his services to the open market this offseason, where he would have been the biggest prize.  But the Dodgers clearly believe Betts is worth handing what would be the largest contract in team history - even at a time when the coronavirus threatens the sport's economics well beyond this summer. Many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans Arrested for Tweeting About Virus, Locked in Rotting Hotels....</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2020/07/22/caruzo-arrested-for-tweeting-and-locked-in-rotting-hotels-how-socialist-venezuela-fights-the-colombian-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has now been four months since the Chinese coronavirus lockdowns began in Venezuela with no apparent end in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holder Concerned Trump Could Use Force to Suppress Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/07/21/holder-we-have-to-be-concerned-about-trump-using-paramilitary-forces-to-suppress-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday's broadcast of MSNBC's "the ReidOut," former Attorney General Eric Holder stated that we should "be concerned" about President Trump using | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA NEARS PEAK LEVEL OF HOSPITALIZATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1286067275200512001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mutation outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/new-covid-19-mutation-helps-outbreaks-spread-quicker-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new coronavirus mutation has become the most dominant strain of the virus — and is causing outbreaks to spread more quickly across the world, an expert said. Professor Nick Loman, of the Un…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA surpasses NY in cases...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/california-coronavirus-governor-gavin-newsom-record-number-of-daily-new-cases-1202992176/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Governor Gavin Newsom on Wednesday reported a record 12,807 new coronavirus cases on Monday. He said this total was “the highest in the nation.” The previous record came on July 7 of 11…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAY BALL! Masked men, empty parks, odd sounds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59db961e7181936b80d834fede417167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opening day, at last. A baseball season that was on the brink before it ever began because of the virus outbreak is set to start Thursday night when excitable Max Scherzer and the World...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Love Hormone' May Reverse Alzheimer's Brain Damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/oxytocin-love-hormone-may-reverse-alzheimers-disease-brain-damage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although scientists know many of the underlying symptoms which trigger Alzheimer’s disease, a cure remains elusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARST Employees Say Mag Boss Led Toxic Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/featured/sns-nyt-hearst-harassment-troy-young-20200722-3i6gyysqbbdzpd3tqlsnefqr54-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades Hearst magazines have advised American women on how they should conduct themselves in the home (Good Housekeeping, Redbook); in society (Harper’s Bazaar, Town &amp; Country); and in the bedroom (Cosmopolitan).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Dropping Oppo on VP Rivals?</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/2020-election/kamala-harris-oppo-dump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris (D., Calif.), whose failed presidential campaign flamed out before any primary votes were cast, is a top contender to be Joe Biden's running mate in 2020. Curiously enough, negative stories about Harris's potential rivals for the VP slot have been popping up of late in mainstream media outlets. Imagine that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS Ink Outfielder Mookie Betts To $365M Mega Deal...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/22/rumor-mookie-betts-dodgers-close-to-massive-contract-extension/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Red Sox traded Mookie Betts away this past winter, some Red Sox fans held on to some hope that Betts may sign back with Boston as a free agent. Those hopes, small as they may have been, might already be dashed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Fall of Prominent CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-bizarre-fall-of-the-ceo-of-coach-and-kate-spades-parent-company</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of only five Black chiefs of a Fortune 500 company abruptly resigned after strange allegations — involving a hidden identity as photographer and an extramarital affair — resurfaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announces 'surge' of federal agents to Chicago, other cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-to-surge-federal-agents-to-chicago-amid-spike-in-violent-crime-move-opposed-by-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump announced on Wednesday that he is deploying 100 federal agents to Chicago to help combat rising crime rates – a move that marks an expansion of the White House’s intervention into local law enforcement as Trump continues to position himself as the “law and order” president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXAS TIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/trump-biden-locked-in-tight-race-in-texas-poll-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump and Joe Biden are in a dead heat in Texas, with a new Quinnipiac University poll showing the presumptive Democratic nominee with a slight edge, 45 percent to 44 percent, within the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas' first drive-thru strip club...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/texas-first-drive-thru-strip-club-has-2-song-limit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s all buns and no burger at this drive-thru. A Texas jiggle joint has found a creative way to attract customers while still letting their ladies strut their stuff during the COVID-19 outbr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs Warn Of Satanic Cult Activity, Animal Sacrifice Near SoCal Lake...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/21/fake-signs-satanic-cult-big-bear-lake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signs posted around Big Bear Lake warning campers of "satanic cult activity" are fake, city officials confirmed on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON expands robot delivery to more cities...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/amazon-expands-robot-package-delivery-system-to-more-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seen any 6-wheel delivery robots trekking about Snohomish County or Irvine, California? That&amp;rsquo;s Scout, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s fully-electric delivery system designed to distribute packages to customers using autonomous delivery devices. The system was officially launched in January of 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Kingdom of Judah complex found near US Embassy in Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/huge-kingdom-of-judah-government-complex-found-stones-throw-from-us-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the 2,700-year-old finds: 120 inscribed seal impressions on jars at storage facility holding food collected as taxes for kings Hezekiah, Menashe in First Temple times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans mull extending unemployment bonus at $400 through December...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/coronavirus-stimulus-republicans-consider-unemployment-insurance-extension.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are considering extending the enhanced unemployment insurance benefit at a reduced level of $400 per month through the rest of the year, sources told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Hospitals Struggling: 'Rooms Look Like War Zones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-coronavirus-hospitals-cases-covid-19-war-zones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While cities like Dallas and Houston are seeing a decrease in positive cases and hospitalizations, virus-related deaths in the state are up 33% over the last 10 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA WHISTLEBLOWER: 'THIS WAS INEVITABLE'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/a-public-health-employee-predicted-floridas-coronavirus-catastrophe-then-she-was-fired-this-is-everything-i-was-trying-to-warn-184810565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a complaint filed last Thursday, attorneys for Rebekah Jones, who designed a dashboard on coronavirus spread in the state, say she was fired for “refusing to publish misleading health data.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAMS WITH OBAMA IN NEW PUSH...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/joe-biden-barack-obama-2020-presidential-race-donald-trump-1202991746/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden’s campaign debuted a new video with Barack Obama, meant as a teaser of a longer conversation between the two on Thursday, as well as to show a contrast with Donald Trump’s pre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push to remove Confederate statues stalls in rural America...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/805877a5a480f49033ab8c726f5a7531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLINTON, La. (AP) — The statue of the anonymous Confederate soldier has stood in front of the white-columned East Feliciana Parish courthouse for more than a century, leaning on his rifle as he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety in the Bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/inside-the-nbas-covid-free-bubble </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC 'When You Leave Home' Mask Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.popville.com/2020/07/new-dc-mayor-order-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From the Mayor's briefing: "Lastly, it's simple: Wear a mask. Save lives. Stop the spread." Full release from the Mayor's Office: "Today, Mayor Bowser issued Mayor's Order 2020-080 to clarify and extend requirements related to wearing masks indoors and outdoors in Washington, DC. Additionally,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Uniformed sailor screams, 'F*** Trump', angrily confronts protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2020/07/21/video-shows-uniformed-sailor-screaming-f-trump-and-angrily-confronting-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her command saw the video and is investigating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARST Employees Say Mag Boss Led Toxic Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/22/business/media/hearst-harassment-troy-young.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Cosmopolitan staff meetings, workers complain of discrimination and tokenism. Former employees say Hearst Magazines president Troy Young made sexually offensive remarks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Sweden, female priests now outnumber male ones...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200722-in-sweden-female-priests-now-outnumber-male-ones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Sweden, female priests now outnumber male ones</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300,000 deaths by year-end?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/22/dr-scott-gottlieb-us-coronavirus-deaths-may-hit-300000-by-year-end.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Right now we have close to 1,000 casualties a day so if we don't change that trajectory, you could do the math," the former FDA commissioner told CNBC on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German state bars students from wearing full-face Muslim veils...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/22/german-state-bars-students-from-wearing-full-face-muslim-veils/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany’s third-largest state has banned girls from wearing full-face Muslim veils in its schools, according to a report. The move by officials in Baden-Württemberg came amid growing national…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try 'glory holes' for safer sex, B.C. CDC says...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/7204384/coronavirus-glory-holes-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;B.C.'s Centre for Disease Control suggested using a barrier to limit sexual contact during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUBIO:  Is front for 'massive spy operation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/22/marco-rubio-chinese-consulate-houston-front-massiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Marco Rubio, Florida Republican, on Wednesday said the Chinese consulate in Houston is basically a front for a massive spy operation after the State Department ordered the consulate to close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sees Ad 'Tsunami' with triple header Saturday!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/fox-sees-tsunami-of-ads-with-baseball-triple-header-saturday/ar-BB173xia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLD NEARS ALL-TIME HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/ever-lower-us-bond-yields-are-driving-gold-e2-80-99s-relentless-rally/ar-BB173rUT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typo gives away man who faked own death...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/da-typo-gives-away-man-who-faked-death-to-avoid-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spelling error and a font inconsistency indicated that a death certificate was fake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Restart: Sneak Peek Shows 'Black Lives Matter' Painted On Courts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-restart-sneak-peek-shows-black-lives-matter-painted-on-bubble-courts-distanced-seats-and-large-screens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The league continues to spread social justice messages as it prepares to resume its season in Orlando</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second wave hits Australia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-pandemic-worse-australia-sees-record-infections-090910225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus death toll in the United States has spiked again with President Donald Trump conceding the pandemic crisis is likely to get worse, as governments across Asia and Europe battled second waves of infections. Australia set a new daily high of 500 cases on Wednesday, likewise Hong Kong broke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Russians fuel private jet demand...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rich-russians-fuel-private-jet-demand-skirt-virus-032913920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For high-flying Russians used to spending summer holidays at Mediterranean resorts or in London penthouses, coronavirus restrictions that closed borders and grounded flights have made international travel a distant dream. Privately-operated flights from Moscow's airports more than doubled between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans in America 30,000 years ago, far earlier than thought... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/humans-america-30-000-years-ago-far-earlier-160114498.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tools excavated from a cave in central Mexico are strong evidence that humans were living in North America at least 30,000 years ago, some 15,000 years earlier than previously thought, scientists said Wednesday. Artefacts, including 1,900 stone tools, showed human occupation of the high-altitude Chiquihuite</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female leaders doing 'better job', says Lagarde... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/female-leaders-doing-better-job-virus-crisis-says-155427839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Female leaders are doing a better job handling the coronavirus crisis, European Central Bank chief Christine Lagarde said Wednesday, praising them for their honest communication and for showing they cared. Lagarde, who is the ECB's first female president, singled out German Chancellor Angela Merkel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEAMS WITH OBAMA IN NEW PUSH...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biden-teams-back-obama-election-push-145511405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's getting a big new assist from his old boss Barack Obama this week in the push to defeat President Donald Trump in just over 100 days. A preview of a sleekly produced discussion between the former president and vice president that will air Thursday features Biden questioning Trump'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amber Heard says Johnny Depp threw bottles at her 'like grenades'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amber-heard-says-johnny-depp-threw-bottles-her-152959610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US actress Amber Heard on Wednesday said her ex-husband Johnny Depp threw dozens of bottles at her "like grenades", as she gave evidence for a third day at his London libel action. Heard, 34, said Depp, 57, had lobbed "all the bottles in reach" towards her during an explosive 2015</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELP:  More Than Half Business Closures Permanent...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/yelp-restaurants-temporary-permanent-closures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eateries have been hit the hardest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-inspired food labeling raises alarms for those with food allergies...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/pandemic-inspired-food-labeling-raises-alarms-for-those-with-food-allergies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration released new “temporary guidance” for manufacturers facing supply chain shortages that allows them to make some ingredient substitutions without changing food label…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation on Verge of Lockdown 2.0...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-verge-lockdown-2-0-143003881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- After two months of what looked like a nascent recovery, the U.S. economy is faltering again. Restaurant reservations, one of the most commonly tracked indicators of local business activity, are stagnating:Americans are also a bit less mobile in July than in June:It’s not hard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insane stock price makes sense in world gone mad!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teslas-insane-stock-price-makes-110020507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can Tesla and the stock market as a whole continue to defy gravity?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
