<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Denmark's Omicron Surge Is Warning to Rest of World...</title>
      <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/government-economy/denmarks-omicron-surge-is-a-warning-to-the-rest-of-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businesstimes.com.sg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States preparing future without Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/12/10/abortion-restrictions-sanctuary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Either emboldened or alarmed by the Supreme Court, state leaders are enacting stiff new restrictions and mulling plans to provide a "sanctuary" for abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa Tops Major Cities at 8%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/tampa-inflation-tops-major-us-cities-at-8-25-in-november-from-year-ago/ar-AARGVdt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK MOST COVID IN YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10298323/Vast-majority-Britons-NO-PROTECTION-against-Omicron.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Britons have effectively no protection against the Omicron Covid variant, health experts have warned as the public was urged to get their booster jabs before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires Helping Ultra-Rich Live Their Space Fantasies....</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/billionaires-are-helping-ultra-rich-live-their-space-fantasies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires Are Helping Ultra-Rich Live Their Space Fantasies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark's Omicron Surge Is Warning to Rest of World...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-12-10/denmark-s-omicron-surge-is-a-warning-to-the-rest-of-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sticker shock!</title>
      <link>https://sg.finance.yahoo.com/news/high-sticker-shock-us-gas-222650437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Standing with the pump in her hand, Telila Scott was stunned to see the price of gas in Washington -- a sentiment many are feeling as costs rise across the United States."This is outrageous," said Scott, who is currently unemployed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom in Housing Prices Helps Hawaii More Than Any Other State...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boom-housing-prices-helps-hawaii-173040437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Home prices are rising in many areas of the U.S. Hawaii may be the state that benefits most.Most Read from BloombergAnatomy of a Bad RoadThe 15 Best Beers We Drank This YearSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaFormer Oil Trader Is Now Betting on Lumber for SkyscrapersLocal governments in the Aloha State are likely to reap the biggest property tax boost, followed by those in Connecticut and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Says Massive Cloud Outage Caused By 'Unexpected Behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-says-unexpected-behavior-caused-003144464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Amazon.com Inc. said automated processes in its cloud computing business caused cascading outages across the internet this week, affecting everything from Disney amusement parks and Netflix videos to robot vacuums and Adele ticket sales.Most Read from BloombergAnatomy of a Bad RoadThe 15 Best Beers We Drank This YearSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaFormer Oil Trader Is Now Betting on L</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy commander fired over refusal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/dec/10/lucian-kins-navy-commander-fired-over-vaccine-refu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Navy commander has been fired from his job as the executive officer of a warship because he refused to get a COVID-19 vaccine as required and refused to be tested for the virus, Navy officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine thinks Epstein was murdered in jail!</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/ian-maxwell-ghislaine-thinks-epstein-was-murdered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Away from the shenanigans of Westminster, the details of Ghislaine Maxwell’s ongoing trial have been filling our national newspapers this week. Images have been released of the British socialite cavorting with the convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein at Balmoral, the Queen’s home in Scotland, with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States call on military medics to relieve staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-delta-surges-and-the-threat-of-omicron-states-call-on-military-medics-to-relieve-hospital-staff/ar-AARHv9y?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges Biden agenda, but president says worst will soon pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/inflation-pinch-challenges-biden-agenda-but-president-says-worst-will-soon-pass/ar-AARHiqg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOLT:  Inflation highest since 1982!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/prices-climbed-68-25-in-november-compared-with-last-year-largest-rise-in-nearly-four-decades-as-inflation-spreads-through-economy/ar-AARGuFZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8-1 vote; Thomas dissent...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/abortion-providers-get-supreme-court-backing-to-fight-texas-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI patients dying 'at rate never seen before'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/09/us/hospital-covid-19-deaths-michigan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nurse Katie Sefton never thought Covid-19 could get this bad -- and certainly not this late in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASHES OUT MORE STOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/10/elon-musk-sells-another-963-million-of-tesla-stock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk sold 934,091 Tesla shares, according to filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission published Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40 degrees above normal!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/december-heat-wave-to-send-temps-soaring-30-40-degrees-above-normal/1059866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The approaching weather pattern next week has the potential to break a slew of records -- and leave some feeling like the last days before winter are more like the last days of summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron in CA weeks ago, before officials raised alarms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/omicron-california-weeks-officials-raised-164704430.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron coronavirus strain was detected in California's wastewater last month, even before the WHO declared it a 'variant of concern,' data suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial victory for opponents of law...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-says-challenge-texas-near-total-ban-abortion-can-n1285732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court didn't rule on the merits of the law, but rather on whether the abortion providers' lawsuit can move forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice urgent plea to colleagues...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/chief-justice-john-roberts-warns-supreme-court-over-texas-abortion-n1285747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roberts joined the high court’s three liberal justices in discussing the constitutionality of the Texas abortion law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA wins appeal to extradite Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/10/us-wins-appeal-over-extradition-of-wikileaks-founder-assange.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange, the 50-year-old founder of Wikileaks, is a step closer to being extradited after the U.S. government won an appeal in London's High Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes won't stop abortion ban, but OKs clinics' suit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-supreme-court-texas-56fe96917e21b53b581005cb30db66e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The &lt;a href="A divided Supreme Court refused Friday to block Texas’ ban on most abortions, offering only a glimmer of daylight for clinics in the state to challenge the nation’s most restrictive abortion law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOW TO PRESS FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/12/julian-assange-extradition-press-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A London court opened the door for the WikiLeaks founder to be sent to the United States to face charges for publishing government secrets, alarming First Amendment advocates. “This indictment criminalizes investigative journalism,” said one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA'S CONCORDE?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4247054/china-plans-build-12000mph-hypersonic-passenger-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA is developing a hypersonic aircraft that can transport ten people anywhere on Earth in one hour. The prototype has a pair of delta wings similar to those of the French and British designed Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia to ban capturing whales for aquariums...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211210-russia-to-ban-capturing-whales-for-aquariums</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian activists on Friday welcomed a move by President Vladimir Putin to close a legal loophole that allowed sea creatures, particularly whales, to be captured to perform in aquariums and other ven…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecution rests in sex-abuse trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-day-10-db137da495a547e4c3ffd4d9c16da4bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Another key accuser at the sex-abuse trial of Ghislaine Maxwell testified Friday that Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein forced themselves on her during a 1996 visit to the financier's sprawling New Mexico ranch when she was just 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after Quran damaged at university...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-crime-education-arrests-arizona-4f95e6cda18a7f5e29bfb2f6be8c4703</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEMPE, Ariz. (AP) — Arizona State University police have arrested a man they say is responsible for damaging Islamic literature and a copy of the Quran at the campus library. Police are investigating a motive for damage at the Hayden Library's interfaith room on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combat Mission in Iraq Has Ended. But Troops Not Coming Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2021/12/combat-mission-iraq-has-ended-troops-arent-coming-home/187433/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Train-advise-assist will continue, Pentagon says, with no force cuts planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift set to face trial over accusations she stole lyrics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taylor-swift-set-face-jury-152210133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Songwriters Sean Hall and Nathan Butler alleged that Swift copied the lyrics to the 2001 song 3LW they co-authored "Playas Gon' Play."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY imposes statewide mask mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/10/ny-gov-kathy-hochul-imposes-statewide-mask-mandate-amid-spread-of-omicron-covid-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Kathy Hochul issues a statewide mask mandate for all indoor public places unless businesses or venues have implemented a vaccine requirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  'Woke' On Wrong Side Of History...</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/the-woke-on-the-wrong-side-of-history-e7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need a racial politics for 2119, not 1619. Latinos will lead the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 school districts use 'cultural competency' to screening teachers' political beliefs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10296505/School-districts-screening-teaching-applicants-political-beliefs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent report from Ed Week detailed how school districts across the US are screening teachers' racial biases during the hiring process through 'cultural competency' questions about politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong to require quarantine camp stay for travellers from US...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211210-hong-kong-to-require-quarantine-camp-stay-for-travellers-from-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong will require inbound travellers from the United States to spend seven days at a government quarantine camp, after a passenger coming from the US tested positive for the Omicron variant of C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery: Scientists focus on animal origins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-covid-19-083bd75a801f9824e0b9ad7316062a5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly two years into the COVID-19 pandemic, the origin of the virus tormenting the world remains shrouded in mystery. Most scientists believe it emerged in the wild and jumped from bats to humans, either directly or through another animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONKEES singer-songwriter Michael Nesmith dies at 78...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/michael-nesmith-monkees-singer-songwriter-dies-78-rcna8395</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkees singer and guitarist Michael Nesmith, whose band exploded in popularity in the 1960s, has died, his manager said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent brawl breaks out at HARRAH'S in Atlantic City...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/10/brawl-erupts-at-harrahs-resort-in-atlantic-city-new-jersey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one person was taken to a nearby hospital to be treated for non-life-threatening injuries sustained in the melee, according to cops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary predicts Trump running again in '24: 'Make-or-break point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/politics/hillary-clinton-predicts-trump-running-2024-calling-make-break-point-rcna8347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton says Donald Trump running for president again in 2024 would have dire consequences for the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE allowing FACEBOOK to skirt privacy restrictions?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrum.com/news/2021/12/09/apple-allowing-meta-snap-skirt-privacy-restrictions-the-industry-reacts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrum.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Financial Times yesterday published a bombshell report that alleges Apple is allowing big tech players including Meta and Snap to access user-level data via iPhones – despite such approaches being supposedly forbidden under Apple’s new privacy policies. The Drum asks industry experts on what it means for marketers and media professionals – as well as the privacy space at large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIAMS FINAL WARNING: AMERICA UNRECONGNIZABLE</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/12/10/brian_williams_quits_msnbc_theyve_decided_to_burn_it_all_down_with_us_inside.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime NBC News broadcaster Brian Williams issued a strange warning Thursday as he retired from his 11 p.m. MSNBC show. "The reality is though, I will wake up tomorrow in the America of the year 2021, a nation unrecognizable to those who came before us and fought to protect it, which is what you must do now," Williams said. "They've decided to burn it all down with us inside. That should scare you to no end as much as it scares an aging volunteer fireman." BRIAN WILLIAMS, NBC NEWS: Well, look at the time. I'll try to keep this brief. After 28 years of peacock logos on much of what I own, it is my choice now to jump without a net into the great unknown. As I do for the first time in my 62 years, my biggest worry is for my country.  The truth is, I'm not a liberal or a conservative. I'm an institutionalist. I believe in is place. And in my love of my country, I yield to no one. But the darkness on the edge of town has spread to the main roads and highways and neighborhoods. It is now at the local bar, and the bowling alley, the school board, and the grocery store. And it must be acknowledged and answered for.  Grown men and women who swore an oath to our Constitution, elected by their constituents, possessing the kinds of college degrees I could only dream of, have decided to join the mob and become something they are not while hoping we somehow forget who they were. They've decided to burn it all down with us inside. That should scare you to no end as much as it scares an aging volunteer fireman. To my coworkers, my love and thanks... As a proud New Jersey native, this is where I get to say, "regrets, I've had a few, but then again, too few to mention."  What a ride it's been. Where else, how else was a kid like me going to meet presidents and kings and the occasional rock star? These lovely testimonials that I can never truly repay make me hyper-aware that it has been and remains a wonderful life. It's as if I'm going to wake up tomorrow morning in Bedford Falls.  The reality is though, I will wake up tomorrow in the America of the year 2021, a nation unrecognizable to those who came before us and fought to protect it, which is what you must do now. My colleagues will take it from here. I will probably find it impossible to be silent and stay away from you and lights and cameras after I experiment with relaxation and find out what I've missed and what's out there.  Every weeknight for decades now, I've said some version of the same thing. Thank you for being here with us. Us, meaning the people who produced this broadcast for you. And you, well, without you, there's no us. I'll show myself out. Until we meet again, that is our broadcast for this Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Blunder prevents early BUZZFEED employees from selling shares...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/buzzfeed-early-employees-stock-shares-4ec29fbd-0df5-4381-b3bc-90f5580ce384.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has given no indication that it plans to compensate them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Vows To Open Fire on US Troops Coming to Taiwan's Aid...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/china-vows-to-open-fire-on-us-troops-that-come-to-taiwans-aid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's military "will heavily attack U.S. troops who come to Taiwan's rescue" if a war between China and Taiwan breaks out, a possibility that is increasingly likely as the Communist regime readies its war machine on Taiwan's borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bishop tells children Santa doesn't exist...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-business-lifestyle-sicily-italy-793fc5902c3d4e203bb97ae873f94278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — A Roman Catholic diocese in Sicily publicly apologized to outraged parents after its bishop told a group of children that Santa Claus doesn’t exist. In a Facebook post and subsequent comments Friday, the diocese of Noto insisted that Bishop Antonio Stagliano didn’t mean to dash the dreams of the youngsters two weeks before Christmas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastating Solar Storm Spotted In Nearby Star System Could Be Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/solar-storm-life-on-earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study suggests that such a solar flare would fry satellites in orbit and crash power grids which serve entire cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA may be at start of winter surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/la-county-may-be-at-the-start-of-a-winter-covid-19-surge-health-official-says/ar-AARGCcz?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID crisis threatens holiday season as hospitals overflow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/covid-hospital-admissions-jump-in-u-s-led-by-northeast-states/ar-AAREQTC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos sending Strahan to space. But that's not what makes this flight significant...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Jeff-Bezos-is-sending-Michael-Strahan-to-space-16690872.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of the most remarkable years for human spaceflight, 2021 has seen more flights...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Williams Signs Off;  Warns 'They've Decided to Burn It Down With Us Inside'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/brian-williams-signs-off-the-11th-hour-for-the-final-time-warns-theyve-decided-to-burn-it-all-down-with-us-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Williams hosted his final episode of MSNBC’s The 11th Hour on Thursday night. The anchor’s final monologue lasted just over three minutes. It was as much a warning of what lies ahead for the country as it was an appreciation of those who made the show possible over the last five years. Last month, […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funds Ensnared in Expansive DOJ Probe Into Short Selling...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/hedge-funds-ensnared-in-expansive-doj-probe-into-short-selling-1.1694005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Justice Department has launched an expansive criminal investigation into short selling by hedge funds and research firms, scrutinizing their symbiotic relationships and hunting for signs that they improperly coordinated trades or broke other laws to profit, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From New York to Rockies, Spring-Like Warmth May Set New Records...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/york-rockies-may-basking-record-142238167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Temperatures from New York City to the Rocky Mountains will soar to spring-like heights in the days ahead -- once the Central U.S. shakes off Friday’s snow and ice warnings. Most Read from BloombergAnatomy of a Bad RoadThe 15 Best Beers We Drank This YearThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsFormer Oil Trader Is Now Betting on Lumber for SkyscrapersWarmth and mild air will sweep in just abo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buzz builds for new 'MATRIX'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/matrix-resurrections-teaser-clip-1235060627/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest sneak peek at the fourth film in the franchise dropped during The Game Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Muhammad Ali's grandson, family legacy extends beyond ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/2021/12/10/nico-ali-walsh-muhammad-ali-grandson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nico Ali Walsh looks to remain undefeated in his pro career as he prepares for his final challenge of 2021, a middleweight bout Saturday at Madison Square Garden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Maxwell Photo Signal Fresh Legal Danger for Prince Andrew?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/does-ghislaine-and-epstein-photograph-signal-fresh-legal-danger-for-prince-andrew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A just-revealed photograph of Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell lounging in the queen’s private Balmoral cabin shows just how toxic Andrew’s past is for the royals’ future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is NASA Sending New Telescope Million Miles Away?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/12/james-webb-space-telescope-lagrange-point/620935/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From one very specific point, a space telescope can see for light-years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another variant spreads in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1534321/covid-new-variant-found-france-marseille-hospital-forcalquier-ihu-b16402-omicron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANOTHER variant of coronavirus has been detected by experts working in Marseille, France, as the world continues to battle the deadly virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VR studio launches high-tech sex dolls to take user to 'futuristic brothel'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/vr-studio-launches-high-tech-25663944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virtual reality porn studio DaDoinkVR has teamed up with Berlin-based sex doll creator Kokeshi Cybrothel to merge the world of high-tech sex dolls with 180 degree stereoscopic virtual reality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Over, Tennis and Golf. Networks, Brands Cashing In on Pickleball...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/move-over-tennis-and-golf-networks-and-brands-are-cashing-in-on-pickleball</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move Over, Tennis and Golf. Networks and Brands Are Cashing In on Pickleball.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to make 1st late-night TV appearance as president...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-jimmy-fallon-2cfef220d15c5dcc07352d07e46c297c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is getting ready for his first late-night TV appearance since taking office. Biden is set to appear Friday on NBC’s “The Tonight Show” with comedian Jimmy Fallon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold weather states struggling to hire snowplow drivers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-storms-pennsylvania-e694fe4467db0116dd32fae4806d5dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) — More U.S. drivers could find themselves stuck on snowy highways or have their travel delayed this winter due to a shortage of snowplow drivers — a reality that could hit home Friday as winter storms start dumping snow from the Intermountain West to the Upper Great Lakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rift Between Senator, Son Shows the Challenge of Taxing Ultrarich...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/rift-between-senator-and-son-shows-the-challenge-of-taxing-the-ultrarich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — ADW Capital Partners would appear to be the kind of hedge fund that Democrats on the Senate Finance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In TX, Battle Over What Can Be Taught, and What Books Can Be Read...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/in-texas-a-battle-over-what-can-be-taught-and-what-books-can-be-read/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO — In late September, Carrie Damon, a middle school librarian, celebrated “Banned Books Week,” an annual free-speech event,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Innovation: Troll Philanthropy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/10/elon-musks-latest-innovation-troll-philanthropy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The richest people on earth typically devote a share of their vast resources to charity. That is the bargain and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK: I'M THINKING OF QUITTING...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/teslas-musk-says-he-is-thinking-of-quitting-his-jobs-2021-12-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk is "thinking of" leaving his jobs and becoming an influencer, the world's richest man tweeted on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braces for latest inflation surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/09/investors-brace-for-the-highest-inflation-reading-in-nearly-40-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street expects the the CPI to reflect a 0.7% gain for the month, which would translate into a 6.7% increase from a year ago</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan probing if lab mouse bite behind infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/asia/taiwan-probing-lab-mouse-bite-worker-covid-19-infection-2371846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI: Taiwan on Friday (Dec 10) said it was investigating whether a mouse bite may have been responsible for a worker at a high-security laboratory testing positive for the coronavirus, the island's first local infection in weeks. Health officials are scrambling to work out how a female employee at Acade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia Man Says YALE Secret Society Made Him Storm Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/militia-member-says-yale-secret-society-made-him-storm-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Militia Member Says Yale Secret Society Made Him Storm Capitol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House points finger at press...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/585187-white-house-points-finger-at-the-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden White House, plagued by low approval ratings that have weakened the president’s clout and raised fears among Democrats over next year’s midterms, is blaming the media for some of its problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hours after community gathered for Christmas tree lighting, it was set on fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hours-community-members-gathered-christmas-155300558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Beginning in 2019, the Washington Park Chamber of Commerce has hosted a Christmas tree lighting at Garfield Boulevard and Martin Luther King Drive where the community can gather and celebrate the holidays and decorations. And every year, the tree has been destroyed, according to the chamber’s CEO Donna Hampton-Smith. In 2019, someone ran over the display with their car, leaving ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: Plane Diverted After Passenger Assaults Air Marshal, Flight Attendant...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/09/passenger-detained-during-after-assaulting-an-air-marshal-and-flight-attendant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a Delta flight from Washington D.C. to Los Angeles has been detained in Oklahoma City after assaulting an air marshal and a flight attendant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax group targeted head of California Medical Board in 'stalking' incident...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/news/california-connection/anti-vaccine-group-targets-californias-medical-director/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of California’s medical board, which issues medical licenses and disciplines doctors, says a group of anti-vaccine activists stalked her at home and followed her to her office — where…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>53 die in horror crash of truck smuggling migrants in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-accidents-smuggling-4a101767083046f872999fe26c788c47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TUXTLA GUTIERREZ, Mexico (AP) — Rescue workers rushing to a highway accident found a horrific scene of death and injury after a freight truck jammed with as many as 200 migrants tipped over and crashed into the base of a steel pedestrian bridge in southern Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demaryius Thomas, former Pro Bowl wide receiver for BRONCOS, dies at 33...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/demaryius-thomas-former-pro-bowl-wide-receiver-for-the-broncos-dies-at-33/ar-AARGkwU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris nightmare before Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-e2-80-99s-nightmare-before-christmas/ar-AARFvKb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man filmed state trooper taking nap in car. Then he was retaliated against...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-man-filmed-a-massachusetts-state-trooper-taking-a-nap-in-his-car-then-he-was-retaliated-against-he-says/ar-AARGm71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
