<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Oil to $100?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/13/crude-to-100-trader-makes-the-case-for-a-spike-in-oil-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising crude oil prices should benefit several key energy stocks, two traders say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Arrested For Refusing To Cover Up Inside TX Bank...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/03/12/woman-arrested-for-resisting-trespass-after-not-wearing-mask-inside-texas-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was arrested at a bank in Galveston on Thursday after she refused to wear a face mask inside the building, police said. The encounter was captured on an officer's body camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of the wild: Great outdoors is great escape in pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-park-city-hiking-utah-coronavirus-pandemic-b05acc8365c0cbb7cc052d8d5ea69b68</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those venturing off the beaten path, be advised — it’s a little crowded out there. By nature’s standards, anyway, as the great outdoors has become the great escape. Hiking trails,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'd Much Rather Be in Florida'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/13/id-much-rather-be-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Other than New York, no big city in the United States has been struggling with more coronavirus cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway Reports Severe Blood Clot Cases After ASTRAZENECA Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/norway-reports-3-severe-blood-clot-cases-after-astrazeneca-shot/ar-BB1eyiZ9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Norway, among the countries that have suspended the use of AstraZeneca Plc’s Covid-19 vaccine, said three people who received the shot are being treated for severe blood clots and cerebral hemorrhages but said it was too soon to say if there was a connection. The people, who were all “of younger age,” had a reduced number of platelets in the blood, the Norwegian Medicines Agency said in a statement on Saturday. Norwegian health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress in naked lockdown protest at French Oscars...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/no-culture-no-future-actress-101455123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French actress stripped down naked on stage at the César Awards during a politically charged in protest at the months-long shutdown of cultural venues. Corinne Masiero wore a bloodstained donkey costume before removing her clothes to reveal the words "No culture, no future" written across her front as she presented the costume award on Friday. While most businesses have opened in France, theatres and cinemas have been closed for more than three months. Demonstrators have demanded that the government do more to end the halt of performances and support the industry battered by the pandemic. Several theatres were occupied on Friday in at least nine cities, while sit-ins at the Odeon Theatre on the Left Bank in Paris entered their eighth day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Singles Pleasuring Selves 3 Times A Day; 1 In 4 Watch More Porn; Third Claim 'Best Orgasm Ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/singles-pleasuring-themselves-more-than-ever-during-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Self-pleasure has seen an uptick since March 2020, with nearly half of respondents (48%) admitting to doing it more frequently than ever before as a result of their isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald and Hillary: Forever connected by self-created failure...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/542864-trump-and-hillary-forever-connected-by-self-created-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump both betrayed voters' trust with their vanity and condescending attitudes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction markets bet against Cuomo amid calls for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/13/prediction-markets-bet-against-gov-cuomo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The odds are against Gov. Cuomo. At least that’s according to the traders of PredictIt, a political predictions market that’s more or less a sportsbook for policy wonks.  The traders pu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-wife slept in locked bathroom?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2504621/andrew-cuomo-ex-wife-kennedy-locked-bathroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANDREW Cuomo’s ex-wife slept in a lockdown bathroom when he was home as the couple went through their divorce, it has been claimed. Cuomo biographer Michael Shnayerson revealed the claims abo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: ICE asks for volunteers as migrant complex SEVEN times over capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9358335/ICE-asks-volunteers-send-border-weekend-facilities-7-times-limit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 3,500 unaccompanied teens and children have been held in Customs Border Patrol (CBP) detention centers designed for adults in recent days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEBDO uses George Floyd death to mock Queen and Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14328040/fury-as-french-magazine-mock-the-queen-and-meghan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRENCH magazine Charlie Hebdo has sparked fury after they used George Floyd’s death to mock the Queen and Meghan Markle’s racism concerns. The satirical mag published a cover showing a cartoon cari…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. airport passengers hit highest level since March 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/u-s-airport-passengers-hit-highest-level-march-2020-n1261031</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials on Friday screened 1.357 million U.S. airport passengers, the highest number screened since March 15, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen has EIGHTH meeting with Manhattan DA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/12/former-trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-aids-da-vance-criminal-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan DA Cyrus Vance Jr., who said Friday he will not seek reelection, is investigating ex-President Donald Trump's company with the help of Michael Cohen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Manipulation Chatter Rises as Digital Art Scene Explodes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/market-manipulation-chatter-rises-digital-140000123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A digital artwork by Beeple set auction records Thursday when it sold at Christie’s for a mind-bending $69 million. Twitter Inc. co-founder Jack Dorsey is auctioning the non-fungible token for the first tweet ever, “just setting up my twttr,” with the highest bid coming in at $2.5 million, so far. LeBron James highlights are fetching six figures.If you were somehow unaware, digital assets are booming, with buyers paying up for so-called NFTs that give them exclusive ownership of electronic tchotchkes. Explanations for why, say, a GIF of a cat with a rainbow trail commands a king’s ransom aren’t hard to come by. The more prosaic theories say the price per pixel is surging as Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies mint new millionaires every day and those newly rich digital natives look to spend in their adopted domain. And sure, it could be as simple as a good old mania around the latest shiny object that’s caught people’s attention.But there’s also a nefarious suggestion popping up on message boards, Twitter and blogs that attributes at least some of the rise in prices to wash trading. That’s when a trader or group of traders buy and sell the same asset to create the illusion of heightened demand.The claim is hardly new: Wash trading has been called “crypto’s open secret” and concerns about its prevalence have dogged the space for years. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission in a 2019 response to an application for a Bitcoin exchange traded fund cited “fraudulent and manipulative activity” in the market as grounds for rejection.In a world where identities are abstractions with 30 or so alphanumeric characters representing some hidden person’s digital wallet address, claiming wash trading is at once plausible and yet nearly impossible to prove. Except for the most brazen of acts where two accounts repeatedly trade back and forth with each other, identifying self dealing requires forensic accounting tricks like employing Benford’s law or analyzing trade size distributions by how they fit with established mathematical principles like Pareto-Levy.“Crypto exchanges today are not regulated as much as regular exchanges where wash trading is clearly prohibited by regulators,” said Matthieu Soule, head of BNP Paribas C.Lab Americas, the bank’s innovation workshop. “That means that today’s investors have to trust the platforms where they are transacting on to prohibit and monitor such wash trade practices.”For its part, Nifty Gateway, one of the largest NFT exchanges by volume, says that it keeps watch for questionable transactions on its system.“To date we haven’t seen any evidence of wash trading on our platform, and we do monitor sales for abnormal activity,” a spokesperson for Nifty Gateway wrote in an email. “The majority of our customers purchase Nifties with credit cards, which require them to provide some personally identifiable information, and limits the risk of wash trading.”Still there are signs that there’s some truth to the tale of the wash trading boogie man.In a clear-cut case, analysts at NonFungible.com identified a Blockchain Cuties character that two accounts traded back and forth with each other over the course of a day.More extensive research has been done by two groups of academics focusing on cryptocurrency exchanges. While neither looked specifically at NFT markets, they both believe their research is applicable and that the illicit transactions may be present there as well.Will Cong, an associate professor at Cornell University’s SC Johnson College of Business and one of the authors of a paper that claims to have detected abnormal trading patterns on unregulated cryptocurrency exchanges, said that he didn’t see a major difference between the incentives to wash trade in currency and NFT markets.“Fraud detection is hard,” said Cong. “Even if they are all non-fungible, they’re still anonymous and it would be hard to track down market manipulators.”In another study, two researchers from the Technical University of Berlin wrote that decentralized exchanges where many crypto assets and tokens trade are “prone to manipulative behavior.”“Every interaction happens on chain and they’re done with some account that is virtually cost free to create,” said Friedhelm Victor, an author of the Berlin paper. “It’s really easy to create multiple accounts and trade with yourself.”But Victor cautions that high transaction fees on the Ethereum blockchain make wash trading a losing proposition.“Right now it’s so expensive to execute a transaction, for the fungible tokens it’s probably not attractive to do this right now,” said Victor. “That might change in a bear market” or as upgrades to the Ethereum blockchain which will make it cheaper to transact roll out.Victor’s sentiment is echoed by Tom Robinson, chief scientist and co-founder of Elliptic, a blockchain data tracker.“Wash trading of NFTs is unlikely because trades are taking place on transparent, public blockchains for everyone to examine,” said Robinson. “In addition, transaction fees on blockchains such as Ethereum are very high, making such activity prohibitively expensive.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's ATV Wars Put Greens and Gas Guzzlers on Collision Course...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/utahs-atv-wars-put-greens-and-gas-guzzlers-on-a-collision-course</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fight between off-highway vehicles and environmentalists has been raging for years. Now it’s gotten even hotter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German cases could revisit December peak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210313131558-9pe16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GERMANY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-German COVID cases could revisit December peak in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress strips at Cesar Awards to protest France's COVID-19 strategy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210313095851-l6ll1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-CINEMA/CESAR (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Actress strips at Cesar Awards to protest France's COVID-19 strategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai Sees Population Surging 76% on Lure of Beaches, Greenery...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/dubai-sees-population-surging-76percent-on-lure-of-beaches-greenery/ar-BB1exO1k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Dubai unveiled an urban plan for the next two decades that envisages the population growing by 76% and focuses on boosting waterfront acreage with the view of making the city’s quality of life the best in the world. “The length of our beaches will increase by 400% during the next 20 years and 60% of Dubai’s area will be nature reserves,” Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid al Maktoum, ruler of the emirate known for man-made islands, wrote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman pretending to be plastic surgeon arrested after bad nose surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/2021/03/12/florida-woman-pretending-to-be-plastic-surgeon-arrested-after-bad-nose-surgery-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was in the middle of performing another procedure on a different patient on Thursday when detectives got to the office and arrested her, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Million Masks Thrown Out -- Every Minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/3-million-face-masks-thrown-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disposable masks are not biodegradable and don't completely break down, meaning plastic particles linger and spread into the local ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Granny shouldn't be out here': Maskless spring breakers flout South Beach rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/granny-shouldn-t-be-out-here-maskless-spring-breakers-flout-floridas-south-beach-covid-19/article_216f39ef-ba1d-5ecd-870e-180cc96fe9a3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — With a black mask pulled under his chin, 22-year-old Ace Beck weaved through spring breakers on busy Ocean Drive without any concern for catching COVID-19 — or unwittingly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mauna Loa, World's Biggest Volcano, Waking Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/ericmack/2021/03/12/mauna-loa-the-worlds-biggest-volcano-is-waking-up-and-its-time-to-prep-for-an-eruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mauna Loa’s long nap may be coming to an end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin $60,000...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-hits-60-000-record-115241121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin, the world's biggest cryptocurrency, on Saturday crossed a record high of $60,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insulting police officer crime in Kentucky? Senate approves it...</title>
      <link>http://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/will-insulting-a-police-officer-become-a-crime-in-kentucky-the-senate-approved-it/article_e25da9f4-e374-5db4-a1dd-561c63c719a8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEXINGTON, Ky. —After one of the most emotional and confrontational debates in Kentucky's General Assembly this year, the state Senate Thursday night approved a bill that would make insulting a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another mystery boom leaves San Diego grasping for answers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/science/story/2021-03-13/big-boom-mystery-noise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonic boom? Skyquake? The weather? Latest San Diego noisemaker has people wondering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Thirds of Italians Set For Lockdown as Pandemic Worsens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/two-thirds-of-italians-set-for-lockdown-as-pandemic-worsens/ar-BB1evIez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government of Prime Minister Mario Draghi is weighing stringent new restrictions on as many as two-thirds of Italians, with the regions encompassing the country’s largest cities possibly heading into lockdown amid a resurgence in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany declares 'third wave' has begun...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/12/germany-declares-a-covid-third-wave-has-begun-italy-set-for-easter-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy is reportedly set to impose another near national lockdown over the Easter weekend in an effort to curb the spread of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Cuomo won't resign, bow to 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/542957-cuomo-defiant-in-face-of-calls-to-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) said Friday he would not resign from office in the face of mounting allegations of sexual misconduct, hours after most Democratic members of Congress from his home state urged him to quit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
