<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Real data on Wuhan virus deaths may have leaked...</title>
      <link>https://www.taiwannews.com.tw/en/news/3871594</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.taiwannews.com.tw&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tencent briefly lists 154,023 infections and 24,589 deaths from Wuhan coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom seeks peace with Trump in water wars. Enviros ready to fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/environment/article239967733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot could call last orders on human bartenders...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-robot-bar/japanese-robot-could-call-last-orders-on-human-bartenders-idUSKBN1ZY17K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's first robot bartender has begun serving up drinks in a Tokyo pub in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine has been boon for civilization. But it has come at a cost...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Caffeine-has-been-a-boon-for-civilization-15031811.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Pollan laughs and says, yes, he's on drugs while conducting this interview. Okay, he doesn't use those exact words, but he acknowledges that he has a "tall, takeout container" of half-caff coffee at his side as we discuss, via phone, his latest project, simply titled "Caffeine," available only as an audio book from Audible.  Pollan, the author of "The Omnivore's Dilemma," "The Botany of Desire," "In Defense of Food" and "How to Change Your Mind" - in which he has explored our complicated relationship with food, plants, drugs and many other things we take for granted - has turned his imposing analytical skills to caffeine, the most popular mind-altering chemical on the planet.  "For most of us, to be caffeinated to one degree or another has simply become baseline human consciousness," Pollan writes, well, reads in "Caffeine." "Something like 90% of humans ingest caffeine regularly, making it the most widely used psychoactive drug in the world and the only one we routinely give to children, commonly in the form of soda. It's so pervasive that it's easy to overlook the fact that to be caffeinated is not baseline consciousness but, in fact, is an altered state."  After others suggested the idea, Pollan decided to get off caffeine, cold turkey, to better understand the stimulant's effects on human consciousness. Last year, he abstained from coffee and tea for three months. As he notes in "Caffeine," the experiment nearly killed his enthusiasm for the book. "How can you possibly expect to write anything when you can't concentrate?" Pollan writes about his withdrawal symptoms, a state so intense that it's officially classified as a mental disorder by the American Psychiatric Association.  When Pollan ended his caffeine fast, he promised himself to drink coffee and tea only on Saturdays. Our interview was on a Monday....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record year for Morocco tourism with 13 million visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabnews.com/node/1623446/middle-east</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RABAT: A record 13 million tourists visited Morocco in 2019, up 5.2 percent from the previous year, official figures showed Wednesday. The number includes Moroccans from the diaspora, who account for around half of visitors annually. Tourism revenues hit 78.6 billion dirhams ($8.16 billion) in 2019, up from 73.04 billion dirhams ($7.58 billion) the year before, the Moroccan Tourism Observatory said. It attributed the rise — for the first crossing the 12-million mark — to its primary markets, France and Spain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right backing for regional politician shocks Germany...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/far-backing-regional-politician-shocks-germany-151451818.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny central state of Thuringia broke a German political taboo Wednesday after a candidate for the regional premiership was heaved into office with help from the far right for the first time ever, prompting a storm of outrage. Thomas Kemmerich, a politician from the economically liberal Free Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In divided America, impeachment may become less rare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/divided-america-impeachment-may-become-less-rare-144448209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the more than 230 years of US history, only three presidents have suffered the humiliation of an impeachment trial. Only Andrew Johnson in 1868, Bill Clinton in 1998 and now Donald Trump have faced Senate impeachment trials. The Constitution sets a high bar for the removal of a president requiring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond burnout: Doctors decry 'moral injury' from financial pressures of health care...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/beyond-burnout-docs-decry-moral-injury-from-financial-pressures-of-health-care/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors and other clinicians say they’re enduring moral injury because the business of health care interferes with patient care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rock 'SAW' Reboot Offers Up First Twisted Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/spiral-trailer-chris-rock-saw-reboot-gets-first-twisted-preview-1276453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lionsgate's 'Spiral,' directed by Darren Lynn Bousman, stars Rock and Samuel L. Jackson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Woman wearing face mask attacked; 'Diseased bitch'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/05/woman-wearing-face-mask-attacked-in-possible-coronavirus-hate-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eyewitness claimed the victim had already been hit on the head when she ran to confront her attacker, who unleashed a another flurry of blows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby tests positive 30 hours after birth...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/05/chinese-baby-tests-positive-for-coronavirus-30-hours-after-birth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese baby has been diagnosed with coronavirus just 30 hours after a woman who had tested positive for the deadly disease gave birth in the epicenter city of Wuhan, according to state media. Do…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump acquittal on track ahead of Senate vote... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/93c85dcfb0e6b2185391965e77ebea51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is on the verge of acquittal by the Senate, an end to only the third presidential impeachment trial in American history but coming at the start of a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB Mainstream March as Stars Debut at Fashion Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/pornhub-continues-its-march-to-the-mainstream-as-streaming-stars-make-fashion-week-debut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The YouTube of porn is a privately owned behemoth generating an estimated million dollars a day. Now fashion brands are seeking to cash in on the brand’s ubiquity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan crematoriums burning '100 bodies a day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/wuhan-coronavirus-crematoriums-working-247-21434630</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worker at a funeral home in Wuhan has reportedly made the disturbing claims – as Chinese authorities have insisted the official death toll remains at just under 500</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private payrolls soar; Best gain in 5 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/05/adp-moodys-private-payrolls-january-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADP/Moody's Analytics said private payrolls rose by 291,000 in January, nearly twice the expected gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Jones Warns Dems: Trump Helping African-Americans 'In Real Life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/02/05/van-jones-warns-democrats-trump-is-helping-african-americans-in-real-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN contributor Van Jones warned Democrats that President Donald Trump was helping African-Americans "in real life."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Lock Potential Victim in Own Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/china-police-lock-potential-coronavirus-victim-in-her-own-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House arrest gets a new meaning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped on virus-ravaged cruise ship, shocked passengers struggle to keep spirits up...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trapped-on-virus-ravaged-cruise-ship-shocked-15031425.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOKOHAMA, Japan - Quarantined for two weeks on a cruise ship ravaged by coronavirus, the Britons on board have only one option: keep calm and carry on.  David Abel and his wife Sally are still smiling, for now. Their friends Alan and Wendy Steele are going "stir crazy" trapped in their cabin - although they say they are not worried about catching the deadly illness. Still, this was not how the Steeles planned to spend their honeymoon.  Many of the 2,666 passengers and 1,045 crew members on the Diamond Princess are struggling to keep their spirits up, after the luxury liner was quarantined off the Japanese coast Wednesday, with passengers forbidden to leave their cabins.  Last Saturday, a man from Hong Kong who had spent five days aboard the ship was confirmed as having contracted coronavirus. On Wednesday, with the ship docked at the port of Yokohama, Japan's Health Ministry said nine other passengers and one Filipino crew member had tested positive.  "We've got two weeks' extra cruise, albeit a confined cruise," David Abel, 74, said on a Skype call from his cabin. "You've got to make the best of the situation, haven't you? But I'm sure that in 10 or 12 days' time, I'll be pulling my hair out."  The nine passengers who tested positive - two Australians, three from Japan, three from Hong Kong, and one American - have been transferred to hospitals, but none is in serious condition, said Japanese Health Minister Katsunobu Kato. They were among 31 people deemed at high risk who were initially examined for the virus, while samples from 242 other people are still being tested.  For those left on board, there is nothing to do but sit in their cabins, wait for meals to be delivered, watch television or a choose from a limited selection of movies on demand. Those lucky enough to have a balcony can at least sit in the sun, look at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priests on sex offender registry find home in alternative ministry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/priests-on-sex-offender-registry-florida-alternative-catholic-churches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Independent catholic churches tout themselves as beacons of progressive ideology and "forgiveness" — but some are hiring registered sex offenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City braces for throngs of fans at CHIEFS parade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ad2e86bd9620028158cfd9f99e13f39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — Hundreds of thousands are expected to flood downtown Kansas City on Wednesday despite a predicted winter storm as the triumphant Chiefs bring home a Super Bowl trophy for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not robot': AMAZON workers condemn unsafe, grueling conditions at warehouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/feb/05/amazon-workers-protest-unsafe-grueling-conditions-warehouse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees under pressure to work faster call on retail giant to improve conditions – and take their complaints seriously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Admiral Warns East Coast No Longer 'Safe Haven' Thanks To Russian Subs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/32087/admiral-warns-americas-east-coast-is-no-longer-a-safe-haven-thanks-to-russian-subs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increased Russian sub activity means that the Navy no longer views sailing off the East Coast or across the Atlantic to be "uncontested" movements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of trial to leave deep scars...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/481516-end-of-impeachment-trial-to-leave-deep-scars-in-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bruising battle over President Trump’s impeachment will come to an end Wednesday afternoon, and senators who have clashed for weeks over trial procedures say it will leave deep scars that may take months to heal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight-year-old rapper strikes chord in Uganda with songs about poverty...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200205092514-cs9vo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eight-year-old rapper has become a household name in Uganda, a country mired in poverty and corruption, for singing about his parents' struggles to provide for him and his four siblings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Born Kind? Researchers Prove Altruistic Behavior Begins In Infancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/benevolent-babies-infants-quick-to-share-food-help-others-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers studied nearly 100 infants, and discovered they were quick to share their food, even when they themselves were undoubtedly hungry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES 'BEST IS YET TO COME'</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/02/04/trump_at_state_of_the_union_the_best_is_yet_to_come.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump promised "the best is yet to come" at the 2020 State of the Union address. PRESIDENT DONALD J. TRUMP: This is our glorious and magnificent inheritance. We are Americans, we are pioneers, we are the pathfinders, we settled the new world, we built the modern world and we changed history forever by embracing the eternal truth that everyone is made equal by the almighty hand of God. America is the place where anything can happen. America is the place where anyone can rise. Here, on this land, on this soil, on this continent, the most incredible dreams come true. This nation is our canvas and this country is our masterpiece. We look at tomorrow and see a limited frontiers just waiting to be explored. Our brightest discoveries are not yet known. Our most thrilling stories are not yet told. Our grandest journeys are not yet made. The American age, the American epic, the American adventure has only just begun. Our spirit is still young. The sun is still rising. God's grace is still shining. My fellow Americans, the best is yet to come. Thank you. Thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkland father removed from speech after protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article239976003.html?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI RIPS UP SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/watch-nancy-pelosi-rips-up-trumps-sotu-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi tore up a copy of President Donald Trump's speech at the conclusion of his State of the Union address on Tuesday night. The event was marked by concurrent spectacles. T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotions run high...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200205030741-tofp0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/SPEECH (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Trump snubs Pelosi, she tears up his speech as impeachment trial nears end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP AWARDS LIMBAUGH MEDAL OF FREEDOM AT STATE OF UNION</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/02/04/melania_trump_awards_rush_limbaugh_presidential_medal_of_freedom_at_trump_state_of_the_union_address.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch: First lady Melania Trump presents Rush Limbaugh with Presidential Medal of Freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF UNION: President confronts impeachment foes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/314d6d298427151dc580f81a3ebece78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Addressing the nation in extraordinary times, President Donald Trump declared America “stronger than ever before” Tuesday night as he delivered his State of the Union address on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence photos of naked Harvey passed around jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-harvey-weinstein-trial-20200204-voz53d3oxvfwrhw3vjydczl2q4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jessica Mann, returning to a Manhattan courtroom one day after a witness stand meltdown, also testified that her access to the Oscar-winning movie maker could be a positive thing when asked by defense attorney Donna Rotunno about reaching out to Weinstein for help with a 2016 business venture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD scandal opens window into California's secret gang database as reforms debated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lapd-scandal-opens-window-into-californias-secret-gang-database-as-reforms-debated/ar-BBZDnOD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless camp the size of 3 football fields catches fire in Austin...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/officials-consider-next-steps-after-large-homeless-camp-fire-in-ne-austin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire broke out at a large homeless camp below the eastbound frontage road of Anderson Lane, between IH-35 and Cameron Road Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468549-1/2020-state-union-address&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump delivers the State of the Union address to a joint session of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Seeks to Capitalize With New Ad Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-seeks-capitalize-iowa-chaos-213026309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Michael Bloomberg is doubling his already unprecedented television advertising budget and expanding his field staff in an effort to capitalize on the chaos in the Iowa caucus.Bloomberg, who is skipping the first four contests in February, is immediately increasing spending on ads in markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubs Pelosi handshake...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-snubs-pelosi-handshake-attempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS Voter Reveals Ballot: 'MARRIAGE STORY' Was Fake, 'IRISHMAN' Boring...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/brutally-honest-oscar-ballot-irishman-was-boring-tarantino-amazing-1275576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As voting ends, a female member of the Academy's actors branch, granted anonymity to speak freely, shares which films earn her precious vote (and — gulp — why).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madness or visionary investing?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b98dbef7b86e27b98698cddf9567d778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Eight months after it seemed headed for the corporate junkyard, Tesla is now worth more than General Motors, Ford and Fiat Chrysler combined, even though the Big Three together sell...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's poor showing shakes establishment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a6ea236b5abcb43b40f79cfbf3f8c20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Joe Biden's third presidential bid enters a critical stretch after a disappointing finish in the Iowa caucuses sent the former vice president on to New Hampshire with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newport Beach Swinging Surgeon Cleared of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/grant-robicheaux-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Newport Beach surgeon and girlfriend Cerissa Riley were charged with rape by drugs, oral copulation by anesthesia, and assault with intent to commit sexual offenses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Administration Proposes Government Licenses for News Websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2020/02/03/trudeau-minister-proposes-forcing-news-websites-government-license/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Heritage Minister Steven Guilbeault has stated that news websites could be forced to obtain government licenses to operate in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIZA OPENS UP  IN RARE INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/features/liza-minnelli-judy-garland-bob-fosse-rehab-1203490846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liza Minnelli is getting ready to be photographed for the cover of Variety. She’s wearing an off-the-shoulder black beaded shirtdress and perched on a director’s chair. As she adjusts herself, tryi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Attorney Questions Accuser's Psychiatric History; 'Private' Photos Of Harvey Shown To Jury...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-jessica-mann-psychiatric-history-private-photos-shown-to-jury-1202851381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defense team for accused rapist Harvey Weinstein on Tuesday questioned accuser Jessica Mann about her psychiatric and emotional history, eliciting responses indicating that Mann had been diagno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Unveils Electronic Trackers for Suspected Virus Carriers...</title>
      <link>https://coconuts.co/hongkong/news/govt-unveils-new-electronic-tags-for-people-under-wuhan-coronavirus-home-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coconuts.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Top TV News Anchors Over for Lunch; Eats Them Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-had-americas-top-tv-news-anchors-over-for-lunch-and-ate-them-alive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast learned that Trump’s off-record Tuesday lunch with prominent news anchors was surprisingly “chill,” with the president mocking his chuckling guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUCUS CONFUSION:  DEMS RELEASE PARTIAL RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2020/02/04/iowa-democratic-party-delayed-caucus-results-should-soon-published/4659581002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We hit a stumbling block," Iowa Democratic Party chair Troy Price said Tuesday, "but we know this data is accurate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TO AWARD LIMBAUGH MEDAL OF FREEDOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/rush-limbaugh-donald-trump-medal-of-freedom/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump told network anchors during a private lunch Tuesday that he will award Rush Limbaugh with the Medal of Freedom, one day after the prominent political radio host announced he has advanced lung cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Hyped Digital Startup Behind 'Shadow'...</title>
      <link>https://theoutline.com/post/8636/acronym-shadow-iowa-caucus-results-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theoutline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shadow, a branch of the glossy digital strategy startup, was a mess from the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Dolls Experience raises eyebrows in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-las-vegas/sex-dolls-experience-raises-eyebrows-in-las-vegas-neighborhood-1950537/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neighbors and county officials are concerned about the existence of an alleged sex doll brothel and sex club operating in a central Las Vegas neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not bitter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/04/trump-on-impeachment-not-bitter-110720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president told television anchors ahead of his State of the Union address that he’ll defer comments about impeachment until his acquittal a day later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/2020-election/results/iowa/?2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explore POLITICO's real-time 2020 Iowa election results and live maps by county and district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Collins will vote to acquit...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/maine-gop-sen-susan-collins-key-swing-vote-senator-announces-she-will-acquit-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine Republican Sen. Susan Collins, a key swing vote in President Trump's impeachment trial, announced she would vote to acquit on both articles of impeachment -- noting that Democrats' "abuse of power" charge "did not even attempt" to allege that Trump had committed a crime, and instead constituted a "difficult-to-define, non-criminal act."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates snipe at each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/04/buttigieg-narrative-iowa-caucus-official-results-110663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blame game kicked into high gear as the Iowa Democratic Party prepares to release a portion of the caucus results at 5 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House excludes CNN from session, with no protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/ap-top-news/2020/02/04/white-house-excludes-cnn-from-trump-session-with-no-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House excluded CNN from its annual off-the-record briefing with television news personalities prior to the State of the Union address</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic 'black goo' base used by U.S. had enriched uranium. Vets report cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article239856133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S to close 125 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/macys-to-close-125-stores-sees-480-million-in-restructuring-costs-to-2000-corporate-jobs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macy's stock, which is valued at more than $5 billion, has fallen 36% over the past 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez skipping...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/AOC/status/1224794340272242689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“After much deliberation, I have decided that I will not use my presence at a state ceremony to normalize Trump’s lawless conduct &amp;amp; subversion of the Constitution. None of this is normal, and I will not legitimize it. Consequently, I will not be attending the State of the Union.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macau casinos told to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/china-virus-claims-second-life-off-mainland-macau-casinos-told-to-close-idUSKBN1ZY05A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus outbreak claimed its first life in Hong Kong on Tuesday, compoun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even middle class having trouble paying rent now...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-rent-is-too-damn-high-even-for-middle-income-americans-2020-02-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in four renters now spend more than half their incomes on housing, a new study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'accidentally' sends users' private videos to strangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/google-accidentally-sent-some-users-private-videos-to-strangers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google apologized on Tuesday for accidentally sending users' private videos to strangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why vegans inspire hatred...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200203-the-hidden-biases-that-drive-anti-vegan-hatred</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People love to moan about vegans: research shows only drug addicts inspire the same loathing. Now psychologists may understand why – and the reasoning isn't entirely rational.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors Rush to Downplay Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/investors-rush-to-downplay-ties-to-shadow-the-firm-behind-iowa-caucus-clusterfuck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frantic cleanup put a microscope on one of Democratic Party’s fastest-rising digital stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE FURIOUS...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2020/02/04/bernie-sanders-disappointed-iowa-democrats-havent-released-caucus-results/4656451002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before heading to New Hampshire, the senator said that results should not take this much time to release in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tries to reassure donors; Guarantees Nevada, SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/biden-reassures-donors-he-will-win-nevada-south-carolina-after-iowa-caucus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a conference call with some of Biden's top donors hours after the Iowa contest concluded, campaign officials said they were confident they can win the two votes at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Wilson Urges Fans To Boycott BEACH BOYS Over  Trump Jr. Hunting Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brian-wilson-beach-boys-boycott-urges-fans-over-donald-trump-jr-hunting-event-safari-club/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wilson shared a petition that urges fans to stop buying or downloading the band's music, going to their concerts and purchasing merchandise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand names 'whistleblower' in Senate...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200204173901-7ij95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-PAUL:Republican Rand Paul names purported 'whistleblower' in the Senate</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
