<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg claims humans will live in metaverse one day and leave reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4808267/mark-zuckerberg-living-in-metaverse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOU may think you spend too much time on Facebook but its founder thinks we’ll all live in a virtual reality one day. Mark Zuckerberg, CEO of Meta Platforms, has big plans for the metaverse a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MAJOR CITY FALLS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4810517/ukraine-city-falls-russians-kherson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE first major city in Ukraine has fallen to the Russian invaders a week after Vladimir Putin ordered his troops into the country. The mayor of Kherson has now admitted Kremlin forces are now in c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India and China abstain on UN vote to condemn...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4808822/china-india-abstain-un-vote-russian-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA and China faced an angry backlash last night after they abstained on a UN vote to condemn the invasion of Ukraine. Most of the world united in backing the UN General Assembly motion calling o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer travelers are nervous about Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/after-russia-e2-80-99s-invasion-of-ukraine-summer-travelers-are-nervous-about-europe-should-they-be/ar-AAUwVXx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efforts to pressure Pence, overturn election results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-committee-alleges-trump-allies-engaged-in-potential-e2-80-99criminal-conspiracy-e2-80-99-by-trying-to-block-congress-from-certifying-election/ar-AAUwYUj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI detects mental disorders based on web posts...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-03-ai-mental-disorders-based-web.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dartmouth researchers have built an artificial intelligence model for detecting mental disorders using conversations on Reddit, part of an emerging wave of screening tools that use computers to analyze social media posts and gain an insight into people's mental states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to lift strict travel requirements...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hawaii-lift-strict-travel-requirements-180026419.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii will lift its strict entry requirements later this month, eliminating its self-quarantine requirement and allowing domestic travelers to enter the state more easily. Starting March 26, domestic visitors will no longer have to show proof of vaccination or a negative test result to bypass a mandatory five-day quarantine as part of the state's Safe Travels program, Gov. David Ige, a Democrat, announced Tuesday.Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stori</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 Committee Lays Out Potential Criminal Charges Against Trump...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/jan-6-panel-claims-evidence-033014507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump adviser John Eastman’s emails may have evidence of at least three crimes the former president and his associates committed, a House committee investigating the Jan. 6 insurrection said in a court filing, urging a judge to reject Eastman’s request to block the release of the communications.Most Read from BloombergFitch And Moody’s Cut Russia’s Rating to Junk: Ukraine UpdateChina Holds Talks With Ukraine, Further Edging Away From RussiaChina Spy Think Tank Advising Xi P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXODUS:  Refugee count tops 1 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-volodymyr-zelenskyy-joe-biden-kyiv-1b396834ff3e753f8953d86c8db85383</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The number of people sent fleeing Ukraine by Russia's invasion topped 1 million on Wednesday, the swiftest refugee exodus this century, the United Nations said, as Russian forces kept up their bombardment of the country's second-biggest city, Kharkiv, and laid siege to two strategic seaports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-crime-donald-trump-united-states-presidential-elections-d6f316446682ea36e85e2fc4e0581a87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House committee investigating the U.S. Capitol insurrection said Wednesday night that its evidence shows former President Donald Trump and his associates engaged in a “criminal conspiracy” to prevent Congress from certifying the results of the presidential election, spread false information about the outcome and pressured state officials to overturn it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin nuclear threat part of new escalation policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/mar/2/putin-nuclear-threat-part-new-escalation-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin’s veiled threats to use his nuclear arsenal if the West comes to Ukraine’s aid in the current fighting highlight a new military doctrine called “escalate to de-escalate,” one that calls on the military to resort to nuclear weapons more rapidly in conflicts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Asked to Delay War Until After Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/02/china-asked-russia-to-delay-ukraine-war-until-after-olympics-u-s-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A Western intelligence report said senior Chinese officials told senior Russian officials in early February not to invade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MAJOR CITY FALLS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-au/news/australia/russia-claims-control-of-kherson-the-first-major-ukrainian-city-to-fall-with-peace-talks-set-to-resume/ar-AAUwT0B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strategically important coastal city of Kherson in Ukraine's south has reportedly Reuters Irpin destructionbecome the first major city in the country to be taken over by Russian forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden CANCELS ballistic missile test to 'demonstrate restraint'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10570747/Pentagon-CANCELS-test-ballistic-missiles-restraint-avoid-Putins-misunderstanding.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon announced Wednesday it will delay its test of intercontinental ballistic missiles scheduled for this weekend to avoid any misunderstanding on Vladimir Putin's part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>37M Viewers...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/joe-biden-state-of-the-union-viewership-ratings-ukraine-fox-trump-1234968911/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 1:44 PM: There’s still some stragglers like PBS to come in, but right now it looks like Joe Biden’s first State of the Union speech was watched by about 37 million people last n…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-IL House Speaker indicted in political corruption probe...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/2022/3/2/22958533/michael-madigan-indicted-charges-illinois-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madigan is now one of the most significant politicians in Illinois history ever to face criminal charges, despite having left office more than a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring break back: 'Bears coming out of hibernation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/spring-break-travel-is-back-and-so-are-high-prices-like-bears-coming-out-of-hibernation/ar-AAUw7J0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Drunk' JETBLUE pilot removed from aircraft in Buffalo with BAC twice legal limit...</title>
      <link>https://buffalonews.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/jetblue-pilot-pulled-from-cockpit-at-buffalo-airport-with-0-17-bac-nfta-says/article_953b8c7c-9a5c-11ec-ba26-5346cd9f6cee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;buffalonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police removed James Clifton, 52, of Orlando, from the cockpit of a plane about to depart Buffalo Niagara International Airport on Wednesday morning who had a blood-alcohol level more than</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germans Seize Russian Billionaire Oligarch's Mega-Yacht...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/giacomotognini/2022/03/02/germans-seize-russian-billionaire-alisher-usmanovs-mega-yacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His 512-foot yacht Dilbar, which has been in Hamburg since October for refitting, appears to be the first Russian-owned yacht frozen by authorities since Vladimir Putin’s attack on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mood darkens in Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/video/mood-darkens-moscow-putin-presses-235622076.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even with the cratering ruble, Hollywood movies on hold and snarled metro payments, Putin still holds sway among many Russians despite sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST MAJOR CITY FALLS</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2022/03/02/world/ukraine-russia-war/the-strategic-city-of-kherson-in-ukraines-south-falls-to-russian-forces</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO Countries Pour Weapons In, Risking Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/nato-countries-pour-weapons-into-ukraine-risking-conflict-with-russia/ar-AAUvGGN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson Sues Wood Over Alleged 'Malicious Falsehood' Of Abuse Claims...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/marilyn-manson-lawsuit-evan-rachel-wood-abuse-claims-hbo-documentary-1234968988/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Marilyn Manson is taking ex-fiancée Evan Rachel Wood to court over her allegations of abuse that occurred over the course of the relationship between the widely accused shock rocker and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks NY bid to shutter NRA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-lawsuits-manhattan-national-rifle-association-ab050b840a1930b7b316ac71741077e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A judge has rejected an effort by New York's attorney general to put the National Rifle Association out of business, but will allow her lawsuit accusing top executives of illegally diverting tens of millions of dollars from the powerful gun advocacy organization to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Russian fighter jets violate Swedish airspace...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/four-russian-fighter-jets-violate-swedish-airspace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incursions happen regularly, but the latest one draws increased scrutiny, given Russia's invasion of Ukraine. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan CIA Interpreter Pleads with U.S. to Rescue Family from Taliban...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/afghan-cia-interpreter-pleads-with-u-s-to-rescue-family-before-taliban-gets-to-them-so-helpless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorists Nasratullah Sepahizada interrogated are now running the Afghan government. And they’re coming after his family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA puts on show of force with dozens of fighter jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4804789/us-fighter-jets-elephant-walk-biden-warns-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOZENS of US fighter jets have been showcased in an “elephant walk” at an airbase in Japan as Washington displays its military might. It comes as Joe Biden branded Russian president Vladimir Putin …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers sawed through steel U.S.-Mexico border wall more than 3,000 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-border-wall-has-been-breached-more-than-3000-times-by-smugglers-cbp-records-show/ar-AAUwpuh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin adviser breaks ranks: 'Cannot comprehend' invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10569613/Kremlin-adviser-says-comprehend-invasion-says-Russians-depressed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrey Kortunov said 'many of us are depressed' in an extraordinary intervention, after Vladimir Putin made his country a pariah on the international stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to close all of its physical bookstores...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-amazon-close-physical-bookstores-185141601.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) -Amazon.com Inc on Wednesday told Reuters it plans to close all 68 of its physical book stores, pop up shops and "4-star" stores in the United States and United Kingdom, ending some of its longest-running experiments in physical retail. The news marks a turning point for a company that started out as an online bookseller, disrupting brick-and-mortar incumbents such as Borders and Barnes &amp; Noble, only to open its own physical shops decades later. Amazon said physical retail remains an important way for it to reach shoppers and said it will continue to work on other concepts, such as its recently announced fashion store in greater Los Angeles and cashierless grocery stores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yoga teacher fired for partner's 'virulent antisemitism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/yoga-instructor-kelly-johnson-fired-antisemitism-16968941.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He leads the group responsible for distributing antisemitic flyers across the Bay Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin sanctions could be next...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/02/bitcoin-sanctions-could-be-next-as-doj-unveils-crypto-crackdown-plans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington takes aim at Russia's access to digital cash as the U.S. and its allies levy heavy punitive measures against Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities Keep Trying to Stop Churches From Helping Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3nga3/churches-banned-from-helping-homeless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To fight back, churches are arguing that feeding and housing the homeless falls under their First Amendment rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abramovich selling CHELSEA soccer club...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/02/russian-oligarch-abramovich-says-he-will-sell-chelsea-soccer-club-amid-ukraine-furor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  RUSSIAN TROOPS SURRENDERING WITHOUT A FIGHT; RUNNING OUR OF FOOD, FUEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4804335/russia-ukraine-soldiers-abandoned-military-equipment-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s demoralised and disillusioned troops are fleeing the war in Ukraine and surrendering without a fight, reports claim. As Russia’s forces run out of food and fuel, some h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Propaganda Machine Now Cranking for Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-features/russia-china-ukraine-propaganda-invasion-ccp-1315024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s Communist Party wants you to think the West fueled Russia’s invasion and that China is the world’s new peacemaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oligarchs pour money into U.S. real estate market...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/real-estate/russian-money-flows-us-real-estate-rcna17723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite new sanctions, Russians have spent years pouring funds into properties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYING RUSSIAN SOLDIERS</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/captured-russian-soldiers-cry-tell-26367528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian prisoners of war broke down in tears as they told their families back home that they had been 'sent to their deaths' in the invasion, with Ukraine claiming to have killed 6,000 Russians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX robbed: Thieves heist $500K from sets...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/netflix-robbed-lupin-the-crown-1235102749/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 20 thieves throwing fireworks held up 'Lupin' set in the latest Netflix swindle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar TV Ratings Headache Turns Into a Migraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/oscars-tv-ratings-live-telecast-1235102498/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The closely-guarded Academy/ABC deal for the Oscars’ broadcasting rights offers insight into the controversial decision to present eight Oscar categories differently than the other 15 on March 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyiv streets empty over fears of Russian ground assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Kyiv-s-streets-empty-as-tensions-rise-over-fears-16971137.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine - The Ukrainian capital's streets remained largely empty Wednesday as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casualties mount as Russia unleashes greater firepower...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Casualties-mount-in-Ukraine-as-Russia-advances-16970967.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian troops advanced inside a key Ukrainian port city Wednesday, but Moscow's ground...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell Juror May Be Made to Testify About His Conduct...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/02/nyregion/ghislaine-maxwell-trial-juror.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The juror, whose failure to disclose his past abuse has clouded the guilty verdict against Ms. Maxwell, would be granted immunity from prosecution in exchange for his testimony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY SOLVED? Experts claim Stone Henge was ancient solar calendar...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4803579/stonehenge-mystery-solved-ancient-solar-calendar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE MYSTERY surrounding why prehistoric Brits built Stonehenge has finally been solved after research confirmed that the monument served as an ancient solar calendar. Professor Timothy Darvill conc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian POWs had no idea they were being sent to war?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10568725/We-sent-cannon-fodder-killing-peaceful-people-Weeping-Russian-POWs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian soldiers, speaking in video posted to the Ukraine security services' Facebook page, said 'we were sent as cannon fodder' and asked 'mothers and wives' to 'collect your husbands'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melinda Gates set to lift the lid on divorce for first time in tell-all interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10568973/Melinda-Gates-set-lift-lid-divorce-billionaire-Microsoft-founder-Bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 57-year-old philanthropist is set to speak out about her divorce from Bill, 66, for the first time in an interview airing on CBS Mornings on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Holocaust museum so dependent on Russian oligarch that it wants to protect him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-holocaust-museum-is-so-dependent-on-a-russian-oligarch-that-it-wants-to-protect-him-from-sanctions/ar-AAUvK2G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Assassination plot against Zelensky foiled; Unit sent to kill him 'destroyed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/assassination-plot-against-zelensky-was-foiled-and-unit-sent-to-kill-him-was-destroyed-ukraine-says/ar-AAUvQrN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports stars join fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220302-ukraine-sports-stars-joining-fight-against-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From world boxing champions to football stars, top Ukrainian sports people are resisting the Russian invasion of their country, with some even returning home to take up arms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two years into pandemic, is end in sight?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220302-two-years-into-the-pandemic-is-the-end-in-sight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years after the official start of the pandemic, some countries are now trying to "live with Covid", however scientists warn that potential new variants and unequal vaccination rates threaten any…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Minister No': Lavrov embodies Moscow's steely posture...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-war-sergey-lavrov-e5d83adaee90b6d66687a6bddcabc8e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — As Russia's top diplomat during the invasion of Ukraine , Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov is embodying the Kremlin's defiant posture with a mixture of toughness and sarcasm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic dangers from Russia invasion ripple across globe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-9478a9825c9abfde5f6505bd34b2998c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Moscow’s war on Ukraine and the ferocious financial backlash it’s unleashed are not only inflicting an economic catastrophe on President Vladimir Putin’s Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB host 'secretly took 2,000 videos of guests naked and having sex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4803543/airbnb-owner-videos-guests-naked-sex-hidden-camera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A HOTEL owner allegedly took more than 2,000 videos and images of guests naked and having sex on a hidden camera. The device was found inside one of the rooms of Airbnb host A Jay Allee’s secl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House prices to rise another 10% this year?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/usa-property-poll/u-s-house-prices-to-rise-another-10-this-year-reuters-poll-idUSKBN2KZ1IL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. house prices are set to climb in double digits this year even as the Federal Reserve embarks on its expected series of interest rate hikes, according to a Reuters poll of property analysts who forecast a sellers' market for another two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 2,000 civilians reported killed during invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-civilians/more-than-2000-ukrainian-civilians-killed-during-russian-invasion-ukrainian-emergency-service-idUSKBN2KZ1H1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian invasion of Ukraine has killed more than 2,000 Ukrainian civilians and destroyed hundreds of structures including transport facilities, hospitals, kindergartens and homes, Ukraine's emergency service said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger Muscles in 3 Seconds a Day...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/02/stronger-muscles-in-3-seconds-a-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could three seconds a day of resistance exercise really increase muscular strength? That question was at the heart of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Ally to Face Bush in Showdown for AG...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-ally-to-face-bush-in-showdown-for-texas-attorney-general/ar-AAUuHmR?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Plea Collides With Reality of Bitterly Divided Nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-unity-plea-collides-with-reality-of-bitterly-divided-us/ar-AAUuRsC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi distracts viewers with bizarre behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10569077/What-hell-doing-Nancy-Pelosis-bizarre-behavior-distracts-State-Union-viewers.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi was sitting directly behind the President and was in full view throughout the speech, that went on for an hour and two minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Says Controls Land Around Biggest Atomic Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/russia-says-it-controls-land-around-biggest-ukraine-atomic-plant-1.1731155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia told the International Atomic Energy Agency that its military had taken control of territory around Ukraine’s Zaporizhzhya nuclear power plant as diplomats hold an emergency meeting to voice their mounting concern over safety as fighting escalates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CHATEAU MARMONT Boss Plans New Private Club and Hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/former-chateau-marmont-boss-plans-new-los-angeles-private-club-and-hotel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Chateau Marmont Boss PlansÂ New Los AngelesÂ Club and Hotel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Scenes as NZ Police Move to End Occupation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/02/explosive-scenes-as-new-zealand-police-move-to-end-weekslong-occupation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than three weeks, hundreds of protesters have disabled the center of New Zealand’s capital city, occupying the area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF BARTS: Billionaires Clash Over Future in Caribbean Eden...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/02/billionaires-clash-over-the-future-in-a-caribbean-eden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Midwinter on the Caribbean island of St. Barts is a kind of second hurricane season. December’s annual landfall of billionaires</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA prepares to expand financial attack on oligarchs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-prepares-to-expand-financial-attack-on-russian-oligarchs-aiming-to-seize-billions-held-by-putin-allies/ar-AAUvs7X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As assault stalls, Russia unleashes greater firepower...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/convoy-approaching-ukrainian-capital-appears-stalled-as-russia-unleashes-greater-firepower/ar-AAUtLeR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still bearing emotional scars, jury to hear testimony in first Jan. 6 Capitol attack trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/still-bearing-emotional-scars-jury-to-hear-testimony-in-first-jan-6-capitol-attack-trial/ar-AAUvpLr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court nominee heads to Senate for confirmation process...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-nominee-heads-to-senate-for-confirmation-process/ar-AAUtKpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid 'need no longer control our lives'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Biden-declares-pandemic-reset-saying-covid-need-16970126.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden sought to reassure Americans in his State of the Union...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead soldiers. Icy river. Ukraine town on  front lines prepares to battle Russians...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dead-soldiers-icy-river-ukraine-222134361.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian invasion in Ukraine has set its sights on Kyiv. But first it has to go through this town, where Russian soldiers lay dead, and people flee to safety across a river on a broken bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens Big Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2022/3/1/22957507/biden-state-of-the-union-social-media-mental-health-children-accountability-frances-haugen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his State of the Union speech, the president vowed to hold social media platforms accountable for their harms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos show smouldering convoy blitzed to ashes by resistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17816255/incredible-photos-russian-convoy-wreckage-bucha-kyiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLING images show a smouldering Russian convoy of tanks blitzed to ashes by the heroic Ukrainian resistance on the outskirts of Kyiv. The biggest war in Europe since World War 2 has now been rag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile hit site of Babyn Yar Holocaust memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Ukraine-s-president-says-Russian-missile-hit-site-16969617.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DNIPRO, Ukraine - A Russian missile strike that appeared to target a TV tower in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER 'fact-check' no show...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-Ukraine-misinformation-rages-Twitter-s-16969529.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Ukraine war unfolding on social media, parsing fact from fiction has never been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion opens fissures between Vlad and oligarchs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/ukraine-invasion-opens-faint-but-once-unthinkable-fissures-between-putin-and-russian-oligarchs/ar-AAUr8ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Putin, intelligence analysts see an isolated leader who underestimated West but could lash out if cornered...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-putin-intelligence-analysts-see-an-isolated-leader-who-underestimated-the-west-but-could-lash-out-if-cornered/ar-AAUub5X </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lukashenko may have accidentally revealed Moldova next target...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10565523/Ukraine-war-Belarus-dictator-stands-battle-map-live-TV.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexander Lukashenko, dictatorial ruler of Belarus, stood in front of a large map apparently detailing Russia's attack plan for Ukraine as he addressed his security council today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL HITS DECADE HIGH: $111 A BARREL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/02/us-oil-jumps-to-highest-since-2013-tops-109-a-barrel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices continued their march higher, rising to the highest since 2013 amid shortage fears as Russia's war on Ukraine intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Britain believe Ukraine war could last 10-20 years!</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/russo-ukrainian-war/1010797/us-and-britain-reportedly-believe-the-ukraine-war-could-last-10-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the Union: Biden vows to halt Russia, hit inflation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-state-of-the-union-4d6eb9fed9a46bb4efb63ea4e015725c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Addressing a concerned nation and anxious world, President Joe Biden vowed in his first State of the Union address Tuesday night to check Russian aggression in Ukraine,  tame soaring U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas primary sets up Abbott-O'Rourke race as midterms begin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-texas-c4955491dbef028e2c702e276543da1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Republican Gov. Greg Abbott will face Democrat Beto O’Rourke after voters in Texas opened what could be a lengthy, bruising primary season poised to reshape political power from state capitals to Washington.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
