<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kerry overheard saying 'Sanders taking down Party'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/john-kerry-overheard-discussing-possible-2020-bid-amid-concern-sanders-n1128476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That he would even discuss the possibility suggests that prominent members of the Democratic Party remain deeply unsettled by the current field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacino suffers dramatic fall on red carpet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/irishman-star-al-pacino-suffers-21416543</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar winner and Hollywood legend Al Pacino has fallen down on the red carpet for the BAFTA Film Awards 2020 ahead of the prestigious ceremony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears 5G network could lower sperm counts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/fears-uks-new-5g-network-21415777</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Scientists and academics are among those concerned about the high-speed network's electro-magnetic radiation having a harmful effect on young men's reproductive systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Iowa, anxiety and unpredictability cloud caucus finish...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ce049651af41d729193cf574be5465af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — On the eve of the Iowa caucuses, Democratic presidential candidates hustled across the state on Sunday trying to fire up voters and make one last appeal to those struggling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spray planes combat the huge locust outbreak in Africa...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/854648cd0a9f634ec0473f7442469295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASUULU CONSERVANCY, Kenya (AP) — As locusts by the billions — yes, billions — descend on parts of Kenya in the worst outbreak in 70 years, small planes are flying low over affected areas to spray...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump speech to project optimism at time of bitter division...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/39a1aa616aaaec2f41d6a67010bb79b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Standing before lawmakers in the grand-domed Capitol where his impeachment trial is still underway, President Donald Trump on Tuesday night will declare the state of the union s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917' Dominates BAFTAs...</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2020-bafta-award-winners-1273649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Mendes' WWI epic came away with seven awards, while 'Joker' was behind with three (including best actor)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE Permanently Suspended From TWITTER for 'Harassment'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200202180911-1sd4x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/TWITTER (PIX):Financial market website Zero Hedge knocked off Twitter over coronavirus story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda claims December shooting at Florida naval base...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200202174909-yweia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLORIDA-SHOOTING/ALQAEDA (URGENT):Al Qaeda in Arabian Peninsula claims December shooting at Florida naval base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONAIRES BATTLE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/trump-attacks-bloomberg-s-height-hours-their-dueling-super-bowl-n1128451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former mayor was responding to Trump attacking his height.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DES MOINES REGISTER SPIKES FINAL POLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/iowa-2020-poll-not-released-des-moines-register-caeea162-0861-47d9-a4d9-107725c81dfc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It appears a candidate's name was omitted in at least one interview," The Des Moines Register said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass stabbing on London street as terror suspect is shot dead by cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10874360/man-shot-terrorist-streatham-london-high-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN has been shot dead by armed cops today after stabbing two people in a knife rampage terror attack on a London high street. Frantic witnesses heard gunshots and saw the man – who securit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER INSULTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/election-2020/bloomberg-camp-hits-back-at-lying-trump-he-lies-about-his-fake-hair-his-obesity-and-his-spray-on-tan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has been attacking Michael Bloomberg quite a bit recently, including plenty of mockery of his height.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hispanics largest minority voting bloc for first time in American history...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/demographic-shifts-what-matters-2020-424161bf-1e6e-4da9-b2b2-9a6b2b2099fa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's identity is nearing a tipping point as demographics change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siri spying? iPad shifts to Spanish after conversations in home...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/columnist/2020/02/02/siri-spying-why-apple-ipad-changed-after-hearing-spanish-home/4627367002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ads on iPad apps changed from English to Spanish after a few conversations in the language at home. Could Siri have been listening?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As inmates grow old, Kansas prisons plan for geriatric care...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article239842598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists Occupy Coal Plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-02-02/activists-occupy-german-coal-plant-in-protest-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slowing economy complicates campaign messaging for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/480963-slowing-economy-complicates-campaign-messaging-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is heading into the 2020 campaign with a resilient economy behind him and new trade deals under his belt, counting on both to help bolster his reelection odds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady Gaga: 'Better hear no lip-syncing' at halftime show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a14ab53ad4c7d296d41ed30fe8c96d6a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Descending from the air, Lady Gaga kicked off a pre-Super Bowl concert by mimicking her entrance to her Super Bowl halftime performance three years ago, which earned her raved...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They paid money to walk out': Southern rock band takes on Trump, guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/feb/2/drive-truckers-take-trump-guns-new-album-unravelin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the rock band Drive-By Truckers, it’s demoralizing to release angry songs about Donald Trump’s America just as the president’s impeachment trial is winding down toward an acquittal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: More People Excited About Parties For Food, Not Game...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/super-bowl-parties-most-people-enjoy-the-snacks-more-than-the-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 Americans asked respondents why they attend Super Bowl parties each year, and for many, the actual game is the last thing on their minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far From Epicentre, Another City Put Under Lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/coronavirus-china-puts-wenzhou-city-under-lockdown-as-deaths-cross-300-2173669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China imposed a lockdown Sunday on a major city far from the epicentre of a coronavirus epidemic, as its death toll from the disease soared to 304 and the first fatality outside the country was reported in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Habits Delayed Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/as-new-coronavirus-spread-chinas-old-habits-delayed-fight/ar-BBZyiSz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church stampede leaves 20 dead after pastor pours 'holy oil' on ground...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/church-stampede-leaves-20-dead-124156114.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 20 people have died in a stampede at a church service in an open ground stadium in Tanzania, officials have said.Hundreds of people attended the prayer service on Saturday evening led by a popular preacher in the town of Moshi, near Mount Kilimanjaro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US troops held in SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/481064-us-troops-who-recently-traveled-to-china-quarantined-in-south-korea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military officials in South Korea announced on Sunday that a 14-day self-quarantine has been imposed on U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses Threaten To Strike If Borders Aren't Shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2020/02/01/801837678/coronavirus-fears-lead-nurses-to-threaten-strike-in-hong-kong-if-borders-arent-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hong Kong is dealing with hundreds of suspected cases. Nurses say they'll walk out on Monday if the city doesn't seal its border with China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missteps, state secrecy helped spread farther and faster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/early-missteps-and-state-secrecy-in-china-probably-allowed-the-coronavirus-to-spread-farther-and-faster/ar-BBZya9o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient declared 'disease-free' after treatment with HIV, flu drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7957889/Thai-medics-claim-coronavirus-break-Patient-declared-disease-free-48-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medics in Thailand tested the drug mix on a patient in a 'serious condition' with the disease and within 48 hours they were declared disease-free. The drugs are normally used for HIV and influenza treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic in Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/panic-buying-in-hong-kong-amid-alarming-spread-of-coronavirus-11924399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky's Alex Crawford reports from Hong Kong where there are fears political ties with China are being put above citizens' safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian-American emerges as new star of Italy's left-wing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/004a5aa3dcc720460ef4cab2b7101661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOLOGNA, Italy (AP) — A dual U.S.-Italian citizen who cut her political organizing teeth on two Barack Obama campaigns is emerging as the latest rising star in Italian politics. Inside a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie draws massive crowd to party-like rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/live-music-booze-sanders-draws-massive-crowd-party-iowa-campaign-n1128376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3,000 people turned out for his rally in Cedar Rapids on Saturday night, dwarfing attendance figures for events held by rival campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress claims she slept with Mick Jagger when she was 15...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7956443/Rae-Dawn-reveals-spent-night-Rolling-Stone-underage-married.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rae Dawn says she is only speaking out to 'own' the story after accidentally blurting out during a podcast that she had sex with Jagger when she was two years under the age of consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberalism's 'cesspit'?: Tech giants have turned San Fran into dystopian nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-7956517/IAN-BIRRELL-tech-giants-turned-San-Francisco-dystopian-nightmare.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IAN BIRRELL: One fed-up resident showed me Hondurans handing out socks filled with wraps of drugs in front of a building being turned into an upmarket Whole Foods store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funerals Banned for Victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/china-bans-funerals-for-coronavirus-victims-as-death-toll-rises-2020-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Wuhan virus continues to claim lives, Chinese authorities issued regulations banning funerals for victims and requiring immediate cremation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of new virus trigger anti-China sentiment worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/04f18aafe1074a1c06b4203edcbdc661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — A scary new virus from China has spread around the world. So has rising anti-Chinese sentiment, calls for a full travel ban on Chinese visitors and indignities for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students using tablets in class. Some parents want to hit off switch...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/more-students-are-learning-on-laptops-and-tablets-in-class-some-parents-want-to-hit-the-off-switch/ar-BBZyB0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
