<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Stray mongrel beats pedigrees to become elite sniffer dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/03/06/stray-mongrel-beats-pedigrees-become-elite-indian-sniffer-dog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 18 months after being rescued from stone-throwing children, a street-dwelling mongrel has emerged as India's top dog in the country's elite bomb- and drug-sniffing squad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson songs banned from radio stations around the world...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/michael-jackson-songs-banned-from-radio-stations-around-the-world-2457781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio stations across the world have dropped Michael Jackson songs from their playlists in wake of 'Leaving Neverland' documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil President Posts Sexually Explicit Video to Denounce Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/brazils-president-jair-bolsonaro-posts-sexually-explicit-golden-showers-video-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein shake before bed for BIGGER muscles?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6774069/Want-bigger-muscles-Drink-protein-shake-bed-Late-night-intake-increases-gains.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists at Maastricht University in the Netherlands found the extra consumption of calories won't make you fat - even though it's followed by hours of inactivity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames parents for 'selling' daughters to him...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/06/r-kelly-claims-parents-sold-daughters-to-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “I Believe I Can Fly” singer flew off the handle in his 80-minute sit-down with “CBS This Morning” co-host Gayle King.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOLE FOODS cuts worker hours after AMAZON introduces minimum wage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/06/whole-foods-amazon-cuts-minimum-wage-workers-hours-changes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An email shared with the Guardian by a Whole Foods employee cites the shift cuts as a ‘direct result of guidance from our regional team’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleanse spirit, meditate, stargaze...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/asia/indonesia/bali/articles/nyepi-why-bali-is-going-silent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No flights or internet during Bali's sacred Day of Silence...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/bendbulletin/article/f5309ba059b04b35b628bd2acf2c0755/no-flights-or-internet-during-balis-sacred-day-silence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENPASAR, Indonesia (AP) — Bali's airport will close for 24 hours, the internet will be turned off and streets emptied as the predominantly Hindu island in Indonesia observes its New Year with an annual day of silence."Nyepi" begins at 6 a.m. Thursday, clearing beaches and all public spaces of people except for special patrols to ensure silence is observed. For the second year, phone companies will turn off the mobile internet on the island, home to more than 4 million people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen 4th day of testimony could touch on Russia, finances...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/article/991f1295ab4d436f99e11b20fd1c433f/cohen-returns-capitol-hill-4th-day-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's former lawyer is returning to Capitol Hill for a fourth day of testimony as Democrats pursue a flurry of investigations into Trump's White House, businesses and presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgian mayor defends float featuring Jews with money and rat...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/belgian-mayor-defends-carnival-float-featuring-jews-with-money-and-a-rat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite widespread condemnation, Aalst Mayor Christoph D’Haese argues display 'should be allowed' and that 'carnival participants had no sinister intentions'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time for Chinese miracle': Beijing's new English language propaganda push...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/mar/06/time-for-the-chinese-miracle-beijings-new-english-language-propaganda-push</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign including confusing rap song and stilted video explainer coincides with the annual Two Sessions political conference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500 pulses of lightning off SoCal coast in 5 mins...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-socal-lightning-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A band of thunderstorms that stretch from southern Kern County past the Channel Islands was producing a dramatic lightning show Tuesday night in the Southern California sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitism Rebuke Threatens Rift Among Dems...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-semitism-rebuke-threatens-rift-090000290.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota freshman’s name doesn’t appear in the resolution, which could go to the House floor as soon as Thursday, but it denounces anti-Semitism by describing tropes similar to some of those she has invoked. Omar has apologized for some of her controversial remarks and defended others. The fact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN passengers quarantined after '150 hit with mystery coughing sickness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/8572000/passengers-on-virgin-atlantic-flight-from-barbados-quarantined-after-150-people-affected-by-mystery-coughing-sickness/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VIRGIN Atlantic flight was grounded at Gatwick Airport this morning after “150 passengers” fell sick on board. The flight had returned from Barbados at 5.20am when the plane was surro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't look now: Machines reading emotions...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/mar/06/facial-recognition-software-emotional-science</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Machines can now allegedly identify anger, fear, disgust and sadness. ‘Emotion detection’ has grown from a research project to a $20bn industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD SURGE AT BORDER</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/more-migrant-families-arrested-at-border-in-five-months-than-any-previous-full-year-11551810657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has set a new record for the number of migrant families caught crossing its southern border over an entire year. It took just five months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyer Beware: Hollywood Special Effects Now Permeate Property Listings...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/home-sellers-doctored-photos-challenge-buyers-bots-11551708001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A computer-versus-computer showdown is brewing in the residential property market, pitting investors’ house-hunting algorithms against sellers’ virtual listing photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal immigration at worst rate in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/5/illegal-immigration-worst-rate-2007/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of families snared trying to sneak into the U.S. soared by 50 percent in one month alone, setting an all-time record with more than 36,000 family members apprehended, Homeland Security officials announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-dollar donors, including Donald Trump, fueled Kamala Harris' political rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article226975319.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans advance paid leave plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/republicans-seeing-opportunities-suburbs-advance-paid-leave</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are now poised to introduce a raft of new proposals in the coming weeks, reflecting the party’s effort to win back the suburban women it lost in the midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busloads...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/03/05/700428069/migrant-families-arrive-in-busloads-as-border-crossings-hit-10-year-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system is "overwhelmed," says Manuel Padilla, director of Joint Task Force-West. The migrants apprehended at the Southern border in February made for the highest monthly total in almost a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muir Hits Ratings High As No. 1 Evening News Anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/markjoyella/2019/03/05/abcs-david-muir-hits-ratings-high-as-americas-no-1-evening-news-anchor/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a week packed with news, from Capitol Hill to Vietnam, ABC's David Muir grew his lead over rival evening newscasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE SIGNALS SHE'LL REVOKE ROGER STONE'S BAIL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6774555/Judge-revoke-Roger-Stones-bail-new-book-calling-Mueller-crooked-sale.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge criticized Stone and his lawyers for failing to tell her when she issued a gag order that his latest book – which includes slashing commentary about Robert Mueller – was already on sale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion intensifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/new-awful-data-shows-border-invasion-worse-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are we a country or not?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'surpass Obama Era'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/05/illegal-immigration-under-trump-projected-to-surpass-obama-era-levels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is projected to oversee the largest flow of illegal immigration at the U.S.-Mexico border since former President Bush's administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55 Illegals Transported to Hospitals Each Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/03/05/55-migrants-transported-to-u-s-hospitals-each-day-say-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection officials report that agents and officers are referring an average of 55 migrants per day to hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens involved in swastika party apologize as outrage grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/teens-involved-in-swastika-party-apologize-as-outrage-grows-my/article_db37109d-4c3d-5096-9219-5865230a9a64.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWPORT BEACH, Calif. — Teens who attended an Orange County party this weekend that included Nazi symbolism purportedly had this to say:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somali Gangs Battle in Minneapolis...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/michaelwalsh/somali-gangs-battle-in-minneapolis-somalis-demand-that-cops-do-something/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wages of "diversity" is division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Bans Tommy Robinson Book...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/amazon-bans-tommy-robinsons-book-mohammeds-koran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Left-fascists begin their book burnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget Deficit Widens 77%...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-budget-deficit-widens-77-190217899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The budget gap widened 77 percent compared with the same October-January period a year earlier, according to the Treasury monthly budget report released on Tuesday, which was delayed by the government shutdown. The financial shortfall is set to widen further in the coming years as the Republican tax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Sowell warns USA may not resist siren song of socialism: 'I wouldn't bet on it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/5/thomas-sowell-warns-us-may-not-resist-siren-song-o/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Sowell, a living legend in the field of economics, says he fears the U.S. may eventually succumb to the siren song of socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ailes biopic flops...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/divide-conquer-debut-ratings-second-smallest-audience-ae-calendar-year-1202569958/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divide &amp; Conquer: The Story of Roger Ailes notched 228K viewers in its debut on A&amp;E Sunday night – the cable net’s second smallest primetime audience of 2019 to date. That includes 52…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Oversight Committee, White House in standoff...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/house-oversight-committee-white-house-standoff-viewing-security/story?id=61455537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's White House and the oversight committee are in a standoff over viewing security documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN decorates restaurant to honor Chinese Communist hero...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-kfc-chinese-restaurant-lei-feng-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast food chain Kentucky Fried Chicken (KFC) launched a restaurant themed to honor Communist hero Lei Feng, ahead of the soldier's remembrance day Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More $100 bills in circulation than $1 bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-100-dollar-bill-mysteriously-popular-20190305-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago, the number of $100 bills lagged well behind $1 and $20 notes. But the tally has doubled since the end of the financial crisis; by 2017 the C-note had eclipsed the $1 to become the most widely distributed U.S. currency. Output is still climbing, and experts are perplexed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 'oldest' tattooing kit made from bones of dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-03-05/worlds-oldest-tattoo-kit-human-bones-tonga-archaeology/10872926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests tools thought to have been destroyed by the Canberra firestorm of 2003 were fashioned from the remains of ancient Tongan tattooists' ancestors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Zucker refused to meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/national-association-of-black-journalists-calls-out-cnn-over-lack-of-diversity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organization also says CNN boss Jeff Zucker refused to meet with a NABJ delegation to discuss the issue when asked about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: NKorea rebuilding long-range rocket site...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/north-korea/north-korea-rebuilding-long-range-rocket-site-photos-show-n979721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos taken just 2 days after the Trump-Kim Hanoi summit show rebuilding at the Sohae Satellite Launching Station, North Korea's operational space launch facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credit Card Debt Record $870 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-credit-card-debt-closed-2018-at-a-record-870-billion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Credit Card Debt Closed 2018 at a Record $870 Billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pet lion mauls owner to death in back yard...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-47454610</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big cat was one of two held illegally by Michal Prasek, causing concern among local residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to seek 10 years of tax returns in 2 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/05/democrats-plan-to-demand-trumps-tax-returns-in-about-two-weeks-1205449</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s returns are unlikely to be released anytime soon, even once Democrats make their request. The administration is promising a fight in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colbert Beats Fallon for First Time in Key Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/05/business/media/colbert-fallon-ratings-nielsen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS late-night host, who has led in total viewers for more than a year, beats his NBC rival for the first time in viewers 18 to 49 years old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Think Solved Mystery of Green Icebergs...</title>
      <link>https://www.geek.com/news/scientists-may-soon-solve-century-old-mystery-of-green-icebergs-1777172/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most icebergs appear white or blue when floating in seawater, but since the early 1900s explorers and sailors have reported seeing peculiar green icebergs in certain parts of Antarctica. The strange green icebergs …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance broker subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/05/politics/trump-organization-aon-insurance-broker-subpoena-new-york/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State Department of Financial Services has opened an inquiry into the Trump Organization's insurance practices, sending a subpoena Monday to the company's longtime insurance broker, according to a person familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33109: America's richest zip code not in NY or CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/bloomberg-analysis-this-is-americas-richest-zip-code.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the country's wealthiest zip code had an average annual income of $2.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black journalist group places CNN on 'special monitoring list'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/432714-black-journalists-group-places-cnn-on-special-monitoring-list-citing-lack-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Association of Black Journalists (NABJ) said Tuesday that it would place CNN on a "special media monitoring list," citing a lack of black representation among the network's leadership ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG: NO</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/05/michael-bloomberg-will-not-run-for-president-in-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Bloomberg will not run for president in 2020, the billionaire businessman said in a statement posted online on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Goes Easy on NCAA Convicts, Citing Widespread Corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-03-05/ex-adidas-official-two-others-sentenced-in-ncaa-bribery-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blood everywhere': Cruise ship rocked by extreme wind...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/03/05/blood-everywhere-cruise-ship-rocked-by-extreme-wind-gust/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Norwegian Cruise Line is blaming a strong, sudden gust of wind for tilting the Norwegian Escape on Sunday night, an incident reportedly responsible for injuring multiple passengers. “Just befor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company offers to build 234 miles of border wall for $1.4 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/company-offers-to-build-234-miles-of-border-wall-for-1-4-billion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. company is offering to build 234 miles of President Trump's border wall for just $1.4 billion, a fraction of the $8 billion the Trump administration is hoping to use for that project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron declaration of love awkward scoop for Italy state TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190305-macron-italy-interview-rai-salvini</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aimed at healing a vicious spat between France and Italy, French President Emmanuel Macron’s interview on Italian television has shed light on the battle waged by Italy's ruling populist parties for control of the country’s state broadcaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intensity of Far-Left Protests Up...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/tennessee-gop-says-intensity-of-far-left-protests-has-increased/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican members of the Tennessee legislature say they are concerned about the increased willingness for physical confrontation exhibited by protesters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Saves Family From Carbon Monoxide Poisoning...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/cat-saves-florida-family-carbon-monoxide-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Central Florida couple is crediting Bella for saving their lives. Bella is not their daughter or their dog, she is their cat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suits and ties optional, GOLDMAN hedges dress code...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-world-work-goldman-sachs/suits-and-ties-now-optional-goldman-sachs-hedges-dress-code-idUSKCN1QM283</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs Group Inc said on Tuesday that it is relaxing the dress code for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT: Agree 100% with keeping U.S. troops in Syria...</title>
      <link>chttps://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/trump-says-he-agrees-100-percent-keeping-u-s-troops-n979466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The End Of Recycling...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2019/03/china-has-stopped-accepting-our-trash/584131/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are consuming more and more stuff. Now that other countries won’t take our papers and plastics, they’re ending up in the trash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Median 1-BR Rent In San Fran Soars To $3,700 A Month...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/03/05/median-1-bedroom-rent-sf-3690-month-zumper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Already known for outrageously high rents, the monthly rent in San Francisco has just hit a whole new level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau climate rally interrupted by melee, protester heckles...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/5021524/justin-trudeau-climate-rally-interrupted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Trudeau was speaking about Jane Philpott's resignation from cabinet. Then the heckling started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE PORN BLOCKED IN UK</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8565486/porn-uk-ban-unlock-card/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WATCHING free porn in Britain is about to get a lot trickier thanks to new rules that aim to protect children from online smut. As early as next month, porn sites will be required to get proof of I…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FDA Set to Approve Ketamine Nasal Spray for Depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/03/04/700014137/fda-expected-to-approve-esketamine-nasal-spray-for-depression</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration is expected to approve a new type of drug for depression. It is esketamine, a chemical cousin of the anesthetic and party drug ketamine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff Hires Ex-Prosecutor to Lead Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/adam-schiff-hires-a-former-prosecutor-to-lead-the-trump-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the House Intelligence Committee is conducting an aggressive inquiry into the Trump campaign’s ties to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian couples flogged in front of crowd for having sex outside marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/six-young-couples-flogged-front-14090286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of men cheered and filmed the Sharia law punishment before one of the women was pictured limping away in tears in Aceh, Indonesia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media, comedy replace news as Maduro's grip on media blacks out turmoil in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/4/nicolas-maduro-media-control-censors-news-venezuel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news that Venezuelan residents watch and read depends on the whims of a regime that would rather not have them ponder whether they truly live in the democratic workers’ paradise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's saddest elephant' dies after 43 YEARS locked up in solitary confinement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8567026/worlds-saddest-elephant-dies-after-43-years-locked-up-in-solitary-confinement-at-spanish-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s saddest elephant has died after 43 YEARS locked up in solitary confinement at a Spanish zoo. Cordoba Zoo said that keepers awoke to “sad news of the death of our beloved elephant …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT:  Rio Carnival reveler dressed as Michael Jackson stuns crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8564032/rio-carnival-paedo-michael-jackson-costume/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RIO carnival reveller shocked crowds when he turned up at the spectacular parade in this Michael Jackson outfit. The Sae Clemente samba school performer attracted some strange looks as he cavorte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Guy Trump Called 'Fat Jerry' Is Chairman Nadler Now...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-and-nadler-have-warred-for-years-but-the-stakes-have-never-been-higher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressman who stood his ground against the developer in New York is up against the president in Washington now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spacecraft Beresheet takes first selfie in space... </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Israeli-spacecraft-Beresheet-takes-first-selfie-in-space-582512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The selfie shows the Southern Hemisphere, and Australia can clearly be seen in the background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHT FRIGHT: 'Drop everything, evacuate immediately. Plane will explode'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6772417/Passengers-scramble-safety-flight-China-LA-forced-make-emergency-landing.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cabin on the plane from Beijing to Los Angeles was full of 'screams and panic' over a suspected fire in the baggage hold on the Air China Boeing 777.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Boss Talks League Growing Mental Health Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/sports/nba/2019/03/01/adam-silver-sloan-nba-unhappy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it’s a generational issue.’’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen asked about pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/lawyer-for-cohen-approached-trump-attorneys-about-pardon-11551753372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attorney for Michael Cohen, Donald Trump’s former personal lawyer, raised the possibility of a pardon with attorneys for the president after federal agents raided Mr. Cohen’s properties in April, according to people familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influence of centrists fading fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/The-influence-of-centrist-Democrats-is-fading-13663777.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To state the obvious, the policy agenda of the Democratic Party has moved to the left. Ideas that used to be on the fringe - Medicare-for-all, guaranteed jobs and the Green New Deal, all financed by very progressive taxation - are now much more widely accepted by Democrats. Two possible theories explain this evolution: the old one from the center-left and the new one from the "leftier" left. The center left was/is essentially friendly, and largely deferential, to markets. Left to their own devices, financial markets will efficiently allocate excess savings to their most productive uses - so over-regulation is dangerous. Same with globalization. Taxes should be progressive, but not too much so or you'll dampen private investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke, a sheriff in Appalachian coal country struggles to provide law and order...</title>
      <link>https://www.officer.com/command-hq/news/21070781/kentucky-sheriff-struggles-to-provide-law-and-order-as-county-struggles-with-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.officer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With only one other paid law enforcement officer on staff now to help Martin County Sheriff John Kirk monitor a 231-square-mile area day and night, the department is stretched to its limit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of dead West Point cadet retrieve his sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/parents-dead-west-point-cadet-retrieve-his-sperm-n979316</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Military Academy Cadet Peter Zhu was declared brain dead Wednesday, four days after the California resident was involved in a skiing accident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama tornado survivors reckon with 'Armageddon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.inforum.com/news/science-and-nature/981769-Alabama-tornado-survivors-reckon-with-Armageddon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inforum.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A couple and their grandson survive deadly tornadoes by sheltering under a mattress as their house disintegrated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CAPTAIN MARVEL' review: Mundane, unimaginative, bland; Lack of elan in every dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/captain-marvel-review-1192277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brie Larson stars as the titular hero in the Marvel adaptation, also featuring Samuel L. Jackson, Jude Law, Gemma Chan and Annette Bening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely to seek 10 years of tax returns in coming weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/House-Democrats-likely-to-seek-10-years-of-13663805.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Congressional Democrats are likely to request 10 years of President Donald Trump's tax returns in coming weeks, tailoring their inquiry in a way they hope will survive a court battle, according to according to lawmakers and others involved in the discussions. The exact parameters of the request are still in flux, including whether to seek tax returns related to Trump's many business enterprises in addition to his personal returns. But Democrats led by House Ways and Means Committee Chairman Richard Neal, D-Mass., along with congressional lawyers, are in the advanced stages of preparing the request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHANEL brings out stars to honor Lagerfeld final collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/chanel-brings-out-stars-honour-lagerfelds-final-collection-doc-1e83up4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN focus group rejects Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/432611-cnn-focus-group-rejects-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CNN focus group comprised of Democratic voters has rejected former Vice President Joe Biden as their presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities investigating swastikas scrawled in blood near Holocaust museum...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/04/blood-swastikas-la-brea-public-restroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating what they say may be a possible hate crime at a public restroom Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron first season in LA has become disaster...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/26137383/lebron-first-season-los-angeles-become-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lakers are on the verge of missing the playoffs in LeBron James' first season in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May Hold Clues to Rise and Fall of Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8563177/sealed-maya-ritual-cave-untouched-for-1000-years-was-opening-to-the-underworld-and-is-filled-with-spooky-relics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ANCIENT ‘untouched’ Maya ritual cave has accidentally been discovered by archaeologists in Mexico who were actually searching for a sacred well. The cave is thought to have been seal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales of safe rooms, nuclear bunkers rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/property/luxury/dont-panic-sales-safe-rooms-nuclear-bunkers-rising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the daily news cycle leaves you wanting to batten down the hatches and wait for it all to blow over, you&amp;rsquo;re far from alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE patronage of Trump hotel rose sharply after merger announcement...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/T-Mobile-patronage-of-Trump-s-DC-hotel-rose-13663614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - T-Mobile's patronage of President Donald Trump's hotel here increased sharply after last April's announcement of its merger with Sprint, with executives since spending about $195,000 at the property, the company told congressional Democrats in a letter last month. Before news of the megadeal between rival companies broke on April 29, 2018, the company said, only two top officials from T-Mobile had ever stayed at the Trump International Hotel Washington, with one overnight stay each in August 2017. But the day after the merger's announcement, nine of T-Mobile's top executives were schedule to check in, The Washington Post reported in January.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
