<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sperm donor fathers 24 kids in 12 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7612979/i-sold-my-sperm-for-quick-cash-when-i-was-skint-now-ive-got-24-kids-meet-the-57-year-old-sperm-donor-who-believes-he-could-have-hundreds-of-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEN Peter Ellenstein received a Facebook message from a young woman he didn’t recognise in 2016, he did not expect to open it and find out she was his daughter. Nor could he have possibly im…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll crush replicas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/740553/sex-doll-replicas-crush-copies-women-they-fancy-video-real</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOWE'S to close 51 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/lowes-to-close-51-stores-including-20-in-the-us-2018-11-05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder tried to break in to embassy to kidnap Assange, claims legal team...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6353833/Break-attempt-Julian-Assanges-residence-Ecuadorian-Embassy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiLeaks founder (pictured) was woken up in the night after an alleged intruder attempted to enter a window at the front of the embassy building in Knightsbridge, west London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stockman believes 40% market downturn he's long predicted has finally arrived...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/03/david-stockman-epic-downturn-is-here-brace-for-40percent-market-plunge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Reagan's OMB director warns a recession is closing in on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Administration prepares for massive shake-up after midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-administration-prepares-for-massive-13362905.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Trump administration is bracing for a massive staff shake-up in the weeks following the midterm elections, as the fates of a number of Cabinet secretaries and top White House aides are increasingly uncertain heading into a potentially perilous time for President Donald Trump. Some embattled officials, including Attorney General Jeff Sessions, are expected to be fired or actively pushed out by Trump after months of bitter recriminations. Others, like Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen, may leave amid a mutual recognition that their relationship with the president has become too strained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Bomber Makes Provocative Flyover Of U.S. Command Ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-03/russian-bomber-conducts-provocative-flyover-us-command-ship-during-trident-juncture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish Nurse Who Treated Synagogue Shooter Opens Up...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/11/04/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-jewish-nurse-treated-robert-bowers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jewish nurse who treated Pittsburgh synagogue shooting suspect Robert Bowers when he arrived at the hospital is telling his side of the story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy told to clean room shoots grandmother, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/southwest-valley-breaking/2018/11/04/mcso-11-year-old-shoots-grandmother-yvonne-woodard-before-killing-self/1886514002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An MCSO spokesman said 65-year-old Yvonne Woodard had asked the grandson to clean his room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another SoCal home-price boom cooling. Crash looming?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-housing-busts-20181104-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The housing market is slowing down, leading many would-be buyers to ponder if a crash is on the horizon. The history of Southern California housing booms is that they build steadily and end suddenly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pow! 'Good Guy' Superheroes Engage In More Violence Than Evil Enemies...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/superheroes-engage-more-violence-than-evil-enemies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your favorite superheroes may put their lives on the line to rid the world of evil, but they might not be the great role models for young children that they're often made out to be, it seems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOM FORD manager said she 'needed sex for breakfast, lunch and dinner': suit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/04/tom-ford-manager-said-she-needed-sex-for-breakfast-lunch-and-dinner-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seamstress for famed fashion designer Tom Ford says one of her bosses over-shared about her favorite accessory — sex toys — while boasting that she “needed sex for breakfast, lunch and dinner.” Y…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I killed soccer star and cut off genitals for raping wife'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/04/i-mutilated-nearly-beheaded-soccer-star-for-raping-my-wife/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The businessman who allegedly killed Brazilian soccer player Daniel Correa Freitas says he did so after finding the midfielder in his underwear trying to rape his wife. The Sao Paulo star’s b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market Boogeyman May Come for Bonds, Not Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/market-boogeyman-may-come-for-bonds-not-stocks-1541419320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Risk-parity funds are often cited as culprits during stock selloffs like the recent one. In this case, though, the worry should be in bonds, not stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Georgia, 11th-hour daggers over voting system...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/business/technology/article221117220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest indication of poor management of Georgia's secretary of state's office, run by Republican gubernatorial candidate Brian Kemp, follows a citizen's tip that the voter registration system used for Tuesday's election may be vulnerable to hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defiant Rouhani Promises Iran Will 'Break' New U.S. Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/iranian-president-promises-to-break-new-u-s-sanctions-1541413178 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani vowed that his country would resist tough new U.S. sanctions on Iran’s oil and banks, as Tehran braced for a new era of political and economic isolation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancels production boost...</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Companies/Apple-cancels-production-boost-for-budget-iPhone-XR-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;asia.nikkei.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimmer outlook for new model contrasts with extra orders for older versions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARTIES BRACE FOR SURPRISES</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/midterm-campaign-down-to-wire-as-two-parties-brace-for-surprises#gs.uoc8cNY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A split verdict would hand the House to Democrats, leave Republicans holding onto or expanding their Senate majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Citizens Replacing Teens at Fast-Food Joints...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/senior-citizens-are-replacing-teenagers-at-fast-food-joints</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Citizens Are Replacing Teenagers atÂ Fast-Food Joints</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diddy to headline Gillum rally...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414828-diddy-to-headline-gillum-rally-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean "Diddy" Combs will headline a rally for Andrew Gillum's Florida governor campaign midnight Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top Senate seats most likely to flip...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414658-the-top-senate-seats-most-likely-to-flip</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Republicans believe they are on the cusp of increasing their majority in the midterm elections despite historic headwinds that seem likely to cost the GOP control of the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. Emerges as GOP 'Relief Pitcher'...</title>
      <link>https://lasvegasnews.media/donald-trump-jr-emerges-as-the-g-o-p-relief-pitcher-of-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lasvegasnews.media&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force falcon expected to recover from 'life-threatening' injuries after West Point prank...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/military/west-point-apologizes-for-falcon-s-injuries-air-force-academy/article_5e36d640-e070-11e8-8c47-97fe443c471f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army’s military academy issued an apology Sunday for an apparent prank in which a live Air Force mascot falcon was abducted and injured ahead of this weekend’s Army-Air Force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Farrakhan Leads 'Death to America' Chant in Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.algemeiner.com/2018/11/04/renowned-antisemite-louis-farrakhan-chants-death-to-america-on-solidarity-trip-to-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.algemeiner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Midterm like no other in generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/This-midterm-election-is-like-no-other-in-a-13362028.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday's midterm election is about many things. It's about health care and immigration. It's about the economy. It's about power and who will hold it, both in Washington and in the states. Above all, it's about something more elemental: what kind of country Americans see today and want to see in the future. That makes these midterms unlike any in the recent past. Talk to voters almost anywhere about what this election means to them, and the answer almost invariably involves personal feelings about President Donald Trump and perceptions about the overall state of the country. This debate about America's divisions has been underway for some time, but Trump has raised the emotional level to something not seen before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influx of tech companies pushes Bay Area residents to breaking point...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-East-Palo-Alto-the-influx-of-tech-companies-13361661.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST PALO ALTO, Calif. - This poor city is surrounded by the temples of the new American economy that has, in nearly every way imaginable, passed it by. Just outside the northern city limit, Facebook is expanding the blocks-long headquarters it built seven years ago. Google's offices sit just outside the southern edge, and just a few miles to the west, Stanford University stands as the rich proving ground of the economy's future. Amazon just moved in. Only a small fraction of jobs in those companies go to those who live in this city of 30,000 people, one of the region's few whose population is majority minority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiment plays music -- to cheese -- to improve taste...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.ch/20181102/swiss-cheese-maker-experiments-with-music-to-increase-taste-led-zeppelin-a-tribe-called-quest-emmental-bern-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When searching a fromagerie for the perfect chunk of cheddar or parmesan, cheese aficionados have probably never grilled vendors over what kind of music was played to their cheeses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants camped at border worry caravans will shut them out...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f4d231f3a56c4156a06650245215f92d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATAMOROS, Mexico (AP) — Waiting on the southern end of a bridge that leads to the United States, Humberto Alvarez Gonzalez warily follows the progress of the caravan winding through Mexico with the goal of reaching the border. Alvarez and about two dozen other people are waiting in Matamoros, across the Rio Grande from Brownsville, Texas, because U.S. customs officers say there's no space to process them. They sleep on cots near the bridge and rely on donors who bring them food and clothing. Some have waited for two weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Buffett takes musical shots at Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-wpb-buffett-political-rally-20181103-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida music legend Jimmy Buffett supported the Sunshine State’s Democratic ticket in West Palm Beach Saturday, performing a free concert and changing lyrics to take shots at Gov. Rick Scott and President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Marchers Chant 'Death To America' On Sanctions Eve...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-oil-sanctions-iranian-marchers-chant-death-to-america-on-eve-of-us-oil-sanctions-1942828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Iranians chanting "Death to America" rallied on Sunday to mark the anniversary of the seizure of the U.S. Embassy during the 1979 Islamic Revolution and the imminent reimposition of U.S. sanctions on Iran's oil sector.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate: 'Demanding apology culture' not healthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dan-crenshaw-doesnt-think-snls-pete-davidson-owes-him-an-apology-we-dont-need-to-be-outwardly-outraged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Drunk fan mounts horse, tries to ride on BREEDER'S CUP track...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/local/crime/article221099660.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgetown man was arrested after Kentucky State Police say he tried to ride a horse onto the track during Breeders’ Cup racing at Churchill Downs. Michael Wells-Rody was charged with public intoxication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic bishops promised reform in sex-abuse scandal. They didn't look at own misdeeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/11/03/bishops/qVYEiZ5SY5wVzCgA3gvN5O/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. — Bishop Robert Finn wasn’t going anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Beto Blow It?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/04/ted-cruz-beto-orourke-texas-senate-2018-election-222188</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Republicans believe Ted Cruz was beatable — if only his opponent paid attention to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FOCUS ON SENATE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-heads-georgia-tennessee-2-days-until-midterms-170104574--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MACON, Ga. (AP) — President Donald Trump appeared to distance himself from the fate of House Republican candidates Sunday as he devotes his final two days before Tuesday's midterm elections to helping Senate and gubernatorial candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skin cancer deaths rates soar, mostly for men...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/skin-cancer-deaths-rates-soar-mostly-men-study-215426625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skin cancer deaths among men have soared in wealthy nations since 1985, with mortality rates among women rising more slowly or even declining, researchers told a medical conference in Glasgow Sunday. Reasons for the discrepancy between sexes are unclear but evidence suggests men are "less likely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee becomes Republican firewall...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/shock-polls-defy-forecasts-show-democrats-tightening-gaps-in-key-senate-races</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the final stretch of the 2018 midterms cycle comes to a close, Democrats are poised to take the House. But will the Senate also drift away from Republicans?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's next president declares war on 'fake news' media...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/brazils-next-president-declares-war-fake-news-media-192452131--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With half a billion dollars in public-sector marketing budgets coming under his discretion, the fiery former Army captain is threatening to slash ad buys with adversarial media groups, striking at the financial foundations of Brazil's free press. After a campaign in which Bolsonaro dismissed investigative</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Hit By 39 Quakes In 24 Hours; 'Movement Along San Andreas Fault'...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-03/california-hit-39-quakes-24-hours-scientists-warn-movement-along-san-andreas-fault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG EDGES CLOSE TO RUNNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/michael-r-bloomberg-to-air-5-million-in-ads-before-midterm-elections-to-tout-democrats----and-himself/2018/11/04/a1ef2196-e05a-11e8-ab2c-b31dcd53ca6b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire former New York City mayor has already given $110 million to the party and its candidates this year as he ponders a 2020 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood, betrayal, family bonds. How kingpin came to trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/nov/03/el-chapo-trial-betrayal-sinaloa-cartel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why was the world’s biggest druglord extradited to the US after decades of protection at every level of power in Mexico?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems traumatized by 2016 having nightmares...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/04/2018-elections-democrats-2016-nightmares-midterms-960458</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite forecasts of a Democratic House takeover, liberals grappling with &amp;quot;PTSD&amp;quot; are braced for another surprise election disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier will attempt to be first person to cross Antarctica solo...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6349769/British-soldier-attempt-person-cross-Antarctica-solo-1-500km-journey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Captain Louis Rudd, 47, will attempt to cross 1,500km of Antarctic ice in a 75 day solo expedition called the 'Spirit of Endurance.' He will face temperatures as low as -50C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis Call for AMAZON Boycott Over Anger at WASH POST...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/saudis-call-for-amazon-boycott-over-anger-at-washington-post</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudis Call for Amazon Boycott Over Anger at Washington Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida record-high early turnout...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414750-florida-sees-record-high-early-voting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Florida has seen record-high early voting totals ahead of Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Deep South, residents of upscale suburb fight to secede from neighbors...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-georgia-eagles-landing-20181102-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands who live within the proposed city boundaries of Eagle's Landing will have the opportunity to vote in a referendum on whether to form a new city. Those who would be left behind will not get to vote – even though their city could lose much of its population and bustling commercial hub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY AND LIMBAUGH AT RALLY WITH TRUMP!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414774-limbaugh-hannity-joining-trump-on-campaign-trail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rush Limbaugh and Sean Hannity will join President Trump at a rally on the eve of this week's midterm elections, the Trump campaign announced Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY AND LIMBAUGH TO RALLY WITH TRUMP!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-militia-groups-caravan-immigration-border-57149dd0-8e66-40d4-8714-2474e59a21cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But U.S. military officials are worried about their presence there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-test-of-trump-midterms-could-result-in-a-mixed-verdict-1541336400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2018 midterm elections, widely viewed as a referendum on Donald Trump’s presidency, appears headed for a split decision, with Republicans on track to keep control of the Senate while losing their House majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIEST ATTACKED ON LIVE BROADCAST...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/horror-deranged-man-charges-altar-screaming-profanities-at-priest-during-live-broadcast-of-mass-on-ewtn-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' MOCKS NAVY SEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/nicholas-fondacaro/2018/11/04/snl-mocks-gross-gop-candidate-who-lost-his-eye-ied-blast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the Vietnam War, liberals have been known for their great disdain for America’s service members, despite their efforts to hide it. During NBC’s latest edition Saturday Night Live, that disdain poked its ugly head out in the form of supposed comedian Pete Davison mocking Republican congressional candidate Dan Crenshaw about the eye he lost to an IED blast while serving in Afghanistan, “or whatever” according to the funny man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter enthusiasm surges among Hispanics...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-latinos/ready-for-a-fight-voter-enthusiasm-surges-among-u-s-hispanics-idUSKCN1N90AS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hispanics are more interested in voting this year than in the last U.S. congress...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Both media and Trump have responsibility to tone it down...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/03/both-the-media-and-trump-have-a-responsibility-to-tone-it-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Tuesday’s election touted as the most important in modern memory, morning-after scenarios run the gamut of possibilities. President Trump will be vindicated by a GOP sweep, weakened by a split…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-stop ads and robocalls: Welcome to America's costliest election...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/non-stop-ads-robocalls-welcome-americas-costliest-election-113052901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALMDALE, Calif. (Reuters) - Wendy Burke has had enough. Campaign advertisements bombard her favorite TV shows. Dozens of election pamphlets fill her mailbox. Every day, she gets several political calls on her cell phone and more on her landline. Strangers knock at her door seeking her vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen ahead of Macron in EU election polling...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/marine-le-pen-emmanuel-macron-in-eu-election-polling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-point edge going into midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/first-read/democrats-hold-7-point-edge-final-national-nbc-wsj-poll-n931001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty percent of likely voters say they prefer a Democratic-controlled Congress, while 43 percent want Republicans in charge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants who can't vote working hard to influence those who can....</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article221076975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although President Donald Trump is not on the ballot, immigrants in Miami and around the country are trying to turn the midterm elections into a referendum on presidential policies and they view as anti-immigrant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Digs In for a Long, Cold War With Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-digs-in-for-a-long-cold-war-with-iran-1541329200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has put Iran on notice that the punishing sanctions he plans to impose are just the opening salvo of an ambitious strategy to compel Tehran to pull back from its assertive posture in the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired and angry, migrant caravan splinters in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d12be31914c04c6ba4b66c5c112da59f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISLA, Mexico (AP) — A 4,000-strong caravan of Central American migrants traveling through Mexico split up into several groups with one spending the night in a town in the coastal state of Veracruz and other migrants continuing toward the country's capital. The divisions came during a tense day in which tempers flared and some migrants argued with caravan organizers and criticized Mexican officials. They were upset that Veracruz Gov. Miguel Angel Yunes had reneged on an offer late Friday to provide buses on Saturday to leapfrog the migrants to Mexico City.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
