<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>What It Was Like For Only American That Watched From Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42330/what-9-11-was-like-for-the-only-american-that-watched-it-from-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only American in space on 9/11 had no idea the towers were hit until he made a call to NASA. He soon saw ground zero for himself from orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest Colleges Would See Relief?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/richest-us-colleges-would-see-relief-under-democrats-tax-plan/ar-AAOkUYu </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Film Festival awards coveted Golden Lion after roaring back to life...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/09/venice-film-festival-winners-2021-1234663899/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who will receive the Golden Lion this year? The Italian film festival is handing out its top prizes on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans honor fallen...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210911174108-6gc8l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SEPT11/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-'Like an eternal flame': Americans honor the fallen on 20th anniversary of Sept. 11</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia uses new hardware at big military drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210911170606-h1150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-BELARUS/MILITARY DRILLS (TV):Russia uses new hardware at big military drills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Obama, Clinton share moment of silence...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-new-york-d6904990d776af784dd9f8c727ef19ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Three American presidents stood somberly side by side on Saturday at the National September 11 Memorial in New York, sharing a moment of silence to mark the anniversary of the nation’s worst terrorist attack with a display of unity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain path to closing Gitmo...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/20-years-after-911-biden-faces-uncertain-path-to-closing-guant-c3-a1namo-bay/ar-AAOkOO0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a tiny population of detainees remains, but political opposition to closure persists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban raise flag at presidential palace on 9/11 anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/571825-taliban-raise-flag-at-presidential-palace-on-9-11-anniversary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban raised its flag at the presidential palace in Kabul, Afghanistan on Saturday as the United States commemorated the 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11 attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Ceremonies At Ground Zero...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/photo-galleries/2021/09/11/remembering-9-11-twenty-years-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The names of the thousands of lives lost in the terror attacks were read out loud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Film Festival awards coveted Golden Lion after roaring back to life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tight-race-close-metoo-influenced-143524738.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Venice Film Festival was set to award its coveted Golden Lion on Saturday after roaring back to life this year with a starry and feminist-tinged selection that leaves the competition wide open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelical Lutheran church installs 1st trans bishop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-california-san-francisco-3442c30f6ab2cc4269630535d6e5fc4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — The Evangelical Lutheran Church of America is set to install its first openly transgender bishop on Saturday. The Rev. Megan Rohrer will lead one of the church's 65 synods, overseeing nearly 200 congregations in Northern California and northern Nevada, following the installation service at Grace Cathedral in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush makes appeal for unity; Warns of domestic threat...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210911153903-t8fd3/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SEPT11/PENNSYLVANIA-BUSH (PIX):George W. Bush calls out threat of domestic terrorism on 9/11 anniversary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen Performs at Anniversary Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/bruce-springsteen-9-11-20th-anniversary-memorial-1224193/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer delivers impromptu, poignant rendition of Letter to You closer following moment of silence to victims of terror attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper-partisan America: Not even another attack would pull nation together?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/571728-hyper-partisan-america-not-even-another-9-11-would-pull-the-nation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are we wiser than we were 20 years ago? More resilient? Less susceptible to surprise attack?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vindication of Capote...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vindication-truman-capote-032418151.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenwich EntertainmentAt his death in 1984, just shy of 60, in the Bel Air home of one of Johnny Carson’s ex-wives, Truman Capote was conspicuous less for his literary output than for his ubiquitous guest spots on late-night talk shows. Wallowing in performative agony, he was intoxicated by his own celebrity—to say nothing of alcohol and drugs—as he confided to the likes of Carson and Dick Cavett, in his trademark simpering squeal, how his apparently never-finished novel-length sendup of Manhat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vindication of Capote...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-vindication-of-truman-capote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Ebs Burnough’s new documentary “The Capote Tapes,” featuring interviews with friends, contemporaries, and Capote himself, seeks to cast the author in a new light.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew lawyers claim sex assault papers not properly served...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3640183/prince-andrew-served-epstein-accuser-case-tossed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew’s legal team have reportedly claimed that he hasn’t been legally served by his sexual abuse accuser Virginia Roberts – and plan to get the case tossed out. Lawyers f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists debate promise, peril of tweaking wild genomes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210911-scientists-debate-promise-peril-of-tweaking-wild-genomes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists debate promise, peril of tweaking wild genomes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/9-11-attacks-20th-anniversary/h_554fe18d6754bfd0b8d0bf479d837d3c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today marks 20 years since the Sept. 11, 2001, terrorist attacks on the United States. Follow here for live updates from the vigils and memorials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elder prepares for recall loss with lawyers, voter fraud site...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/larry-elder-prepares-for-california-recall-loss-with-lawyers-voter-fraud-website/article_2377ad25-f4d3-5fda-8d72-509af53fdcb9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — With less than a week to go until the California recall election, some Republicans are falsely claiming that votes are rigged in favor of Democrats and suggesting,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unions split...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-police-oregon-coronavirus-pandemic-workers-rights-05ff3bd3325fb47f90061b1cc8e339a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Nurses Union applauded President Joe Biden's proposal to require that companies with more than 100 employees vaccinate their work force. The American Federation of Teachers once said vaccine mandates weren't necessary, but now embraces them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House, Dems tangle over bid to raise taxes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-tax-reform-economy-2b5295280d2ee72f6b3b722cebc41c84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden has a simple message for fellow Democrats about his plan to raise taxes to remake large swaths of the American economy: look beyond the bottom line. Biden is trying to persuade Democrats to embrace a more emotional argument, namely that the plan is fair, that it increases taxes on those who can afford to pay more and spends money on programs targeting children and the middle class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice film awards race wide open after star-studded festival...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910215939-kqql1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FILMFESTIVAL-VENICE/ (PIX, TV):Venice film awards race wide open after star-studded festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin Clubs Return With Vengeance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/11/berlin-clubs-return-with-a-vengeance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — The beats were pumping inside Salon zur wilden Renate long after the sun had risen. Hundreds of euphoric,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELSA Bot Raises Serious Concerns for Humanity...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/09/elon-musks-tesla-bot-raises-serious-concerns-probably-not-ones-you-think/185202/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla Bot comes with a whole portfolio of risks that are hard to quantify and easy to overlook and yet inevitably end up tripping up innovators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/attacks-anniversary-world-trade-center-pentagon-pennsylvania-696e656f355a6ef55f37b29d2e90e648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The 9/11 anniversary commemoration at ground zero began Saturday with a tolling bell and a moment of silence, exactly 20 years after the start of the deadliest terror attack on U.S. soil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars rock samples reveal lengthy water exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Science_News/2021/09/10/Mars-Perseverance-rover-rock-sample/7121631286076/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first two rock samples examined by NASA's Mars rover Perseverance give scientists a firm belief that water inundated Jezero Crater for a sustained period of time, the agency announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion surrounds enforcement for federal workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/federal-workers-e2-80-99-vaccine-mandate-prompts-confusion-as-the-government-struggles-to-return-to-offices/ar-AAOjuK1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden announced the vaccine requirement Thursday, part of a raft of proposals meant to help curb the threat of the delta variant and lesson coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark lifts ALL covid curbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-the-way-we-were-denmark-lifts-all-covid-curbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The way we were: Denmark lifts all Covid curbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI FLASHBACK:  We Cannot Require Someone.  Not What We Can Do...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/pelosi-april-2021-we-cannot-require-someone-be-vaccinated-thats-just-not-what </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE:  APPLE can't force developers to use in-app purchasing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-v-apple-judge-reaches-decision-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial took place in Oakland, California, in May, and included both company CEOs testifying in open court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR TRAVEL NEXT?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-official-doesnt-rule-175031942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're not taking any measures off the table," White House COVID-19 response coordinator Jeff Zients said during a virtual press briefing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal powerhouse BOIES suffers lawyer exodus over controversies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/boies-schiller-loses-lawyers-over-controversies-involving-theranos-harvey-weinstein.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boies Schiller Flexner has experienced a rapid exodus of several top attorneys, many of whom were bothered by purported decisions by the firm's founders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Sheen daughter claims she was 'trapped' in 'abusive' home...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/10/charlie-sheen-denise-richards-daughter-claims-she-was-trapped-in-abusive-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sami Sheen said she dropped out of high school and moved out of the “Real Housewives of Beverly Hills” star’s home in a viral TikTok, but a source told us there’s more to he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 million viewers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-entertainment-nfl-dallas-texas-61cf595dc61bc315737dcdca61a5110d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL came into kickoff weekend looking for increased audiences over last season. After one game, the league is off to a strong start with the most-watched opener in six years. Thursday night's 31-29 victory by the Tampa Bay Buccaneers over the Dallas Cowboys averaged approximately 26 million viewers on NBC, Peacock and the NFL's digital platforms according to preliminary data from Nielsen and Adobe Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Imminent Threat' or Aid Worker: Did Drone Strike Kill Wrong Person?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/video/world/asia/100000007963596/us-drone-attack-kabul-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times obtained exclusive security camera footage and witness accounts to show how the military launched a drone strike that killed 10 people in Kabul on Aug. 29 without knowing who it was hitting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French ex-health minister charged over handling of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-french-ex-health-minister-charged-over-handling-of-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French ex-health minister charged over handling of pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fetuses found at funeral home were university collection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-biology-idaho-pocatello-idaho-state-university-2dfe8459de3335607fd1a61a878318de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POCATELLO, Idaho (AP) — Police say the remains of roughly 50 fetuses found at a Pocatello, Idaho, funeral home were part of a biological collection that Idaho State University provided to the funeral home for cremation in 2017.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
