<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>City sues company for flying giant American flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/local/camping-world-fighting-statesville-fines-legal-action-over-giant-american-flag/950640074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversy over a massive American flag is now reaching a new level as the company responsible for flying the flag is rallying community support to fight the City of Statesville, which has reportedly filed a lawsuit to have the flag removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deflated Opposition Considers Negotiating With Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/21/world/americas/venezuela-juan-guaido-nicolas-maduro.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juan Guaidó remains upbeat in public. But he acknowledged in an interview that the opposition’s capacity to operate is hurting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sherpa Sets Mt. Everest Record -- Climbing Twice In Week!</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/21/725324340/nepalese-sherpa-sets-mount-everest-record-again-climbing-mountain-twice-in-a-wee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nepalese mountain climber has now climbed Mount Everest a record 24 times — and he's hoping to do it one more time before he retires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunity Bill to Stop Netanyahu Indictment Reaches Knesset...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Bill-to-stop-Netanyahu-corruption-indictment-reaches-Knesset-590308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The immunity bill comes after Attorney-General Avichai Mandelblit recommended to indict Netanyahu for three counts of fraud and breach of trust and one of bribery, pending a pre-indictment hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police to return property seized from San Fran reporter...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b015a5c1e80c483f961ca29bf019724c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Police agreed Tuesday to return property seized from a San Francisco journalist in a raid, but the decision did little to ease tensions in the case, which has alarmed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-FACEBOOK exec to Zuckerberg: Hire a new CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/21/ex-facebook-security-chief-stamos-says-zuckerberg-should-hire-new-ceo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Facebook executive Alex Stamos said Mark Zuckerberg should hire a new CEO and turn his focus to building products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 MINUTE STANDING O!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/markets-festivals/quentin-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-score-six-minute-standing-ovation-at-cannes-1203222162/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty five years after Quentin Tarantino took Cannes by storm with “Pulp Fiction,” the maverick director returned with “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood,” receiving a six-minu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Therapy Giving Arthritic Dogs Longer Lives...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/05/21/dog-hip-dysplasia-study-arthritis-pain-pets-colorado-colorado-animal-pain-center-northglenn-rob-landry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local health study in Colorado seems to be doing wonders for pets with arthritis pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loose change left at airports to fund border security...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/tsa-could-use-3-million-in-loose-change-to-pay-for-dhs-backup-border-funding-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration plans to use loose change left in trays at airports to partly fund the $232 million that its parent agency, the Department of Homeland Security, has requested to help pay for border operations if Congress doesn’t agree to its $1.1 billion funding request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR BUCKLES UNDER SCHIFF?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/21/politics/justice-department-doj-counterintelligence-adam-schiff/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department is trying to stave off an "enforcement action" against Attorney General William Barr this week, making a rare offer to have the House Intelligence Committee review materials from special counsel Robert Mueller's report if House Intelligence Chairman Adam Schiff agrees to back down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Bets on Gambling...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/newsletters/axios-media-trends-1245102a-65f3-4dc4-8b50-2b7e6cfc5d30.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trends reshaping the digital media ecosystem, by Sara Fischer. Tuesday mornings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top baseball prospect chooses Japan over MLB...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/braves/2019/05/21/carter-stewart-mlb-draft-japan-league/3753088002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Draft prospect Carter Stewart is making aÂ unique career decision, foregoing hisÂ chance in this June's Major League Baseball draft to play overseas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation tied to Michael Cohen ongoing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/investigation-tied-michael-cohen-search-warrant-are-ongoing-n1008306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part of the Michael Cohen search warrant will remain redacted until at least July because it's related to an active investigation, a judge ordered Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ prisons ban book on black men in justice system...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/state/arizona-prisons-ban-book-on-black-men-in-the-justice-system</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona has banned prisoners from reading a book that discusses the impact of the criminal justice system on black men, drawing outcry from First Amendment advocates who say the move is censorship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Religious Couples Have Happier Marriages...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/report-religious-couples-have-happier-marriages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both religion and egalitarianism have something to offer those seeking a happy marriage in a world of shifting mores, a new report shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller hesitant about testifying...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/21/politics/robert-mueller-testify-congress-negotiations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller's team has expressed reluctance to him testifying publicly in front of the House Judiciary Committee, according to sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA stock could drop to $10, analyst says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/21/morgan-stanley-tesla-shares-could-drop-to-10-in-worst-case-scenario.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morgan Stanley analysts said the reduction was driven by concerns around Chinese demand for Tesla products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Date defrauds woman of $80,000 after meeting on site...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/man-meets-alpharetta-woman-dating-site-defrauds-her-out-80k-police-say/R0uEatSAK0FVmVlShiEyyO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gwinnett County police are looking for a man they say defrauded an Alpharetta woman out of more than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors admit Kraft 'sneak and peek' warrants flawed...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/05/21/prosecutors-admit-sneak-and-peek-warrants-in-kraft-case-were-flawed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prosecution of Patriots owner Robert Kraft — or, more accurately, his aggressive effort to challenge it — has brought to light troubling police practices regarding so-called “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexicans buy fake phones to hand over in muggings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4fe25feb5481467fbcc0a2f275a287f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Armed robberies have gotten so common aboard buses in Mexico City that commuters have come up with a clever if disheartening solution: Many are buying fake cellphones, to hand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service Testing Self-Driving Trucks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/usps-tests-self-driving-trucks-hauling-mail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a two-week test, startup TuSimple will transport mail for the US Postal Service between Phoenix and Dallas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are consequences?</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/nadler-prepares-contempt-vote-mcgahn-consequences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Judiciary Chairman Jerrold Nadler preparing committee vote to hold former White House counsel Don McGahn in contempt after no-show at Tuesday hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your own best friend with $3,000 robo-dog kit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7052747/Build-best-friend-Students-design-3-000-kit-robo-dog-jump-flip-dance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students from Stanford University's Student Robotics club have created a robot dog that can backflip and even dance. Its creators have also put all the plans for making the robot yourself online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of U.S. colleges have segregated residence halls...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/05/20/study-75-american-colleges-offer-black-only-graduation-ceremonies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by the National Association of Scholars revealed that at least 75 American colleges have black-only graduation ceremonies and 43 percent of surveyed colleges offer segregated residential halls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN President Takes a Knee: 'Fans Do Not Want Us to Cover Politics'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/05/21/nolte-espn-president-takes-a-knee-fans-do-not-want-us-to-cover-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN President Jimmy Pitaro finally conceded defeat by admitting, “Our fans do not want us to cover politics.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Cozy Up to Wall Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-21/democrats-cozy-up-to-wall-street-while-shunning-corporate-cash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Headwinds for reelection are severe...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/444674-the-memo-trump-faces-steep-climb-to-reelection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump faces a steep uphill climb to a second term, even if it’s far too early to count him out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McGahn defies subpoena for testimony...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6384c08d99de4bfa982cdd5065f63434</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Judiciary Chairman Jerrold Nadler gaveled open a Trump-Russia hearing Tuesday with an empty witness chair and a stern warning that former White House Counsel Don McGahn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie theater allows dogs and offers bottomless wine...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/movie-theater-allows-dogs-and-offers-bottomless-wine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;K9 Cinemas in Plano provides a place for dog lovers to watch their favorite movies with their canine companions, and if for some reason you&amp;rsquo;re still not sold, your ticket comes with all the wine you can drink.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE CHAOS:  May asks lawmakers to vote on SECOND Brexit referendum?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190521151703-ksu54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/MAY-REFERENDUM (URGENT):May to ask lawmakers to vote on a second Brexit referendum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENVER RECORD COLD...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/05/21/denver-sees-biggest-late-may-snow-in-44-years-plus-record-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of 8 a.m. on Tuesday, Denver had officially received 3.4 inches of snow. That's the most snow measured this late in the season since May 29, 1975 when 5.6 inches hit the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK:  Secret NASA plans for permanent Moon base...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9119244/secret-nasa-plan-moon-outpost-rocket-launches/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA’S official plans to build a permanent base on the Moon have leaked online, revealing how and when astronauts will return to the rocky world for the first time in 50 years. Internal docum…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Pentagon Interested in UFOs?</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/why-ufos-interest-the-pentagon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mars colonists 'will be super-mutants' that die 'if mate with Earthlings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9119985/mars-colonists-super-mutant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE FIRST humans on Mars will quickly become too fragile to have sex with. That’s according to one scientist, who reckons colonists will warp into super-mutants who’ll keel over the mom…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Man: What lies behind Sunshine State's crazy stereotype?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/21/florida-man-what-lies-behind-the-sunshine-states-crazy-stereotype</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brawling Easter bunnies, alligator-filled pants, naked basketball … all reflect Florida’s antic spirit but perhaps also its darker side</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Film Poster Features Decapitated Trump Head in MAGA Hat...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/cannes-sci-fi-film-poster-features-decapitated-donald-trump-head-maga-hat-1211199 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The B-movie-style one-sheet shows a woman holding two decapitated heads, including one that looks like the commander-in-chief wearing his signature campaign headgear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town offers free VIAGRA to boost birth rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7052683/French-town-offers-FREE-VIAGRA-boost-birth-rate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jean Debouzy, mayor of Montereau in northern France (stock photo), issued a decree saying he was 'favourable to the distribution of the little blue pills'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17-year-old to graduate HARVARD days after graduating high school...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Living/17-year-graduate-harvard-11-days-graduating-high/story?id=63156576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teen from Kansas will soon take home a degree from Harvard just days after he walked the stage to receive his high school diploma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says Biden 'deserted' PA. In Scranton, he's 'hometown boy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-tries-to-downplay-generations-of-family-13866122.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 1950s, Scranton, Pennslyvania, was at the start of a long, slow decline. The coal mines that had fueled the city's early prosperity were shutting down, leaving residents to cope with gaping sinkholes and a scarred landscape. Textile factories, too, were on their way out, and thousands of people picked up and left for better opportunities elsewhere. Joining the exodus were 10-year-old Joe Biden and his family.  Unable to find a steady source of work, Biden's father, Joe Sr., had been commuting to Wilmington, Delaware, to clean boilers. By 1953, he decided it was time to move the whole family across the state lines.  Biden, who was in grade school at the time, presumably didn't have much say in the matter. But that didn't stop PresidentDonald Trump from declaring on Monday night that the Democratic presidential contender had abandoned Pennsylvania.  "Biden deserted you," he told the crowd at a campaign rally in Montoursville, Pennslyvania, located about 80 miles west of Scranton. "I guess he was born here, but he left you, folks. He left you for another state."  The eyebrow-raising assertion received only a muted response from the audience, suggesting that even Trump's die-hard supporters weren't necessarily sold on the claim. Over the years, Biden has repeatedly referenced his Scranton roots, which pundits see as a strategic political move geared to appeal to working-class voters in a crucial swing state. But locals have consistently insisted that his affection for the hardscrabble city is genuine.  "You think it's an opportunist thing, but it's not," his childhood friend, Tom Bell, told the Scranton Times-Tribune in 2008. "The guy's that way. He's always been. Before he was even in the limelight."  The former vice president's ties to the area go back generations. Biden, a noted genealogy enthusiast, took part in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Americans believe OK to cheat on taxes, according to IRS poll...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/more-americans-believe-its-ok-to-cheat-on-your-taxes-according-to-irs-poll-2019-05-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll was published during an increasingly heated battle between President Trump and Congressional Democrats over his own tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 178 cats found in waste-filled home...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/oakland-county/2019/05/20/178-cats-found-waste-filled-west-bloomfield-home/3746216002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty cats have been euthanized because of serious injuries and medical problems in what officials believe is the county's largest animal neglect case</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSANTO Kept 'Watch Lists' of GMO Opponents...</title>
      <link>https://www.european-views.com/2019/05/bayer-reveals-monsanto-had-watch-lists-of-gmo-opponents-in-7-eu-countries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.european-views.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bayer has inherited a large number of lawsuits with its 63-billion-dollar takeover of US company Monsanto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb-carrying drone targets Saudi airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d7a332d8303349b6bc2f63b8eb8675e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Yemen's Iranian-allied Houthi rebels said Tuesday they attacked a Saudi airport and military base with a bomb-laden drone, an assault acknowledged by the kingdom...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Medicare for All's' rich benefits 'leapfrog' other nations...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/15163a801e854345a836d4287809fc44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Generous benefits. No copays. No need for private policies. The "Medicare for All" plan advocated by leading 2020 Democrats appears more lavish than what's offered in other...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video game urges players to kill journalists...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/20/video-game-urges-players-to-kill-journalists-to-make-them-famous-in-a-different-way/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A twisted video game featured on Apple and Android devices urged players to gun down journalists to make headlines before the level was yanked by developers. “Sniper 3D Assassin,” which…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLS-ROYCE Selling $47,000 Champagne Cooler...</title>
      <link>https://www.bosshunting.com.au/gear/rolls-royce-champagne-chest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bosshunting.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I tell you what, there's no Jacob's Creek or Yellowglen within a hundred miles of this little scummy little package from Rolls-Royce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Wealthy Brazilians, Portugal the New Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/for-many-wealthy-brazilians-portugal-is-becoming-the-new-miami</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Many Wealthy Brazilians, Portugal Is Becoming the New Miami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom Was Right. Politeness Pays...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-21/mom-was-right-politeness-pays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily duels outside Alabama clinics...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/daily-duels-over-abortion-outside-alabama-clinics-064300590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a particularly tough week for Margaux Hartline, a volunteer who holds a large umbrella over women going into an Alabama abortion clinic so their faces are unidentifiable to religious activists. Last week, the southeastern US state passed the strictest anti-abortion law in the country,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley Shame: Living in Van in GOOGLE Backyard...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/silicon-valley-shame-living-van-090010246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sergeant Wahed Magee, of the Mountain View Police Department, was furious. Mountain View is a wealthy town that’s home to Alphabet Inc., the world’s fourth-most valuable public corporation and Google’s owner. This is the epicenter of a Silicon Valley tech boom that is minting millionaires but also</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino back at Cannes 25 years after 'PULP FICTION'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tarantino-back-cannes-25-years-pulp-fiction-093716794.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mastermind behind hits including "Reservoir Dogs" and the "Kill Bill" series, Tarantino, 56, is in Cannes to premiere his ninth movie, one of the festival's most hotly-anticipated screenings. It's a remarkable trajectory for the self-taught American director born in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO:  I WANT ONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/20/beto-fox-town-hall-2020-1335374</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His remarks come a day after South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg participated in one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican holds ground on impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/20/gop-rep-justin-amash-holds-ground-calls-trump-impeachment/3745203002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Justin Amash disputed several talking points that Republicans, including Trump, have used as reasons the president did not commit obstruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Poor Sleep Makes People Lonely, Anti-Social...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/poor-sleep-causes-social-anxiety-that-affects-others-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By now, we should all be aware of the health dangers that come with a lack of sleep, but new research from the University of California, Berkeley suggests that poor sleeping habits can also lead a person to become more anti-social.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Taliban' set for early release from prison... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/senators-ask-trump-administration-american-taliban-getting-prison-early</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bipartisan team of senators is asking the Trump administration why the “American Taliban” is about to get early release from federal prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell introduces bill making the legal smoking age 21...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/senate-majority-leader-mitch-mcconnell-introduces-bill-raise-federal-legal-smoking-age-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McConnell’s comes amid growing concerns about the youth use of e-cigarettes, which reached record levels in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA DANGER:  Rural Iowans ponder Trump alternatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-trade/rural-iowans-ponder-trump-alternatives-as-china-trade-war-drags-on-idUSKCN1SQ1LG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic U.S. presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg asked a crowd of supporter...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US census vulnerable to Russian meddling, top official warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/census-russian-interference-hacking-2020-20190521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Most of the agencies of the federal government that ingest data are very concerned about interference in the process of taking the 2020 census,” said John Abowd, chief scientist at the U.S. Census Bureau.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great white comes to Long Island Sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-great-white-long-island-sound-20190520-4nedfszk2ndfbmjvrleutxo2eq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just in time for Memorial Day, oceanic researchers said they have tracked a great white shark off Connecticut’s coast, the first time ever that the prodigious predator of summer movie fame has been pinpointed in Long Island Sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobach lists demands to join administration; Jet on call, future cabinet post...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-would-be-trump-aide-s-demands-a-jet-on-call-a-future-cabinet-post-and-more/ar-AABE6Gc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUMPING:  ICE looked to hire transport provider to move unaccompanied minors and migrant families...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/immigration/article230577329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump questions FOXNEWS after Mayor Pete showcase...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7051311/Pete-Buttigieg-Fox-News-hit-Democratic-candidates-town-hall-draws-1-1-million-viewers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump thinks 'something strange is going on' at Fox News Channel with the recent influx of Democrat town halls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeps 'Hate Agents' List...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/05/20/exclusive-more-names-on-facebook-hate-agents-list-revealed-including-brigitte-gabriel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebanese-American conservative author and religion critic Brigitte Gabriel (born Hanan Qahwaji) is also on an internal list of “Hate Agents” maintained by Facebook, Breitbart News can exclusively reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freak snow falls in  Midwest week before Memorial Day!</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/social-media-users-express-dismay-as-may-snow-falls-in-the-midwest-and-west/70008327</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTRESS FAINTS, HITS TABLE WITH A THUD...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/elle-fanning-faints-cannes-film-festival-dakota-fanning-2019-1203221408/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elle Fanning, a member of this year’s Cannes jury, had a brief scare Monday night when she fainted at the Chopard Trophee dinner. Festival director Thierry Fremaux had just introduced actor F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life was easier when humans hunted and gathered their food, Cambridge University finds...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/life-easier-humans-hunted-gathered-150000389.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switching from hunting to farming made life 50 per cent more difficult for humans, a study by Cambridge University suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULTER:   Four myths media and politicians tell you about border crisis... </title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/immigration/444437-ann-coulter-four-myths-the-media-and-politicians-tell-you-about-our</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every single thing the mainstream media says about the border crisis is a lie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amash storm hits Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/444676-amash-storm-hits-capitol-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Justin Amash (R-Mich.) doubled down Monday on his case that President Trump should be impeached for obstruction of justice, ensuring the spotlight will stay on the stunning attacks against his party’s leader all week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  4 IN 10 AMERICANS EMBRACE SOCIALISM</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/257639/four-americans-embrace-form-socialism.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While half of Americans view socialism as a bad thing for the country, 43% say it would be a good thing, a much smaller gap than when last measured in 1942.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial Billboard On Highway: 'Welcome To Colorado, Where You Can Get A Safe, Legal Abortion'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/05/20/billboard-colorado-legal-abortion-utah-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billboard reads "Welcome to Colorado. Where you can get a safe, legal abortion.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran accelerates production of enriched uranium as tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-accelerates-production-enriched-uranium-164543278.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The semi-official Tasnim news agency quoted Behrouz Kamalvandi, an official at Iran’s Atomic Energy Organization, as saying that Iran had increased its output of 3.67% enriched uranium as of Monday, and that the United Nations nuclear watchdog had been informed. Crucially, Iran hasn’t increased the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders holds up fried chicken leg for pic with black man in SC!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/colonel-sanders-bernie-poses-with-black-man-holds-up-fried-chicken-leg-in-sc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only Democrats can get away with this level of pandering. Bernie Sanders visited a Taste of Black Columbia in South Carolina on Friday and posed with a black worker while holding a fried chicken leg. Another photo shows him biting into it. .@BernieSanders visits a Taste of Black Columbia, an annual showcase for local SC …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crepe Caper:  Students investigated for adding bodily fluids to food served to teachers...   </title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/crepes/ohio-crepe-caper-216590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight Ohio middle school students could face felony assault charges for allegedly putting bodily fluids in crepes that were consumed by teachers, according to police who say that the young suspects r</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court upholds Dem subpoena for Trump financial records...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/20/judge-upholds-dem-subpoena-for-trump-financial-records-1335370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge, Amit Mehta, ruled that Congress can investigate the president without beginning formal impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders makes appeal to Deep South black voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a252a47ff1114df7978634dcac0efbc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders made an appeal Monday to black voters in the Deep South, stopping at a historically African American church and calling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Impeachment Clash With Colleagues Behind Closed Doors...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/20/nancy-pelosi-impeachment-1336587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three members of the Democratic House leadership all pushed to begin an impeachment inquiry on the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF HELL: Autistic family member forced to live in cage, eat cremation ashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/crime/2019/05/guilty-pleas-in-caging-beating-abuse-of-autistic-woman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terry Knope II, 46, and Raylaine Knope, 43, both pleaded guilty in New Orleans to charges involving forced labor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work with phone companies alarms legal experts; Confidential doc...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/05/20/facebook-data-phone-carriers-ads-credit-score/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal experts believe Facebook profiling may run afoul of federal law on credit checks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh and Gorsuch Disagree on 3 Decisions -- In Day...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/conservative-scotus-justices-kavanaugh-and-gorsuch-disagreed-on-three-decisions-in-one-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BIDEN, BERNIE LOCKED IN IOWA TIE...</title>
      <link>https://iowastartingline.com/2019/05/20/starting-line-change-research-poll-biden-sanders-locked-in-iowa-tie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;iowastartingline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Starting Line/Change Research Poll shows both Sanders and Biden at 24% in Iowa, though there's good news in the data for several other candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infamous Forum For Social Media Hackers Hacked by Other Hackers...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/bj97nd/infamous-forum-for-instagram-hackers-gets-hacked-by-other-hackers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers hacked the OGUSERS forum and published its database in another hacker forum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long before 'Varsity Blues' scandal, universities saw fraud signs...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-college-admissions-scandal-universities-what-know-explainer-20190520-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the investigation continues, a key question is what universities knew and whether more could have been done to detect the widespread fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen told lawmakers Sekulow instructed to make false claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cohen-told-lawmakers-trump-attorney-jay-sekulow-instructed-him-to-falsely-claim-moscow-project-ended-in-january-2016/ar-AABE5Tk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images reveal glacial masses drifting in 'Iceberg Alley'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7050969/Jaw-dropping-images-reveal-150-FOOT-TALL-glacial-masses-floating-Canadas-iceberg-alley.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a series of tweets, an amateur photographer captured the breadth and versatility of icebergs from his vantage in what's known as 'iceberg alley' located off the coast of Canada.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
