<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX employees file federal labor charge over Chappelle controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/netflix-employees-file-labor-charges-023520645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two trans Netflix employees have filed labor charges alleging the company retaliated against them for speaking out against Dave Chappelle's special.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency of violent threats on Capitol Hill unnerves staffers...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Frequency-of-violent-threats-on-Capitol-Hill-16576979.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It was her first bomb scare on the job, and yet the work day Wednesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida activist says cop warned her not to wear condo costume to Halloween party...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/florida-activist-says-cop-warned-her-not-to-wear-condo-costume-to-halloween-party/article_d0392bd1-3a1c-5a56-a3e6-678e9ab7b310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Imagine getting a spooky call from a cop warning you not to wear a boxy condo costume to a Halloween party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Thinks Unthinkable: Life After Elizabeth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/what-happens-when-queen-elizabeth-ii-dies-britain-must-confront-the-question</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything will change — from the head on bank notes to the sense of certainty and continuity Elizabeth II has so calmly embodied.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Hasn't Left China in 21 Months. Covid Only Part of Reason...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/xi-hasnt-left-china-in-21-months-covid-may-be-only-part-of-the-reason/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the presidents and prime ministers of the Group of 20 nations meet in Rome this weekend, China’s leader, Xi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Assaults Worsening Crisis at Rikers, Jail Officers Say...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/sexual-assaults-are-worsening-a-crisis-at-rikers-jail-officers-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One female correction officer was attacked and choked by a man who had been convicted of sexual assault. Another, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Rural West, Residents Taking Firefighting Into Own Hands...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/in-the-rural-west-some-residents-are-taking-firefighting-into-their-own-hands/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALISADES, Wash. — Molly Linville vividly remembers the “wall of flame” that tore through the grasslands of her 600-acre ranch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did The Don's $300 Million SPAC Deal Skirt Securities Laws?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/29/trumps-300-million-spac-deal-may-have-skirted-securities-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just days after Donald J. Trump left the White House, two former contestants on his reality show, “The Apprentice,” approached</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Mounts Attack Against Woman Who Accused Him of Sex Abuse...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/29/prince-andrew-mounts-attack-against-woman-who-accused-him-of-sexual-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Prince Andrew on Friday issued a blistering attack on a woman who has accused him in a lawsuit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants call logs, aide's notes hidden from Jan 6 panel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-lawsuits-united-states-capitol-siege-4e55ed79b42043fbdef1628d684e1495</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump is trying to block documents including call logs, drafts of remarks and speeches and handwritten notes from his chief of staff relating to the Jan. 6 Capitol insurrection from being released to the committee investigating the riot, the National Archives revealed in a court filing early Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ HOSPITAL MANDATES BOOSTERS</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article255384931.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers at a New Jersey hospital have until Dec. 24 to get a COVID booster shot if they got the Johnson &amp; Johnson shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Deadliest September Since WWII With Virus Untamed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-suffers-deadliest-september-since-world-war-ii-with-covid-untamed/ar-AAQ6yVy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia suffered its deadliest September since World War II, according to figures published Friday, even before the peak of its current wave of the Covid-19 pandemic forced authorities to order non-working days for the first week of November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD preparing for crush of retirements ahead of vax mandate... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/28/nypd-preparing-for-slew-of-retirements-amid-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is bracing for mass resignations over the city’s COVID-19 vaccine mandate — issuing numerous guidance Thursday for cops who would rather quit than get the jab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  VA GOV RACE TOSS UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/virginia-governor-s-race-a-toss-up-as-election-day-nears-post-schar-school-poll-finds/ar-AAQ69nW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are locked in a tight race for the Executive Mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  MORE REST FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10145583/Queen-advised-doctors-continue-rest-TWO-WEEKS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 95-year-old will not undertake any official visits and will be confined to 'light, desk-based' duties only, a Buckingham Palace statement said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian had right to mock disabled teen, court rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/29/canada-jeremy-gabriel-mike-ward-discrimination</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legal battle had waged for more than a decade and raised questions over satire and the need to protect vulnerable children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Munger bankrolls windowless dorm. Architect quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/29/business/ucsb-munger-hall/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Charlie Munger is bankrolling the design of a massive dormitory at the University of California, Santa Barbara. The $1.5 billion project comes with a major catch — 94% of the dorm's single occupancy rooms have no windows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy agencies may never be able to identify origins...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029205834-bc0i1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ORIGINS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. spy agencies may never be able to identify origins of COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Ramp Up Patrols: Potential Threats to Malls...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/virginia/fairfax-police-ramp-up-police-presence-for-halloween-weeken/65-976cff2b-5f34-4e62-91f6-24c29509cf62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fairfax County Police Chief Kevin Davis said his department had received information about "potential public safety impacts" to malls and shopping centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising ESPN personality taken off air after DUI arrest...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/29/espn-personality-harry-lyles-jr-off-air-after-dui-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up-and-coming College GameDay personality Harry Lyles Jr. will be off the show Saturday because of a DUI arrest after last week’s program in Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Iran's brutal 'eye for eye' justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3959967/irans-brutal-justice-system-gouged-eyeballs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AROUND the world, the justice system doesn’t come much more barbaric than in Iran. Its “eye for an eye” laws – known as Qisas – sees prisoners subject to brutal punish…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cube Exits SONY Comedy 'OH HELL NO' After Declining Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/ice-cube-exits-sony-comedy-oh-hell-no-after-declining-covid-19-vaccine-1235038369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sony film, which co-stars Jack Black, had been set to shoot this winter in Hawaii.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoke bombs, floods, virus fears for world climate summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211029-smoke-bombs-floods-and-virus-fears-as-glasgow-readies-for-cop26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A soft drizzle fell on a cluster of American climate activists as they set off smoke bombs in George Square in Glasgow's city centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT becomes world's most valuable company...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/29/microsoft-passes-apple-to-become-the-worlds-most-valuable-company-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft and Apple have each had their turn as the world's most valuable company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters Suspended for Threatening Sen., FDNY Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/firefighters-suspended-for-threatening-sen-myrie-staff-over-vaccine-mandate-fdny-says/3362652/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FDNY members of Ladder 113 have been suspended for driving their truck to a state senator’s New York City office and threatening his staff over the vaccine mandate for city workers. The firefighters drove to state Senator Zellnor Myrie’s office in Brooklyn on Friday and questioned staff as to where the politician lives. The crew is accused of telling his…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces mug shot, fingerprinting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/29/andrew-cuomo-faces-mug-shot-fingerprinting-and-overwhelming-evidence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Gov. Andrew Cuomo will get his mug shot taken and be fingerprinted next month — when he faces “an overwhelming amount of evidence against him” in court, authorities said Fr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo sex crime case: Sheriff says 'overwhelming evidence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/29/cuomo-sex-crime-case-new-york-sheriff-says-we-have-an-overwhelming-amount-of-evidence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The complaint accuses Andrew Cuomo of forcible touching of a female executive assistant last December in the New York governor's mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts Sound Alarm On Stalkerware,' Allows Others To Spy On Phone...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/10/28/cyberstalking-stalkerware-domestic-violence-awareness-month-smartphone-apps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we recognize October as Domestic Violence Awareness Month, we want to shed light on a type of abuse that many don't even realize is such a problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayoral candidate hit by cab in Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/new-york-city-mayoral-candidate-curtis-sliwa-hospitalized-after-being-hit-by-cab-in-manhattan/ar-AAQ6EQk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP candidate got hit by the taxi near the corner of 50th Street and Sixth Avenue after getting out of his campaign van to walk over to the nearby WABC radio studio for an interview, the adviser, Rob Cole, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION: 'White Nationalists' Pose at Campaign Stop...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/guybenson/2021/10/29/pathetic-dems-pose-as-white-nationalists-supporting-glenn-youngkin-n2598259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Desperation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England to Become First Country To Prescribe Vapes...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/jgmx5k/england-to-become-first-country-in-world-to-prescribe-vapes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New guidelines from health experts mean that e-cigarettes will be prescribed on the NHS to cut smoking rates, despite warnings of the dangers of vaping from the WHO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover cause of Alzheimer's progression in brain...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/scientists-discover-cause-alzheimers-progression-180513448.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toxic protein clusters thought responsible for the cognitive decline associated with Alzheimer's disease reach different regions of the brain early and then accumulate over the course of decades, according to a new study Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Condors can have 'virgin births'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-california-san-diego-681720b1602ab1a93792c7c1f68a9c54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — Endangered California condors can have “'virgin births," according to a study released Thursday. Researchers with the San Diego Zoo Wildlife Alliance said genetic testing confirmed that two male chicks hatched in 2001 and 2009 from unfertilized eggs were related to their mothers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Series sticker shock: $1,000-plus for standing-room-only tickets...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/atlanta-braves/world-series-sticker-shock-1000-plus-for-standing-room-only-tickets/2QUXVEY4V5CEJKZHSXKYGM2LUU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ticket prices on the secondary market for Friday night’s World Series game at Truist Park remained above $1,000 as of Thursday afternoon, and some of those tickets came without a seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American flags, Dem political sign set afire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/american-flags-democratic-political-sign-set-afire-outside-homes-in-arlington/ar-AAQ4gUO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three American flags and one Democratic yard sign have been torched in Arlington in the last two weeks, but no houses were damaged and no one was hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore,</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/weather/bs-md-coastal-flooding-maryland-forecast-20211028-g3pmoudzxbagrf4g6zrk4d5nne-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports of flooding, storm damage and power outages began circulating rapidly Friday morning, as the winds strengthened on the Chesapeake Bay amidst a storm forecasters predicted to yield some of the worst flooding along Maryland’s coastline since Hurricane Isabel in 2003.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC brace...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/weather-news/2021/10/powerful-storm-system-brings-heavy-rain-flooding-to-dc-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful storm system is bringing heavy rainfall and flooding to parts of the D.C. region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  MORE REST FOR QUEEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-queen-advised-doctors-rest-25332597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors have advised the Queen to rest for at least the next two weeks following a bout of illness, meaning Her Majesty will not attend a Remembrance event on November 13, Buckingham Palace has announced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside controversial gunshot-detection firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-59072745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BBC News has been given access to ShotSpotter, the controversial US technology company that detects gunshots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Equals NFL With Slavery In New NETFLIX Series...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/video/colin-kaepernick-review-netflix-nfl-colin-in-black-and-white-ava-duvernay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the very nature of its co-creators and the tale they have to tell, Colin Kaepernick and Ava DuVernay’s Colin in Black &amp; White was never going to be your standard coming-of-age drama. In that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tidal Flooding Leaves Annapolis Underwater...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/29/live-tidal-flooding-inundates-downtown-annapolis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tidal flooding on Friday left streets in downtown Annapolis underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman struck victim in head with chicken inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/walmart-chicken-attack-745830</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 29--A Pennsylvania woman is facing a criminal charge after allegedly striking another woman in the back of the head with a “cold chicken” at a Walmart Supercenter, according to police and cou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley turns blood into human eggs?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/10/28/1038172/conception-eggs-reproduction-vitro-gametogenesis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-connected startup company is trying to rewrite the rules of reproduction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/author-all/richard-johnson/0/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWYER UP...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/alec-baldwin-shooting-rust-david-halls-hannah-gutierrez-hire-lawyers-halyna-hutchins-1234864561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A week after the fatal shooting of cinematographer Halyna Hutchins by Alec Baldwin on the New Mexico set of Rust, two crew members at the center of the police probe have hired a pair of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MINS:  FUTURIST WARNS HUMANS WILL BE HACKED IF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE NOT REGULATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/yuval-harari-sapiens-60-minutes-2021-10-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harari says global cooperation is needed to prevent human data from getting into the hands of a powerful few. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS ABBA:  NOTHING SELLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/27/abba-sos-on-eve-of-marketing-launch-three-new-singles-in-a-row-have-failed-to-sell-or-get-radio-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Travelers Suffer Back Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/10/half-space-travelers-experience-back-pain/186449/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The human spine is built to support our bodies under the gravitational forces experienced on Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis says he should keep receiving Communion...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029143433-2n239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-BIDEN/COMMUNION (URGENT):U.S. President Biden says Pope told him he should keep receiving Communion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KISS Roadies Blame Band for Covid Death of Guitar Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-features/kiss-francis-stueber-covid-tour-protocols-death-1249590/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The band, meanwhile, claims that some crew members concealed sickness and faked vaccine cards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Black athletes bring stories to screen, Kevin Durant delivers 'SWAGGER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/as-black-athletes-bring-their-stories-to-the-screen-kevin-durant-delivers-e2-80-98swagger-e2-80-99/ar-AAQ63qX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Durant and Colin Kaepernick are joining a growing movement of Black athletes telling their own stories with the help of Black filmmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy over Communion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-visits-pope-francis-amid-political-controversy-over-communion/ar-AAQ57cE </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innoculated just as likely to spread delta within household...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/579068-vaccinated-just-as-likely-to-spread-delta-variant-as-unvaccinated-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who have received COVID-19 vaccinations are able to spread the delta variant within their household despite their vaccination status just as easily as unvaccinated individuals,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusually long meeting...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211029121049-3xdpa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POPE (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Biden has unusually long meeting with pope as abortion debate flares at home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halloween solar flare headed for Earth; Could disrupt power grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3957750/halloween-solar-flare-headed-earth-power-grid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SUN launched a massive solar flare yesterday that’s headed in Earth’s direction – the strongest storm seen in the current weather cycle. The volley of radiation may trigger the nort…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE MEETS POPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10144177/Joe-Jill-Biden-arrive-closed-door-meeting-Pope-Francis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden got a 75-minute meeting with Pope Francis on Friday, longer than his two predecessors in the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Employee Training Program Says, 'White People, You are Problem'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/t-employee-training-program-says-222048736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T Corporation is putting its employees through a racial reeducation program that teaches that “American racism is a uniquely white trait” and tells white people that they are “the problem,” according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
