<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Frenzy: TV Networks Blast With 96% Negative News...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/rich-noyes/2019/11/12/impeachment-frenzy-nets-aim-destroy-trump-96-negative-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the six weeks since the Democrats’ impeachment inquiry was announced, the liberal media have tried to help the cause by giving the effort wall-to-wall coverage, blasting the President with 96% negative coverage (even including criticism of his performance after the successful mission against ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi), even as they ignore how Trump’s policies have benefited the record-setting economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Kamala Harris slips to 1% in NH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/quinnipiac-kamala-harris-polling-at-1-percent-in-new-hampshire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest Quinnipiac poll of New Hampshire shows Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden with a narrow lead in a close four-way race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator: All comes down to motive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/gop-senator-john-kennedy-quid-pro-quo-probably-impeachable-if-trump-motive-political/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsey Graham agrees, except that he doesn’t think there was a quid pro quo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West to take stage at Joel Osteen Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.disrn.com/2019/11/12/kanye-west-to-take-stage-at-joel-osteens-lakewood-church-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.disrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West is scheduled to take the stage at Joel Osteen's Lakewood Church this Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daytime TV Shocker: Entire 'DAYS OF OUR LIVES' Cast Fired...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/11/12/days-of-our-lives-cancelled-cast-fired-season-56/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sand appears to be leaking out of the hourglass. TVLine has learned exclusively that the producers of Days of Our Lives have released the entire cast from their contracts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITI Warns of  'War on Wall Street and Wealth' in 2020 Election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citi-warns-war-wall-street-153355457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The road to the White House in 2020 may entail a war against Wall Street and wealth itself, as polling results encourage more candidates to cast a jaundiced eye toward the financial world, Citi warned in a note to clients.Some candidates are prioritizing greater accountability for big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: USC Student Found Dead Off-Campus, Brings Semester Death Toll To 9...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/11/12/9th-usc-student-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The student was a 28-year-old man and LAPD now says no foul play is suspected, after the death was reportedly considered suspicious Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gervais Back As GOLDEN GLOBES Host...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/ricky-gervais-host-golden-globes-2020-nbc-hfpa-1202783565/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Ricky Gervais has been pressed into service once again and will host the 77th annual Golden Globes next year. While the Oscars and the Emmys went hostless this year, the Hollywood Foreig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO DAIRY:  Top milk company declares bankruptcy amid drop in demand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5eb1173f5e2b4994927bc921f5b49f0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dean Foods, America's biggest milk processor, filed for bankruptcy Tuesday amid a decades-long drop-off in U.S. milk consumption blamed on changing trends and a growing variety of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: Election vendors are 'prime targets,' need oversight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4fe79d4ef9ff487f97f0bc3981cf7fd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — The private companies that make voting equipment and build and maintain voter registration databases lack any meaningful federal oversight despite the crucial role they play in U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican who helped lead Clinton impeachment:   'Troublesome'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/republican-congressman-helped-lead-clinton-impeachment-trump-ukraine/story?id=66914842 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asa Hutchinson, governor of Arkansas, called the call between President Trump and Ukraine's president "very troublesome" on "The Investigation" podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reckless driver told cops he was speeding home after 'cheating on wife'...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/cheating/cheating-florida-man-390568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Man pulled over Sunday night for driving recklessly told police that he “needed to get home in a hurry because he was cheating on his wife,” according to an arrest affidavit. Cops report th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Meditate To Make Fewer Mistakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hate-mistakes-meditation-may-make-you-less-error-prone-in-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who are clumsy or error-prone when completing a task may want to consider adding meditation to their daily routines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 10 earthquakes shakes Southern California...</title>
      <link>https://www.modbee.com/news/california/article237275064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.modbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake video shows Boris Johnson back Jeremy Corbyn for PM...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/creepily-realistic-deepfake-video-shows-20866883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deepfake was made by London-based thinktank Future Advocacy to alert people to the danger of fake news and video while the UK is just a month away from a General Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic blast to plunge 200 million into deep freeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/200-million-americans-to-experience-harsh-record-challenging-cold-this-week/622611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Take Probe Public as Trump Roars Defiant...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-impeachment-probe-public-trump-090000085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- House Democrats this week are taking their effort to impeach Donald Trump into a risky new phase of public hearings that the president is eager to turn into a made-for-TV personal battle, echoing his successful White House run in 2016.The hearings on Wednesday and Friday feature three</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong bloodshed in dangerous new phase... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2b32e41e4314aaf9d58cf117f19581d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Police and protesters battled outside university campuses and several thousand demonstrators blocked roads as they took over a central business district at lunchtime on Tuesday in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden autobiography censored in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/12/edward-snowden-says-autobiography-permanent-record-censored-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sections on democracy and privacy appear to be missing in Chinese edition of Permanent Record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Don Jr. Landed Smack in Middle of Right-Wing Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-donald-trump-jr-landed-smack-in-the-middle-of-a-right-wing-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Jr. is the latest conservative celeb to be besieged by racist “groypers,” who style themselves after an obese cartoon frog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC RACING MOVIE AS REAL AS EVER GONNA GET...</title>
      <link>https://autoweek.com/article/car-life/new-ford-v-ferrari-movie-real-its-ever-gonna-get</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;autoweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can predict if you'll die soon -- but we've no idea how it works...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2222907-ai-can-predict-if-youll-die-soon-but-weve-no-idea-how-it-works/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence can predict a person’s chances of dying within a year by looking at heart test results, but doctors can't work out what patterns it’s picking up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small quakes strike near big faults along California-Mexico border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-11-11/several-small-earthquakes-strike-el-centro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small earthquakes under El Centro, Calif., are important to closely monitor, especially since they occur close to major faults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'cult' quietly operating in NY for decades...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/11/inside-the-alleged-cult-that-has-been-quietly-operating-in-ny-for-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In December 1978, a bizarre theater company headed by an actress from the “Slaughterhouse-Five” film was run out of San Francisco. Members of Sharon Gans’ so-called Theater of All…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAIN ZAP: NEW HEADSET COULD HELP SLEEP BETTER...</title>
      <link>https://home.bt.com/news/uk-news/new-headset-could-help-people-enjoy-better-nights-sleep-11364410252667</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;home.bt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Modius SLEEP was launched on Tuesday by Belfast-based company Neurovalens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A NATION COMING APART...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a3b7df66e50f488a841a31ce31124987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Atlantic magazine was founded in the years leading up to the Civil War, so it's worth noting when it produces a special new issue on the theme, "How to stop a Civil...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Then and now: How Trump impeachment hearing is different...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a2efee2cfbfb4b5dbe7ed347ae8c8068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The public impeachment inquiry hearings this week usher in a rare and momentous occasion in American history as Congress debates whether to remove a president from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RON PAUL: Bubble Pop?</title>
      <link>http://ronpaulinstitute.org/archives/featured-articles/2019/november/11/is-the-mother-of-all-bubbles-about-to-pop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ronpaulinstitute.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corbyn backs Boris for Prime Minister in eerily realistic deepfake clip...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10328958/jeremy-corbyn-boris-johnson-election-deepfake-clips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SCARILY realistic fake video of Jeremy Corbyn backing fierce rival Boris Johnson to be Britain’s next Prime Minister has emerged online. The shock clip is an example of a so-called “d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A NATION COMING APART...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/12/a-nation-coming-apart/600730/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meaning of the American idea in 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY+ Hit by Technical Issues on Launch Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/disney-hit-by-technical-issues-launch-day-1254094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users mentioned problems accessing the service or some of its features around 7 a.m. New York time, and Downdetector.com showed 6,900 reports of problems with the service around 7:30 a.m. ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy Amass Record $121 Billion in Tax-Sheltered Accounts...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wealthy-amass-record-121-billion-050001203.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s better to give than to receive, the saying goes. But to give, receive an immediate tax deduction and then dole out charitable dollars at your leisure is even better, judging by a recent report.More than $37 billion flowed into tax-sheltered donor-advised funds in 2018, according to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>150 rockets fired at Israel after IDF assassinates Gaza terror leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/idf-orders-schools-businesses-shot-from-gaza-to-tel-aviv-for-1st-time-since-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens wail in Tel Aviv; IDF orders schools shut from Gaza to Tel Aviv for 1st time since 2014; army says it's prepared for several days of fighting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Threatened From NY to Texas With Blast of Arctic Air...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2019-11-08-arctic-cold-outbreak-mid-november-record-midwest-south-east?cm_ven=hp-slot-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent cold fronts have been notable, but this week's plunge will be the coldest so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX HOST:  WHY IS DRUDGE COVERING NEWS?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jesse-watters-accuses-drudge-of-being-anti-trump-thats-what-you-log-on-to-cnn-com-for/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Jesse Watters went after The Drudge Report editor Matt Drudge arguing his site is turning against President Donald Trump because it has posted negative headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TILLERSON DENIES TRUMP SABOTAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/11/11/rex-tillerson-said-he-resisted-trumps-decisions-or-else-people-would-die-nikki-haley-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON – Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson is disputing a claim by Nikki Haley, the former U.S. ambassador to the United Nations, that he sought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://video.foxnews.com/v/6102221338001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the internet's top websites has shifted to negative Trump headlines and pro-Buttigieg coverage. Fox News media analyst Howard Kurtz reacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump's Stock Market Record Stacks Up...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-stock-market-record-stacks-193002360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- It’s been three years now since Donald Trump was elected president, which means it’s been three years of listening to Donald Trump bragging about how great the stock market is doing. Contrary to one now-infamous pre-election prediction, it has done quite well.The Dow Jones Industrial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon official testifies freeze on aid to Ukraine came from Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fded1157e52341338fd3f7086a0eb28d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The view among the national security officials was unanimous: Military aid to Ukraine should not be stopped. But President Donald Trump's acting chief of staff thought...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuel-theft rings fill South Florida roads with 'moving bombs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/crime/fl-ne-fuel-theft-south-florida-credit-card-fraud-20191111-iyhiq7hyf5fabpvj3hc2jo2jce-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These criminals lug huge amounts of stolen gasoline across South Florida’s roadways, hiding hundreds of gallons in modified trucks and SUVs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-month-old to be taken off life support against mom's wishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article237224574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House at war with itself even as it fights  inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/white-house-at-war-with-itself-even-as-it-fights-impeachment-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The White House's bifurcated and disjointed response to Democrats' impeachment inquiry has been fueled by a fierce West Wing battle between two of President Donald Trump's top advisers, and the outcome of the messy skirmish could be on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDOLEEZZA RICE:  The call is murky, it is really murky...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment-condoleezza/former-u-s-top-diplomat-rice-concerned-by-shadow-diplomacy-on-ukraine-idUSKBN1XL2A7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Condoleezza Rice, a secretary of state under Republican President George W. Bush...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. 'Dreamers' may come down to Chief Justice Roberts...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-11-11/supreme-court-case-about-dreamers-may-come-down-to-chief-justice-roberts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dreamers' best hope for victory at the Supreme Court almost surely depends on Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco's New DA: Public Urination 'Will Not Be Prosecuted'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/11/san-francisco-chesa-boudin-public-urination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chesa Boudin, the urine-and-feces-plagued city's incoming district attorney, pledged during the campaign not to prosecute public urination and other quality-of-life crimes if he was elected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable news networks to preempt regular programming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/15e3ce69ef7b49219ff3855fb75be96f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Impeachable or not? Both Democrats and Republicans see the televised impeachment hearings starting this week as their first and best opportunity to shape public opinion...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi promo video labels feminism, atheism, homosexuality as extremist ideas...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191111183240-ipalt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homosexuality and atheism have long been illegal and punishable by death in the absolute monarchy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia's Most Populous State Prepares for Extreme Fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/education/article/Australia-s-most-populous-state-prepares-for-14826772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Hundreds of schools remained closed across Australia's most populous state on Tuesday, and residents were urged to evacuate woodlands for the relative safety of city centers as authorities braced for extreme fire danger. New South Wales on Monday declared a weeklong state of emergency in preparation for Tuesday's hot, dry and windy conditions. The declaration gives the Rural Fire Service sweeping powers to control resources and direct other government agencies. Rural Fire Service Commissioner Shane Fitzsimmons said 3,000 firefighters were available to fight more than 50 fires blazing across the state. The fires are expected to worsen as winds are forecast to gust at between 70 kmh (43 mph) and 90 kmh (56 mph) later Tuesday. The worst fires are expected in the state's northeast, where three people have died and more than 150 homes have been destroyed since Friday, as well as around Sydney. "Now is the time to exercise those decisions to leave, leave early and go to safer locations, safer towns and villages or safer places in your local community, such as the shopping centers," Fitzsimmons told reporters. "We plan for these sorts of days. But we always hope they never come," he added. More than 600 schools and technical colleges across the state are closed on Tuesday because they are close to woodlands at risk of fire. The annual Australian fire season, which peaks during the Southern Hemisphere summer, has started early after an unusually warm and dry winter. More than 1 million hectares (3,800 square miles) of forest and farmland had already burned across the state this fire season, more than three times the 280,000 hectares (1,080 square miles) that burned during the entire last season, Fitzsimmons said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deval Patrick Mulls Last-Minute Entry Into Presidential Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/new-england/Former-Mass-Gov-Deval-Patrick-Presidential-Run-Report-564768242.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick is exploring a late run for president, according to people with knowledge of Patrick's deliberations, who spoke on condition of anonymity because they were not authorized...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera, tripwire device found near Charlottesville Confederate monument...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/11/stonewall-jackson-confederate-monument-camera-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have removed an unauthorized camera and apparent tripwire device from the vicinity of a Confederate monument in Charlottesville, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top US general says 500 American troops to stay in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2019/11/10/top-us-general-says-500-600-american-troops-to-stay-in-syria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff says about 500 or 600 U.S. troops will remain in Syria to counter Islamic State fighters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Hockey Host Fired After Calling Immigrants 'You People'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/don-cherry-fired</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cherry, 85, had singled out new immigrants for not honouring Canada’s veterans and dead soldiers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Doctors Remove 8-Inch Screwdriver From Mentally Ill Man's Rectum...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/11/doctors-remove-8-inch-screwdriver-from-mans-rectum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 46-year-old man had a screwdriver pulled out of his rectum after he apparently pushed it inside himself and leaving it there for a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoping for Tears...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/pbs-correspondent-dems-hoping-witness-will-cry-during-impeachment-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PBS White House correspondent Yamiche Alcindor said congressional Democrats are looking for emotional witnesses to get viewers invested in impeachment proceedings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Rejects Legal Alliance With Mulvaney...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/11/bolton-rejects-legal-alliance-with-mulvaney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A long-simmering feud within the White House broke into the open on Monday as a lawyer for John</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's tiniest twin boys defy odds after being born at 23 weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10318673/worlds-tiniest-twin-boys-23-weeks-one-pound/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUM Talia Keates cradles her “little miracles” — the world’s tiniest twin boys. Ashley and Joe each weighed less than 1lb when born at 23 weeks. The Brit mum says the boys are her “one in a million…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Can Marriage Counseling Save America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/12/better-angels-can-this-union-be-saved/600775/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Borrowing techniques from couples therapy to bring liberals and conservatives back together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy launching -- podcast?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/politics/rudy-giuliani-impeachment-podcast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani is considering re-entering the impeachment fray by launching a podcast to provide impeachment analysis of the public hearings in the House of Representatives scheduled for later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor arrested for performing procedures on patients without consent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/11/health/virginia-doctor-hysterectomies-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia doctor has been arrested after he was accused of performing hysterectomies and other unnecessary medical procedures on patients without their consent, according to a federal affidavit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can't sue NY to stop release of tax returns, judge says...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/judge-dismisses-trump-lawsuit-ny-officials-house-committee/story?id=66918561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Monday issued another blow to President Donald Trump and his ongoing effort to avoid having his tax records turned over to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pub crawl in NKorea? Tour offers St Patrick's Day party like no other...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/pub-crawl-north-korea-tour-172859249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cities dye their rivers green (looking at you, Chicago), others light up the sky with emerald fireworks, but across the globe, St Patrick’s Day is universally celebrated with a drink or two. And it seems in North Korea it is no different. Although the Foreign Office advises against visiting North</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-7672837/Simon-Cowell-looks-slimmer-steps-London.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The X Factor head judge revealed a noticeably slender physique while greeting onlookers ahead of his appearance at Heart Radio studios in Leicester Square.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense firms on track to make killer bots reality...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1746154/lacking-regulation-firms-on-track-to-make-killer-robots-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such weapons “violate fundamental legal and ethical principles and would destabilize international peace and security,” says a Dutch NGO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students turn against free speech amid 'culture of conformity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7672091/Fewer-HALF-UK-students-support-freedom-speech-polls-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey by think tank The Policy Exchange shows youngsters whose views don't conform with the majority of students, such as those who support Brexit, feel silenced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO REPLACE IPHONES WITH GLASSES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/11/smart-glasses-that-replace-phones-may-be-the-next-hottest-tech-trend.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft, Snap, Facebook, Google, Apple and Amazon are all racing to replace our phones with glasses we wear everywhere.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
