<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Women Recall Sex Misconduct, Retaliation by Amb. Sondland...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/multiple-women-recall-sexual-misconduct-and-retaliation-by-gordon-sondland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three women recall Sondland made unwanted sexual contact in business settings. One says he exposed himself. All recall professional retaliation after they rejected him. Sondland denies the allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Want to Add Own Facial Recognition to RING...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/carolinehaskins1/ring-doesnt-have-facial-recognition-some-police-want-to-add</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assistant police chief of Chandler, Arizona, briefed colleagues in April on “leveraging consumer surveillance systems.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first HIV-positive sperm bank...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/first-hiv-positive-sperm-bank-is-launched-in-new-zealand-finds-three-donors-in-a-matter-of-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The donors are confirmed to carry ‘undetectable’ levels of the virus in their blood, which means they can’t pass it on, even through childbirth or condomless sex</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Inquiry Review Expected to Undercut Claim of FBI Spying...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/russia-inquiry-review-is-expected-to-undercut-trump-claim-of-fbi-spying/ar-BBXqMKh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>104-Year-Old Woman Bags Buck! </title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/11/27/104-year-old-kills-buck-to-become-wisconsins-oldest-hunter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 104-year-old woman has bagged a buck to become the oldest person in Wisconsin to ever harvest a deer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, Russia, China to Hold Joint Wargames in 'Message to World'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-russia-china-to-hold-joint-wargames-in-message-to-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran, China, and Russia will hold in the coming weeks their first-ever joint war drills, which leaders say are meant to send a "message to the world" about increased military cooperation between the rogue countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homelessness 'getting worse' -- some cities pushing back...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/27/homeless-thanksgiving-pushback-donald-trump-california/4308909002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cities are taking steps to limit the degree in which homeless people can sleep on sidewalks. The Trump administration may also take action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Links to Jewish Village...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rudy-giuliani-has-curious-links-to-a-jewish-village-in-ukraine/ar-BBXoTJ5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewest abortions since Roe v Wade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7732261/US-abortion-hits-record-low-Roe-v-Wade-Rates-fell-24-10-years-CDC-report-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abortion rates continue fall in the US, with a 2% drop reported from 2015 to 2016, the CDC reported Wednesday. The agency also reported encouraging declines in teen pregnancy rates in an earlier release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: School Bus Driver Drinks Beer While Operating Full Bus...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/bus-driver-busted-for-drinking-booze-while-driving-schoolchildren/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are two very strong messages that are going out. That it's not tolerated and we need the community's involvement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani was in talks to be paid by Ukraine's top prosecutor as they together sought damaging info on Dems... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Giuliani-was-in-talks-to-be-paid-by-Ukraine-s-top-14866932.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's personal attorney, Rudy Giuliani, negotiated earlier this year to represent Ukraine's top prosecutor for at least $200,000 during the same months that Giuliani was working with the prosecutor to dig up dirt on Vice President Joe Biden, according to people familiar with the discussions.  The people said that Giuliani began negotiations with Ukraine's top prosecutor, Yuri Lutsenko, about a possible agreement in February. In the agreement, Giuliani's company would receive payment to represent Lutsenko as the Ukrainian sought to recover assets he believed had been stolen from the government in Kyiv, those familiar with the discussions said.  The talks occurred as Giuliani met with Lutsenko in New York in January and then in Warsaw in February while he was also gathering information from Lutsenko on two topics Giuliani believed could prove useful to Trump: the involvement of Biden, and his son, Hunter, in Ukraine and allegations that Ukraine, not Russia, had interfered in the 2016 election.  Trump ultimately pressed Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to open investigations into the two issues during a July 25 phone call between the two leaders, a call that sparked a whistleblower complaint and the Congressional impeachment inquiry.  A person familiar with the negotiations described a series of contracts that were drafted earlier this year in which Giuliani would have worked for Lutsenko or separately, the Ukrainian Ministry of Justice.  For Lutsenko, the agreement would have provided a pipeline to Trump's lawyer and, through him, potentially to other top U.S. officials. For Giuliani, the agreements would have been a way to accrue financial benefit from a person who was also providing him politically damaging information that could help another client, the president of the United States.  Giuliani...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Obesity Can Cause Brain Damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/g00/en-in/health/health-news/obesity-can-cause-brain-damage-says-study/ar-BBXlduS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Blackout Wednesday': Thanksgiving Eve Huge Night for Drunk Driving...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article237684934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants from 30 Nations Crossed into Single TX Border Sector Since September...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/11/27/migrants-from-30-nations-apprehended-in-one-texas-border-sector-since-september-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Del Rio Sector Border Patrol agents apprehended migrants from at least 30 different nations since the beginning of October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon protesters demand 'haircuts for the rich'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lebanon-protesters-demand-haircuts-rich-172826380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebanese anti-government protesters lined up for free haircuts outside the central bank in Beirut Wednesday in a symbolic plea to make the rich pay and help rescue an economy in freefall. "We're here to teach them what a good haircut looks like," said 34-year-old Rebecca Saade, waiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxoffice Surprise: Mr. Rogers Movie 'BEAUTIFUL DAY' Has Legs...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/27/box-office-surprise-mr-rogers-movie-beautiful-day-has-legs-as-tom-hanks-aims-for-best-supporting-actor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good news. Mister Rogers is cleaning up the neighborhood. A small movie by comparison to things like “Frozen 2” and “Joker,” “A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood&amp;#8221…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuselage of new BOEING 777X ruptured in pressure tests... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/boeing-aerospace/boeing-777xs-fuselage-split-dramatically-during-september-stress-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Boeing's new 777X suffered a ground test failure in early September, the damage was much more alarming than previously reported. It wasn't a cargo door blowout. It was worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paints impeachment as probe of all conservatives...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/buoyed-polls-trump-paints-impeachment-probe-conservatives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump slung "Make America Great Again" caps into the crowd - then said the impeachment inquiry is about them as him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balloon makes an appearance at rally -- with its own security team!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/national-politics/article237791349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG:  We need more immigrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bloomberg-u-s-needs-more-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Mayor Mike Bloomberg said the United States would benefit from more immigrants, not fewer. Bloomberg is running for president as a Democrat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Debt Up $1.3 Trillion Since Last Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/federal-debt-13-trillion-last-thanksgiving-10137-household</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal debt has increased by $1,303,466.578.471.45 since last Thanksgiving, according to data released by the U.S. Treasury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY:  TRUMP APPROVAL 41.7%...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Wind could ground big balloons at NYC's Thanksgiving parade...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wind-could-ground-big-balloons-151126185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smokey Bear might feel like he’s battling Santa Ana winds — if he even gets a chance to fly. New York City’s big Macy’s Thanksgiving Day Parade will take place Thursday amid strong winds that could potentially ground the giant character balloons, which have caused mishaps and injuries in the past when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labour accuses UK PM of plot to 'sell' NHS to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/labour-accuses-uk-pm-plot-sell-nhs-trump-142024719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's main opposition Labour party on Wednesday accused Prime Minister Boris Johnson of plotting a "toxic" deal with President Donald Trump to allow US pharmaceutical companies access to the state health service. Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn held up what he claimed were 451 pages of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP 2.1%...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/17c1023b42894f6caed3da623cb50918</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. economy grew at a moderate 2.1% annual rate over the summer, slightly faster than first estimated, the government said Wednesday. But many economists say they think...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it arrested eight with CIA links during unrest...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191127154354-ujpkf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-GASOLINE/CIA (URGENT):Iran says it arrested eight with CIA links during unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy Danes who want to make deposit will need to pay up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-denmark-cenbank/wealthy-danes-who-want-to-make-a-deposit-will-need-to-pay-up-idUSKBN1Y11SS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy Danes might soon decide to put their cash somewhere besides their bank, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un advances nuclear threat as Trump talks stall...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/kim-jong-un-advances-nuclear-threat-to-us-as-trump/article_354ac653-b2c3-5b6d-8167-fd1416edf5d8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been about two years since Kim Jong Un launched a missile capable of hitting the entire U.S., declared his nuclear weapons program “complete” and halted all ICBM tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Allen decries 'thought police,' political correctness in comedy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/tim-allen-thought-police-view</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Tim Allen took aim at political correctness in his field, lamenting the fact that he has to accommodate the "thought police" when speaking to big arenas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyal pup cries at owner's grave and refuses to leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/loyal-dog-cries-late-owners-20972769</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 12-year-old pooch was filmed trying to dig into the grave to be reunited with its owner, who he had lived with for 10 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP 2.1%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/27/us-gdp-q3-2019-second-reading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy grew at a moderate 2.1% rate over the summer, slightly faster than first estimated. But many economists say they think growth is slowing sharply in the current quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang attacks Jewish teens walking in Brooklyn...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/27/gang-of-five-men-attack-jewish-teens-walking-on-brooklyn-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gang of five men assaulted two Jewish teens walking down the street in Brooklyn, knocking a yarmulke off one of their heads, police said Wednesday. The group approached a 14-year-old boy dressed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storms snarl Thanksgiving travel...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/storms-snarl-thanksgiving-travel-us-153813351.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of storms packing heavy snow and hurricane-force winds wreaked havoc Wednesday for Americans on the move for the Thanksgiving holiday. On one of the busiest travel days of the year in America -- an estimated 55 million people planning to drive or fly -- highways in the West and Midwest were closed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile simmers after another night of unrest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-simmers-another-night-unrest-153011595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looters sacked a hotel and several supermarkets in Chile in another night of unrest as tensions flared in the crisis-hit South American country. The violence "is reaching levels not seen in Chile since the return of democracy" in 1990, Defense Minister Alberto Espina warned Congress in an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Americans Say They Weigh 200 Lbs. or More...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/268847/americans-say-weigh-200-lbs-decade.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An average of 28% of Americans from 2010-2019 said they weigh 200 pounds or more, up from 24% who said the same from 2001-2009.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Porn Producer Accused of Sexually Exploiting 22 Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-fugitive-porn-producer-accused-of-sexually-exploiting-22-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Pratt has been sued by 22 women for coercing and defrauding them into adult videos. He fled the country before he could testify. Here are his only depositions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Caffeine, Xanax Found In Most Blood Used For Transfusions...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-caffeine-xanax-found-in-pure-blood-samples-used-for-transfusions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research finds that caffeine consumption is so widespread, it was detected in 100% of supposedly pure analyzed blood samples provided by blood banks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: POLICE NOW ACTIVELY USING ROBOT DOGS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/it-begins-police-are-now-actively-using-robot-dogs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil Liberties group warns machines could be weaponized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISERY!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7730125/Thousands-passengers-stranded-Denver-Airport-bomb-cyclone-causes-travel-chaos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of passengers have been stranded at the Denver International Airport as power outages, road closures and car pileups, add to the mix of travel chaos for millions ahead of Thanksgiving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: MORE STOCK RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/27/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-earnings-beige-book-and-data.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose slightly on Wednesday, building on their record-setting run after the release of stronger-than-forecast economic data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Women Brawl At Supermarket Over Too Many Items In Express Checkout Lane...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/police-2-women-brawl-at-new-jersey-shoprite-over-accusations-of-too-many-items-in-express-checkout-lane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight at the ShopRite in Howell broke out shortly before noon Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police search for suspect in string of attacks with 'liquefied fecal matter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/11/26/toronto-police-man-liquefied-fecal-matter-assaults/4314711002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Toronto Police Service is looking for a suspect who has emptied buckets of "liquefied fecal matter" on people in a string of assaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy swirls around APPLE film...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/entertainment/article/Controversy-over-The-Banker-means-it-may-not-be-14864516.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Apple TV Plus acquired "The Banker," a film about two black businessmen circumventing racist practices during the 1950s and '60s, it seemed to throw the new streaming service into awards-show contention.  But the Dec. 6 release of the film, which is inspired by real events, has now been delayed, the Associated Press reported. It's unclear when the film, which stars Samuel L. Jackson and Anthony Mackie, will be available in theaters or on Apple's streaming service. The move came as relatives of one of the film's real-life subjects made sexual misconduct accusations against another relative involved with "The Banker."  Here is a guide to the controversy surrounding the film:  -What is the film about?  George Nolfi's "The Banker" is based on two real people. Jackson and Mackie star as Joe Morris and Bernard Garrett, two black businessmen who recruit a working class white man to serve as the face of their real estate and banking empire. Meanwhile, Garrett and Morris pose as chauffeur and janitor as the business grows.  The men eventually attracted law enforcement's attention and eventually were convicted of misusing bank funds.  -What are the accusations?  Cynthia Garrett, a former VH1 and MTV interviewer and founder of Cynthia Garrett Ministries, is one of the daughters of Bernard Garrett Sr. (played by Mackie). In a statement, she accuses her half brother, Bernard Garrett Jr., of repeatedly sexually abusing her and her sister when they were girls. She also accuses Garrett Jr. of misrepresenting their father's life story. She called the project "an exploitative orientation of our family."  Garrett Jr., who had been reportedly listed as a producer on the film, appeared onstage alongside the director during a Nov. 5 IndieWire event.  This week, Garrett Jr. publicly denied the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A healthy man was licked by his dog. He was dead within weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-healthy-man-was-licked-by-his-dog-He-was-dead-14865198.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 63-year-old man showed up in the hospital with a burning sensation in his left leg and muscle pain in both. His flu-like symptoms were severe, with labored breathing for three days. He had petechiae, or rounds spots on the skin that look like rashes as a result of bleeding capillaries, which made his legs look discolored.  The patient's heartbeat was stable, doctors said, even though he was running a temperature of 102. His belabored breathing caused an inadequate supply of oxygen to his tissue. His failing kidneys were not producing urine, researchers wrote.  But doctors had no idea what was wrong with him. He had not recently been in the hospital. They suspected some kind of bacteria, but he didn't have any open wounds and he didn't have meningitis.  It wasn't until his fourth day in the hospital that a blood test revealed that the man had a type of bacteria found in the saliva of healthy dogs and cats. It's a kind of bacteria that's usually only transmitted to humans if they are bitten.  But the German man is dead because his dog licked him.  A paper published in the European Journal of Case Reports in Internal Medicine details how an otherwise healthy man lost his life within weeks of being infected by bacteria found in his dog's saliva.  Doctors at the hospital determined that he had multiple, serious ailments: severe kidney injury, signs of live dysfunction and rhabdomyolysis, a deterioration of muscle tissue that can result in kidney failure. He also had a build up of lactic acid in his bloodstream.  Once he was transferred to an intensive care unit, he was diagnosed as having severe sepsis with skin death and blood clotting, or purpura fulminans, according to doctors.  He was treated with antibiotics, but his health took a rapid decline for the worst over the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor, 35, suffers fatal heart attack on reality set...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/godfrey-gao-dead-collapse-reality-show-set</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Godfrey Gao died after suffering an apparent heart attack on the set of a TV show in China. He was 35.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAVENS Now Ahead Of PATRIOTS As Super Bowl Frontrunners...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/ravens-finally-replace-the-patriots-as-the-team-most-likely-to-win-the-super-bowl-per-simulation-projections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We now have a new Super Bowl frontrunner, according to SportsLine simulations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climber saved by 'FREE SOLO' star after El Capitan fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article237804629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says hundreds of banks torched in 'vast' unrest plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gasoline-protests-minister/iran-says-hundreds-of-banks-were-torched-in-vast-unrest-plot-idUSKBN1Y10GY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's top leader on Wednesday denounced an outbreak of deadly unrest as a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French farmers clog highways to protest at 'agri-bashing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-farmers/french-farmers-clog-highways-to-protest-at-agri-bashing-idUSKBN1Y10MQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French farmers angered by government policies that they say threaten their livel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI mind-reading tool produces video of human thoughts in real-time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ai-mind-reading-tool-produces-20971379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling footage shows an AI created by Russian researchers using the brainwaves of human participants to accurately guess their thoughts in real-time through video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Climate anxiety' churns up psychological storm...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-climate-anxiety-churns-psychological-storm-012205399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fears about climate change are prompting worldwide action, but one knock-on effect in the United States is mounting anxiety about everything from plastics to class-based environmental disparities. Schapira, a 40-year-old senior lecturer in the English department at Brown University, is addressing that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO grandmaster quits saying computers 'cannot be defeated'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/grandmaster-says-computers-cannot-defeated-104015667.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only human ever to beat Google's computer algorithm at the ancient Chinese strategy game Go decided to retire because he is convinced machines "cannot be defeated", a report said Wednesday. South Korean Lee Se-Dol's five-match showdown with Google's artificial intelligence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's AfD plots new course with radicals on rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-afd-plots-course-radicals-rise-025153180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's far right AfD party is choosing new leaders on Saturday in a vote shaped by an increasingly powerful radical wing which wants a rethink of the country's culture of atonement for Nazi crimes. The anti-migrant party's radicals have the upper hand following a series of electoral gains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight leaves voters cold in contested Wisconsin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed75f30906384abaad31b7b69a49d163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RACINE, Wis. (AP) — There’s not a lot that Republicans and Democrats in this political battlefield agree on, but the impeachment probe into President Donald Trump may have surfaced one: The public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Thanksgiving menu: Turkey, with side of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/deb5250314a44feea5aaa36150b479fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — Some people heading to Thanksgiving gatherings predict it’s not just the turkey that will get roasted. Already polarized over Republican Donald Trump’s presidency,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility Rate Record Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/us-fertility-rate-hits-record-low-after-four-consecutive-years-of-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were just over 59 births for every 1,000 women of childbearing age last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence erupts again in Colombia ahead of nationwide protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/violence-erupts-again-in-colombia-ahead-of-nationwide-protests/article_51d827c6-18f8-56df-a4c0-a3a3db72d51d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTA, Colombia — Violent protests erupted in Colombia on Tuesday ahead of nationwide marches that have been called for the second time in the span of a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo on rocky terrain...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/472181-pompeo-trump-relationship-tested-by-impeachment-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo is on rocky terrain with President Trump and members of the State Department following critical testimony by diplomatic officials in the public impeachment hearings led by House Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL RETURNS TO 405...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/video/4222753-watch-traffic-jammed-on-405-freeway-ahead-of-thanksgiving-getaway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the 405 is never easy driving through West L.A., it was all brake lights Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wintry weather to snarl holiday travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e0b05febb6b84aaebad59ca58a6841d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A storm packing heavy snow and high winds that wreaked havoc as it whipped through Colorado, Wyoming and Nebraska marched into the upper Midwest on Wednesday as anxious...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant explosion in Texas blows windows from homes miles away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98a09d85392e4cdfbc617fb7caf1e8bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT NECHES, Texas (AP) — A chemical company says three people were injured in an explosion at its plant in East Texas. The powerful blast blew out the windows of homes and sent a chemical plume...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb chef dies at 59...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5428beca21da4296bb49563256ee47a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Celebrity chef Gary Rhodes, who helped transform the stodgy reputation of British food, has died aged 59 with his wife Jennie by his side, his family said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg to visit church in NC... </title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article237748079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Haitian LGBTQ activist found dead amid suspicious circumstances...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonblade.com/2019/11/25/prominent-haitian-lgbtq-activist-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports indicate Charlot Jeudy may have been poisoned at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man has 700 tapeworms in brain and chest from undercooked pork...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10430920/more-than-700-tapeworms-found-in-mans-brain-and-chest-after-he-ate-undercooked-pork/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOCTORS were left stunned when they examined a scan showing their patient’s brain and chest was riddled with more than 700 worms. Zhu Zhongfa, 43, is believed to have ingested eggs of the parasite …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg tol visit church in NC... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/suicides-and-overdoses-among-factors-fueling-drop-in-us-life-expectancy/ar-BBXmQcB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUAWEI phone rated higher than IPHONE, SAMSUNG...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2019/11/24/huawei-beats-apple-iphone-11-pro-max-samsung-galaxy-s10-in-new-rating/#61b35ff732e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of nowhere, Huawei has just won an award for outstanding audio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX Threatened By NYC Mayor After Unauthorized Delivery Robot Roams Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90436843/even-the-mere-appearance-of-a-fedex-delivery-robot-freaks-out-the-mayor-of-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City officials were quick to tell FedEx to screw off, even though the robot’s appearance was just a marketing stunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Denies Sending Rudy to Ukraine for Biden Dirt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-denies-sending-rudy-giuliani-223426705.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump denied directing Rudy Giuliani to go to Ukraine to look for dirt on his political rivals, in an interview with former Fox News host Bill O’Reilly.“No, I didn’t direct him, but he is a warrior, he is a warrior,” Trump told O’Reilly in an interview streamed on the internet on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEAK TOO SOON?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/buttigieg-claims-2nd-warren-sinks-us-2020-poll-213929575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Political wunderkind Pete Buttigieg rocketed into second place in the Democratic presidential nomination race, polling showed Tuesday, with support for progressive ex-frontrunner Elizabeth Warren sliding as voters sour on her universal health care proposal. Buttigieg, the moderate millennial mayor of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE says recent changes improve user privacy, but lawmakers see them as an effort to edge out rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/apple-says-recent-changes-improve-user-privacy-but-some-lawmakers-see-them-as-an-effort-to-edge-out-rivals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has made strengthening privacy protections a central part of its brand. Critics increasingly warn that the iPhone maker may be using privacy as a guise for anti-competitive behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court's desire to be seen as neutral arbiter to be tested... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/national/as-trump-cases-arrive-supreme-court-s-desire-to-be-seen-as-neutral-arbiter-will-be-tested/ar-BBXnTnd?li=BBnbfcN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newborn offered for sale on CRAIGSLIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article237751089.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage After Video Shows Horse Being Pulled By Truck On Snowy Road...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/11/25/horse-tied-pickup-truck-colorado-grand-county-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video posted on Facebook showing a horse tied to the back of a pickup truck and being pulled has sparked outrage across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign attacks GOOGLE's new ad policy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a730d4aa93d143f6a42e21e0420a65f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s reelection campaign and other Republican election groups criticized tech giant Google on Tuesday for making it harder for political advertisers to target...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems accelerate impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/160472d13671476584be900f818a76aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House Judiciary Committee is set to take over the impeachment probe of President Donald Trump, Democrats announced Tuesday, scheduling a hearing for next week as they push...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine -- Might Help Alcoholics...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/11/26/782066337/a-single-dose-of-ketamine-might-help-heavy-drinkers-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants in the U.K. experimental study dramatically reduced their average alcohol intake for months after the initial dose. Ketamine has also been used to treat severe depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Influential neo-Nazi eats at soup kitchens, lives in govt housing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/influential-neo-nazi-eats-soup-kitchens-lives-government-housing-n1091681</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his writings, James Mason advocates waging war against "the system." But at 67 and living in Denver, he's now dependent on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Robbins starts legal actions against BUZZFEED -- in Ireland...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/tony-robbins-starts-legal-actions-against-buzzfeed-over-sexual-assault-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed self-help guru Tony Robbins filed a summons against BuzzFeed News in Ireland Tuesday after the digital news outlet published a report about an alleged sexual assault by Robbins that took place decades ago -- but the news organization said it stands by its reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary hearings next week...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/26/judiciary-committee-to-hold-first-impeachment-hearing-next-week-073991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are also giving Trump the option to let White House lawyers participate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANONYMOUS' to answer public questions -- anonymously...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/26/anonymous-trump-official-reddit-ama-074040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mysterious author of the famous op-ed and new book will answer questions for the first time in a Reddit AMA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN WIPEOUT? Poll shows plummeting support...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/quinnipiac-poll-half-of-warrens-supporters-have-abandoned-her-in-one-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest national poll of the Democratic primary conducted by Quinnipiac shows support for Elizabeth Warren plummeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans dying young at alarming rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/theres-something-terribly-wrong-americans-are-dying-young-at-alarming-rates/ar-BBXmP82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to Participate?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-invited-to-participate-in-impeachment-hearing-next-week/ar-BBXnC97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow scores 100th record close under Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/stocks-point-upwards-after-possible-us-china-trade-war-breakthrough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks continue to march higher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Admits Giving Wrong Person Kidney Transplant...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/11/26/exclusive-lourdes-hospital-transplant-center-admits-giving-wrong-person-kidney-transplant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two patients have the same name and are around the same age.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
