<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: ISIS Threatened...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-threat-invoking-christmas-market-attack-retribution-coming-on-new-years-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new poster distributed online superimposed a masked jihadist wielding a bloody knife over a collage of images from the 2016 Berlin attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUAWEI Exec Offers Husband, Children As Bail Collateral...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-11/huawei-cfo-offers-husband-children-bail-collateral</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 1 killed at Christmas market...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/11/strasbourg-shooting-in-eastern-france</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French police say several more injured after shooting on Tuesday evening in city centre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunshots in center of Strasbourg, France... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-shots/gunshots-in-center-of-strasbourg-leave-one-dead-fire-department-idUSKBN1OA2A8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunshots in the center of the French city of Strasbourg on the German border on ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLATE votes to strike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/420771-newly-unionized-slate-staff-votes-to-strike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently unionized writers and editors at Slate have reportedly voted almost unanimously to strike over concerns about the company's diversity policies and a rule mandating that union fees be optional for Slate employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory mishap paves street with chocolate...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/us-germany-chocolate-spill/firefighters-to-the-rescue-after-german-chocolate-factory-spill-idUKKBN1OA24Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters in the town of Werl in western Germany tackled an unusual emergency...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the IRS Was Gutted...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/how-the-irs-was-gutted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eight-year campaign to slash the agency’s budget has left it understaffed, hamstrung and operating with archaic equipment. The result: billions less to fund the government. That’s good news for corporations and the wealthy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops find gynecologist's trove of nude images of women...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-usc-gynecologist-storage-unit-20181211-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD raided a storage unit for USC gynecologist George Tyndall and found a trove of homemade pornography and photos of unclothed women in what appeared to be a medical exam room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up, down, back again:  Stocks on another dizzying ride...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/67212a8a2b684d309a267984376a9006</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. stock indexes veered through another dizzying cycle Tuesday, shooting to big gains early in the morning before falling modestly in midday trading. By early afternoon, indexes were mixed. It's just the latest in a series of sharp turns in direction for the market, which has lurched up and mostly down since late September as investors recalibrate how worried they are about the global trade war, rising interest rates and a slowing economy. The S&amp;amp;P 500 initially jumped more than 1 percent, following even bigger gains in Europe, on optimism about U.S.-China trade talks. But falling bank stocks helped weigh on indexes as the day went on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Canadian Diplomat Detained in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/former-canadian-diplomat-held-in-china-11544545983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Kovrig, a former Canadian diplomat and a senior adviser with Brussels-based nonprofit International Crisis Group, was detained after traveling to China this month to work on a research report on North Korea, a person familiar with the matter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA bans puppies as service animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/airport/delta-bans-puppies-service-animals/rWYbfgYBALr67cfdQXyM1L/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Air Lines is banning service and support animals under four months old.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB deaths raise security questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/2018/12/11/airbnb-security-mexico-costa-rica-deaths/2239544002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent weeks, a couple of deaths have raised questions about the safety of Airbnb rentals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spars in Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-congress/trump-spars-with-top-democrats-in-oval-office-over-border-wall-idUSKBN1OA1CF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump openly fought with the top two Democratic lawmakers ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones Storms DC to Confront Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-runs-from-alex-jones-roger-stone-at-congressional-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police threaten Jones with arrest during confrontation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kardashians viewership drops below million...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/11/ratings-kardashians-end-their-season-on-a-low-note-drop-37-from-beginning-of-season-to-just-851k-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kardashians can’t keep up with themselves. Their season finale pulled in just 851,000 viewers on Sunday night– a steep drop of 37% from the season premiere of 1.3 million. They pull…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Brazil cathedral shooting leaves 5 dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/five-dead-in-shooting-at-catholic-cathedral-in-brazil-globonews/ar-BBQOmH1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK's May, boxed in on Brexit, gets locked in her limo...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181211162500-kjhsh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/MAY-CAR (PIX, TV):UK's May, boxed in on Brexit, gets locked in her limo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'No plans' to launch Chinese search engine...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181211162129-23i9g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE-CONGRESS/ (URGENT):Google CEO: 'no plans' to launch Chinese search engine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could notorious biker club's survival hinge on trademark? The feds are betting on it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/could-a-notorious-biker-clubs-survival-hinge-on-a-trademark-the-feds-are-betting-on-it/ar-BBQO9z1?li=AAggFp4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says military to build border wall if Dem refuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9518d24c6bbe41238b8c82f092393284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump sought Tuesday to pressure Democratic congressional leaders into supporting his demand for billions of dollars to build his promised wall along the U.S.-Mexico border, threatening to have the military build it "if Democrats do not give us the votes to secure our Country." Trump tweeted the threat hours before Senate Democratic Leader Chuck Schumer and House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi were to meet with Trump at the White House in an effort to avert a partial government shutdown on Dec. 21, when funding for some agencies is scheduled to expire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-year-old crossed without parents...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/2-year-old-found-near-border-without-parents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Border Patrol agents working near the border found a two-year-old child traveling without her parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian special forces unit shown in action for the first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1056767/World-War-3-Russia-special-forces-video-USA-Ukraine-war-ww3-Spetsnaz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN TV for the first time has offered a glimpse into the training of elite special unit forces as they stormed a mock-up building and engaged with “terrorists”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Inside Jared's personal crusade...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/inside-jared-kushners-personal-crusade-reform-americas-prisons/story?id=53901143</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jared Kushner has been quietly pursuing a personal passion: seeking to improve the lives of roughly 6.7 million Americans in jail, prison, on parole or probation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 illegals caught in one day!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/dec/11/more-3000-illegals-caught-one-day-dhs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government snared more than 3,000 illegal immigrants in just one day last week, the administration’s top border official told Congress on Tuesday, saying the situation qualifies as a full-blown “crisis.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP APPROVAL 49%</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_dec11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian special forces unit shown in action for the first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/russias-elite-special-forces-spetsnaz-13718851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rare footage of the top-secret special forces unit with a deadly reputation aired live on television in Russia in a huge break from protocol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grinch on video driving through Christmas display...</title>
      <link>https://www.theindychannel.com/news/local-news/indianapolis/grinch-driver-caught-on-camera-plowing-through-yard-and-destroying-christmas-decorations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theindychannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local family is asking for help to identify a driver who was caught on camera plowing through their yard to destroy their Christmas decorations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O extends tour as book sales top 3 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/553cb83c491f44ec9226f443b2da22a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sales for Michelle Obama's memoir have topped 3 million and the former first lady is extending her book tour into 2019. "Becoming," published four weeks ago, is among the fastest-selling nonfiction books in history and already among the best-selling political memoirs of all time. Live Nation and Crown Publishing announced Tuesday that Obama will have 21 events next year, six of them in Europe. She has been appearing at such arenas as New York City's Barclays Center and Chicago's United Center, with guest interviewers including Oprah Winfrey and Reese Witherspoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kathie Lee Gifford Stepping Away From 'TODAY'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/kathie-lee-gifford-leaving-today-show-1202517747/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News chief Noah Oppenheim announced this morning that Kathie Lee Gifford has decided to exit Today show, where she has hosted the final hour of the four-hour franchise since 2008. His memo: &amp;nb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Moves on U.S. Car Tariff...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-moves-on-us-car-tariff-cut-trump-tweeted-about-after-xi-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (BLOOMBERG) - China is moving towards cutting its trade war tariffs on imported US-made cars, a step already brandished by President Donald Trump as a concession won during trade talks in Argentina.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE GRILLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/11/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-testifies-before-congress-on-bias-privacy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers will likely pepper Google CEO Sundar Pichai with a broad range of questions on bias, user privacy and its plans in China when he testifies in front of the House Judiciary Committee on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: TESTIMONY...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?455607-1/google-ceo-testifies-data-collection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai testifies on user data practices before the House Judiciary Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rights Groups Turn Up Pressure...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/12/10/rights-groups-pressure-google-on-china-censorship-ahead-of-congressional-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google risks being “complicit in human rights violations” if it brings censored search back to China, said a global coalition of over 60 groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's concessions set to blow out French deficit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181211111210-9ylgg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/ (PIX, GRAPHIC):Macron's concessions set to blow out French deficit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Spent $100 Million on Tropical Real Estate. They Were Scammed, FTC Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/americans-spent-100-million-on-tropical-real-estate-they-were-scammed-ftc-says-11544535843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government’s shutdown of what it called a $100 million real-estate investment scam in Belize highlights a growing concern: the targeting of Americans retiring abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran Creates World's First Trans District...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/san-francisco-creates-worlds-first-ever-transgender-cultural-district</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The creation of Compton’s Transgender Cultural District is to stop the displacement of trans people from a place they were traditionally welcomed in, and to teach trans history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: Military will build border wall if Pelosi, Schumer don't agree to pay for it...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/schumer-pelosi-meet-trump-hash-border-funding/story?id=59726978</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer and House Speaker-elect Nancy Pelosi are set to meet with President Trump at the White House on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doris Kearns Goodwin: 'There's No Joy' in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/presidential-historian-doris-kearns-goodwin-theres-no-joy-in-white-house-trump-might-resign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excavation of 'Little Foot' Skeleton Reveals Mysterious Human Relative...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64275-little-foot-hominin-excavated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following an epic 20-year-long excavation in South Africa, researchers have finally recovered and cleaned the nearly-complete skeleton of an ancient human relative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN: 'Gigantic holes in system'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/11/yellen-warns-of-another-potential-financial-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Federal Reserve Chair Janet Yellen told an audience in New York City Monday night that she fears there could be another financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR TRIBUNE film critic resigns over plagiarism...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.mprnews.org/newscut/2018/12/star-tribune-film-critic-resigns-amid-evidence-of-plagiarism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.mprnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Could smell boat approaching': Grim truth about animal exports...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/11/we-could-smell-the-boat-approaching-grim-truth-animal-exports-israel-haifa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broken bones are common for sheep and cattle held on ships for weeks in cramped pens. Jo-Anne McArthur tracked arrivals in Israel’s Haifa port</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME 'Person of Year' is killed and imprisoned journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/time-s-2018-person-year-killed-imprisoned-journalists-n946311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time magazine is spotlighting a handful of journalists who have one thing in common: They were targeted for their work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Truth isn't truth' tops list of notable quotes...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/truth-isnt-truth-tops-list-of-notable-quotes-in-2018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The assertion that "truth isn't truth," made by a personal attorney for President Donald Trump, tops a Yale Law School librarian's list of the most notable quotes of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RENT CAR WITH FACE SCAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0853260708a64136b983eadbfef694b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biometric screening is expanding to the rental car industry. Hertz said Tuesday it is teaming up with Clear, the maker of biometric screening kiosks found at many airports, in an effort to slash the time it takes to pick up a rental car. Clear hopes it will lead more travelers to its platform, which has 3 million members in the U.S. It's the latest place consumers will find biometric technology, which has migrated over the last 50 years from secure government facilities and banks to airports, stadiums and even smartphones that unlock with the touch a fingerprint. Hertz is the first rental car company to use the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Storm clouds gathering for next financial crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2018/dec/11/imf-financial-crisis-david-lipton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Lipton says world is unprepared for downturn and Fund needs more resources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign investors spurn Treasuries as curve threatens to invert...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-bonds-foreigners/foreign-investors-spurn-us-treasuries-as-curve-threatens-to-invert-idUSKBN1OA0J6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worrying sign of inversion in the U.S. Treasury bond curve is dulling the appe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grass-Fed to Lab-Grown: Meat Evolving...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tasting-the-worlds-first-test-tube-steak-11544524201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is on to create lab-grown meat products. Still, little is known about their safety and potential impact. In Moving Upstream, WSJ’s Jason Bellini visits entrepreneurs, scientists, and ranchers to understand how it’s made, and gets a first taste of steak grown from cultured cells.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam Brothels to Get Review by City's First Female Mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/amsterdam-brothels-to-get-a-review-by-city-s-first-female-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amsterdam Brothels to Get a Review by City's First Female Mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space station crew to inspect mysterious hole on spacewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f770a821e8b24e38b1a9abb5d4aec9d2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Two Russian cosmonauts were preparing to venture outside the International Space Station Tuesday to inspect a section where a mysterious leak has been discovered. The leak was spotted on Aug. 30 in the Russian Soyuz spacecraft attached to the station. The crew quickly located and sealed the tiny hole that created a slight loss of pressure, and space officials said the station has remained safe to operate. Russian cosmonauts Oleg Kononenko and Sergei Prokopyev will conduct a six-hour spacewalk to inspect the Soyuz's outer surface. They will uncover the thermal insulation covering the patched hole and take samples that will be studied by experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Made Remote-Controlled Dogs With Brain Surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-10/newly-released-mkultra-docs-cia-made-remote-controlled-dogs-brain-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak may explode...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/12/ebola-vaccine-having-major-impact-outbreak-may-still-explode-west-africa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed conflict in the Democratic Republic of the Congo hampers health care response and vaccine distribution to combat deadly virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many Want To Have Sex With Robot? Numbers Are In...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-09/how-many-people-want-have-sex-robot-numbers-are</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves scandal looms over CBS shareholder meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5c2459d13df24d448f0d3ed5f177300e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With a $120 million severance package on the line, an investigation into sexual-misconduct claims against former CBS CEO Les Moonves will loom over the network's annual shareholders meeting on Tuesday. But CBS officials are unlikely to say more beyond seeking to reassure shareholders that the board is "on top of that, don't worry, when we have sufficient information we will disclose this," said Porter Bibb, a former media executive now with the advisory firm Mediatech Capital Partners. He said the scandal is likely to be mentioned "only peripherally."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Employees Sought To Block BREITBART From Ads, Emails Show...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/10/google-ads-bias/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'My team has been reviewing the site'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas bill would allow Ten Commandments to be posted in classrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article222625075.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Dan Flynn, R-Van, wants to let Texas teachers display the Ten Commandments in their classrooms, if they’d like. Others argue that this proposal is unconstitutional and will fail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador feeling pain of China loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/ecuador-is-feeling-pain-of-china-loans/article_3456b756-956e-57ec-a869-94251437ae9a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador — Rafael Correa wanted to fast-track development projects when he was president of Ecuador, so he borrowed billions of dollars from China. But the loans have come back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit deal in turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5aec0aa11a15440da182cf6bd225abf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Facing almost certain defeat, British Prime Minister Theresa May on Monday postponed a vote in Parliament on her Brexit deal, saying she would go back to European Union leaders to seek changes to the divorce agreement. May's move threw Britain's Brexit plans into disarray, intensified a domestic political crisis and battered the pound. With EU officials adamant the withdrawal deal was not up for renegotiation, the country does not know on what terms it will leave — and whether May will still be Britain's leader when it does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear Gauge Warns This Selloff Is Different...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fear-gauge-warns-that-this-selloff-is-different-1544472242</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street’s fear gauge settled lower Monday after erasing earlier gains—a sign investors are closely monitoring market signals on future volatility and adjusting options positions accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDakota Passes Venezuela in Oil Output...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/little-caracas-on-the-prairie-1544476509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Dakota has passed once-mighty Venezuela in oil output, but still trails in other things.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the frathouse: Humiliation, homoeroticism, animal cruelty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2018/dec/10/andrew-moisey-american-fraternity-photographer-college-behaviour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photographer Andrew Moisey uncovered ritual hazing, extreme drunkenness and toxic masculinity on one college campus – from men destined to be America’s future leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEUD!  At 102, Olivia de Havilland won't give up fight with FX...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-olivia-de-havilland-interview-20181210-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rare interview, the "Gone With the Wind" star discusses taking her lawsuit against the cable network to the U.S. Supreme Court. "I never imagined that anyone would misrepresent me,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Conway show rolls on...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6481853/The-Conways-Washington-power-couple-divided-Trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He is one of Donald Trump's harshest critics.She is one of the president's closest advisers.And they're husband and wife.The marriage of George T. Conway III...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks on track for worst year in DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/stocks-set-for-worst-year-in-a-decade-four-experts-weigh-in-on-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four experts weigh in on what factors will shape global markets in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAKING IT OFF</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/dc558078d0bb4b3e8aec63960a7091f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's intensifying legal troubles are unnerving some of his fellow Republicans. Despite his brash stance, they believe the turmoil has left him increasingly vulnerable as he gears up for what is sure to be a nasty fight for re-election. Trump, ever confident of his ability to bend story lines to his will, mocks the investigations into his conduct as candidate and president as a "witch hunt" and insists he will survive the threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit soars in first two months of fiscal year...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/budget/420661-budget-deficit-soars-in-first-two-months-of-fiscal-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The budget deficit in the first two months of the 2019 fiscal year was 50 percent higher than in the same period the previous year, according to the CBO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART testing robot fry cook at delis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/exclusive-walmart-testing-robot-fry-cook-delis-154733360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might remember 'Flippy' the burger-flipping robot that's now a fry cook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few at BLOOMBERG wants Mike Bloomberg to run for President!</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/we-asked-dozens-of-bloomberg-staffers-if-they-want-him-to-run-in-2020-only-1-said-yes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast reached out to 60+ Bloomberg News employees about the boss’ White House ambitions. Only a single staffer was psyched about Mike 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sells Iconic 'Television City'... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-sells-television-city-property-750-million-1168095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles-based real estate developer Hackman Capital Partners signed the acquisition agreement on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV's Lesbian BATWOMAN Debuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/ruby-roses-batwoman-makes-her-debut-cws-elseworlds-1168056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, who discovered Kate Kane's (Ruby Rose) alter ego?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 In 10 Lie To Doctors About Their Health...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eighty-percent-lie-doctors-about-health-study-reveals-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the guaranteed confidentiality and even though it could potentially put one's health at risk, a new study finds that as many as eight in 10 people lie to their doctors about their health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Patriotic' prepared remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/10/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-prepared-patriotic-remarks-for-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai amps up the company's patriotism in his prepared remarks ahead of Tuesday's congressional hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptions, overdoses skyrocketing for anti-anxiety drugs...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/health/benzodiazepines-addiction-philadelphia-opioid-crisis-20181210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say an explosion of benzodiazepine prescriptions in the middle of an opioid crisis is particularly concerning, because both drugs become much deadlier when mixed with each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California sued over keeping DNA from arrests with no conviction...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/12/10/watchdogs-sue-california-over-dna-retention-for-non-convicted-arrestees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Department of Justice sued by Electronic Frontier Foundation on behalf of two social-justice groups challenging practice of retaining the DNA profiles of people arrested for alleged felo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final Irony: By being murdered, Whitey Bulger may help compensate his victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/12/10/the-final-irony-being-murdered-whitey-bulger-may-help-compensate-his-victims/cyAjS1WP1PIe17jYphGQdL/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One may be charitable and believe that the Justice Department, which oversees the Bureau of Prisons, will do the right thing and bring all the circumstances to light. But, historically, the Justice Department has been compromised by Bulger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE: Students vow 'Black Tuesday' protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-france-high-school-students-protests-yellow-vests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as it grapples with violent demonstrations over living costs, the French government is hunkering down for a “Black Tuesday” of protests by high-school students who have jumped onto the Yellow Vest bandwagon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal Immigration Hits Highest Level in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/12/10/iillegal-immigration-last-month-hit-highest-level-in-over-a-decade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration skyrocketed to the highest level in over a decade for the month of November as Trump's border wall remains unfunded.,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo cocaine train route from Mexico to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/10/el-chapo-ran-cocaine-train-route-to-nyc-ex-cartel-member/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He should have been called El Choo-po. Mexican cartel kingpin Joaquin “El Chapo” Guzman ran a cocaine train all the way from Mexico to New York City, a witness testified Monday. “Chapo decided who …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP booted after grabbing ceremonial mace amid row...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/politics/mp-booted-from-the-house-of-commons-after-grabbing-ceremonial-mace-amid-brexit-row-a4013741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Labour MP was kicked out of the House of Commons after picking up the ceremonial mace following the Brexit deal vote being delayed.  After a Government whip shouted "tomorrow" in regards to the debate and vote - meaning it will be held on an unspecified future date - jeers rang through the House.  Lloyd Russell-Moyle then went over to the silver gilt mace, picked it up and then walked away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong tops global list for super-rich home buyers...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1490218/hong-kong-tops-list-of-where-the-super-rich-buy-expensive-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2018, the highest number of residential property transactions worth $25 million or more were in Hong Kong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone geyser breaks historical eruption record...</title>
      <link>https://www.localnews8.com/news/kifi-top-story/steamboat-geyser-breaks-historical-yearly-eruption-record/923532758</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.localnews8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Steamboat Geyser in Yellowstone National Park broke decades-old records when it erupted for the 30th time in 2018 Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACADEMY CONSIDERS HOST-LESS OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/oscars-academy-kevin-hart-replacement-1203084598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart’s abrupt departure as Oscars host has left the Academy of Motion Pictures Arts &amp; Sciences scrambling to find someone to take the gig. As of now, the situation remains fluid as …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON delivery driver turns 'porch pirate,' arrested for stealing bait...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/crime/2018/12/amazon-delivery-driver-turns-porch-pirate-arrested-for-stealing-bait-package-from-aloha-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dreaded “porch pirate” isn’t always who you expect it to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Samaritan stops to help crash victims, gets car towed by cops...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/police-tow-good-samaritans-car-after-stopping-to-help-crash-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a car in front of him went out of control, flipping into a ravine on the Suitland Parkway on Sunday night, Benjamin Davis, III could've driven by. But, he says he knew people needed help. So he stopped. "The guy is hanging out of the passenger side door. Unfortunately, his friend was crushed," said Davis. Davis managed to get the survivor out of the car, but the second person in the car, 21-year-old Kyree Payne of Northeast D. C. , died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecosystem below Earth TWICE size of world's oceans...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/dec/10/tread-softly-because-you-tread-on-23bn-tonnes-of-micro-organisms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global team of scientists find ecosystem below earth that is twice the size of world’s oceans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie-like', lives for millions of years...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181210-vast-zombie-like-microbial-life-lurks-beneath-seabed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast, zombie-like microbial life lurks beneath seabed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules law prohibiting secret recording of govt officials is unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/news/boston/index.ssf/2018/12/federal_judge_rules_mass_law_p.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal court judge Monday ruled a Massachusetts General Law prohibiting the secret recording of police or government officials is unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK: Get-Trump talk now campaign finance, not Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-sudden-shift-in-get-trump-talk-now-its-campaign-finance-not-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors investigating President Trump made big news Friday, but it wasn't about Russia. Rather, in their sentencing recommendation for fixer Michael Cohen, lawyers with the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York wrote that in the final weeks of the 2016 campaign, candidate Trump…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False statement charges abound, contrast to Clinton case...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/false-statement-charges-abound-in-mueller-probe-discouraged-in-clinton-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s investigation is abounding with false statement charges against Trump campaign associates, but a Justice Department inspector general report revealed that the FBI and federal prosecutors discouraged charging witnesses under the same offense in the bureau’s probe into Hillary Clinton’s private email server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO: Masked man shoots livestreaming campaign door-knocker...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/man-recovering-from-being-shot-while-campaigning-for-15th-ward-political-candidate/4872789/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxwell Little, also known on social media as Maxwell Omowale Justice, is recovering after being shot in the leg while campaigning for 15th Ward aldermanic candidate Joseph Williams on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman plotted mass murder, corresponded with SC church shooter...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/news/ohio-woman-who-plotted-mass-murder-corresponded-with-dylann-roof/article_e84839b4-fcb8-11e8-ae4f-cb4da1e387eb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio woman accused of plotting what she referred to as an "upscale mass murder" at a Toledo bar had glorified Dylann Roof and corresponded with the self-avowed white supremacist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKEDIN billionaire backs voter data project in 'existential threat' to Democratic Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/10/linkedin-reid-hoffman-dnc-voter-data-1054857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;DNC’s top leaders have been telling people that Hoffman’s project represents an “existential threat&amp;quot; to the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NISSAN Million-Dollar Supercar...</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/news/25359/nissan-opens-orders-for-1-1-million-710-hp-gt-r50-italdesign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is it Nissan's farewell to the R35 GT-R, or is it a glimpse of the R36? Doesn't matter—it's both gorgeous and knock-your-socks-off fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socials outpace print as news source for adults...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/12/10/social-media-outpaces-print-newspapers-in-the-u-s-as-a-news-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One-in-five U.S. adults often get news via social media, slightly higher than the 16% who often do so from print newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star under fire after calling moon landing fake...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/warriors/article/steph-curry-fake-moon-landing-podcast-13454284.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Curry says he does not believe humans have been to the moon, a stance which is clearly unsupported by facts and hopefully just a joke.  Curry made the proclamation on The Ringer's podcast "Winging It" with teammate Andre Iguodala and hosts Vince Carter and Kent Bazemore; you can hear the exchange around the 46-minute mark. There's some talking over each other that makes it hard to hear, but when the discussion turns to the moon landing, almost everyone seems to agree we've never been to there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record count for mysterious paralyzing illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b6cc9d8f3a9c4c84b72a9f45c3a335ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — This year has seen a record number of cases of a mysterious paralyzing illness in children, U.S. health officials said Monday. It's still not clear what's causing the kids to lose the ability to move their face, neck, back, arms or legs. The symptoms tend to occur about a week after the children had a fever and respiratory illness. No one has died from the rare disease this year, but it was blamed for one death last year and it may have caused others in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs officers searching more travelers' devices...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/54497b1d5f5541efb96dc25d11ee66a3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. Customs and Border Protection officers are searching the electronic devices of travelers more often, and did not always follow proper protocol, a new watchdog report has found. The report made public Monday found there were 29,000 devices searched at a port of entry out of 397 million travelers to the U.S. in budget year 2017, up from 18,400 the year before from 390 million travelers. Customs and Border Protection officials note it is less than 1 percent of all travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE announces new security flaw, closes social network...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/google-announces-new-security-flaw-closes-social-network-early-n946201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Plus received its initial kiss of death in early October, when the company revealed that a security bug had exposed the information of 500,000 users.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
