<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-senate-proceedings-set-to-begin-as-rules-come-into-focus-2019-01-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial will get underway at 1 p.m., marking just the third time a president has faced removal from office in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian MP offers $3 million reward for 'whoever kills Trump'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200121092957-pp44x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-USA/TRUMP (URGENT):Iranian MP announces $3 million award for "whoever kills Trump" - ISNA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French workers cut power to world's largest food market in pension protest...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200121082615-bsx2y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRENCH-PROTESTS/PENSIONS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-French workers cut power to world's largest food market in pension protest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10784330/china-coronavirus-reaches-australia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TERRIFYING new virus from China is feared to have reached Australia after a man was tested for the killer mystery bug. The man, from Brisbane, was displaying symptoms of the fatal coronavirus aft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases in Australia, Philippines?</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/philippines-australia-probe-suspected-cases-of-wuhan-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA - Health officials are investigating two patients in the Philippines and Australia showing symptoms of a new, mysterious coronavirus spreading from China's Wuhan province.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing imposes quasi-quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Chinese-officials-urge-people-not-to-travel-in-14991226.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - Chinese health authorities sought to impose a quasi-quarantine around Wuhan, a city of 11 million people, Tuesday as they stepped up efforts to stop the spread of a mystery virus that has now claimed six lives.  With confirmation that the pneumonialike coronavirus can be transmitted from person to person, and with hundreds of millions of Chinese packing onto public transport to make their annual pilgrimages home, a new sense of panic has erupted here.  Long lines formed at pharmacies and convenience stores around the country as people rushed to buy surgical masks, with unlucky customers posting photos on social media of bare shelves. People around the country canceled their trips home for the Spring Festival - the most important holiday on the Chinese calendar.  "I don't really dare to go to the airport right now, or even to the movie theater," said Xie Jing, a 33-year-old who works in advertising in Shanghai, where there have been two confirmed cases of coronavirus. She canceled her planned trip home to Sichuan, where two cases are suspected.  "Everyone is being very careful at the moment in Shanghai, everyone is wearing masks on the streets," Xie said.  The Geneva-based World Health Organization said it would call an emergency meeting on Wednesday to decide whether to designate the outbreak as an international public health emergency. Australia and the Philippines are the latest countries with suspected cases of infection.  The virus was first detected on Dec. 31 and was linked to a dirty food market in Wuhan, not far from one of the main train stations, where wild animals including wolf pups and civet cats had been on sale for consumption.  A total of 298 people in China had been confirmed with the virus at 5 p.m. on Tuesday, the National Health Commission...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazmat Suits Deployed on Planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/hazmat-suits-deployed-on-planes-as-security-tightens-over-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hazmat Suits Deployed on Planes as Security Tightens Over Virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitter fight over rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478895-senate-braces-for-bitter-fight-over-impeachment-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate is barreling toward a bitter, potentially lengthy fight Tuesday over the rules governing President Trump’s impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia steps up defenses as China virus hits 291 people, kills six...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-says-virus-spreading-between-humans-set-meet-030928262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian countries on Tuesday ramped up measures to block the spread of a new virus as the death toll in China rose to six and the number of cases jumped to almost 300, raising concerns in the middle of a major holiday travel rush. From Australia to Thailand and as far as Nepal, nations stepped up fever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEBOW MARRIED!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/2020/01/20/tim-tebow-demi-leigh-nel-peters-married/4527622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow and 2017 Miss Universe winner Demi-Leigh Nel-Peters are married, as the couple shared photos on social media and details on day with People.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7909819/This-isnt-trial-COVER-Chuck-Schumer-rages-against-impeachment-trial-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate minority leader went on offense just after Mitch McConnell unveiled his planned rules for the trial of Donald Trump saying the Republican was trying to hide evidence after dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank details, social security numbers, passport information and addresses for THOUSANDS of porn stars leaked...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/284784/pornstar-data-breach-massive-leak-bank-details/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSANDS of porn stars have had their personal information leaked after a porn site left them exposed in a massive data breach. Information ranging from names, dates of birth, fingerprints, passpo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Pushes Speed Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment/trump-lawyers-call-for-immediate-acquittal-in-legal-political-defense-idUSKBN1ZJ0XZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump on Monday rejected the Democratic-led House of Repre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON BLOCK?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-lawyers-senate-gop-allies-work-privately-to-ensure-bolton-does-not-testify-publicly/ar-BBZa0RT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious-schools case heads to a Supreme Court skeptical of stark lines between church and state..</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2020/01/20/religious-schools-case-heads-supreme-court-skeptical-stark-lines-between-church-and-state/CsC6xr477vHHQ9SuvjTQhK/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court will hear arguments Wednesday in a dispute over a Montana scholarship program for private K-12 education that also makes donors eligible for up to $150 in state tax credits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan of 3,000 Tests Pact With Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/caravan-of-3000-tests-mexico-e2-80-99s-pact-with-trump-to-stop-migrants/ar-BBZa1Es</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Homicides Rise to Record in AMLO First Year in Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/mexico-murders-rise-to-record-in-amlo-e2-80-99s-first-year-in-office/ar-BBZ9Uma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can spread between humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7906235/China-counts-sharp-rise-coronavirus-cases-2-Beijing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As well as 14 healthcare workers, China's National Health Commission team said two patients in southern China had caught the virus from infected family members, according to local media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  BOEING in talks to borrow $10+ billion as 737 Max crisis wears on...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/20/737-max-crisis-boeing-seeks-to-borrow-10-billion-or-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing is facing rising costs from the 737 Max grounding and regulators say they have no firm timeline to lift the flight ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14d7dcffa205d9022fa9ea593bb2a8c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The head of a Chinese government expert team said Monday that human-to-human transmission has been confirmed in an outbreak of a new coronavirus, a development that raises the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron and Trump declare a truce in digital tax dispute...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200120224330-fcy3u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-USA/TAX (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Macron and Trump declare truce in digital tax dispute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Conference Championship Ratings Hit 11-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/nfl-conference-championship-ratings-hit-11-year-low-1271467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday's games pulled in the smallest average audience in more than a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENVER POST Columnist Fired After Arguing There Are Two Sexes...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/denver-post-columnist-fired-after-arguing-there-are-two-sexes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Denver Post columnist says he was fired after penning a pair of opinion pieces that were critical of the idea that there are more than two genders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The private border wall being built on Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/20/politics/border-wall-private-fisher/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump is the name most commonly associated with the border wall. But along this three-mile stretch, Tommy Fisher is the name on everyone's mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immune discovery 'may treat all cancer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-51182451</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research is at an early stage but scientists said it had huge potential for destroying cancers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man named Sexy Vegan pleads no contest to sexually assaulting dog...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/20/california-man-named-sexy-vegan-enters-plea-in-dog-sex-assault-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California man named Sexy Vegan entered a no-contest plea in a case where he was accused of sexually assaulting his dog and posting a video of the abuse on social media, officials announced Frida…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22,000 attend...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/local/live-updates-attended-richmond-gun-rights-rally-police-say/article_af43b67e-def2-5ee1-92db-709d0965655f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 21-year-old Richmond woman was charged Monday with wearing a mask in public following the gun-rights rally in Richmond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUESDAY: TRUMP TRIAL BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/20/trump-lawyers-democrats-impeachment-case-101201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyers argue Democrats didn’t present any evidence the president conditioned security assistance and a White House meeting with the new Ukrainian leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11 plotter will face CIA psychologists in court...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-01-20/ksm-guantanamo-trial-torture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coming trial of Khalid Sheikh Mohammed before a military commission will focus not on what he did — orchestrate the deaths of 2,973 people — but on the torture inflicted on him as a result.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  CHICAGO TRIBUNE staffers seek new owners amid fears of hedge fund takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/20/media/chicago-tribune-ownership/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters at the Chicago Tribune are trying to find a new owner for their newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein's Dark Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/20/nyregion/harvey-weinstein-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As his trial begins, he’s hobbled and “terrified.” His accusers say he deserves his misfortune for his treatment of women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ISIS leader unmasked...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7908975/Sharia-law-graduate-born-Iraqi-Turkmen-family-revealed-hardliner-running-ISIS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two intelligence services said Iraqi al-Salbi (pictured) took over from Abu Bakr Al-Baghdadi after the terrorist leader blew himself up in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster of explosive devices land near Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Israel-Police-find-suspicious-balloons-near-Jerusalem-614705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Incident comes after dozens of others landed in southern Israel over the last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE critic suggests wife's fatal car crash NOT an accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7908435/Google-critic-66-suggests-wifes-fatal-car-crash-not-accident.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Epstein, 66, said in July the internet giant's methods 'gave' millions of votes to Hillary Clinton during the 2016 presidential election. In December he announced that his wife had died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow gripped by mysterious bomb hoaxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51182331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Moscow's metro stations are among public sites targeted, but it is unclear who is responsible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake doctor jailed over electrocution experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51174783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German man who convinced young women and girls to shock themselves on camera is given 11 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-51171035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This comes as China confirms that a new strain of coronavirus can pass from person to person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska volcano activity triggers aviation warnings; Spewing ash, lava...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/activity-alaska-volcano-triggers-aviation-warnings-spewing-ash/story?id=68403872</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activity from one of Alaska's 80 volcanoes triggered aviation warnings after it began to spew ash and lava over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubs Joe over gaffes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/282606/new-york-times-endorsement-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE NEW York Times has sprung a surprise in announcing who it is endorsing in the 2020 election. The Times’ editorial board revealed it is backing two candidates, Elizabeth Warren and Amy Klo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Average American Now Sleeping Just 5.5 Hours Each Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/tired-nation-americans-now-averaging-less-than-6-hours-sleep-per-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the years press forward, sleep is becoming a true challenge for many Americans. That's the main finding of a recent survey consisting of 2,000 adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customs to Roll Out Facial Recognition at all Airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/01/cbp-expands-facial-recognition-global-entry-travelers/162498/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology is already being used at 15 airports—including three abroad—to speed pre-approved travelers through the customs process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY:  FEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/trump-s-senate-impeachment-hearings-will-be-driven-gop-s-ncna1118071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans have toadied to Trump since the day he took office, and in doing so, have left themselves with no room to maneuver politically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>111 day cruise to set sail from LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/111-day-around-the-world-cruise-sets-sail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Cruises is kicking off its 111-day around-the-world voyage on Monday with about 670 guests and 375 crew members aboard the company's 592-foot Pacific Princess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starlink satellites spooking Fort Collins?</title>
      <link>https://www.chieftain.com/news/20200118/first-drones-now-unexplained-lights-reported-in-horsetooth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chieftain.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT COLLINS — It's a bird! It's a plane! It's a drone? It's a ... satellite? Oh, who even knows anymore? A string of unexplained lights was seen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oddsmakers Make CHIEFS Favorites...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/super-bowl-2020-chiefs-49ers-both-looking-to-end-extended-championship-droughts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for the big game set to go down in Miami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Says 'No Need to Panic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2020/01/20/china-says-no-need-to-panic-as-deadly-virus-goes-international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese officials and state media insisted that the emergence of a previously unknown respiratory virus so far presented "no need to panic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD LAST MONTHS?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/478973-cruz-hearing-from-witnesses-could-extend-senate-trial-to-up-to-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz (R-Texas) said Sunday that the Senate’s impeachment trial could last as long as eight weeks if the chamber elects to hear from witnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garoppolo threw just eight passes for win...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/jimmy-garoppolo-fine-eight-pass-051738403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 49ers have a team-first mentality, which is why Jimmy Garoppolo isn&amp;#39;t complaining about his eight pass attempts against the Packers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Endorsement 'Farce' For Endorsing Warren AND Klobuchar...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/156252/new-york-timess-endorsement-charade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weeklong song-and-dance routine ends in farce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands gathers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c997c92fa7acd394f7cbb89882d9b5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Thousands of gun-rights activists — some brandishing their military-style rifles — crowded the streets surrounding Virginia's Capitol building Monday to protest plans by the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backers and critics clash as impeachment trial nears...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c79655e468cc949917f57c085d6bba7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's legal team asserted Monday that he did “absolutely nothing wrong," calling the impeachment case against him “flimsy" and a “dangerous perversion of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Kanye West rides horse into church service -- and falls off...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-kanye-west-rides-horse-into-church-service-and-falls-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe this is why Jesus rode a donkey. Kanye West mounted a horse during a recent church service, but things went awry when the equine appeared to get spooked and the singer went tumbling to the floor. Watch: ﻿ Kanye was dressed in a white robe with with some sort of crown on his head, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llamas and ostriches were taken from exotic meat farm. Was it theft or rescue?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-01-20/llamas-ostriches-taken-from-exotic-meat-farm-perris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before sunrise one day in December, thieves sneaked into Anshu Pathak’s exotic meat farm in Riverside County and pulled off a singular heist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: BIDEN OUT IN FRONT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479027-biden-leads-primary-field-in-iowa-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden maintained his lead in Iowa ahead of the state's first-in-the-nation caucuses, according to a new poll that also shows former South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg and Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would vote to convict Trump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479025-bloomberg-says-he-would-vote-to-convict-trump-if-he-were-a-senator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg said that he would vote to remove President Trump from office if he were a member of the Senate participating in the upcoming impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emaciated lions pictured in horrifying conditions at world's worst zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10777856/emaciated-lions-sudan-zoo-shocking-photos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING photos have emerged of five caged African lions who have lost so much weight their bones are now showing through their skin. The emaciated big cats are stranded behind bars at Al-Qureshi a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian police use spy camera to film opposition member in her bedroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/01/20/russian-police-use-spy-camera-film-opposition-activist-bedroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian police officers had been secretly filming an opposition activist inside her bedroom for months before she was detained and charged under a new law on &amp;ldquo;undesirable organisations&amp;rdquo; in a move that has been described as &amp;quot;outrageous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER BATTLE: Authorities see spike in unaccompanied minors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2020-01-19/unaccompanied-mexican-minors-in-tijuana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights advocates and social workers in Tijuana worry about sexual exploitation and trafficking of migrant children after policy changes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents fear violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/gun-rights-rally-looms-virginia-richmond-residents-fear-another-charlottesville-n1118486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many say they'll be staying as far away as possible from the demonstration they worry will turn violent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES STORMS GUN RALLY IN BATTLE TANK...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/live-now-alex-jones-storms-virginia-in-battle-tank-to-support-2nd-amendment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Share this censored link and use the First Amendment to protect the Second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes set to unseat Brady as  merchandise king...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/20/chiefs-star-patrick-mahomes-challenging-tom-brady-as-nfl-retail-king.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Football League Players Association revealed its latest Top 50 Player Sales List, which sees Kansas City Chiefs quarterback Patrick Mahomes leading the way over New England's Tom Brady.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos Bolsters Security as Protesters March Toward Venue...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2020-01-20/davos-bolsters-security-as-protesters-march-toward-venue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CHRIST' IN THE CLOUDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/10777934/jesus-christ-figure-spotted-clouds-birmingham/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN was left gobsmacked after a Jesus-like figure appeared in the sky above her house in Birmingham. Caroline Hawthorne’s prayers were answered after she snapped the perfectly-timed pictu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The #MeToo Film That Has Hollywood Worried...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-assistant-is-the-metoo-film-that-has-hollywood-worried</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kitty Green’s new film “The Assistant,” in theaters Jan. 31, examines the abuse—both physical and psychological—in Hollywood through the eyes of an office assistant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Religious Death Cult That Massacred Seven in Panama...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-religious-death-cult-that-massacred-seven-in-panama</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fundamentalist sect sacrificed multiple victims, including a pregnant woman and six children, in a remote jungle village. Its extremism was imported direct from the USA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Mystery Drone Swarms Lingering Near Nuclear Missile Silos?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/are-the-mystery-colorado-drone-swarms-lingering-near-nuclear-missile-silos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strange flying objects have been spotted near F.E. Warren Air Force Base in Wyoming, which houses enough nuclear intercontinental ballistic missiles to wipe out several cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 dead, 15 hurt after gunman opens fire on line of people outside Kansas City bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/crime/ny-kansas-city-bar-shooting-leaves-two-dead-fifteen-injured-20200120-n7cos3skdjhkbhfxrshpmo2nae-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were killed and more than a dozen others were injured after a gunman opened fire on a line of people waiting to get into a bar in Kansas City, Missouri, Sunday night, just hours after the city’s football team clinched a spot in the Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Clobbered For Endorsing Warren AND Klobuchar...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ny-times-gets-clobbered-for-grandiose-special-leading-to-warren-klobuchar-copout-have-these-people-zero-self-awareness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Whistleblower Suggests Wife's Fatal Car Crash Not Accident...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/01/20/google-whistleblower-suggests-his-wifes-fatal-car-crash-may-not-have-been-accidental/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Says he was warned of an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Dean revival spurs debate on raising digital dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f9786493b3d029dc18be88025b51298c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The men bringing James Dean back to life for a forthcoming film are aiming not just to give his digital likeness a role, but a whole new career. Dean’s planned appearance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants marooned in Guatemala plan surge into Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/013b95350bd0a2e49decc40620b2bae4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECUN UMAN, Guatemala (AP) — Some 3,000 Central American migrants made another attempt to walk across the border bridge into Mexico, but then sat down halfway across the span early Monday when...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
