<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Dodo could be brought back to life after scientists scan extinct bird's DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4923663/extinct-dodo-brought-back-to-life-dna/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE DODO could be brought back to life hundreds of years after going extinct thanks to a DNA breakthrough. Scientists have managed to sequence the entire genome of the flightless bird for the first…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX slammed for 'revolting' sex scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/4915936/netflix-brand-new-cherry-flavor-sex-scene/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NETFLIX viewers have claimed that they’re “scarred for life” after a revolting sex scene in the horror series Brand New Cherry Flavor. Brand New Cherry Flavor launched on Netflix …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Traders Brace for $3.5 Trillion Triple Witching Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/stock-traders-brace-for-35-trillion-triple-witching-event/ar-AAVd8vD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullard says Fed moving too slowly, putting economy at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bullard-says-fed-risks-credibility-by-moving-too-slowly-to-quell-high-inflation-11647602657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St Louise Federal Reserve President James Bullard doesn't think the U.S. central bank is attacking high inflation with enough urgency --- risking both its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next target may be Moldova, analysts warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/18/russias-putin-may-launch-false-flag-in-moldova-as-europe-war-wages-on.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Russia faces staunch and seemingly unexpected resistance on the ground in Ukraine, analysts warn Putin may be considering his next target: Moldova.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer for mother of Hunter Biden's child says he expects president's son to be indicted...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/lawyer-for-mother-of-hunter-bidens-child-lunden-roberts-says-he-expects-presidents-son-to-be-indicted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for the mother of Hunter Biden’s illegitimate child expects the president’s son “to be indicted” for tax fraud, a report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Black Americans Buying Guns. Is It Driving Up Suicide Rates?</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/more-black-americans-are-buying-guns-is-it-driving-up-black-suicide-rates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun buying among African Americans has soared in recent years. So have suicide rates among young Black men. Suicide prevention and gun safety efforts need to address race and cultural differences, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee faces thorny challenge: Convincing public to care...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/jan-6-committee-faces-a-thorny-challenge-convincing-the-public-to-care/ar-AAVegdY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Giant Moon Rocket Reaches Launchpad...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/18/nasas-giant-moon-rocket-reaches-the-launchpad-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA’s giant new moon rocket is finally at the launchpad, although it is yet to be determined when it might</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes Stalin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-business-europe-5a9f43e0e5e4da1200a440d667d6db91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Facing stiff resistance in Ukraine and crippling economic sanctions at home, Russian President Vladimir Putin is using language that recalls the rhetoric from Josef Stalin’s show trials of the 1930s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Happiest Country Ranking Goes to Finland for Fifth Year in Row...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/culture/2022/03/18/world-happiness-report-finds-light-amid-war-and-disease</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Helping strangers, volunteering, and donations in 2021 were strongly up in every part of the world, reaching levels almost 25% above their pre-pandemic prevalence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Nuke Threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10626267/US-military-fears-Putin-planning-use-nuclear-bomb-Kyiv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DIA Director Lt. Gen. Scott Berrier revealed in a new report Thursday that Putin may threaten to use nuclear weapons if Ukrainian defense forces continue to push back against Russia's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Davidson skipping ride to space on Bezos rocket...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2022-03-pete-davidson-space-jeff-bezos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Davidson has bowed out of a short ride to space on a Jeff Bezos rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden-Xi Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-biden-business-jen-psaki-83c387554e08610bd973051dbd28fcf9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden and China's Xi Jinping are set to speak on Friday as the White House warns Beijing that providing military or economic assistance for Russia's invasion of Ukraine will trigger severe consequences from Washington and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New reforms look to chip away Israeli chief rabbis' power...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-religion-israel-tel-aviv-d66575bd026f2adfc2ccf530b18d314b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israel’s new government has taken aim at the country’s powerful religious establishment with a pair of reforms that would chip away at the tight grip of the country's chief rabbinate on many aspects of daily life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese carrier sails through Taiwan Strait hours before call...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/exclusive-china-sails-carrier-through-taiwan-strait-hours-before-biden-xi-call-2022-03-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese aircraft carrier sailed through the sensitive Taiwan Strait on Friday, Taiwan's Defence Ministry said, just hours before the Chinese and U.S. presidents were due to talk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of trans kids in Texas terrified for families...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dreading-the-knock-at-the-door-parents-of-trans-kids-in-texas-are-terrified-for-their-families/ar-AAVcMXa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why some Americans haven't gotten virus yet and why it's not inevitable they ever will...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/americans-covid-inevitable-experts/story?id=83467858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts said it’s not inevitable Americans who have not gotten COVID yet eventually will, and there are several reasons people have been able to avoid infection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 In 10 Long-Covid Patients Still Dealing With Memory, Concentration Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/long-covid-memory-problems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three in four people with a severe case of long COVID say they have been unable to work because of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely to Make More Nuclear Threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/putin-is-likely-to-make-nuclear-threats-if-war-drags-us-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Pentagon official says Russia is relying on more than 1,000 long-range missile strikes into Ukraine. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi Signals Tweaking of Covid Strategy as Economic Pressure Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/xi-hints-at-tweaks-to-china-s-covid-strategy-virus-update/ar-AAVdexP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS 'Outgunned' in Audits of Major Companies, Agency Chief Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/irs-is-outgunned-in-audits-of-major-companies-agency-chief-says/ar-AAVcyD7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weddings to Hit 40-Year High This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/signet-jewelers-says-weddings-will-hit-a-40-year-high-this-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signet Jewelers Says Weddings Will Hit a 40-Year High This Year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of trans kids in Texas are terrified for their families...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dreading-the-knock-at-the-door-parents-of-trans-kids-in-texas-are-terrified-for-their-families/ar-AAVcMXa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxes, 'mystery' surcharge intensify Californians' pain at the pump...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/598655-taxes-mystery-surcharge-intensify-californians-pain-at-the-pump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California has the most expensive gas in the nation, reaching an average statewide price of $5.44 per gallon early in March even as the nationwide average set a record of $4.173.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case against Ron Jeremy suspended after lawyer questions porn stars mental health...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/case-against-ron-jeremy-suspended-183559585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge suspended the case against Ron Jeremy after doubts were raised about the porn star's mental competency. He is accused of numerous sex assaults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists reveal most dangerous personality type:  The Dark Empath...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4915356/dark-empath-scientist-pesonality-type/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW ‘dangerous’ character trait dubbed “dark empathy” has been identified by scientists – but do you possess it? Recent research has found that individuals who boast dark …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  If Cases Rise, Have To Go Back To Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gxeScOUMlI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puppet Makers Rise Up Against Puppet Masters...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-features/the-jim-henson-company-craftspeople-unsafe-work-conditions-1235111978/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As they push for unionization, craftspeople at the The Jim Henson Company say they are treated as an underclass, subject to abuse and unsafe conditions: "The job of the wrangler is eating sh** and taking blame."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  ENDEAVOR CEO Ari Emanuel's Pay Package Tops $308M...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/ari-emanuels-2021-pay-package-1235113583/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With most of that compensation tied up in stock that may or may not vest, the company says his realized pay was closer to $67 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killing Machine Isn't Working...</title>
      <link>https://newlinesmag.com/first-person/putins-killing-machine-that-isnt-working/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newlinesmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low morale, corruption and bad leadership define Russia's military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do psychedelic drugs do to brains? AI could provide clues...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2022/03/16/1047350/what-do-psychedelic-drugs-do-to-our-brains-ai-could-help-us-find-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The words people used to describe their trip experiences could lead to better drugs to treat mental illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Hollywood filmmaker bankrolling far-right political revolt in rural CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-ex-hollywood-filmmaker-bankrolling-a-far-right-political-revolt-in-rural-california/ar-AAV8gkv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Devices Watching Everywhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smart-devices-violating-privacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of them are sitting right in front of you -- inside televisions, cars, offices, and even your refrigerator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child was driving pickup truck that struck golfers' van, killing 9...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/ntsb-child-was-driving-pickup-that-struck-van-killing-9/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 13-year-old was driving the pickup truck that struck a van in West Texas in a fiery collision that killed nine people, according to the National Transportation Safety Board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust enforcers won't challenge AMAZON's MGM deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/17/u-s-antitrust-enforcers-amazons-mgm-deal-00018252</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Democratic vacancy on the Federal Trade Commission leaves Chair Lina Khan without the votes she would need to sue to block the online giant's acquisition of the movie studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA CEO sold $400 million in stock during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/moderna-ceo-sold-408-million-in-company-stock-since-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephane Bancel cashed out stock options through the 10b5-1 plan which allows executives to sell a predetermined number of shares at regular intervals to avoid the possibility of insider trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden-Xi Set for Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-to-speak-with-xi-friday-in-bid-to-keep-pressuring-putin/ar-AAVbVjv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes Stalin in 'very, very scary' speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/putin-echoes-stalin-in-very-very-scary-speech-185956140.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speech Russian president Vladimir Putin made on Wednesday bore the hallmark of unapologetic authoritarianism, Russia experts and observers said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron vows tax cuts in election manifesto...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220317-macron-vows-tax-cuts-benefits-shake-up-in-election-manifesto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron pledged further tax cuts, reforms to the welfare system and major public investments on Thursday as he unveiled his manifesto less than a month from elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil spikes back above $100...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-17-22/h_86d98b005ab87a65e05b84656b79e2c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian forces inch toward the capital of Kyiv, with intensified fighting to the northeast and east of the city. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden criminal probe heating up, testimony from baby momma...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/17/hunter-biden-criminal-investigation-gets-testimony-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal tax investigation of Hunter Biden, the son of President Joe Biden, has looked at his links to a Ukraine energy company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US citizen killed in Chernihiv...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/us-citizen-killed-in-ukraine-as-russians-shell-chernihiv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We can confirm the death of a US citizen in Ukraine on March 17,” a State Department spokesperson told The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Proposal to Use Civil Forfeiture to Fund Diversity...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3abyv3/civil-forfeiture-police-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey lawmakers have proposed a bill to use seized cash and other assets as funding to recruit, hire, and train minority cops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Legendary' paratroopers obliterated...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17964713/russia-paratroopers-slaughtered-ukraine-putin-bungled-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s elite paratroopers have faced massacre on the battlefield amid Russia’s bungled invasion of Ukraine, experts have claimed. The tyrant unleashed his “legendaryR…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Napping Too Much Linked To Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/03/17/napping-dementia-linked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Napping too much in the day as you get older could be a worrying warning sign of dementia, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan spots 4 Russian amphibious warships sailing West...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10623699/Japan-spots-four-Russian-warships-carrying-combat-vehicles-heading-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia could be sending reinforcements to Ukraine, Japan's defense ministry said after spotting four amphibious warships in the Tsugaru Strait (pictured). Russia has lost thousands of vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S Africa president blames NATO...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/article-701534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shelling in Kyiv kills one as residential building hit • Nine soldiers handed over for Melitopol mayor • Theater allegedly hit in Mariupol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 4th shot offers little protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/article-701520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interim results released show that the vaccine offers little to no protection against the virus when compared to three doses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Surprised By Senate Passing Permanent Daylight Saving Time. Especially Senators...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/paulmcleod/daylight-saving-time-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inspiring story about how presumptuous Senate staffers can accidentally make history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion has stalled on ALL fronts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uk-military-intelligence-says-russias-070355358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine has largely stalled on all fronts, with Russian forces suffering heavy losses and making minimal progress on land, sea or air in recent days, British military intelligence said on Thursday. "Ukrainian resistance remains staunch and well-coordinated," The Ministry of Defence said. "The vast majority of Ukrainian territory, including all major cities, remains in Ukrainian hands."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow:  Will put USA in its place!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-put-enemies-united-states-074753510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -Russia warned the United States on Thursday that Moscow had the might to put the world's pre-eminent superpower in its place and accused the West of stoking a wild Russophobic plot to tear Russia apart. Dmitry Medvedev, who served as president from 2008 to 2012 and is now deputy secretary of Russia's Security Council, said the United States had stoked "disgusting" Russophobia in an attempt to force Russia to its knees. "It will not work - Russia has the might to put all of our brash enemies in their place," Medvedev said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK:  MAN ON MARS IN 7 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4915972/elon-musk-mars-humans-manned-mission-date/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk expects to see another giant leap for mankind not just in this lifetime, but in this decade. The SpaceX CEO tweeted that he predicts humans will touch down on the Mars in 2029.  The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: For Best Sleep, Be In Bed By 9:39 PM..</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/best-sleep-bedtime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a quarter of those who regularly have “bad” sleep find themselves wide awake at least five times a night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why would so few Americans defend their country?</title>
      <link>https://www.spectator.co.uk/article/why-are-so-few-americans-willing-to-defend-their-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spectator.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many of us war voyeurs watching the news with a glass of sherry, admiration of the little-engine-that-could Ukrainian fighters is underwritten by unease. As families escape to safety, plenty of feisty Ukrainians are remaining behind to battle a far more powerful aggressor, and they’re not all me...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As abortion pills take off, some states move to curb them...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/03/16/as-abortion-pills-take-off-some-states-move-to-curb-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in more than 20 states want to restrict or ban access to medication abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violin becomes 'weapon of resistance' in shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.infobae.com/en/2022/03/17/the-violin-weapon-of-resistance-of-ukrainian-musicians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infobae.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The violin, “weapon of resistance” of Ukrainian musicians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schwarzenegger invokes Nazi father in emotional message...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/arnold-schwarzenegger-russia-ukraine-1235113643/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I don't want you to be broken like my father," the actor and former California governor said in part in a nine-minute address, attempting to punch through Russian state propaganda, in which he recalled his dad's failings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin arrests military chief for leaking...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-army-general-arrested-leaking-26492398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Roman Gavrilov, the deputy chief of Russia's Federal National Guard, has reportedly been detained by the much-feared FSB security service and accused of leaking information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASKS OFF!! Heathrow, UK airlines drop mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-60757887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UK's largest airport joins British Airways and Virgin Atlantic in easing mask-wearing rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real estate sharks attempt to sell condo for $13M profit after one month!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/17/real-estate-sharks-try-to-flip-florida-condo-for-13m-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Florida triplex penthouse that sold at auction in February for $20.55 million is being flipped for $33.91 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's Scholz under fire after Zelensky's fierce appeal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-scholz-under-fire-zelenskys-155319097.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky on Thursday called on Germany to help destroy a new "Wall" Russia was erecting in Europe, as he appealed directly to Chancellor Olaf Scholz to bolster his tentative response to the invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt sites facing unprecedented cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/russian-govt-sites-facing-unprecedented-072520127.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian government entities and state-owned companies have been targeted over events in Ukraine, with the websites of the Kremlin, flagship carrier Aeroflot and major lender Sberbank among those to have seen outages or temporary access issues in recent weeks. The ministry was working to adjust to the new conditions, it said, as cyber attacks ratchet up. As Russia becomes increasingly isolated from global financial systems and supply chains, the government has proposed a raft of measures to support the IT sector, among others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid surge in western Europe has USA bracing for another wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-covid-surge-in-western-europe-has-us-bracing-for-another-wave/ar-AAV8kgb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyacht stuck in Norway because no one will sell it fuel...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/russian-oligarchs-superyacht-stuck-because-no-one-will-sell-it-fuel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian oligarch's superyacht is currently stuck at a dock in Norway because no one is willing to sell it any fuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers shooting themselves to get off frontline...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-soldiers-shooting-themselves-avoid-26493353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian troops are so demoralised that they're said to be looking for Ukrainian ammunition in order to shoot themselves in the legs, while others are reportedly fleeing into the woods</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside propaganda bubble: Where war isn't war...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Inside-Russia-s-propaganda-bubble-Where-a-war-17008839.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIGA, Latvia - Fake U.S. biowarfare labs. Fake killer birds. Tucker Carlson and Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA NEWS SERVICE COMES FOR DRUDGE...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/DPRK_News/status/1504359743745404928?s=20&amp;t=ijmMxdyugTxpfQRby6cgGA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bond payment  in limbo as countdown to default begins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-payment-confusion-starts-countdown-074403900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russia’s Finance Ministry said that it has sent payment orders for the interest on its dollar bonds to its correspondent bank, giving incremental details on a debt settlement that has come to exemplify how Moscow plans to handle its future relations with creditors. Most Read from BloombergPutin Vows to Rid Russia of ‘Traitors’ While Waging Ukraine WarRichest Russian Built NYC Power Over Decades and Lost It in WeeksUkraine Update: U.S. House Set to Revoke Russia’s Trade StatusU.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WNBA star's arrest extended to May 19 by Russian court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brittney-griner-russia-arrest-extended-d769f6dfe03a3b55f23ef24960dae787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Moscow court announced it has extended the arrest of WNBA star Brittney Griner until May 19, according to the Russian state news agency Tass. Griner was detained at a Moscow airport in February after Russian authorities said a search of her luggage revealed vape cartridges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar Predictions: Will 'DOG' reign supreme?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-oscars-predictions-1d95a10f6b9385ff2c1acbb5158d5f20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of the 94th Academy Awards, Associated Press Film Writers Lindsey Bahr and Jake Coyle share their predictions for a ceremony with much still up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico Prepare for New Migrant Wave as Inflation Surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberglinea.com/2022/03/17/us-mexico-prepare-for-new-migrant-wave-as-inflation-surges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberglinea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials from the administrations of Presidents Joe Biden and Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador in recent days discussed their concern about the impact that rising food and energy prices will have on the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROOPS WARN 'WE'LL RISE AGAINST YOU'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10622821/Russian-soldiers-warn-Putin-RISE-against-terror-acts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three captured Russian air force pilots, warned President Vladimir Putin 'you will not hide this for long' because 'many' troops share the same feelings and 'sooner or later, we will come home'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt sites facing unprecedented cyber attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-internet/russian-government-sites-facing-unprecedented-cyber-attacks-report-idUSKCN2LE0NB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian government websites are facing unprecedented cyber attacks and technical efforts are being made to filter foreign web traffic, the TASS news agency cited the digital ministry as saying on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans frantic to migrate as economy falters, new hurdles arise...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-migrants/cubans-frantic-to-migrate-as-economy-falters-new-hurdles-arise-idUSKCN2LE15I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bray Perez, a 19-year-old Cuban university student, is fast losing friends to a growing wave of migration off the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN HAS 3 MOVES LEFT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-10622533/Russia-Ukraine-happens-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine has to sustain the ability of its forces to continue fighting effectively and counterattacking to regain lost territory if it is to hold out against the Russians, a military expert told MailOnline today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of most basic hotel amenities disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-travel-lifestyle-2bffd3573fb6bd7f33222e13605f4510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether out of necessity due to staffing shortages, out of respect for social distancing or perhaps just to save money, one of the primary amenities that sets a hotel apart from your home — daily housekeeping — is disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruined game plan visible in south...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/defence/russias-ruined-game-plan-for-ukraine-is-visible-in-the-south/articleshow/90291832.cms </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
