<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Religious symbols proposal ignites fiery debate in Quebec...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c13cb14f729c40648611be9763674307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTREAL (AP) — A proposal to ban many public employees from wearing religious symbols is creating a fiery debate in the Canadian province of Quebec, where people are fighting to freely practice...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The big cat con: Inside shocking battery farms for lions...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/big-cat-con-inside-africas-051500513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing appetite for 'conservation holidays' has shone a light on the dark – and poorly regulated – industry of lion farming, where felines are destined not to be 'released into the wild' - but to be shot by trophy hunters and their bones exported to Asia for use in traditional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Use Electrical Implant to Aid Brain-Damaged Woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/13/health/implant-brain-injury.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pilot study offers “a very promising start” in the effort to help people recover from traumatic brain injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion brand 'FUCT' seeks trademark help from Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a06313f1ab454e9e8af3bbec2133fb85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Erik Brunetti's four-letter fashion brand starts with an "F'' and rhymes with "duct." The federal government calls it "scandalous" and "immoral" and has refused to register the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Says 'New World Order' Being Formed...</title>
      <link>https://tsarizm.com/news/eastern-europe/2019/04/12/russia-says-new-world-order-being-formed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tsarizm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upper Middle Class Feeling the Pinch Too...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/america-upper-middle-class-feeling-130000583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While still wealthier overall than most other groups, even the upper-middle class is feeling the pinch of income stagnation. The cost of many products and services the upper middle class buys, from autos to college educations, is outpacing overall inflation. Credit card interest rates recently reached</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Weakening Of Earth's Magnetic Field Accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-12/weakening-earths-magnetic-field-has-greatly-accelerated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Tax?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-04-12/there-porn-tax-your-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centenarian runs for office in German town...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-politics-centenarian/making-a-splash-centenarian-runs-for-office-in-german-town-idUSKCN1RP06Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most people, reaching 100 would be reason enough to put one's feet up a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden bulldogs give him edge?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/13/biden-bulldogs-1272931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The likely White House contender has a cadre of senior Democrats ready to defend him against attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit couple creates NETFLIX-like service with pro-socialist programming...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/money/business/2019/04/13/detroit-couple-launch-socialism-company-means-tv/3414226002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two filmmakers who gained national attention for making a campaign video for Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez are launching a pro-socialism media company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No religion' now as popular as Catholicism...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/13/us/no-religion-largest-group-first-time-usa-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The non-religious edged out Catholics and Evangelicals in the long-running General Social Survey. The three groups remain within the margin of error of each other though, making it a statistical tie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHT FREAK: Man touches passenger faces, sprays them, jumps on tarmac...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/12/us/unruly-passenger-american-airlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 25-year-old man was acting strange during the flight, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Trafficked Mammal at Risk of Extinction, Record Haul Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/most-trafficked-mammal-at-risk-of-extinction-record-haul-shows </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore confiscated 26 tons of pangolin scales in one week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants break border gate, force way into Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e2833348dcd94b2dae9c328af1bfaa9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican authorities said a group of about 350 migrants broke the locks on a gate at the Guatemalan border Friday and forced their way into southern Mexico to join a larger group...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker group posts hundreds of law officer records...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2ce455dee4f24ce3b3a0aa7f303a9d46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — A hacker group has posted online the personal information of hundreds of federal agents and police officers apparently stolen from websites affiliated with alumni of the FBI's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie sees path to beating Trump in Rust Belt...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/438710-sanders-sees-path-to-beating-trump-in-rust-belt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders’s aides and advisers are convinced that he is the candidate best positioned to win over working-class voters in 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone wants full copy of Mueller report for criminal case...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/13/roger-stone-wants-full-copy-of-mueller-report-for-his-criminal-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone wants a full copy of the Mueller report for his criminal case, according to reports. Lawyers for Stone, who is accused of lying to Congress and obstructing justice, are also seeking to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland populists eye election upset as anti-immigrant feeling rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/finland-populists-eye-election-upset-anti-immigrant-feeling-040529796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the remote, northern Finnish town of Oulu where he has lived for seven years, Syrian-born Jabo Waleed recently started feeling that some people's behaviour towards him was becoming less welcoming. "My wife is Finnish, I have lots of Finnish friends, but if you walk alone in the streets or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iger's Successor Will Inherit Big Online Bet...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-disney-bob-igers-successor-will-inherit-his-big-streaming-bet-11555103311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney Chief Executive Bob Iger won high marks from investors after showcasing the company’s new streaming-video service on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can NATIONAL ENQUIRER Survive? Media Experts Divided...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/will-national-enquirer-survive-media-experts-divided-on-badly-damaged-tabloids-future/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I would rather pay money to someone to take it away from me, to save me from all the legal troubles," one expert told TheWrap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gossip King Richard Johnson Retiring from NY POST After 40 Years... </title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/04/12/shocker-gossip-king-richard-johnson-retiring-from-the-new-york-post-after-41-years-scooping-everyone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re just getting the news: gossip king Richard Johnson is retiring from the New York Post. He’s been in the game 41 years. He’s 65 years old, and he’s had enough. Richard …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC measles-vaccine order on Orthodox Jews tests city's power...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/state-nation-world/nyc-measles-vaccine-order-on-orthodox-jews-tests-citys-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — On the corner of Bedford and Division avenues in Brooklyn, in the heart of the New York borough’s Orthodox Jewish community, men in black hats and suits rushed in and out of cafes and women with headscarves pushed strollers or carts filled with groceries, not eager to speak with an outsid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKILEAKS set 21st century model for cyber-leak journalism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wikileaks-set-21st-century-model-cyber-leak-journalism-041939031.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using cryptography and virtual drop boxes, Julian Assange's WikiLeaks created a revolutionary new model for media to lure massive digitized leaks from whistleblowers, exposing everything from US military secrets to wealthy tax-dodgers' illicit offshore accounts. Assange's arrest in London</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother of 3-DNA baby praises new fertility treatment...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mother-3-dna-baby-praises-fertility-treatment-175805207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Greek mother of the first baby born using DNA from three people on Friday praised the revolutionary technique that helped her conceive -- and thanked the mystery woman who donated her egg. Under the terms of the treatment, she was not allowed to meet the donor, said 32-year-old Matina Karavokyri</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charging Assange reflects dramatic shift in US approach...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d9c190f66cc4e5b8669bcc0b6c1eff9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The decision to seek the extradition of Julian Assange marked a dramatic new approach to the founder of WikiLeaks by the U.S. government, a shift that was signaled in the early...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP THREAT:  FLOOD CITIES WITH ILLEGALS</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190412195230-wi9c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/SANCTUARY (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Trump weighs sending 'unlimited supply' of immigrants to sanctuary cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No espionage charge against Chinese intruder at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article229168134.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT BLUFFING?</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/nation/article_769bce69-7791-5d18-b9d5-7ca05337ef9e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald Trump taunted California on Friday with an attention-grabbing threat to dump detained migrants into the state’s sanctuary cities, despite warnings from his advisers that such action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House proposed releasing illegals in sanctuary cities, targeting political foes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0596f544fe0646ada2a6383e23f74e83</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Friday he is strongly considering releasing "Illegal Immigrants" into Democratic strongholds to punish congressional foes for inaction on the border—...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTERS SCARE: Tiger limps, winces after security slides into...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/golf/news/watch-nearly-injured-by-sliding-security-guard-tiger-woods-drops-clutch-birdie-at-masters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woods went from testing out his tweaked ankle to drilling a birdie putt on No. 14</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Papers lawyer: Snare and delusion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/438709-pentagon-papers-lawyer-indictment-of-assange-snare-and-delusion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;References to conspiracy under the Espionage Act raise the question whether U.S. government is going for a bait-and-switch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is boring!' Bill and Hillary speaking tour interrupted...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/only-a-heckler-can-improve-an-evening-with-the-money-grabbing-clintons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that they’ve been dismissed, defanged and declawed by their own party, Bill and Hillary Clinton are doing what comes naturally: Hitting people up for money. Thursday night marked the kickoff, i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANG PLAN TO CAMPAIGN AS HOLOGRAM!</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/04/12/andrew-yang-3d-hologram-rallies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang plans to use holograms to hold remote rallies for his presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Labels Pro-Life Movie As 'Propaganda'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/04/12/google-apologizes-for-labeling-unplanned-movie-as-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giant Google has apologized for labeling the pro-life film Unplanned as "propaganda" on its search engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian dies onstage during stand-up after joking about death...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-oxfordshire-47911040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran comic Ian Cognito is pronounced dead after sitting down and falling silent mid-performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sperm -- gets competitive when near rival...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-04-zebrafish-reveals-sexual-rivalry-affect.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The presence of a rival male affects sperm quality, according to a research study led by the University of Alicante and the University of Upsala (Sweden). The work was carried out with adult zebrafish (Danio rerio) and reveals that male spermatozoa exposed to high competition (two males and a single female) present dramatic changes in phenotype resulting in faster and more competitive spermatozoa. However, this phenotypic plasticity may incur a cost in the next generation as it has negative effects on DNA integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public interest or 'basically pornography'? Judge weighs vid release...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190412/public-interest-or-basically-pornography-judge-weighs-release-of-robert-kraft-videos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The videos allegedly show the owner of the New England Patriots paying for sex acts at a Jupiter day spa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut spends year in space snapping stunning pics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/12/science/scott-kellys-photos-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In orbit aboard the International Space Station, the astronaut wasn’t just gathering data for NASA’s Twins Study. He also produced some, well, stellar images.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Admit: No Human Trafficking Evidence in Kraft Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcconnecticut.com/news/local/Kraft-Attorneys-Back-in-Court-for-Motions-Hearing-508481301.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcconnecticut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in the Robert Kraft prostitution case admitted in court Friday that there was not enough evidence to prove there was human trafficking in the Orchids of Asia Day Spa investigation. Kraft's attorneys...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hefner son exits PLAYBOY role to start news, adult content site...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/cooper-hefner-exits-playboy-launch-millennial-focused-website-hefpost-1200044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Hugh Hefner's death Sept. 17, 2017, his son Cooper Hefner had been the highest ranking Hefner in the family business, Playboy Enterprises. He revealed today he's exiting the company to launch a media and digital company that will feature adult content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: THE INTERNET OF THOUGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-04-future-human-braincloud-interface-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine a future technology that would provide instant access to the world's knowledge and artificial intelligence, simply by thinking about a specific topic or question. Communications, education, work, and the world as we know it would be transformed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON:  #MeToo comments wrecked deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59a6dfc685d140e3a7c71a371d419cc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Woody Allen breached his four-movie deal with the online giant by making statements about the #MeToo movement that damaged prospects for promoting his films, an Amazon lawyer said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: President told CBP head he'd pardon him if jailed for violating law...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/12/politics/trump-cbp-commissioner-pardon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During President Donald Trump's visit to the border at Calexico, California, a week ago, where he told border agents to block asylum seekers from entering the US contrary to US law, the President also told the commissioner of Customs and Border Protection, Kevin McAleenan, that if he were sent to jail as a result of blocking those migrants from entering the US, the President would grant him a pardon, senior administration officials tell CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant serves menu for 'dieting' dogs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/chelsea-restaurant-serves-up-menu-for-dieting-dogs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who’s a calorie-counting boy? A Manhattan restaurant is taking pooch pampering to absurd new heights with a menu catering to “dieting” doggies, complete with a $26 pan-seared salmon dish and a bowl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truckers hold 'Slow Roll' protests nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/traffic/truck-drivers-hold-slow-roll-protests-nationwide/5245311/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truckers are holding "slow roll" protests in cities across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian dies onstage during stand-up act...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/ian-cognito-dead-comedian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British comedian Ian Cognito died while performing his stand-up show on Thursday in Bicester, England, Fox News has learned. He was 60.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBP officers from Canada border, airports sent to Mexican border...</title>
      <link>https://www.elpasotimes.com/story/news/local/el-paso/2019/04/12/cbp-officers-airports-canadian-border-sent-mexico-border-el-paso/3437622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.elpasotimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBP will send 100 officers from the Canadian border and airports to the southwest border, including El Paso, amid concerns of border wait times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden mulls reviving rape case...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-47910820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged victim's lawyer says she will do everything she can to get the investigation renewed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robots Could Set Tone for Social Interactions...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2019/04/12/how-robots-could-set-the-tone-for-social-interactions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence will likely reshape our economy, society and personal lives in the decades to come. But attaining AI’s broad potential will require not only a continuing slew of technological innovations, but research into societal challenges, says CIO Journal Columnist Irving Wladawsky-Berger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola outbreak nearing global emergency...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/ebola-virus-outbreak/congo-s-ebola-outbreak-might-be-declared-global-emergency-n993856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Red Cross official says he’s “more concerned than I have ever been” about the possible regional spread of the Ebola virus after a new spike in cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA declassifies Argentina coup files in largest ever handover...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190412-us-declassifies-argentina-coup-files-largest-ever-handover</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US declassifies Argentina coup files in largest ever handover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Child Thrown From Balcony At MALL OF AMERICA...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/04/12/witnesses-woman-says-her-child-was-thrown-from-3rd-floor-balcony-at-mall-of-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child was rushed to a hospital Friday after reportedly being thrown from a balcony at the Mall of America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As cashless stores grow, so does backlash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98613f20d0254b8bacd908ef12107fef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hembert Figueroa just wanted a taco. So he was surprised to learn the dollar bills in his pocket were no good at Dos Toros Taqueria in Manhattan, one of a small but growing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breast Milk Hot Health Supplement -- for Adults...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-12/breast-milk-is-the-hot-new-health-supplement-for-adults</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORBYN: Don't Send Him to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-47904837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labour says the Wikileaks boss should not be extradited to the US "for exposing evidence of atrocities".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Schooler Arrested For Trying WWE Wrestler's 'Finishing Move' -- On Principal!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/04/11/high-school-student-arrested-after-trying-wrestling-finishing-move-move-on-principal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high school student was arrested Wednesday after allegedly trying a wrestling move on his high school principal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 shot near Nipsey Hussle procession route...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d3e88f6876947998cf08302592029ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Latest on a memorial and funeral procession for slain rapper Nipsey Hussle (all times local): 7:15 a.m. A shooting killed one person and wounded three others...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange branded himself '87% slut' in dating site ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8851174/julian-assange-bizarre-dating-site-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULIAN Assange’s dating profile from 2006 has been unearthed – where he branded himself a “pig-headed intellectual” and “87 per cent slut”. The then 36-year-old …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$80 oil this summer?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/11/prepare-for-80-oil-this-summer-as-wounded-bulls-rise-rbc-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RBC Capital Markets raises its 2019 Brent crude forecast to $75 a barrel and warns of intermittent bouts of $80 oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laxative-laced cookies given to striking school workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cantonrep.com/news/20190410/uhrichsville-couple-facing-multiple-charges-after-allegedly-giving-laxative-laced-cookies-to-striking-school-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cantonrep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UHRICHSVILLE A Trenton Avenue couple is being held in the Tuscarawas County jail on $1 million bonds after they allegedly gave sugar cookies laced with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEN IVANKA:  SHE HAS GREAT CALMNESS, SAYS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/12/trump-explains-why-he-wanted-ivanka-to-lead-world-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump considered nominating his elder daughter, Ivanka, to lead the World Bank — because “she’s very good with numbers” — and said she would be “very, very hard to beat” if she decided to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long, grinding Brexit stressing people out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa806762f47f4037b367468ba249d4f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Elly Wright can't sleep through the night. The Dutch native, who has lived in Britain for 51 years, keeps thinking about the black boots of Nazi soldiers marching by her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stage set for epic extradition fight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98f7ec1528bf4e9d9edd78271c31c16b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — What is expected to be an epic legal and political battle over whether to extradite Julian Assange to the U.S. began to take shape, with Britain's opposition Labour Party urging the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli spacecraft crashes in attempt to land on moon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b7a46420b114036bff98b1e87b83306</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEHUD, Israel (AP) — An Israeli spacecraft crashed into the moon just moments before touchdown, failing in an ambitious attempt to make history Thursday as the first privately funded lunar...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
