<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trump works to avoid evangelical defections... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/03/trump-evangelical-defection-093071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His campaign is scrambling to ensure that evangelical support doesn’t erode amid some signs of discontent — and vowing that it can even expand its religious base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil prices surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-oil-could-hit-80-even-without-a-full-blown-us-iran-war-2020-01-03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices could “make a run at $80” a barrel even in the absence of a full-blown U.S.-Iran war, one analyst says. And that isn’t necessarily bad news for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strait of Hormuz in focus...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/strait-of-hormuz-the-worlds-biggest-oil-chokepoint-in-focus-as-us-iran-tensions-flare-2020-01-03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The threat of an escalating conflict between the U.S. and Iran puts the Strait of Hormuz, a narrow waterway through which a fifth of the world’s petroleum...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady and PATRIOTS appear vulnerable. Do you want to bet against them? </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Tom-Brady-and-the-Patriots-appear-vulnerable-Do-14947304.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. - Maybe this is really it for those flat-voweled, hard-shelled New England Patriots. Maybe. Go ahead and mark it as the end of an era in pro football if you're sure, absolutely sure, that 42-year-old Tom Brady is finished defying normal cellular degeneration, and 67-year-old head coach Bill Belichick can't muster enough steel and nerve from his guys for one more postseason run. What shall we call their two decades of dominion, if it is indeed complete? An age?  With that peculiar, characteristic, tight-lipped existential state of denial known as their Way, they plodded through meetings and practice this week, affecting total unconcern about their past or future, betraying not a shred of sentimentality over the possibility that their wild-card meeting with the Tennessee Titans could be a closing chapter, and the final home game of Brady's career as a Patriot. "I'm not much for nostalgia," Brady said.  You don't win 78 percent of your games over 10 years by studying yesterday's scores, or tomorrow's predictions, or listening to the skeptics who've been saying you're past it for a decade. Or by dwelling on a season-ending loss to the Miami Dolphins so startling that, combined with Brady's age, impending free agency and uncertain future, it made the Patriots seem suddenly more faded and vulnerable than usual, maybe even underdogs against a surging team radiating the fresh strength of youth in the Titans.  "I don't know what we are, or aren't," Belichick said. "We're past last week. We're past every week."  People go to ashrams and consult sages for that kind of be-here-nowness. The thing is, the Patriots actually practice it. If they have shown one quality over the past 20 years, it's concentration in the face of threat. That unwaveringness is hard to properly appreciate; the numbers boggle. They've...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRISTIANITY TODAY editor says many ignorant about 'the gravity of moral failings'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/476639-christianity-today-editor-says-other-evangelicals-ignorant-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christianity Today editor-in-chief Mark Galli says in a new interview that he was shocked by the reaction to the magazine's recent editorial calling for President Trump’s removal from office, saying anger at the piece demonstrates "wides</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sending 3,000 more troops to Mideast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2742111f6d0489313da688557d1123e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The United States is sending nearly 3,000 more Army troops to the Mideast as reinforcements in the volatile aftermath of the killing of an Iranian general in a strike ordered by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC ON ALERT...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200103170546-5nb43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/BLAST-NEW YORK:New York mayor says city bracing for Iranian retaliation after Soleimani killed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIME'S UP Introduces 'Safety Guide' For Hollywood Nude Scenes...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/times-up-reveals-safety-guide-entertainment-industry-employees-1264822</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The three-part resource covers auditions and nude, intimate and simulated sex scenes and also details how to report sexual misconduct and harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC ON ALERT...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-york-city-warns-it-could-be-target-for-attack-by-iranians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor of New York City has ordered the NYPD to take immediate steps to protect key locations across the city after a U.S. airstrike killed Iran's top general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect's APPLE watch used to prove he was lying...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/mans-apple-watch-proves-he-lied-about-anti-semitic-stabbing-in-west-bloomfield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say Sean Samitt fabricated an attack on December 15 as he left a synagogue leaving the Jewish community in West Bloomfield shaken up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughing mob kick great white shark to death  -- then take selfies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/great-white-shark-kicked-death-21208556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people claim they saw a group of men purposefully net the 9ft long animal and kick it repeatedly on an Auckland beach, before taking selfies and laughing as it died</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soleimani 'torn to shreds' by missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7847795/How-airstrike-Iranian-general-unfolded-Baghdad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qassem Soleimani, head of Iran's feared Quds force, had just arrived at Baghdad airport early on Friday morning when a US Reaper drone fired four guided missiles at two cars, killing him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-CIA DIRECTOR:  'THERE WILL BE DEAD AMERICANS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/qassem-soleimani-iran-general-killed-dead-americans-as-result-former-acting-cia-director-michael-morell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The targeted killing of Qassem Soleimani, one of Iran's top military leaders, has escalated tensions between the U.S. and Iran, with Iran vowing revenge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body identified by ring...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/03/qassem-soleimani-airstrike-ring-from-corpse-identified-irans-top-general/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although Qassem Soleiman was blown to bits in the US drone strike, the top Iranian commander was identified by this red ring still attached to a finger on his hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND PAUL:  NO WAR...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/03/rand-paul-iran-congress-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul warned against war with Iran without congressional approval following the death of top Iranian General Qasem Soleimani.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Westerners 'should leave Dubai'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10662864/westerners-should-leave-dubai-region-immediately-us-killing-qasem-soleimani-iran-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have told Westerners to get out of the United Arab Emirates immediately fearing reprisals for today’s assassination of the top Iranian general. Tensions have escalated steeply after t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge gamble...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-01-02/trumps-biggest-foreign-policy-gamble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The killing of a top Iranian general in Iraq brings the U.S. and Iran to edge of war — one of the biggest gambles of Trump's presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Terrorist' wearing explosive vest shot dead in Paris after stabbing four people...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7848923/Terrorist-kinifeman-wearing-explosive-vest-shot-dead-Paris-stabbing-four-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses told local media the attacker was yelling 'Allahu Akbar' as he launched the attack in the suburb of Villejuif shortly after 2pm on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: '60 MINS' Investigates Never-Seen Evidence in Epstein Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/inside-jeffrey-epstein-cell-sunday-on-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death of convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein in a federal prison has sparked countless conspiracy theories. Sunday, 60 Minutes reports on the investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR OF CYBER ATTACK</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-iran-war-footing-qasem-soleimani-airstrike-13cbe74f-9095-47b4-8d03-85f1e702f447.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could destabilize the world's most volatile region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAG THE DOG THEORIES ERUPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/2020/01/article/is-trump-wagging-the-dog-in-the-middle-east/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember that old, and good, advice: ‘Keep your powder dry’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rose McGowan Sparks Outrage After Apologizing To Iran For Airstrike...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/celebrity/2020/01/03/rose-mcgowan-sparks-twitter-controversy-apologizing-iran-soleimani-airstrike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rose McGowan sparked backlash on Twitter early Friday morning when she tweeted an apology to Iran [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Having Plant On Office Desk Reduces Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/having-a-plant-on-your-office-desk-helps-reduce-daily-stress-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the University of Hyogo in Japan say that small potted plants around the office can go a long way towards relieving employee stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLEEPER CELLS IN USA?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/iran-has-hezbollah-sleeper-cells-in-the-u-s-ready-to-strike/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ali Kourani previously tasked with conducting surveillance of JFK &amp; Pearson airports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL ON EARTH: DEVIL FACE IN FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7847319/The-face-fire-Dairy-farmer-claims-spotted-DEVIL-lurking-bushfire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dairy darmer Craig Calvert shared a photo depicting a demonic apparition coming from the smoke of the fires in East Gippsland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robot Priests Will Change Human Spirituality...</title>
      <link>https://onezero.medium.com/how-robot-priests-will-change-human-spirituality-913a19386698</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;onezero.medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If our tools amplify our intentions, we need to question our motivation for developing robots that automate blessings or hearing confession</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One more ride for Brady in New England -- then nothing promised...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/sports/one-more-ride-for-tom-brady-in-new-england-then-nothing-promised-223238167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady didn&amp;#39;t build Gillette Stadium. But for 18 seasons, he has been its king.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READIES CIVIL WAR WITH BIDEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/ascendant-bernie-sanders-turns-his-focus-to-joe-biden-as-iowa-nears/ar-BBYyRHu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French govt huddles as unions vow to harden strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200103-french-govt-huddles-as-unions-vow-to-harden-strike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French govt huddles as unions vow to harden strike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON accused of threatening to fire climate activists...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/amazon-climate-crisis-activists-threaten-121421244.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Employees for Climate Justice took to Twitter to complain they were being "silenced" by the e-commerce giant's management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dying has become luxury in crisis-ridden Argentina...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dying-become-luxury-crisis-ridden-argentina-012015096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one can escape Argentina's biggest economic crisis in almost two decades -- not even the dead. Juan Tapia runs the Cocheria Tacuari undertakers in Buenos Aires, which has been operating for 60 years. The cheapest service offered by Cocheria Tacuari is a cremation without a wake, which costs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest bloom: 'World's largest' flower spotted in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/biggest-bloom-worlds-largest-flower-spotted-indonesia-100446247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesian conservationists say they've spotted the biggest specimen ever of what's already been billed as one of the world's largest flowers. The giant Rafflesia tuan-mudae -- a fleshy red flower with white blister-like spots on its enormous petals -- came in at a whopping 111 centimetres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWIII</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2020/01/03/world-war-3-trends-donald-trump-airstrike-kills-iran-general-11993960/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's ruler has warned of 'harsh vengeance' after the death of General Qasem Soleimani at Baghdad Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel braces for retaliation...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200103065710-idbbh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/BLAST-ISRAEL (PIX):Israel braces for Iranian retaliation after Soleimani assassination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says was planning new attacks...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200103030822-g9myn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-SECURITY/BLAST-PENTAGON (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Pentagon says Iranian commander Soleimani was developing plans to attack Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEHRAN VOWS CRUSHING REVENGE</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10661549/us-airstrike-iranian-general-baghdad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN’S most powerful military commander was killed at Baghdad airport on Friday by a US air strike – as the two countries stand on the brink of war. President Donald Trump personally ap…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage shows aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/video/2020/jan/03/footage-shows-aftermath-of-us-airstrike-that-killed-top-iranian-general-qassem-suleimani-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The killing of the powerful Iranian military general presents a dramatic escalation of an already bloody struggle between Washington and Tehran for influence across the region</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans urged to depart Iraq immediately...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security-blast-embassy/us-embassy-urges-citizens-to-depart-iraq-immediately-statement-idUSKBN1Z20NR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States embassy in Baghdad urged on Friday all citizens to depart Iraq...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber returns with 'YUMMY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/music/justin-bieber-returns-with-smooth-new-track-yummy-2592439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justin Bieber has returned with new track 'Yummy' – and it sees the singer heading in a smooth R&amp;B direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands rally in Iran against 'crimes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200103-tens-of-thousands-rally-in-iran-capital-against-us-crimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands rally in Iran capital against US 'crimes'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GARRETT GONE?</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28412867/cowboys-move-jason-garrett-source-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Jones and Stephen Jones have decided that Jason Garrett will not be part of the organization moving forward, a source told ESPN's Ed Werder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrorist general killed hundreds of US troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7847905/Qassem-Soleimani-terrorist-general-blood-THOUSANDS-hands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qassem Soleimani, who was killed in a US drone strike Thursday, led Iran's feared Quds force for two decades, helping Shia militias kill US troops in Iraq and backing Assad as he slaughtered civilians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil prices surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/03/oil-prices-surge-after-reports-that-a-key-iranian-general-was-killed-in-iraq-airstrike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Qasem Soleimani, who led a special forces unit of Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards, has been killed in a U.S. airstrike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks shook...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/03/dow-futures-after-us-air-strike-kills-iran-top-military-leader.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock index futures were sharply lower Friday morning, after the U.S. confirmed an air strike that killed a top Iranian commander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rattles Mideast With Risky Strike...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-rattles-mideast-u-politics-055619552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump ordered the killing of a top Iranian general on Thursday, and in his characteristic style, the president made sure the world knew who was responsible.As reports filtered out from Iraq that Qassem Soleimani had been killed in a U.S. airstrike, some administration officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/middleeast/live-news/baghdad-airport-strike-live-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump ordered a strike that killed the commander of Iran's Quds Force, the Pentagon said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assassination triggers global alarm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de0fd53597fa0c261bd7d2c6072b0be8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Global powers warned Friday that the world has become a more dangerous place and urged restraint after the U.S. assassinated Iran’s top general, although Britain and Germany also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIKE ON BAGHDAD AIRPORT</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2020/01/03/iraq-rockets-fired-at-baghdad-airport-7-people-killed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An official with the group known as the Popular Mobilization Forces said the dead included its airport protocol officer, identifying him as Mohammed Reda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 BEGINS WITH BANG</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/rockets-baghdad-airport-injuries-reported</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three rockets were fired at Baghdad International Airport Friday killing at least seven people, including Iranian Gen. Qassim Soleimani, the head of the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps' elite Quds Force, according to multiple reports early Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP IRAN COMMANDER KILLED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5597ff0f046a67805cc233d5933a53ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baghdad (AP) — Gen. Qassim Soleimani, the head of Iran’s elite Quds Force, was killed in an airstrike at Baghdad’s international airport Friday, Iraqi television and three Iraqi officials said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READIES CIVIL WAR WITH BIDEN</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/ascendant-bernie-sanders-turns-his-focus-to-joe-biden-as-iowa-nears/2020/01/02/1132e622-2d7c-11ea-bcd4-24597950008f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is building momentum in Iowa â€” and nationally. But is his movement, now fueled by rage against health-care costs, enough to win?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG releasing 65" rollable TV which unfurls from ceiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10660591/lg-65-inch-rollable-tv-ceiling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LG is set to release a 65-inch rollable television which unfurls itself from your ceiling. The ultra-high definition, wafer-thin screen is set to be unveiled at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex assaults on airplanes on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/crime/article238558198.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man having home built dresses up as sheriff to intimidate contractor...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/florida/os-ne-sarasota-impersonating-law-enforcement-home-building-dispute-20200102-ejdxdtnye5hsvluoea6t4me5nu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man dressed up in a sheriff's costume and drove to a contractor's house to try to intimidate him, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City nearly hit its all-time record for homicides. Most unsolved...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article238524473.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Poised to Surpass NY in Congressional Seats...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-poised-surpass-york-congressional-165831036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Florida is expected to control more seats in the U.S. Congress than New York after April’s decennial census, according to a study by Election Data Services Inc.New York and California are projected to each lose a U.S. congressional seat due to population declines, while Texas and Florida</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami evangelical Trump event could mix pastors, politics, and illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article238900983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRET EASTON ELLIS:  'ONCE UPON TIME IN HOLLYWOOD' BEST OF YEAR; 'PARASITE' RUNNER-UP...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/BretEastonEllis/status/1212162161478258688</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Top Ten 2019 Ford v Ferrari The Irishman Little Women Marriage Story Midsommar 1917 Once Upon A Time In Hollywood (1) Parasite (2) Toy Story 4 Under the Silver Lake (3)”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet No Longer Disruptive Technology...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/internet-no-longer-disruptive-technology-150035326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Internet-enabled industry disruption defined business strategy in the 2010s, but as 2020 begins, that era appears to be winding down. The disruptors have largely become the new establishment, and unlike a decade ago, it doesn’t look like the new leaders will be displaced any time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No nostalgia for Brady as he enters latest postseason run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/307bc55b238a0557a204672ce6a6e9a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOXBOROUGH, Mass. (AP) — Tom Brady made one thing clear on Thursday: He isn't thinking about the past or the future this week as he prepares for the 17th postseason of his 20-year NFL career....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Now the Divided Republic Framers Feared...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/01/two-party-system-broke-constitution/604213/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Adams worried that “a division of the republic into two great parties … is to be dreaded as the great political evil.” And that’s exactly what has come to pass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  RICHMOND TIMES-DISPATCH building sold to hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/business/times-dispatch-building-in-downtown-richmond-sold-newspaper-to-remain/article_a4689c9e-1f19-5330-b42e-d13ed0d47abb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Richmond Times-Dispatch building in downtown Richmond has been sold to the region’s largest hotel operator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi, McConnell Begin 2020 in Standoff...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/pelosi-and-mcconnell-begin-2020-in-standoff-over-trump-impeachment-trial/ar-BBYxvFV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man urinates in airport terminal in front of horrified passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/travel/man-urinates-airport-horrified-passengers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking video of a man urinating at an airport terminal has the Internet completely horrified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Tops $300 for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-01-02/apple-tops-300-for-first-time-as-shares-extend-record-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marianne Williamson lays off ALL staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/democrat-marianne-williamson-lays-off-campaign-staff-nationally-including-nh/30382582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marianne Williamson, who has been campaigning for the Democratic presidential nomination on a message of love and has been urging voters to “join the evolution,” has laid off her entire staff in New Hampshire and nationally, sources close to the campaign confirmed to WMUR on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules Texas baby can be taken off life support against family's wishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article238902013.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Spent Last Decade Losing Population -- and Learning Nothing...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/01/02/illinois-spent-the-last-decade-losing-population-and-learning-nothing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2010s will likely end up being a lost decade for Illinois. I mean that literally: According to U.S. census</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXODUS: More People Leaving NY Than Any Other State...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/01/01/people-leaving-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“New York has lost nearly 1.4 million residents to the rest of the country since 2010,” a Dec. 30 Empire Center release said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA Declines to Prosecute Anti-Semitic Attack as Hate Crime...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/manhattan-da-declines-to-prosecute-anti-semitic-attack-as-hate-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney declined to prosecute a recent anti-Semitic attack on a Jewish passenger riding on the city's subway as a hate crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg fails to file for Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/02/bloomberg-fails-to-file-nevada-democratic-caucuses-092761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former New York mayor is intending to bypass the four early voting states, including Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-HAUL to stop hiring smokers...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/article238910053.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House official said aide hold came from Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/02/politics/unredacted-ukraine-documents-pentagon-concerns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the face of warnings from the Pentagon that the hold on military aid to Ukraine could be illegal, an official from the Office of Management and Budget made it clear that the order to keep the freeze in place came directly from President Donald Trump, according to unredacted documents reviewed by Just Security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSKINS Owner Mocked for 'Happy Thanksgiving' Wish While Introducing New Head Coach...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/02/washington-redskins-owner-dan-snyder-wishes-everyone-happy-thanksgiving-while-introducing-new-head-coach-ron-rivera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Redskins owner Dan Snyder apparently forgot what holiday the country just celebrated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON threatens to fire workers who are outspoken...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon-threatens-to-fire-workers-who-are-outspoken-on-its-environmental-policies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon has warned at least two employees who publicly criticized the Seattle-based company's environmental policies that they could be fired for future violations of its communications policy. A lawyer in the e-commerce giant's employee-relations group sent a letter to two...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon: Additional Attacks Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iraq-security-usa-iran-pentagon/u-s-sees-signs-iran-or-allies-may-be-planning-more-attacks-pentagon-chief-idUSKBN1Z113U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Mark Esper said on Thursday there were indications Iran o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mountain lions euthanized after finding, eating human body on trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7845049/Three-mountain-lions-feeding-HUMAN-remains-near-popular-Arizona-trail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pima County Sheriff's Department said Tuesday it had found human remains at Pima Canyon Trail in the hills north of Tucson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden raises $22.7 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/02/joe-biden-raises-22point7-million-in-the-fourth-quarter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's presidential campaign took in $22.7 million in the fourth quarter, an improving fundraising pace that still lags some of his top competitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Of UBER, LYFT Drivers Reportedly Not Getting Paid...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/01/rideshare-pay-uber-lyft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a fare freeze. Some Sacramento-area Uber and Lyft drivers are saying they're not getting paid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackface again mars Philly New Year parade...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/01/mummers-group-disqualified-after-several-members-wear-blackface-as-part-of-gritty-themed-costume/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two mummers who wore blackface claim it's not racist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-GOOGLE Exec: Company Put Profits Over Human Rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-google-exec-company-put-184238352.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Google policy executive accused the company of choosing profits over human rights in a searing essay published Thursday. Ross LaJeunesse, a candidate for U.S. Senate in Maine and Google’s former head of international relations, blamed the leadership team that has replaced founders Sergey Brin</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
