<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Chernobyl plant suffers 'blackout'; Fears of radiation leak...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4850584/chernobyl-safeguard-system-ukraine-at-risk-russian-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Chernobyl nuclear power plant has suffered a “complete blackout” sparking fears of a radiation leak disaster after Russia disconnected the site from the national grid. Ukraine’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using stealth drone fleet 'The Punisher'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/ukrainians-using-stealth-drones-wipe-26413916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drones only have a 2.2m wingspan but can carry up to three explosives, and are being used to take out supply lines up to 50km behind enemy lines in a significant blow to Russian invaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ALL IN': PUTIN BETS PRESIDENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/putin-diplomacy-russia-ukraine-war-demands-invasion-rcna19029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The challenge is this: Putin continues to press this aggression, and that is why we are concerned this could go on for some time,” a State Department spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian forces tighten grip on Kyiv gateway as residents describe growing perils...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-forces-tighten-grip-on-kyiv-gateway-as-residents-describe-growing-perils/ar-AAUOa6R?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC says avoid travel to New Zealand, Hong Kong and Thailand as corona cases surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cdc-says-avoid-travel-to-new-zealand-hong-kong-and-thailand-as-covid-cases-surge/ar-AAUN6qU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSKY:  Elon asks court to scrap SEC agreement over his tweets, claiming was 'forced' to enter into it ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-asks-court-to-scrap-sec-agreement-over-his-tweets-claiming-he-was-forced-to-enter-into-it/ar-AAUNKp9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CRACKDOWN?</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/03/08/lawmakers-fear-cryptocurrencies-could-be-backdoor-for-sanctioned-rubles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers from both parties are worried that cryptocurrencies could help Russians use to evade western sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT anchor quits, warns world on brink of nuclear war...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/maria-baronova-fears-were-on-the-brink-of-a-nuclear-war-after-quitting-russian-state-run-media-over-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I wouldn’t lose my salary and job if I was sure that we are going to be alive for many years,’ Baronova told Fox News Digital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky echoes Churchill in historic address to UK Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1577662/ukraine-russia-war-zelensky-house-of-commons-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INSPIRATIONAL Volodymyr Zelensky invoked Winston Churchill with a vow to fight Russian forces in the air, at sea and on land during a moving historic address to Parliament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NUKE CONCERNS RISING</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/threats/2022/03/concern-rising-putin-could-use-nuclear-weapons/362913/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian “escalate to de-escalate” doctrine suggests Putin is thinking the unthinkable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA BANS RUSSIAN OIL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/us-expected-to-announce-ban-on-russian-oil-as-soon-as-today-nbc-news-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move came as Western-allied nations work to sever Moscow from the global economy as punishment for its ongoing war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside high-tech sex parties, S&amp;M dungeons of Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/inside-the-high-tech-sex-parties-and-sm-dungeons-of-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her new book, “Special Characters: My Adventures with Tech’s Titans and Misfits,” Laurie Segall writes about the high-tech sex secrets of the Silicon Valley tech world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TO THE RESCUE: Beijing Considers Buying Stakes in Russian Energy, Commodity Firms...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/china-considers-buying-stakes-in-russian-energy-commodity-firms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchdog Loses Contact With Safeguards Monitoring Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-03-08/iaea-loses-contact-with-safeguards-monitoring-systems-at-chernobyl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENTRAL PARK ARSON: 10 fires set, smoke billows over Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/central-park-fire-spews-smoke-over-manhattan/3589034/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up to 10 small fires broke out in Central Park Tuesday afternoon in an apparent act of arson, say two law enforcement sources with knowledge of the case, enshrouding the iconic space’s tall trees in a thick, billowy white smoke. The fires, at least six but as many as 10, appeared to have started in the North Woods, the largest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K Street was fine taking cash -- until it couldn't...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/07/k-street-lobbying-russia-00014442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after the annexation of Crimea and the hacking of the DNC, firms took on major Russia clients. Then came the sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell juror explains why he failed to reveal past sex abuse: 'Thinking about my ex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/ghislaine-maxwell-juror-explains-why-he-failed-to-reveal-past-sex-abuse-he-was-thinking-about-my-ex/ar-AAUNPhn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MI Republican Candidate Tells Daughters 'If Rape Inevitable, Lie Back And Enjoy It'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wxyz.com/news/michigan-gop-nominee-under-fire-for-comments-over-rape</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wxyz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republican nominee for the Michigan House of Representatives is facing backlash for a comment he made on a Facebook Live over the weekend while discussing a possible decertification of the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bag of animal heads linked to sacrifice ritual?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-rhode-island-animal-welfare-a69457139e63d6140f1757152de9b3d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST GREENWICH, R.I. (AP) — Several animal heads found in a plastic bag in East Greenwich last month appear to be related to some sort of religious animal sacrifice ritual, the Rhode Island Society for the Prevention of Cruelty said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Z': On tanks and capturing public's military mindset...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220308-z-on-russia-s-tanks-and-capturing-the-public-s-military-mindset</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Russia moved troops into Ukraine, the letter "Z" -- emblazoned on Moscow's advancing armoured vehicles -- has gripped the country's public consciousness on social media, in manicures and on an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S, COCA-COLA, STARBUCKS suspend business...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/coca-cola-follows-mcdonalds-starbucks-in-suspending-business-in-russia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Army vet explains why he's fighting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/08/us-army-vet-on-fighting-in-ukraine-im-doing-it-for-my-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-Army vet Cody Heard is heading to Ukraine to help fight the Russians — a decision he made because of his kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for Meaning in Mysterious Brain Signal at Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxdbgw/the-search-for-meaning-in-a-mysterious-brain-signal-at-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research on a surge of gamma wave activity at death has been cited as proof your life flashes before your eyes before you die; in truth, no one knows exactly what it means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S closes 850 restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/mcdonalds-will-temporarily-close-850-restaurants-in-russia-nearly-2-weeks-after-putin-invaded-ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McDonald's said will temporarily close 850 locations in Russia after the company took heat for staying silent on the war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricanes keep killing people long after landfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/hidden-burden-hurricanes-keep-killing-people-long-after-landfall-study-suggests/ar-AAUNs2J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN tells staff not to call conflict 'war' or 'invasion'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/08/un-tells-comms-staff-not-to-call-ukraine-conflict-war-or-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An email from the UN’s global communications department, reported that employees have been told to refer to the fighting as a “conflict” or “military offensive.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson headed to BRONCOS in blockbuster deal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/08/russell-wilson-traded-to-broncos-from-seahawks-in-nfl-blockbuster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of the biggest blockbuster trades in recent memory, the Seattle Seahawks have traded QB Russell Wilson to the Denver Broncos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE unveils new budget iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/apple-event-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple announced a new budget iPhone SE, a new iPhone Air, the Mac Studio computer and its new M1 Ultra chip during the event. CNBC has live updates here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow patriarch stokes Orthodox tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-religion-europe-moscow-0670305be2e010e02a4e195ced2b7523</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Orthodox Patriarch Kirill, leader of Russia’s dominant religious group, has sent his strongest signal yet justifying his country's invasion of Ukraine — describing the conflict as part of a struggle against sin and pressure from liberal foreigners to hold “gay parades” as the price of admission to their ranks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  NFL star kills 2,000-pound buffalo and takes pic holding its heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4848311/nfl-derek-wolfe-baltimore-ravens-dead-buffalo-pictures/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL star and Super Bowl champ Derek Wolfe has caused outrage after killing a 2,000 pound buffalo with an arrow. The Baltimore Ravens’ defensive end uploaded pictures of the dead beast to Instagram …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet fragments as invasion pushes platforms to choose sides...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/internet-fragments-as-russian-invasion-pushes-platforms-to-choose-sides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West's effort to curb pro-Russian websites and media outlets in reaction to Russian President Vladimir Putin's invasion of Ukraine could lead to an increasingly fragmented internet, cyberwarfare experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RODGERS STAYING WITH PACKERS FOR $200 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/aaron-rodgers-packers-agree-to-terms-on-four-year-200m-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Packers and quarterback Aaron Rodgers have agreed to terms on a four-year, $200 million deal that makes him the highest-paid player on an annual basis in NFL history, Ian Rapoport reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST:  Proud Boys leader Tarrio charged with conspiracy in Jan. 6 attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/longtime-proud-boys-leader-enrique-tarrio-charged-with-conspiracy-in-jan-6-attack-on-capitol/ar-AAUN7eg?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VOWS: PUTIN WILL NEVER TAKE UKRAINE!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4847411/biden-gas-speech-today-russia-oil-ban-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden announced a ban on Russian oil imports in a speech on Tuesday. President Biden has decided to make the move to toughen the toll on Russia’s economy in retaliation for its invasion of Ukra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine animal shelters appeal for help to save 1,000 dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukraine-animal-shelters-shelled-russian-26413131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In war-torn Ukraine, at least two animal shelters have been attacked by Russian missiles, resulting in a large number of animal deaths, while food supplies are rapidly dwindling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT ABS, BAD EARS:  BLASTING MUSIC DURING WORKOUT WRECKS HEARING...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/exercise/article-700433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyone who has ever walked into a gym or training studio knows that loud music is part of the business, and can help us move, but it can be very harmful over time. Here are all the details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan Migrants Coming Home as Maduro Embraces Capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.batimes.com.ar/news/latin-america/venezuelan-emigrants-return-as-maduro-embraces-capitalism.phtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.batimes.com.ar&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After leading his country’s economy over a cliff, President Nicolas Maduro has brought it a certain measure of stability. By allowing dollars to flow freely and private enterprise to flourish in recent months, he seems to have breathed new life into his regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 arrested after girl forced to wear electric shock collar meant for dog...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/stratford-child-abuse-girl-wearing-shock-collar-nj-case-camden-county/11629798/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person interviewed by police allegedly said the dog collar was forced on the girl as punishment when she was "bad."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian police detain over 100 people at anti-war protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-protests/russian-police-detain-over-100-people-at-anti-war-protests-monitor-idUSKBN2L51S0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian police arrested at least 100 people at protests against the invasion of Ukraine on Tuesday, the OVD-Info monitoring group said, adding that detentions were still continuing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Pulls Staff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/597305-new-york-times-pulling-staffers-out-of-russia-citing-safety-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times will pull its journalists out of Russia, saying it is making the move in the interest of staffers' safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK JOINS</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-k-phase-russian-oil-145358364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.K. government plans to ban all imports of Russian oil, its latest sanctions move against Vladimir Putin’s administration over the war in Ukraine, a person familiar with the matter said. Most Read from BloombergUkraine Update: Russia’s Gas Threat; Cease-Fire Talks StruggleChina Warns U.S. Over Forming Pacific NATO, Backing TaiwanBiden to Sign Crypto Order as Firms Face Sanctions PressureCovid Can Shrink the Brain as Much as a Decade of Aging, Study FindsU.S. Spies See Grim Gl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish man crashes truck through Russian Embassy gates as protests target Moscow's diplomats worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/irish-man-crashes-truck-through-russian-embassy-gates-as-protests-target-moscows-diplomats-around-the-world/ar-AAUMPbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU presents plan to cut gas imports by two-thirds this year, stops short of boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/eu-presents-plan-to-cut-russian-gas-imports-by-two-thirds-this-year-stops-short-of-boycott/ar-AAUMRXV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to sign exec order on regulating, issuing crypto...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/597296-biden-to-sign-exec-order-on-regulating-issuing-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is reportedly set to sign an executive order on cryptocurrency this week that will direct several federal agencies to investigate and develop policies and regulations on digital currencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer Complains About Dead General, Comms Meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/russian-officer-complains-dead-general-113255353.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irina Rybakova/Press service of the Ukrainian ground forces/ReutersThe Ukrainian defence ministry has a released audio from a call which it claims captured two Russian officers lamenting the death of a top general and the collapse of its secure communications network in Ukraine.In the call—which has been verified by Bellingcat, the fact-checking group known for exposing Kremlin misinformation—two purported Russian FSB officers are heard discussing the death of a general killed in fighting near K</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Truth Social Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2022/03/donald-trump-truth-social-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truth Social has been a complete disaster and the ex-president seems to know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan Migrants Coming Home as Maduro Embraces Capitalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/maduro-s-switch-from-socialism-is-helping-bring-venezuelan-migrants-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan Migrants Are Coming Home as Maduro Embraces Capitalism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your toilet paper roll is slimming down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/business/toilet-paper-roll-shrinking-inflation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slimmed down toilet paper, fewer cookies in a bag, less conditioner in squeeze tubes. The changes are subtle and might evade less discerning shoppers. But retail industry experts say we could see more consumer products start shrinking in size or quantity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators look to lock down Moscow gold reserves...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-senators-look-to-lock-down-russias-gold-reserves-04c6c7bb-cc32-4e72-981e-fa972c31a1a4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal is to include the legislation in the omnibus spending bill lawmakers hope to pass by Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How Did This Many Deaths Become Normal?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2022/03/covid-us-death-rate/626972/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is nearing 1 million recorded COVID-19 deaths without the social reckoning that such a tragedy should provoke. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers 'Desert Posts' After Heavy Losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4845314/russian-general-killed-ukraine-vladimir-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ONE OF Vladimir Putin’s top generals has been killed in fighting outside of Ukraine’s second city Kharkiv, in another major blow for the Russian president. Vitaly Gerasimov is the secon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proposes nationalizing foreign-owned factories that shut...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/ukraine-crisis-russia-sanctions/russia-proposes-nationalising-foreign-owned-factories-that-shut-operations-idUSKBN2L51BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior member of Russia's ruling party has proposed nationalising foreign-owned factories that shut down operations in the country over what the Kremlin calls a special military operation in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Spies See Grim Global Outlook With Russia, China Top Foes...</title>
      <link>https://www.moneyweb.co.za/news/international/us-spies-see-grim-global-outlook-with-russia-china-top-foes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moneyweb.co.za&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the annual threat assessment by the Office of the Director of National Intelligence.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoppers Scramble for Staples as Food Fallout From War Spreads Around World...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6155752/ukraine-war-food-prices-inflation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shockwaves in global crop markets from Russia’s invasion of Ukraine are spreading to store shelves around the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN New Boss Signals for Truce With FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/cnns-new-boss-signals-for-truce-with-fox-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this week’s Source Material, we reveal massive changes coming to CNN, the way Twitter quietly changed its rules during wartime, and the drama at ABC News and G/O Media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eternal Youth On Horizon? Cell Therapy Reverses Signs Of Aging...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/reverses-signs-of-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakthrough may be able to extend life and help people gain the ability to become more resistant to stress, injury, and disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Drug Factory' Implants Cure Certain Cancers -- In 6 Days!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/drug-factory-implants-cure-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team tested this potentially groundbreaking treatment in mice, but they add that clinical trials in human cancer patients could start by fall 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>459-Foot Mystery in Tuscan Port: Is It Oligarch Superyacht?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/08/a-459-foot-mystery-in-a-tuscan-port-is-it-a-russians-superyacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Germany’s North Sea ports to the French Riviera, open season has been declared on superyachts. Across Europe, authorities are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States move to roll back firearm permits, over police objections...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/597227-states-move-to-roll-back-firearm-permits-over-police</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Russia Military Stumbles, Adversaries Take Note...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/07/as-russias-military-stumbles-its-adversaries-take-note/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONSTANTA, Romania — When it comes to war, generals say that “mass matters.” But nearly two weeks into President Vladimir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seemingly stuck convoy hides mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/seemingly-stuck-russian-convoy-hides-mysteries/ar-AAUKVUU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden sends Harris to Poland and Romania...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-sends-harris-to-poland-and-romania-amid-global-crisis/ar-AAUM95K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DWTS' alum escaped. Wracked by survivor's guilt, he says he's returning to Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-dancing-with-the-stars-alum-escaped-ukraine-wracked-by-survivor-s-guilt-he-says-he-s-returning-to-europe/ar-AAUMhQm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHELL CUTS TIES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/energy/shell-russia-oil-ban/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is finding it ever harder to sell its oil and gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltic states fear Putin has in sights...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/08/baltic-states-in-europe-fear-putin-has-them-in-his-sights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions are rising in Europe's ex-Soviet Baltic nations that Putin might not stop at invading Ukraine, and could have his sights set on them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB, other sex sites face ban in France...</title>
      <link>https://thestreetjournal.org/pornhub-four-other-sex-sites-face-ban-in-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thestreetjournal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pornhub and four other sites hosting sexually explicit content face a possible ban in France after the country’s media regulator said Tuesday it had filed a legal complaint against them. The sites were told in late 2021 that they needed to bring in a system that prevented children from viewing their videos. Under a new […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEST DRAMA: Spielberg, others grumbling about OSCARS changes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/steven-spielberg-isnt-only-director-000347723.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's big dogs are barking about changes to the Oscars, including best-picture nominees Steven Spielberg, Jane Campion and Denis Villeneuve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Now it's no mercy,' Ukrainian soldiers vow, as showdown nears...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/now-no-mercy-ukrainian-soldiers-223041610.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian troops in Irpin, on the outskirts of Kyiv, dig in as a long column of Russian tanks advances toward them. They vow to fight to the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civilian suffering intensifies as new Russian-Ukrainian talks fail to yield breakthrough...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/ap/international/civilian-suffering-intensifies-as-new-russian-ukrainian-talks-fail-to-yield-breakthrough/article_20312ff0-a248-5db9-9cec-dc27e6caab24.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine — A dozen days into a devastating war and a burgeoning refugee crisis, Russian forces on Monday launched withering new attacks on civilian areas and strategic centers in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs Russian Oil Ban as Gas Prices Surge and Ukraine War Grows...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/07/u-s-weighs-russian-oil-ban-as-gas-prices-surge-and-ukraine-war-grows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden came under increasing pressure on Monday to ban Russian oil imports into the United States, forcing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former California Gov. Jerry Brown living off grid in retirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-climate-biden-science-b7f4d8399218bdc4330305a913d56bb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILLIAMS, Calif. (AP) — Former California Gov. Jerry Brown is living off the grid in retirement, but he's still deeply connected on two issues that captivated him while in office and now are center stage globally: climate change and the threat of nuclear war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge set to question juror who convicted Ghislaine Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-entertainment-crime-jeffrey-epstein-alison-j-nathan-1e73604530ea5e4013545163f3970766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A U.S. judge was set Tuesday to question one of the jurors who convicted the British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell of helping the millionaire Jeffrey Epstein sexually abuse teenage girls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
