<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Feeling Sick? Googling Symptoms Actually Leads To Accurate Diagnoses!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dr-google-symptoms-accurate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers admit that “cyberchondria” has made the value of internet medical searches controversial in the eyes of many doctors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fought 'revenge porn' law...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/os-ne-matt-gaetz-revenge-porn-20210405-5qbme6ilzna3rhry6gzqeevwpq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While serving in the Florida Legislature, U.S. Rep. Matt Gaetz opposed a bill meant to stop people from sharing sexually explicit images of their ex-lovers because Gaetz believed that recipients of those images had a right to share them, according to the sponsor of the legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boehner Blasts Trump: Insurrection Happened Because of Bullsh*t He's Shoveling...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/john-boehner-destroys-trump-bloody-insurrection-happened-because-of-the-election-bullsht-hes-been-shoveling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times has obtained an early copy of former House Speaker John Boehner’s new book titled On the House: A Washington Memoir, which appears to include a number of critiques of members of his own Republican party. Perhaps most noteworthy? He blames former President Donald Trump for the deadly insurrection on the Capitol […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver eyes open-container 'entertainment districts' to boost restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/denver-entertainment-districts-open-container-alcohol-3d1d50fa-885c-4c8f-89c9-96b13940d10a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several other Colorado cities have adopted similar programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sought Blanket Pardon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/06/matt-gaetz-loyal-for-years-to-trump-is-said-to-have-sought-a-blanket-pardon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Matt Gaetz, Republican of Florida, was one of President Donald J. Trump’s most vocal allies during his term, publicly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU life expectancy drops across bloc...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-pandemics-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-covid-19-pandemic-8457898bffd5733e28eb9f566d54232c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Life expectancy across much of the European Union has dropped last year, as the 27-nation bloc struggled with the impact of the coronavirus pandemic. The EU statistical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ZOOM zombies' roaming streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90622296/potentially-deadly-zoom-zombies-are-roaming-the-streets-a-new-report-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-four percent of motorists who’ve driven their vehicles soon after using a videoconferencing platform report having trouble concentrating on the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon Sees Economic Boom Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/07/jamie-dimon-says-economic-boom-fueled-by-deficit-spending-vaccines-could-easily-run-into-2023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While he is bullish for the economy's immediate future, he sees serious challenges for the U.S., thanks to political and societal dysfunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arabs talk sex and taboos on Clubhouse app, but for how long?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210407105244-50r1w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and Ukraine on brink of war 'signals coming of Messiah' in 400-year-old prophecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/russia-ukraine-brink-war-signals-23867984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A famous rabbi made an eerie prediction in the 18th century that seems to mirror the rising tensions and military build-up between the two Eastern European nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Share of Dems Spikes After Biden Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/share-of-democrats-in-u-s-spikes-after-biden-win-poll-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Share of Democrats in U.S. Spikes After Biden Win, Poll Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan says may shoot down Chinese drones in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210407091802-1vqza</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTHCHINASEA-TAIWAN/:Taiwan says may shoot down Chinese drones in S.China Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods Crash Caused By Speed; Many Unanswered Questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/04/07/tiger-woods-crash-investigation-report-results-revealed-lasd-golf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods' car crash was caused by excessive speed, but there may be more to the story that we may never know ... TMZ has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood actor arrested in $227-million Ponzi scheme...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-actor-arrested-alleged-227-230903207.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Zach Avery forged Netflix and HBO emails in sweeping fraud, the FBI says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil prostitutes strike for first-line shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-prostitutes-strike-first-line-012522147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prostitutes in the city of Belo Horizonte in southeast Brazil have gone on strike for a week, demanding to be included in the group of front-line workers receiving priority coronavirus vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Passports' advance despite growing controversy...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-vaccine-passports-advance-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the United States' vaccination campaign accelerates, so-called vaccine passports are gaining traction despite political divisions and a fragmented health care system that complicates the centralization of data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wilderness Explorers Straining Search and Rescue...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/07/pandemic-wilderness-explorers-are-straining-search-and-rescue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PINEDALE, Wyo. — Kenna Tanner and her team can list the cases from memory: There was the woman who got</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis officers line up to reject Chauvin's actions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trials-minneapolis-death-of-george-floyd-racial-injustice-322955cf7a62c1f8aaf9fa2bc6732d20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — The parade of Minneapolis police officers rejecting a former officer’s actions in restraining George Floyd continued at his murder trial, including a use-of-force instructor who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders of RussiaChina tighten grips, grow closer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-world-news-xi-jinping-moscow-coronavirus-pandemic-9b38a8258305a016e7fd819b532f9c77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — They're not leaders for life — not technically, at least. But in political reality, the powerful tenures of China's Xi Jinping and, as of this week, Russia's Vladimir Putin are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half new infections in just 5 states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nearly-half-us-coronavirus-infections-come-from-5-states-53888dc78894cc76cb1bb50f8300f102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of new coronavirus infections nationwide are in just five states — a situation that is putting pressure on the federal government to consider changing how it distributes vaccines by...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite technology puts into orbit swarms of spacecraft no bigger than loaf of bread...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Satellite-technology-puts-into-orbit-swarms-of-16080556.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The avalanche was a stunning disaster, 247 million cubic feet of glacial ice and snow...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump White House provided reporters with gusher of leaks. Everything's changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/entertainment/article/The-Trump-White-House-provided-reporters-with-a-16080772.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - After 2 1/2 months of Joe Biden's presidency, something is missing from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINUTES' STANDS BY DESANTIS 'PAY FOR PLAY' INVESTIGATION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/60-minutes-stands-by-controversial-publix-report-says-desantis-presser-comments-were-cut-for-clarity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is standing by a 60 Minutes report about vaccine distribution in Florida after it was widely panned on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 survivors suffer mental, neurological problems...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/third-covid-survivors-suffer-neurological-223000621.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in three COVID-19 survivors in a study of more than 230,000 mostly American patients were diagnosed with a brain or psychiatric disorder within six months, suggesting the pandemic could lead to a wave of mental and neurological problems, scientists said on Tuesday. Researchers who conducted the analysis said it was not clear how the virus was linked to psychiatric conditions such as anxiety and depression, but that these were the most common diagnoses among the 14 disorders they looked at. Post-COVID cases of stroke, dementia and other neurological disorders were rarer, the researchers said, but were still significant, especially in those who had severe COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires club grows to 2,755 during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/billionaires-club-grew-by-nearly-a-third-to-2755-during-pandemic/ar-BB1fmcYV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos, with a fortune of $177 billion, tops the Forbes ranking for the fourth year running, followed by Elon Musk at $151 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British public want WILLIAM to be King in blow to Charles...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/public-want-prince-william-king-23864734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Pollsters Deltapoll interviewed 1,590 adults and found a generational divide with over who should take the throne - while younger people even call for rebel Harry to become king</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality show would send winner to space!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/space-hero-tv-show-43396966-f4c8-4ebb-a377-bc067e7f1907.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The competition will focus on testing the participants' physical and mental strength in preparation for spaceflight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit will send workers door-to-door to urge...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wwjnewsradio/news/local/detroit-will-send-workers-door-to-door-to-urge-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Detroit, still struggling with the coronavirus, plans to send workers door-to-door to encourage residents to get the vaccine. “We will knock on every residential door in the city of Detroit.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy medic shoots 2, is shot and killed on base...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/04/06/frederick-active-shooter-fort-detrick-2-injured-shooter-down-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI-led investigation is underway into why a Navy medic shot two sailors near Fort Detrick Tuesday morning. The suspect, 38-year-old Fantahun Girma Woldesenbet, was shot and killed when he drove onto the base past a security checkpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon ramps up attacks: 'Not defeated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/6/pentagon-ramps-attacks-resurgent-isis-it-not-defea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is ramping up its war against an enemy declared “territorially defeated” two years ago, fueling questions about whether the U.S. and its allies have the right long-term strategy to truly crush the Islamic State terrorist group once and for all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF office vacancy hits all-time high, surpassing dot-com bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/realestate/article/SF-office-vacancy-high-rent-dropping-16081154.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;S.F. office rental prices have steadily fallen over the past year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Supports Infrastructure Bill, Corporate Tax Hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/amazons-jeff-bezos-supports-infrastructure-bill-corporate-tax-hike/ar-BB1fmErr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. Chief Executive Officer Jeff Bezos said he supported investing in U.S. infrastructure and a hike in the corporate tax rate to help pay for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation of Islam Calls Member Who Killed Capitol Cop 'Brother With Such Great Potential'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/latest-news/nation-of-islam-calls-member-who-assaulted-u-s-capitol-brother-with-such-great-potential/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nation of Islam said it is investigating what caused one of its followers to stage a deadly assault against U.S. Capitol police last week, calling the deceased attacker a "brother with such great potential" who could have been a "star in the mission of the resurrection of our people." The group distanced itself from …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant owners clash with Rome police in lockdown protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-rome-italy-coronavirus-pandemic-097446c7734ee7e5a9af960b6e7e30e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italian restaurant owners and others angry at having their businesses shut for weeks due to a virus lockdown clashed with police Tuesday during a protest outside Parliament in Rome,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family sues after man dies in taco-eating contest...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article250448501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit accuses the event organizers of not doing enough to warn amateur competitors about the risks of choking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another prominent GOOGLE scientist leaving company...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/06/googles-samy-bengio-is-leaving-amid-fallout-from-ai-researcher-firing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the highest ranking team member to resign after AI researcher Timnit Gebru's was fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas becomes first state to trans treatments, surgery for kids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-arkansas-legislature-legislation-asa-hutchinson-dce1d5ca9450b255caabc18f547f7b9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas lawmakers on Tuesday made the state the first to ban gender confirming treatments and surgery for transgender youth, enacting the prohibition over the governor's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Persona non grata in Trumpworld'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/06/trump-matt-gaetz-lifeline-479126</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressman was a MAGA fixture. Now, engulfed in scandal, he’s persona non grata in Trumpworld.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers Wants To Host 'JEOPARDY!' -- While Still Playing In NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/aaron-rodgers-has-a-crazy-plan-qb-explains-how-he-could-host-jeopardy-full-time-while-still-playing-in-nfl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Packers quarterback wants to hold two full-time jobs and here's how he would make it work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA considering joining boycott of 2022 Beijing Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/06/us-considering-joining-boycott-of-2022-beijing-olympics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan University First To Offer Cannabis Chemistry Scholarship...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/michigan-lake-superior-state-university-cannabis-chemistry-scholarship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chemistry program claims to be the first in the country that focuses specifically on cannabis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tearful Deshaun Watson accuser shakes when she recalls 'sex assault'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2648706/deshaun-watson-first-accuser-ashley-solis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE FIRST woman to accuse Texans quarterback Deshaun Watson of sexual assault identified herself on Tuesday as massage therapist Ashley Solis. During a press conference in Texas, Solis tearfully sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State experiences 3rd-driest year...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/california-reports-third-driest-year-on-record/927591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impacts will be felt in state reservoirs after precipitation was measured at only 50% of average for the 2021 water year, and as wildfire season looms, the drought conditions could spell danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Claims Victory Over USA as New Nuke Talks Begin...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-claims-victory-over-united-states-as-new-nuke-talks-begin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian officials are claiming victory over the United States as diplomats gather this week for negotiations over a revamped nuclear deal, discussions that are likely to result in the Biden administration lifting tough economic sanctions on the Islamic Republic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen diagnosed with Guillain-Barre syndrome after first dose...</title>
      <link>https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2021/04/05/local-teen-diagnosed-with-guillain-barre-syndrome-questions-covid-19-vaccine-after-receiving-first-dose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.click2houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wyatt McGlaun, a teenager in The Woodlands, said he got Guillan-Barre syndrome a few weeks after his first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRAZENECA trial on children paused...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/uk-trial-of-oxford-covid-jab-on-children-paused-as-regulator-probes-blood-clots-in-adults-12267780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trial of the Oxford-AstraZeneca COVID vaccine on children in the UK has been paused while the medicines regulator investigates a possible link between the jab and rare blood clots in adults.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Wall of Silence Crumbling...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/society/chauvin-police-testimony/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For one of the first times in memory, police are testifying against one of their own. But will it lead to an actual conviction?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House rules out involvement in passports...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/546705-white-house-rules-out-involvement-in-vaccine-passports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Jen Psaki on Tuesday ruled out the Biden administration playing any role in a vaccine passport system as Republican governors in particular balk at the concept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell warns biz off political speech; 'Stupid'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-politics-mlb-baseball-voting-rights-3560226607d89796a8123a2c19da5348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your 'smart home' is watching  --  and possibly sharing your data with police...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/apr/05/tech-police-surveillance-smart-home-devices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart-home devices like thermostats and fridges may be too smart for comfort – especially in a country with few laws preventing the sale of digital data to third parties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump got evicted from 'the swamp.' Some of his people are trying to stick around...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-got-evicted-from-the-swamp-Some-of-his-16080470.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are plenty of fish in the swamp, but some of the best-connected ones live in a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has NFT Bubble Popped Already?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/04/nft-crypto-bubble-trading-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An average NFT sold in April is 70% cheaper than in late February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's death surge set to pass worst of USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210406124116-x41eq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Hill:  Gaetz Defended Me When My Nudes Were Shared Without Consent. Now He's Accused of Doing It!</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/04/katie-hill-on-matt-gaetz-needing-to-resign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt and I forged an unlikely friendship in Congress, and he was one of the few colleagues who spoke out after a malicious nude-photo leak upended my life. But if recent reports are true, he engaged in the very practice he defended me from—and should resign immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand opens up travel bubble with Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/new-zealand-opens-up-travel-bubble-with-neighboring-australia/ar-BB1flYNw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand Prime Minister Jacinda Ardern warned people to prepare for their travel plans to be disrupted if there is a coronavirus outbreak in either country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to Announce EVERY American Vaccine Eligible...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-president-biden-to-announce-every-american-will-be-vaccine-eligible-2-weeks-earlier-tout-150-million-shots-in-1st-75-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House confirmed that President Joe Biden will announce he’s moving up the timeline for states to make every American adult eligible for a coronavirus vaccine by two weeks, and will tout 150 million vaccinations in his administration’s first 75 days. On Tuesday, President Biden is scheduled to visit the vaccination site at Virginia […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Cyber Group Launches Cloud, Chat Platforms...</title>
      <link>https://www.hstoday.us/subject-matter-areas/cybersecurity/isis-cyber-group-launches-cloud-chat-platforms-to-close-ranks-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hstoday.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Taste of freedom' for Germans amid controversial reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taste-freedom-germans-amid-controversial-095457862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beer lovers and fitness fanatics braved sleet and snow to return to restaurants and gyms Tuesday as the small German state of Saarland began a controversial easing of coronavirus restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF:  GLOBAL GROWTH SET FOR RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-economic-growth-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-95c0c07f39af685fac274df73738f61a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The rollout of COVID-19 vaccines and vast sums of government aid will accelerate global economic growth to a record high this year in a powerful rebound from the pandemic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Alcee Hastings, after career of triumph, calamity and comeback, dies at 84...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-alcee-hastings-civil-right-impeached-judge-congress-obituary-20210406-lnjgt4hokrh3zdzacufao4erqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressman Alcee Hastings died Tuesday. The South Florida congressman, who was 84, made history in many ways — positive and negative. He was a civil rights lawyer in 1960s and '70s Fort Lauderdale. He was Florida's first Black federal judge, and was later impeached and removed. He was part of the first Black members of Congress from Florida since Reconstruction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land seizures, 'unethical' research: University of Minnesota confronts troubled history with tribes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/land-seizures-unethical-research-university-of-minnesota-confronts-troubled-history-with-tribes/ar-BB1flPLn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS — Every time Kevin DuPuis steps foot in the rugged red pine forest just west of Cloquet, Minnesota, he's reminded of the painful truth that this slice of land within the borders of the Fond du Lac Reservation does not belong to his tribe. For more than a century, the 3,400-acre stretch has been home to the University of Minnesota Cloquet Forestry Center, a research outpost on land ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Israel's king, Benjamin Netanyahu, been dethroned?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/has-israels-king-benjamin-netanyahu-been-dethroned-664243</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister has a lot of problems to deal with right now: vaccines, Iran, Jordan, the coalition – and of course, his corruption trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired WALMART worker drives car through store...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/fired-walmart-worker-drives-car-through-store-cops-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fired Walmart employee crashed a car through the front door of the store and kept driving inside the building, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Cook Wants Americans to Vote on Their IPhones!</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/apple-ceo-tim-cook-on-voting-technology-iphones-smartphones-2021-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We do our banking on phones. We have our health data on phones," Tim Cook said before asking "why not" expand voting tech to smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police crowdfunded K-9's hospital bills  -- before admitting they had shot him!</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/04/05/police-shot-k9-dog-arlo-gofundme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cops in Thurston County, Washington, made no such efforts to support the recovery of the man they shot and who had to be hospitalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There are no perfect defenses against shark bites. But wearable tech might help...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/there-are-no-perfect-defenses-against-shark-bites-but-wearable-tech-might-help-researchers-say/ar-BB1flH4G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say it's crucial to find better shark-deterring technology that saves humans from bites without harming an already-vulnerable species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friend with George Floyd on day of arrest to appear in murder trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/friend-george-floyd-day-arrest-122900221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A seventh day of testimony is on tap in the Derek Chauvin murder trial, but the jurors will not be present when a witness to George Floyd's arrest speaks in court Tuesday. Morries L. Hall was with Floyd on that night late last spring, when Floyd was apprehended by police outside a corner store in south Minneapolis and pinned on the pavement under an officer's knee until dying. Hall has said he ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Injured In Shooting Near MD Army Base; Sailors Involved...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/04/06/2-injured-in-active-shooter-incident-in-frederick-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frederick Police are on the scene of an "active shooter" in the 8400 block of Progress Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Mykonos, Greece's Famed Party Island, 'Everyone About to Explode'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mykonos-greeces-famed-party-island-084758695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisa Gouliamaki/AFP via Getty ImagesThe narrow, stone-paved alleys on the traditional village of Oia, in Santorini, are usually packed with tourists even this time of the year. The Greek island with the most famous sunset view in the world is always a top travel destination. But COVID-19 put the growing popularity of the Greek islands on hold in 2020 and even though the warm Mediterranean weather means the tourist season in Greece usually starts in early April and lasts until late October, the streets are relatively quiet.With vaccination continuing worldwide, though, and the convenience of rapid tests, Greece is opening up to international travelers May 14, after almost a year, and hopes to recapture its past success. And business owners on two of its most famous islands, Santorini and Mykonos, are expecting the reopening to go with a bang. Giorgos Dimitrokalis wakes up everyday looking at the magnificent view of the caldera, and although he was born and raised in Santorini, this view of the Aegean Sea never ceases to amaze him. But for the owner of KD Hotels and Resorts and vice president of the Santorini Hoteliers Association, it’s hard to be the only one to enjoy this view. “It feels like a completely different island. Unrecognizable. Last year we were joking that the locals had the chance to enjoy the island for themselves. I hope this summer, things will go back to as it was before the pandemic, because the island has really suffered."Unlike other places in Greece, islands such as Santorini and Mykonos base the majority of their economy on tourism. In 2019, tourism was a little more than 20 percent of the country’s overall economy , according to the Institute of the Greek Tourism Confederation. It was the best year in a decade.And then, coronavirus came. A view of Oia on the island of Santorini, Greece. Alkis Konstantinidis “It was summer outside, but the people out in the streets were as many as if it was winter. There was not even a soul out there. It was surreal,” says Poly Linoxylaki, owner of the Sand Lily boutique at Imerovigli in Santorini.Desperate not to lose another year, the Greek minister of tourism, Harry Theoharis, announced recently that the government will reopen tourism in Greece from May 14.There are two types of tourists who visit Santorini, explains Dimitrokalis, who owns 10 hotels all around the island: “At the hotels that are close to the beach, we’ve seen a more increased interest so far this year. Our customers there stay for around seven days, are usually families, and most of them Europeans. At the more central hotels, like the ones at Caldera and Fyra, are usually travelers who come from overseas, such as Americans, Brazilians, Chinese, and Australians, and they usually stay for no longer than three days. They come to see the island, admire the sunset, and leave.”For Embark Beyond, a luxury travel advisory company based in New York, “Greece and Turkey may be the only European countries open this summer” for Americans, and because of that they suggest to their clients to “reserve now, before the flood gates open and it’s too late."“What we’ve been told is that the international flights to Greece for tourism will be open from everywhere in the world on May 14. We are just waiting for the officials to tell us what the protocols for this year will be” says Dimitrokalis, who points out that Americans are among the biggest fans of the island.“Most tourists who visit Santorini are from the U.S. and Australia, and if they won’t be able to come for some reason, I will have a big trouble” says Linoxylaki, who sells clothes and accessories, mostly made by Greek designers. “These are my customers. They support small businesses like mine."During this time of the year the reservations for summer would normally be at around 70-80 percent, but according to Dimitrokalis, today the number is down to 25-30 percent. “We hope that next month more people will be interested and we expect that by the end of the season we might be able to reach around 50 percent of 2019. We are putting our hopes in last-minute reservations to reach our goal,” he says.Most of the reservations are starting from mid-summer, but everyone is optimistic. “If the weather is good we expect to expand this year’s season, because we are already losing the first three months” says Dimitrokalis, and that is something Linoxylaki agrees, even though she has her doubts about the reopening: “We are hoping that September and October will be the peak of this season. But I must be honest, I personally don’t believe that we will be able to open up on May 14, as the government said.”Similar to Santorini, most of the Greek islands suffered their share too last year. Among them, Mykonos, the popular Cycladic island with the bright white houses and wild nightlife.When Kim Kardashian and her family traveled to Mykonos in 2013 to film the eighth season of Keeping Up with the Kardashians, Kim was pregnant with North and the island was full with paparazzi… and lots of tourists. Overview of the Chora of Mykonos at sunset. Demetrios Ioannou Today Iraklis Zisimopoulos, CEO of the Semeli Hospitality Group who hosted the Kardashian family and their crew almost a decade ago, looks back at those days with some nostalgia, but with confidence for the future. “I am sure that they will come back again; coronavirus won’t last forever. It might not be this year, but we see that the dynamic of Mykonos is not lost and we are sure that even better days will come” he says.Zisimopoulos is also the general secretary of the Mykonos Catering and Entertainment Association, as well as the president of the Association of Businesses and Professionals of Mykonos Town. “I have hotels, restaurants, bars, clubs, and everything is shut down,” he says with a bitter smile.Speaking to the Athens News Agency last September, Konstantinos Koukas, the mayor of the island, said that last season they reached only 30 percent of 2019, and as Zisimopoulos explains: “Last year was catastrophic, but we hope this year will be different. It definitely won’t be anywhere close to a normal season, but for sure it won’t be like 2020."The most important role in shaping that will be the protocols under which tourists will be able to enter Greece. “So far we know that there are three options: 1) The people who have been already vaccinated, 2) Those who have tested negative the last 48 hours, and 3) Those who have already been sick and now have the antibodies” says Zisimopoulos, a doctor himself.When it comes to Mykonos though, people don’t travel to the island just for the nice view or to swim in the crystal clear blue sea. They go because they want to have fun and everyone has only one thing on mind… the nightlife!Mykonos is known worldwide as the “party island” of Greece and a land where you can openly be who you are. Anastasios Kapetanias contributed as much as anybody to this reputation. For the director and founder of XLSIOR Festival, the only gay music festival in Greece and among the top five in the world, last year was the first time that he had to cancel it, since it was first launched in 2009. But he has high hopes for this summer.“People are thirsty for fun” he says. “We receive lots of emails everyday from people begging us to do the festival this year. They tell us ‘we need to see our friends; we need to feel free again’. Everyone is about to explode; we can’t take it any more."For the Greek government, nightlife isn’t a top priority and will be one of the last things to open, and under which terms is yet unknown. But for the local economy, this is a huge blow. XLSIOR alone brings to the island more than 30,000 people every summer from all around the world. “We have people coming from the U.S., Brazil, Spain, Israel, and most of them are people who come every year”, explains Kapetanias, who also cooperates with several local businesses like hotels, rent-a-cars, restaurants etc. to assist his clients.“Last August when the government decided to close all bars and clubs at midnight, all reservations stopped and many canceled,” says Zisimopoulos. The whole situation was completely surreal, as Kapetanias describes it: “People were all around the streets, looking for some villa parties to go and everyone was hiding as if we were in a war. This is not Mykonos." One of the windmills overlooking the Chora of Mykonos. Demetrios Ioannou The Greek government decided to vaccinate all residents on small islands, with under 1,000 population, with some of the first COVID-free islands in Greece including Kastellorizo and Oinousses,Could a similar plan work for Mykonos, with around 10,000 people? Zisimopoulos is confident it would fix many of their problems: “If all the locals get vaccinated, whatever happens to the island, we will have a strong protective shield. In a normal season, we would have at least 10 reservations per day. Now the maximum is 2. The last 20 days we’ve seen some movement and we have some reservations from the U.K., Israel, and the U.S., where the vaccination goes faster. Most of those reservations are for July and August."Kapetanias, on the other hand, suggests that a good idea for the reopening of live festivals like his could be the rapid tests. “They could go to a clinic on the island earlier on the same day, do the test and if it is negative they could come with the results and enter. We just need to be super organized, so the people will be completely safe."And even though no one knows for sure how this summer nightlife will be like, the engines on the island are on and everyone is organizing, hoping they won’t have to cancel again. “Because of the situation we will be able to organize events in dreamy places, where other years it wasn’t possible. This year most of our events will be outdoors as well. Of course we will also be bringing the best DJs, musicians and dancers that we know our audience loves,” Kapetanias says about this year’s event, which has already been announced for August 18-25.“It will be a year in which we will get a big part of our life and vacations back, and because we have been deprived of so many things this past year, it will make us feel so much better. I really believe there is hope on the horizon,” says Zisimopoulos. Kapetanias concurs: “To be honest, what I want for this summer is to see happy people, who will be laughing, having fun, being safe and would want to come back again next year."Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANY SKIP SECOND DOSE</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/public-health-experts-urge-americans-to-not-skip-2nd-vaccine-dose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The overwhelming scientific evidence shows that both doses offer the best protection against COVID-19, according to experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian joins club...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/04/06/kim-kardashian-is-officially-a-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Not bad for a girl with no talent.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen Confederate monument will become 'toilet' unless 'White Lies Matter' demands met, group vows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/activist-group-white-lies-matter-holds-jefferson-davis-monument-hostage/ar-BB1flbon?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group is not asking for money, but for the United Daughters of the Confederacy to display a banner with a quote by Assata Shakur, "The rulers of this country have always considered their property more important than our lives."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former CIA director was skeptical about aliens until friend's aircraft 'paused at 40,000ft'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9439137/Former-CIA-chief-says-hopes-friendly-dealing-creatures-exist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Woolsey, CIA director under Bill Clinton, on Friday said that he had a new 'openness' to the possibility of alien life, and told how a source he respected said his plane was stopped at 40,000ft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny 'seriously ill'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/06/alexei-navalny-seriously-ill-on-prison-sick-ward-says-lawyer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian opposition figure has fever, cough and has lost weight, according to legal team member who visited him</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
