<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/mass-shooting-reported-at-gaming-tournament-in-florida/17797704/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Jacksonville, Florida, said there were “multiple fatalities” at a mass shooting Sunday at a bar that was hosting a live gaming event during which 12 gunshots could be heard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/26/multiple-fatalities-reported-mass-shooting-games-tournament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four people were reported dead and eleven injured in a &amp;quot;mass shooting&amp;quot; at a pizza restaurant in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED LASER DOT ON PLAYER</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-shooting/multiple-fatalities-in-shooting-at-video-game-tournament-in-florida-sheriff-idUSKCN1LB0M7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a mass shooting at a video game tournament that was being streamed online from a restaurant in Jacksonville, Florida, on Sunday, and the local sheriff's office said there were multiple fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 killed, 11 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-authorities-report-mass-shooting-riverfront-mall-184200664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSONVILLE, Fla. (AP) — Florida authorities are reporting a multiple people dead and "many transported" to hospitals after a mass shooting at a riverfront mall in Jacksonville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS SHOOTING IN JACKSONVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/news/shooting-at-jacksonville-landing-leaves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources say at least eleven people have been shot and four are dead after a shooting at the Jacksonville Landing Sunday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUGHT ON VIDEO</title>
      <link>https://streamable.com/scgs6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;streamable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 DEAD AT ONLINE GAMING TOURNAMENT</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6100355/Four-dead-10-injured-mass-shooting-Florida-Madden-online-gaming-tournament.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mass shooting has been reported at the Jacksonville Landing in Florida on Sunday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shooting at Jacksonville, FL  waterfront... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.firstcoastnews.com/article/news/local/mass-shooting-at-the-jacksonville-landing-multiple-fatalities/77-587766926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.firstcoastnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jacksonville Sheriff's Office is on the scene of a mass shooting at the Jacksonville Landing, multiple fatalities have been reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump won't be present at service...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6100001/Donald-Trump-returns-golf-course-17-hours-John-McCains-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has remained very quiet about the Arizona Republican senator's death, drawing criticism after he posted a meager tweet with his condolences for the McCain family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral speakers expected to include Bush and Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/presidents-lawmakers-laud-mccain-devotion-country-043543645--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two former presidents are expected to speak at Sen. John McCain's service and he will lie in state in both the nation's capital and Arizona as part of a cross-country funeral procession ending with his burial at the U.S. Naval Academy, according to plans taking shape Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Begs for God's forgiveness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-hold-giant-mass-dublin-abuse-victims-rally-030337491.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis "begged for God's forgiveness" on Sunday for multiple abuse scandals within the Irish church but faced accusations by a former Vatican official that he had personally ignored allegations against senior clergy. In front of 45,000 supporters at the rain-soaked Knock shrine in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu warns Jews still under threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netanyahu-warns-jews-still-under-threat-162231736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's prime minister said on Sunday that Jews were still at risk even decades after the Holocaust as he wrapped up a groundbreaking visit to Lithuania, a Baltic state once home to his forefathers. Not the attempts to destroy us, they still seek to destroy us," Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/former-us-nuncio-pope-francis-knew-of-mccarricks-misdeeds-repealed-sanction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an explosive testimony, Archbishop Viganò reveals Francis repealed sanctions on McCarrick imposed by Pope Benedict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Vatican Ambassador Says Warnings Ignored...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pope-francis-knew-of-abusive-priest-claims-former-vatican-official-carlo-maria-vigano/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Pope Francis must be the first to set a good example to Cardinals and Bishops who covered up McCarrick's abuses and resign along with all of them," writes a former Vatican ambassador to Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Aren't Talking Impeachment But Are Vowing Probes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/26/democrats-aren-t-talking-trump-impeachment-but-are-vowing-probes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Aren't Talking Trump Impeachment But Are Vowing Probes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico to Reach NAFTA Deal Soon as Monday...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/26/u-s-mexico-said-poised-to-reach-nafta-deal-as-soon-as-monday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S., Mexico Said Poised to Reach Nafta Deal as Soon as Monday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern District of New York Will Tear Into Organization...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2018-08-26/southern-district-of-new-york-will-tear-into-trump-organization</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBSHELL: Pope Accused of Covering Up for Abusive Priest...</title>
      <link>http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/ex-nuncio-accuses-pope-francis-of-failing-to-act-on-mccarricks-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ncregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a written testimony, Archbishop Carlo Maria Viganò claims Pope Francis withdrew sanctions against Archbishop Theodore McCarrick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug used in VIAGRA linked to record 19 UK deaths...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6099689/Viagra-drug-linked-record-19-UK-deaths-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sildenafil, the active drug in Viagra, caused more than a dozen deaths in 2017 and is currently linked to seven fatalities this year, according to a report by the MHRA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Officials Worried About Containing Latest Ebola Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/health-officials-worried-about-containing-latest-ebola-outbreak-1535290631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world has never been so prepared for an Ebola outbreak, but the latest emergence of the virus in the Democratic Republic of Congo’s conflict-ridden east is proving the most dangerous in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rookie NY firefighter claims sexually assaulted first day...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/25/i-was-sexually-assaulted-by-fdny-firefighters-on-my-first-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A black FDNY rookie says he was “terrified” that a fellow firefighter would rape him after a homoerotic hazing by naked Bravest, explosive court papers reveal. Firefighter Gordon Springs, 28, said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree falls on reporter during broadcast...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/tropical-storm-lane-hurricane-tree-falls-reporter-13182841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reporter's dispatch from then-Hurricane Lane in Hawaii got a startling interruption when a tree fell on him mid-broadcast on Friday, according to the BBC.  James Cook was delivering an update on the storm's path when nature had other ideas.  "The latest forecast suggest the eye will skirt the Big Island in around 12 hours time before brushing past Maui on its way to O'ahu," Cook can be heard saying in the broadcast, when he is interrupted by a loud series of cracking and rustling noises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea newspaper blasts 'double-dealing' USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/north-korea-newspaper-blasts-double-dealing-u-s-after-pompeos-trip-canceled-idUSKCN1LB0BY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea's state-controlled newspaper on Sunday accused the United States of "double-dealing" and "hatching a criminal plot" against Pyongyang, after Washington abruptly canceled a visit by Secretary of State Mike Pompeo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER power outage stuns Dodger Stadium... </title>
      <link>https://www.sbnation.com/mlb/2018/8/26/17782998/dodger-stadium-power-outage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sbnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The power went out at Dodger Stadium in the 12th inning of a game between the Dodgers and Padres. Lots of things surrounding the 20-minute delay were odd, and it wasn’t even the first power outage at Chavez Ravine this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More floods threaten as storm drifts away...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tropical-storm-lane-threatens-more-hawaii-floods-turns-000833018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service (NWS) lifted all remaining tropical storm warnings and watch advisories for Hawaii as trade winds finally began to nudge Lane off to the west. Civil defense officials on the Big Island said more rain and flooding were also possible there, and a high-surf advisory was posted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No grass': Europe livestock sector stricken by drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/no-grass-europes-livestock-sector-stricken-drought-031300962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris (AFP) - "Our cows have been living off hay cut in June, there isn't any grass," says Jean-Guillaume Hannequin, a farmer in eastern France, who like his counterparts across much of northern Europe is wondering how he will feed his animals this winter. Mediterranean countries long</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR driver loses sponsorship over father's racial slur in 1980s...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/sports/motor/2018/08/24/eli-lilly-pulls-sponsorship-conor-daly-nascar-ride-road-america-racial-slur-derek-daly/1089166002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conor Daly is making his NASCAR debut this weekend at Road America, but will do without the decal of his main sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Mogul Key Suspect in Venezuela Corruption Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article217285655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Swiss banker who admitted guilt is helping Miami, Florida prosecutors build a criminal case against Raúl Gorrín, owner of the Globovisión network in Caracas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  FERRARI Sells for Record $48.4 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/2018/08/26/rare-ferrari-250-gto-sells-for-record-48-4-million-at-auction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A red 1962 Ferrari 250 GTO sold for $48.4 million on Saturday in California, the most ever paid for a classic car at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Anchor Busted for Two Fake 'Scoops' in Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/nolte-cnns-jim-sciutto-busted-for-two-fake-news-scoops-in-one-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief national security correspondent Jim Sciutto has had two big scoops debunked as very fake news in the space of just one week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot-Made Burgers Wow Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/08/24/640511068/fad-or-the-future-robot-made-burgers-wow-the-crowds-in-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more culinary robots find their way into commercial food prep, one restaurant in San Francisco called Creator is hoping to strike a balance between high tech and the human touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels vows to testify before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/stormy-daniels-vows-testify-donald-13139717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The porn star who pulled out of Celebrity Big Brother at the 11th hour reveals what happened on THAT night she met the future US President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL PREVIEW:  TWITTER Boss Dorsey to Testify Before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/twitter-chief-jack-dorsey-to-testify-before-congress-in-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter chief executive Jack Dorsey will testify before the House Energy and Commerce Committee regarding his company’s censorship practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Predicts Mueller Will Indict Don Jr...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/roger-stone-donald-trump-jr-mueller-indict-process-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-time Republican operative Roger Stone predicts special counsel Robert Mueller will soon indict Donald Trump Jr. on a process crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tavis Smiley Stumbling in Lawsuit Over PBS Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/tavis-smiley-stumbling-pbs-lawsuit-1137134</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ousted anchor can't force PBS to hand over internal documents dating back decades and two of his claims have been dismissed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawless London: Fearful residents building barricades around homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/725636/notting-hill-carnival-london-acid-attack-barricades-homes-shops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reactions to passing...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/what-theyre-saying-reactions-to-mccains-passing-a2ed4475-e760-4b3a-9b76-704a507b4d0d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former rivals are remembering him as a patriot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HAPPYTIME' KILLED AT BOXOFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/melissa-mccarthy-happytime-murders-crazy-rich-asians-meg-weekend-box-office-1202451694/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4TH UPDATE, Saturday AM Writethru following Friday 11:46PM: Warner Bros.’ Crazy Rich Asians is flat out doing amazing this weekend with an unprecedented $25M, which is an unbelievable -6% dip…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titan of American politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/john-mccain-unbridled-titan-american-politics-004555441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Sidney McCain III had but one employer throughout his iconic and tempestuous career: the United States of America. McCain was a direct descendant, he claimed, of a captain in George Washington's army during the Revolutionary War. McCain ejected, and parachuted into a small lake in the center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Cameos Caused Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2005/07/31369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz. Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., is defending his cameo appearance in “Wedding Crashers,” the sexy comedy the Drudge Report called a “boob raunch fest.” “In Washington, I work with boobs every day,” joked McCain during an appearance on NBC’s “Tonight Show with Jay Leno.” McCain was responding to Leno, who noted Matt […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  Amid betrayals, Trump's barrier breaks down... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amid-betrayals-Trump-s-barrier-breaks-down-13182773.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's wall of secrecy - the work of a lifetime - is starting to crack. His longtime lawyer, Michael Cohen, pleaded guilty last week to breaking campaign-finance laws, and said he'd arranged hush money payments to two women at Trump's direction. Both a tabloid executive - who had served Trump by snuffing out damaging tales before they went public - and Trump's chief financial officer gave testimony in the case. All three had been part of the small circle of family, longtime aides and trusted associates who have long played crucial roles in Trump's strategy to shield the details of his personal life and business dealings from prying outsiders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama beat McCain by two-to-one electoral college margin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/john-mccain-senate-maverick-arizona-dead-at-81-brain-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, his Senate office said he died at 4:28 p.m. on August 25, surrounded by his wife Cindy and his family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Last of the American heroes'...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/792175/john-mccain-last-american-heroes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The indomitable Arizona senator is dead at 81. We may never see his like again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashed with media...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2007/12/mccain-responds-to-drudge-007499</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John McCain denies that he did legislative favors for a lobbyist, says campaign didn't try to spike story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane's Rains Topple Records, Inundate Parts of Big Island ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Lanes-Rains-Topple-Records-Inundate-Parts-Big-Island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rainfall amounts topped 40</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-45276831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a historic visit to Ireland, Pope Francis reportedly condemns abuse in the Church as "filth".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35-year political career...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a8ae4ebb24f4fc5b60381e81fae1249/War-hero-and-presidential-candidate-John-McCain-has-died</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. John McCain, who faced down his captors in a Vietnam prisoner of war camp with jut-jawed defiance and later turned his rebellious streak into a 35-year poli</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie praises Dem move to limit role of superdelegates...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/403601-sanders-praises-decision-to-limit-role-of-superdelegates-after-2016-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) praised a move by the Democratic National Committee (DNC) on Saturday to limit the role of superdelegates in choosing the party's presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarred but Happy Warrior... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/25/opinion/john-mccain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He could be frustratingly inconsistent, but he also bucked orthodoxy time and again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiercely independent... </title>
      <link>https://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Politics/2018/0825/Remembering-John-McCain-the-quintessential-patriot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.csmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Monitor reporters share their interactions with and observations on the Arizona senator and his lifetime of service – including his wry humor, famous temper, and bipartisan striving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senator No One Could Ignore...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/view/2018/08/26/john-mccain-the-senator-no-one-could-ignore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senator No One Could Ignore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
MCCAIN DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/sen-john-mccain-independent-voice-gop-establishment-dies-81-n790971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His family announced that McCain died Saturday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
