<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sailors say US sub has been ravaged by bed bugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bedbugs-aboard-a-navy-sub-is-making-life-uncomfortable-crew-says/ar-BB1euCxd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sailors worry that being kept awake by bug bites could lead to a maritime accident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Action Role-Playing Love Triangle Ends in Pipe Bomb Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/live-action-role-playing-love-triangle-ends-in-pipe-bomb-attack/ar-BB1euBZi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A love triangle among competitors in a medieval combat role-playing game inspired a gruesome pipe bomb attack last fall, according to a new federal indictment. Clayton Alexander McCoy, of Ohio, was charged Thursday in federal court with allegedly trying to blow up his romantic rival last October, leaving the man with extensive injuries and serious burns. The allegedly lovelorn bomber was an avid member of the Dagorhir live action role-playing or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGETOWN prof fired for saying black students 'at bottom of her class'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9350921/Georgetown-investigates-professor-saying-black-students-bottom-class.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgetown Law is investigating a video posted to the school's database of professors Sandra Sellers and David Batson in which Sellers claims black students are always bottom of class.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEEP unveils $111,000 SUV...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/11/jeep-unveils-long-awaited-grand-wagoneer-suv-topping-111000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Grand Wagoneer SUV will test whether Jeep can expand its product range into the lucrative luxury segment and attract new customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groundwork for possible impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/11/nys-assembly-speaker-lays-groundwork-for-possible-cuomo-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The speaker of the New York state Assembly on Thursday asked that its Judiciary Committee open an investigation into Gov. Andrew Cuomo — the first step in potentially drafting articles of imp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 'big one' coming, quake alert system launches in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-washington-oregon-japan-earthquakes-85941f7b479f3f0dce8349d27f25613f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALEM, Ore. (AP) — People in Oregon will be better prepared for earthquakes — particularly important in the Pacific Northwest because experts say “the big one" is coming — as an early warning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Defense Secretary: He Started the Riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx83v4/even-trumps-defense-secretary-during-the-capitol-riot-blames-him-for-inciting-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Acting Secretary of Defense Chris Miller told VICE on Showtime he believes Trump’s speech caused the violent mob to attack the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cuomo allegation referred to police... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cuomo-allegation-potential-crime-mansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police Thursday received word from the governor's own office that New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo may have been involved in an incident that could be a crime. The report was made by the New York State Executive Chamber as a matter of protocol in cases involving physical contact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pact with the Press...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/q-and-a/harry-meghan-and-the-pact-between-the-royals-and-the-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British writer and campaigner Anthony Barnett says the royal controversy is evidence of a country in crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer Spills Entire Plot to Murder Investigative Journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/killer-spills-the-entire-plot-to-murder-investigative-journalist/ar-BB1euGgQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Maltese man who was hired as a lookout to keep tabs on Panama Papers journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia before she was killed in October 2017, told a court he and her killers argued over whether to assassinate her with a rifle at close range—they ultimately decided was “too noisy”—before settling on a bomb, because it was “cleaner.” Vincent Muscat ‘il-Koħħu,’ who is serving a 15-year-sentence after pleading guilty for his role in Galizia’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why $4-a-Gallon Gas May Be Coming This Summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/why-4-a-gallon-gas-may-be-coming-your-way-this-summer/ar-BB1etgvW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — Even as oil and gasoline prices rise, industry executives are resisting their usual impulse to pump more oil out of the ground, which could keep energy prices moving up as the economy recovers. The oil industry is predictably cyclical: When oil prices climb, producers race to drill — until the world is swimming in petroleum and prices fall. Then, energy companies that overextended themselves tumble into bankruptcy. That...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Gen C, the Covid generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/11/us/covid-generation-gen-c/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have started to use a new term -- Gen C, or Generation Covid -- to describe how the lives of today's children could be shaped by the pandemic far into the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cuomo Accusation Referred to Albany Police... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/11/nyregion/cuomo-groping-accusation-albany-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The police characterized the alleged groping by the governor of a female aide as something that may rise “to the level of a crime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distracted Guard, Gate Malfunction Allowed Intruder to Board Aircraft at Andrews...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2021/03/11/distracted-guard-gate-malfunction-allowed-intruder-board-aircraft-joint-base-andrews.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force says a series of missteps at Joint Base Andrews, Maryland, led to a Feb. 4 breach at the installation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy warships head huge international fleet in show of force against Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/royal-navy-warships-head-huge-23688157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavily-armed Type 23 frigates HMS Lancaster and Westminster join military forces from nine northern nations in a show of force against countries threatening Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cesar Millan wants to help Biden's dogs feel at home in White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/cesar-millan-wants-to-help-bidens-dogs-feel-at-home-in-the-white-house-11615482315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former 'Dog Whisperer' tells MarketWatch his tips for helping pups like Major adjust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah mom dies four days after second dose of Moderna vaccine... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://kutv.com/news/local/utah-woman-39-dies-4-days-after-2nd-does-of-covid-19-vaccine-autopsy-ordered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kutv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (KUTV) &amp;mdash; During a KUTV investigation into COVID-19 vaccine side effects and where to report them, we found four reported deaths, filed by Utah families and their caregivers to the CDC&amp;rsquo;s Vaccine Adverse Effects Reporting System. Caption: KUTV: Heidi Hatch reports One case stood out, a 39-year-old single mom from Ogden who died four days after her second dose of the Moderna COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen has SEVENTH meeting with Manhattan DA as Trump investigations ramp up...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/michael-cohen-has-seventh-meeting-manhattan-da-trump-investigation-ramps-n1260548</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting comes as the sprawling investigation into the former president's taxes and finances intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVER THE ANGER:  Stacey Dash, After Washing Out at FOXNEWS, Has Now Turned On Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/stacey-dash-after-washing-out-at-fox-news-has-now-turned-on-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress and former Fox News pundit Stacey Dash walked back her previous support of Donald Trump -- apologizing for her past behavior and "mistakes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DONALD FACING ARREST?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/16/trump-faces-criminal-civil-investigations-after-white-house.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump was acquitted at his Senate impeachment trial. But he still faces potential legal liabilities in a number of probes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: Black Americans Most Concerned Compared To Whites, Hispanics...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/black-americans-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report finds Black Americans actually stand out from other groups as the most concerned about the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Sen. Harry Reid Discusses UFOs, Alien Threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/podcasts/2021/03/critical-update-lets-talk-about-ufos/172536/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s behind unidentified aerial phenomena observed by military officials? Are we alone in the universe? Nextgov asks some experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon and senior members of military call out Tucker Carlson for mocking women serving in armed forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/11/media/tucker-carlson-mocks-military-women/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior members of the US military took to Twitter late Wednesday and Thursday to call out Fox News host Tucker Carlson for a sexist segment in which he mocked women serving in the armed forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY A HUG!</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/colorado-covid-hugs-senior-living/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic seniors who live in group communities, like assisted living, will be able to physically embrace their loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Marathon Bomber Sues Over Treatment In SuperMax Prison...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/boston-marathon-bomber-dzhokhar-tsarnaev-sues-over-treatment-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tsarnaev claims the defendants are interfering with his ability to talk to his family and hurting his chances of avoiding a death sentence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red-state bills to stop online censorship could BACKFIRE, conservative lawyers warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/red-state-online-censorship-could-backfire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican legislation meant to stop censorship on social media platforms could backfire and result in less conservative speech and a number of onerous lawsuits that will hamstring their goals, conservative lawyers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN! EUROPE COVID CASES ROCKET 50%...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2491566/europe-waits-vaccines-pioneers-western-covid-third-wave-eu/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EU countries are waiting for vaccines like “pioneers in a Western movie” as new Covid cases surge by 50 per cent, Italian media says. The rocketing number of infections across the conti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 feet?</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/weather/weather-forecast/major-snowstorm-on-track-for-this-weekend-with-bullseye-in-the-foothills-thursday-morning-update/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The weekend snowstorm is still on track. We are forecasting fog/sun early today then a 20% chance of a rain/snow shower in Denver and across the Front Range. Highs will be in the 40s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrewd and sharp, empathetic and disarming: How Oprah interview went from must-see TV to cultural phenomenon...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/Shrewd-and-sharp-empathetic-and-disarming-How-16017854.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A telephone ringing at 4:30 in the morning is rarely good news, so television executive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fremont, Fargo Happiest Cities...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/03/11/survey-fremont-happiest-residents-in-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a time when Fremont was best known as the home of the Tesla auto plant, but according to a new survey it also may just be the happiest place to live in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Jaded Techies Find Hero in Musk...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/11/chinas-jaded-techies-find-a-hero-in-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is having its techlash moment. The country’s internet giants, once celebrated as engines of economic vitality, are now scorned</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Eyes September Return to Offices...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cnn-back-to-office-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zucker told global staffers Thursday that Atlanta employees will return to the office Aug. 1 and other employees will return Sept. 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital artwork sells for record $69 million at CHRISTIE'S first NFT auction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/digital-artwork-sells-record-60-million-christie-s-first-nft-n1260544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first purely digital work sold by an established auction house brings blockchain into the world of fine art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal Ball Sitting In Window Reflects Sunlight Onto Couch, Causes Major House Fire...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/03/10/crystal-ball-causes-house-fire-near-wisconsin-dells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crystal ball didn't predict a fire in Wisconsin -- but it did start one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burglar caught over bite from German's sausage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/statutes-france-germany-burglary-crime-9d1386976208e91b98913bcc2c02d97a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German police say they have solved a nine-year-old burglary after DNA found on a half-eaten piece of sausage matched that of a man detained in France over an unrelated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving Joel Silver: The Twisted Saga That Entangled Ari Emanuel, Ron Meyer, Anthony Pellicano, MBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/saving-joel-silver-the-twisted-saga-that-entangled-ari-emanuel-ron-meyer-anthony-pellicano-and-even-mohammed-bin-salman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the former power producer couldn't settle his beef with Canadian billionaire Daryl Katz, a who's who of industry players became embroiled in the feud. The question is, why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14-hour days and no bathroom breaks: AMAZON's overworked delivery drivers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/14-hour-days-no-bathroom-100050909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers report being underpaid and having to urinate in bottles in their vehicles to keep up with delivery rates An Amazon delivery driver loads a van outside of a distribution facility on 2 February 2021 in Hawthorne, California. Photograph: Patrick T Fallon/AFP/Getty Images Sign up for the Guardian Today US newsletter James Meyers worked as a driver for several Amazon delivery service providers in Austin, Texas, for about one year until he quit in October 2020 citing the immense workloads and poor working conditions. Fourteen-hour shifts were common because delivery service providers wouldn’t allow drivers to return any packages from their routes and the pressure to meet delivery rates meant Meyers used a plastic bottle to go to the bathroom on a daily basis. “I saw no effort on Amazon’s part to push delivery service providers to allow their drivers to use the restroom on a normal human basis, leading many, myself included, to urinate inside bottles for fear of slowing down our delivery rates,” Meyers said. “Any time a van is off route or stops for longer than three minutes, it notifies the delivery service provider. Amazon encourages the delivery service owners to cut down on said stops. I would personally get called by a dispatcher every time I stopped to go to the bathroom. Sitting on the phone with them made the stop take longer. It just wasn’t worth the angry looks in the morning or the worry I’d get fired.” Amazon uses contractors for delivery services, a move Meyers said makes it exceedingly difficult for workers to organize, and he said, contributes to drivers being overworked and underpaid by the delivery service providers who are paid bonuses on metrics such as route completion percentages. Amazon has been publicly opposed to unionization and organizing among their employees, most recently through an anti-union campaign launched ahead of a union election vote at a warehouse in Bessemer, Alabama, which has included anti-union captive audience meetings and sending mass texts and ads to workers encouraging them to vote against the union. The Teamsters Union is now working to organize drivers at Amazon delivery service providers around the US over concerns about the retail giant’s impact on the transportation industry and use of subcontractors. An Amazon delivery driver pushes a cart of groceries to load into a vehicle outside of a distribution facility on 2 February 2021 in Redondo Beach, California Photograph: Patrick T Fallon/AFP/Getty Images “This sort of model is problematic for the entire industry,” said Randy Korgan, the director of the Teamster’s Amazon Project. “They’re willing to loan these small subcontractors money, get them access to their vans and help them advertise for employees to offload all the responsibility that would normally fall on Amazon.” The Teamsters currently represent pilots at two Amazon air transport contractors. Korgan said the wages Amazon delivery drivers receive, starting at $15 an hour, are far below the average wages for drivers at companies like UPS, where Teamsters represent about 240,000 workers. Based on the union’s current contract, UPS drivers start at $21 an hour and can make up to $40 an hour or more. “If Amazon decides to take millions of jobs and essentially cut their labor costs in half, that only comes out of workers’ pockets,” added Korgan. “That creates a major economic problem in an industry that for the last 50 years has done a good job of supporting millions of middle-class jobs.” In Iowa, the Des Moines Register reported the Teamsters are organizing drivers and warehouse workers at Amazon for higher pay and less stringent rates, utilizing strikes rather than focusing on union elections through the National Labor Relations Board. Drivers for Amazon contractors have complained of the surveillance and pressure they receive through cameras and a tracking app, Mentor. A driver for an Amazon delivery service provider in the Portland, Oregon area, who requested to remain anonymous for fear of retaliation, expressed concerns over the surveillance cameras being installed in delivery vehicles, as she often has to use the bathroom in the van due to the lack of available public restrooms and pressure against taking time off of routes to use them. “In order to take a bathroom break, especially being a woman, we would have to be in an area that has a grocery store. That isn’t always the case and even if it were, that would take at least 10 minutes off our drive time, in which our dispatch would wonder why we’re falling behind,” she said. “So instead, I keep a cup with me and wipes and I go to the bathroom in the back of my van. I’m very concerned about the AI technology being installed in the vans, and being seen while I am urinating is just one of my concerns.” Drivers for Amazon delivery service providers also face fear of retaliation for trying to organize in their workplaces. Derrick Flournoy worked as a driver for an Amazon Delivery Service Provider in Downers Grove, Illinois, for more than one year before he quit after experiencing retaliation from management for organizing an online chat for workers to discuss grievances on the job such as the lack of pay increases. Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk have gone back and forth every week about who is the wealthiest person in the world and I can’t even pay my rent Derrick Flournoy “I started the chat group on a Friday morning, and about an hour after the chat group was put up the manager took it down, which we didn’t even know that he had the power to do if he wasn’t included in the chat, and then he also disabled my ability within the entire app to even communicate with anybody, unless it was directly with management,” said Flournoy, who filed an unfair labor practice charge through the Amazon Delivery Drivers Coalition against Amazon after he was removed from his work shift immediately after the incident. “To me, it was obvious retaliation, and it was his way of showing that he had power and if we didn’t basically form a model of who he wanted, that he could take our hours.” Flournoy made $16 an hour, which remained unchanged from when he started in December 2019 to when he left in February 2021, even as a 40-hour full-time work week wasn’t guaranteed. “Sixteen dollars an hour isn’t enough for the amount of work that we have to do. We’re a representation of the wealthiest company in the world and we’re barely making enough money to live,” Flournoy added. “I just think that it’s crazy to me that Jeff Bezos and Elon Musk have gone back and forth every week about who is the wealthiest person in the world and I can’t even pay my rent. I’m breaking my back to deliver packages every day and there’s no compassion from upper management to understand or to listen to drivers’ concerns.” An Amazon spokesperson claimed drivers have built-in time through their routes for breaks and provide a list of nearby restrooms in the delivery app. They did not comment on the unfair labor practice charge or on organizing efforts by drivers. “We’re proud to empower more than 2,000 delivery service partners around the country – small businesses that create thousands more jobs and offer a great work environment with pay of at least $15/hour, healthcare benefits, and paid time off,” the spokesperson said in an email.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Keeping Vaccines Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2021/03/covid-vaccine-secrecy/618253/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 vaccinations have become a public spectacle, but they touch intensely private questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince William defends royal family against racism claims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-prince-harry-london-oprah-winfrey-prince-william-52698fca3307c802d7d8f6a4be60a074</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Prince William defended Britain's monarchy Thursday against accusations of bigotry made by his brother, Prince Harry, and sister-in-law, Meghan, insisting the family is not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious shaking again rattles San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/public-safety/story/2021-03-10/mysterious-shaking-again-rattles-san-diego-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents from Rancho Bernardo to Chula Vista to El Cajon reported feeling and hearing a shaking and boom in an event similar to one from Feb. 16</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREPS VICTORY LAP</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-prepares-nationwide-victory-lap-to-promote-his-rescue-plan/ar-BB1etfVS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden got his giant coronavirus stimulus bill. Now, he wants to make sure he gets credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans leaving home more than before pandemic, cellphone data shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Americans-have-started-leaving-home-even-more-16017279.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have begun leaving home more often than before the coronavirus pandemic took...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will coronavirus ever go away?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-98ae7fbfdc457425dae47efb38139db2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Will the coronavirus ever go away? No one knows for sure. Scientists think the virus that causes COVID-19 may be with us for decades or longer, but that doesn’t mean it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO still struggling to manage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-pandemics-geneva-coronavirus-pandemic-china-2c173926c95ed3769107c7eaa043fa86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — When the World Health Organization declared the coronavirus a pandemic one year ago Thursday, it did so only after weeks of resisting the term and maintaining that the highly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals buckle in absence of plan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brazil-rio-de-janeiro-health-coronavirus-pandemic-jair-bolsonaro-04931a387c7fb128266235635a1422a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Brazil’s hospitals are faltering as a highly contagious coronavirus variant tears through the country, the president insists on unproven treatments and the only attempt to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're going to lose fast': Air Force war game with Chinese biological attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/were-going-to-lose-fast-us-air-force-held-a-war-game-that-started-with-a-chinese-biological-attack-170003936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many foreign affairs and national security experts believe the global pandemic has accelerated trends that were already pushing the U.S. and China toward a potential confrontation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks his moment with pandemic address...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/542648-biden-seeks-his-moment-with-pandemic-address</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is being urged to combine his well-known empathy with some positivity Thursday night when he makes a primetime address on the anniversary of when much of the country went into lockdown because of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron urged to rethink 'private' vaccine stance...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lebron-urged-rethink-private-vaccine-204653996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James has been urged to reconsider his refusal to confirm whether or not he will take the Covid-19 vaccine after comments which underscored apprehension amongst NBA players over the new coronavirus drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil posts new record of 2,000 deaths in day...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-covid-deaths-top-2-213419542.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil registered a record 2,286 deaths from Covid-19 in the past 24 hours, the health ministry said Wednesday, as a worrying surge pushed the figure past 2,000 for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula blasts 'imbecile' Bolsonaro for mishandling pandemic, economy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310205605-pf6um</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/LULA (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Brazil's Lula, Bolsonaro fire starting gun on 2022 presidential race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of websites offline after fire at French cloud services firm...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210310183756-alpef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-OVH/FIRE (UPDATE 4, PIX):UPDATE 4-Millions of websites offline after fire at French cloud services firm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett Becomes Sixth Member of $100 Billion Club...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/warren-buffett-becomes-sixth-member-214145924.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Warren Buffett has been a fixture at the top of the world’s wealth rankings for decades, but in recent years he’s slipped down the list as tech fortunes soared and his hot hand cooled.Now, at 90, his net worth has blown past $100 billion.The Berkshire Hathaway Inc. chairman’s wealth jumped on Wednesday to $100.4 billion, according to the Bloomberg Billionaires Index, making Buffett the sixth member of the $100 billion club, a group that includes Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk and his friend Bill Gates.The group’s combined wealth has grown rapidly, fueled by government stimulus, central bank policy and the surging equity market. On Wednesday, President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion Covid-19 relief bill cleared its final congressional hurdle as the House voted to approve the legislation, adding to the $3 trillion or so in stimulus Washington has already disbursed in the past year.Berkshire Hathaway, the source of virtually all of Buffett’s wealth, has had a good start to 2021. The firm’s A shares are up 15% this year, outpacing the 3.8% gain of the S&amp;P 500 Index. That’s been helped by Buffett’s recent push to spend record amounts buying back Berkshire’s own stock, a notable shift for an investor who previously preferred to use the $138 billion cash pile to buy other businesses or common stocks.Share BuybacksBuffett’s been struggling in recent years to find sizable deals to spark Berkshire’s growth, partially due to the sheer size of the conglomerate. That’s caused the business to underperform the S&amp;P 500 over the past five years. But last year, Buffett spent a record $24.7 billion on buybacks and filings indicate he’s already bought at least $4.2 billion worth of stock through mid-February.Read more: Berkshire’s Busy 2020 Broke a Record Despite No Major Deals Surpassing $100 billion is all the more notable considering how much the Omaha billionaire has given away. A co-founder of the Giving Pledge, a campaign to encourage billionaire philanthropy, Buffett has donated more than $37 billion in Berkshire stock since 2006. Without those gifts, which have cut his holdings of Berkshire Class A shares nearly in half, he’d be worth more than $192 billion.The staggering amount of wealth accumulated by the ultra-wealthy -- $1.8 trillion by the world’s 500 richest in 2020 alone -- highlights the K-shaped recovery that’s taking shape as the U.S. emerges from the pandemic. While millions of disproportionately poor, working-class and minority people remain unemployed, wealthy Americans have seen incomes and net worth levels rise thanks to a buoyant stock market and rising home prices.Meanwhile more than 8 million Americans -- including many children -- fell into poverty in the second half of last year, according to an analysis by University of Chicago economist Bruce Meyer, University of Notre Dame’s James Sullivan and Zhejiang University’s Jeehoon Han.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marks end to four decades of Reaganism?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/mar/10/joe-biden-covid-relief-bill-passed-analysis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: Reagan’s presidency undermined faith in government. The stimulus package helps restore FDR’s legacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive camera hack exposes growing reach and intimacy of surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Massive-camera-hack-exposes-the-growing-reach-and-16016067.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one video, a woman in a hospital room watches over someone sleeping in an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entertainers discuss disbelief and despair that took over when covid shut down their world...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/entertainment/article/Entertainers-discuss-disbelief-and-despair-that-16015711.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe you were at the Metropolitan Opera House in New York, taking in a matinee of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT criticizes Tucker Carlson for attacking journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-york-times-issues-rare-statement-slamming-tucker-carlson-for-calculated-and-cruel-criticism-of-taylor-lorenz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times responded Wednesday to Fox News host Tucker Carlson's comments about one of its reporters, Taylor Lorenz, who had issued a plea to support women facing online harassment late Tuesday, in connection with International Women's Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARLER denied by App Store again...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/parler-blocked-apples-app-store-211138243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Parler, the controversial conservative social media app, was denied re-entry to Apple Inc.’s App Store recently after it was kicked off the platform in the wake of the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, documents obtained by Bloomberg show.On Wednesday, Parler LLC cut its three remaining iOS developers, according to a person familiar with the matter. The company eliminated seven workers in total, most of whom were contractors. The other staff worked on Parler TV and quality assurance, said the person, who asked not to be identified discussing private matters.When it initially removed Parler from the App Store in January, Apple asked the social network to change its moderation practices. Apple said that Parler’s new community guidelines, released when the service came back online Feb. 15, were insufficient to comply with the App Store rules.“After having reviewed the new information, we do not believe these changes are sufficient to comply with App Store Review guidelines” Apple wrote to Parler’s chief policy officer on Feb. 25. “There is no place for hateful, racist, discriminatory content on the App Store.”Apple included several screenshots to support the rejection. Some screenshots, reviewed by Bloomberg, show user profile pictures with swastikas and other white nationalist imagery, and user names and posts that are misogynistic, homophobic and racist.“As you know, developers are required to implement robust moderation capabilities to proactively identify, prevent and filter this objectionable content to protect the health and safety of users,” Apple added in its letter to Parler, a copy of which was obtained by Bloomberg.“In fact, simple searches reveal highly objectionable content, including easily identified offensive uses of derogatory terms regarding race, religion and sexual orientation, as well as Nazi symbols,” Apple wrote “For these reasons your app cannot be returned to the App Store for distribution until it complies with the guidelines.”Parler’s community guidelines were written by Chief Policy Officer Amy Peikoff, according to two people familiar with the matter. Parler did not immediately respond to a request for comment on Wednesday.Read more: Parler Reboot Is Driven by Ayn Rand Devotee and Never TrumperParler went offline following the riot at the U.S. Capitol. Amazon Web Services cut ties with Parler, and Google and Apple removed Parler from their mobile app stores. The Parler website relaunched in February with support from cloud hosting company SkySilk Inc.(Updates with description of screenshots in fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megayacht-Racing Billionaires Invading NZ in Guise of 'Essential Workers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-megayacht-racing-billionaires-invading-new-zealand-in-the-guise-of-essential-workers/ar-BB1esCrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In case you weren’t aware, a select club of billionaires from around the world—with their superyachts in tow—have descended upon Waitematā Harbour in Auckland, New Zealand to resume one of their favorite activities: watching a bunch of guys race big, fast boats back and forth across an invisible line. It’s a bit like NASCAR for rich people. These billionaire owners were lucky enough to receive special “essential service worker exemptions” to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia China moon base plan sparks fears of space race...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/russia-chinas-joint-moon-base-23668748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The Russia China moon-pact 'could lead to all kinds of security threats' with British and American forces playing catch up by boosting military forces capable of fighting battles against future enemies in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record taxes, record spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/trifecta-federal-taxes-spending-and-deficit-all-set-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal taxes, federal spending and the federal deficit all set records in the first five months of fiscal 2021 (October through February), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geraldo Considering Ohio Senate Run...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-geraldo-rivera-says-hes-considering-a-senate-run-in-ohio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would Geraldo Rivera run for Senate?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican leader fears 'Migrant President' Biden will spark boom time for cartels...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9347257/Migrant-president-Joe-Biden-stirs-angst-boom-time-gangs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's government is worried the new U.S. administration's asylum policies are stoking illegal immigration and creating business for organized crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run for TX gov now 'real consideration,' Matthew McConaughey says...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/politics/run-for-tx-gov-a-real-consideration-mcconaughey-says/10403383/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star actor and proud Texan didn't give a hard no late last year, but that was before criticism with current lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
