<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO: 80% WILL GET VIRUS; NINE MONTH CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/574277/new-york-cuomo-slams-groups-crisis-could-last-nine-months/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW York Governor Andrew Cuomo has warned that 80% of New York state’s population could become infected with the coronavirus and said the crisis could last as long as nine months. Cuomo’s sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'no need' to postpone November vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-says-e2-80-98no-need-e2-80-99-to-postpone-november-vote-over-virus/ar-BB11yfHo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tylenol, soup and internet can treat most symptoms of COVID-19 [whether you have it or not]...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/tylenol-soup-and-the-internet-can-treat-most-symptoms-of-covid-19-whether-you-have-it-or-not/ar-BB11yfoQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Rate May Soar to 30%... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/us-jobless-rate-may-soar-to-30-25-fed-e2-80-99s-bullard-says/ar-BB11y3ER</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ gov. vows to 'take action' against people who don't stay home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gov-murphy-vows-action-to-enforce-nj-stay-at-home-order</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy expressed anger Sunday at reports of people in New Jersey ignoring his stay-at-home order and warned “We're going to take action."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Govt uses Bluetooth to track exposure...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/singapore-coronavirus-big-brother-bd7cec2b-eb47-4b49-a337-f4f4ecff57f2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore is tracing the coronavirus in ways that are simultaneously impressive and terrifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna calls virus the great equalizer in bathtub video...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/22/madonna-calls-coronavirus-the-great-equalizer-in-bizarre-bathtub-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 61-year-old singer preaches to her fans from her tub, surrounded by candles and wearing nothing but jewelry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Nobel laureate predicts a quicker recovery: 'We're going to be fine'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-nobel-laureate-predicts-quicker-210318391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nobel laureate predicted China's recovery weeks before it happened. Analyzing the numbers, he sees a much brighter global outcome than many experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200323001838-oqzqs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VENEZUELA:Venezuela prohibits company layoffs and suspends credit collections over coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLYMPICS ON THE BRINK</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/team-canada-says-wont-participate-020548863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The COC and CPC urgently call on the International Olympic Committee (IOC), and the International Paralympic Committee (IPC) and the World Health Organization (WHO) to postpone the Games for one year and we offer them our full support in helping navigate all the complexities that rescheduling the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel in quarantine... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f71e89eacd7cc6f84b81991c03e82c31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel has gone into quarantine after being informed that a doctor who administered a vaccine to her has tested positive for the new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen.  Rand Paul Tests Positive... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3db22a242e9577126052dece8285d2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. Rand Paul of Kentucky has tested positive for the novel coronavirus, becoming the first case of COVID-19 in the Senate and raising fears about the further transmission of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: Public places stand abandoned...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/af7b4e94c6c0b86f6d35f4c79be99cf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are places meant for people. New York’s Grand Central Terminal — a common metaphor for “busy” in much of the English-speaking world — dotted with only scattered commuters. The Grand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC trying to keep crowds from cherry blossoms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5720c07cc92db122d5f2e147c02b1063</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As signature cherry blossom trees go through peak bloom in the nation's capital, officials in the District of Columbia are resorting to mass street closures to keep large crowds...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEINSTEIN TESTS POSITIVE IN PRISON</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/03/coronavirus-harvey-weinstein-positive-test-prision-1202889800/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein has tested positive for the novel coronavirus in prision. Just days after being transferred to the Wende Correctional Facility from NYC’s Rikers Island, the Oscar winning producer …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The week that America changed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a82294fc0723630d850603dd7b016ad5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Change came to the United States of America during the third week of March in 2020. It did not come all at once, though it came quite rapidly. As had happened in other lands, there was no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White supremacists encouraging members to spread coronavirus to cops, Jews...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/white-supremacists-encouraging-members-spread-coronavirus-cops-jews/story?id=69737522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alert was sent to local police agencies by federal officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felony charge for woman who coughed in paramedic's face and shouted, 'I have coronavirus'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/coronavirus-cougher-971235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARCH 22--A woman arrested for assaulting her boyfriend shouted “I have the coronavirus” before intentionally coughing in the face of a paramedic who she sprayed with “copious amounts of saliva,” pol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man falls to death from NYC apartment during isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/man-falls-death-16th-floor-21735275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters working on dailystar.co.ukwill be working to source the latest information, reaction, pictures and video related to this story</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel in quarantine... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/22/chancellor-angela-merkel-in-quarantine-after-contact-with-doctor-who-tested-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel will be tested regularly over the coming days and will continued to conduct her duties as chancellor from home, her spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen.  Rand Paul Tests Positive... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rand-paul-coronavirus-847b3df1-92bc-4ee6-833b-952d16f3ee3f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's the first U.S. senator to test positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia invokes 'fake news' law...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/20/russia-invokes-fake-news-law-to-order-removal-of-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian media outlets faced penalties Friday after federal regulators invoked the nation’s newly enacted law against “fake news” to censor reports about the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ seeks new emergency powers; Detain people indefinitely without trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/21/doj-coronavirus-emergency-powers-140023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the requests to Congress would allow the department to petition a judge to indefinitely detain someone during an emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says USA 'created coronavirus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/coronaviurs-irans-supreme-leader-says-21733354  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ayatollah Ali Khamenei's outburst came during a televised speech about the crisis, during which he branded it "strange" that America would offer to help while it struggles with the crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Designated Survivor plan' if Boris falls sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/coronavirus-downing-st-draws-up-21733861  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab, who is also First Secretary of State, will stand in for the PM if necessary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED READY WITH $4 TRILLION</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-fed-will-make-up-to-4-trillion-in-loans-to-businesses-to-rescue-economy-mnuchin-says-2020-03-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin said Sunday that the Federal Reserve will play a key role in lending funds to businesses hurt by the coronavirus pandemic....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor in Italy: We no longer help those over 60...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/International/Israeli-doctor-in-Italy-We-no-longer-help-those-over-60-621856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli medical doctor Gai Peleg told Israeli television that in northern Italy the orders are not to allow those over 60 access to respiratory machines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESTING STILL BOTCHED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ad73b37c17d0b73197535b5b836b38a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Drive-thru sites have been opening around the United States to make it quicker and safer to test people for the new coronavirus. But much like the rest of the U.S. response...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebels defy mandates with coughs, 'corona parties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/22/coronavirus-rebels-defy-mandates-coughs-corona-par/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young German adults hold “corona parties” and cough toward older people. A Spanish man leashes a goat to go for a walk to skirt confinement orders. From France to Florida to Australia, kitesurfers, college students and others crowd the beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of cases may be 'silent carriers', classified Chinese data suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/3076323/third-coronavirus-cases-may-be-silent-carriers-classified</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 43,000 people in China had tested positive without immediate symptoms by the end of February and were quarantined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hottest Parties in Town Now Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news/the-hottest-parties-in-town-are-now-online/ar-BB11wffr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Catholic Church Bells To Ring 5 Times A Day As Call To Prayer...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/03/21/chicago-catholic-church-bells-to-ring-5-times-a-day-as-call-to-prayer-during-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic church bells will be ringing throughout Chicago every three hours as a call for all to unite in prayer during the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Writes to Kim Jong-un Offering Help in Virus Fight, NKorea Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-writes-to-kim-jong-un-offering-help-in-virus-fight-north-korea-says/ar-BB11wg3x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC officials publish guide to intimacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8138777/New-York-City-officials-publish-graphic-guide-getting-intimate-coronavirus-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYC Health issued a two-page memo Saturday listing its advice on how people can enjoy a - literally - healthy sex life while still protecting themselves from being infected with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE NEGATIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/olivianiland/mike-karen-pence-coronavirus-test-staffer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president got tested after a staffer came up positive. The White House encouraged Americans who are not displaying symptoms to not be tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy's worst-hit region announces stricter measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-51991972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4,825 people have died in Italy since the coronavirus outbreak began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems grow nervous over delays...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/488685-democrats-grow-nervous-over-primary-delays</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are increasingly nervous about the coronavirus pandemic upending the Democratic primary calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll companies trying to cash in...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/21/naturally-antibacterial-sex-doll-companies-trying-to-cash-in-on-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex doll companies have an important public service message: Self-isolating can be fun and safe at the same time. Abyss, the maker of sex robots RealDolls, assured potential buyers that its dolls a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air quality picking up in quarantined countries...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/air-quality-picking-quarantined-countries-094306534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air quality is improving in countries under coronavirus quarantines, experts say, but it is far too early to speak of long-term change. Images by the US space agency NASA are clear, in February the concentration of nitrogen dioxide (NO2) fell dramatically in Wuhan, China, the epicentre of the COVID-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspired By Italy, Dallas Residents Sing From Apt Windows...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/coronavirus-live-updates/2020/03/21/819603870/inspired-by-italy-dallas-residents-sing-together-from-their-apartment-windows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an act of solidarity amid social distancing and the coronavirus pandemic, residents of a Dallas apartment complex leaned out of their windows to sing "Lean on Me."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran leader refuses US help, citing conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e5f39091afda3b07a70464e602d844ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — The arrival of the coronavirus in the Gaza Strip, an impoverished enclave where the health care system has been gutted by years of conflict, raised fears Sunday the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to quarantine all arrivals to state for 14 days...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a9267e5e23aa5cd66b1d407e13550e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii's governor has instituted a mandatory 14-day self-quarantine starting Thursday of all people traveling to the state as part of efforts to fight the spread of coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea praises Trump for coronavirus outreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/22/north-korea-donald-trump-letter-offers-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump sent a personal letter to North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, seeking to maintain good relations and offering cooperation in fighting the viral pandemic, Kim’s sister said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUSTRALIA SHUTS DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8139579/Australia-SHUTS-Scott-Morrison-orders-restaurants-pubs-close-TOMORROW.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister met with state and territory leaders on Sunday night to discuss further measures to stem the spread of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-ins enjoy sales boom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/south-korea-drive-cinemas-enjoy-sales-boom-over-053925730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A long queue of cars forms in front of a drive-in cinema in Seoul, as South Koreans look for safer spaces to enjoy a movie without the risk of contracting the coronavirus raging across the world. Box office numbers in South Korea -- which has 8,897 confirmed virus cases -- have plummeted in recent weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus advances around the world as medical supplies dwindle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/86ca5e1f6032314115176190c380818d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOAVE, Italy (AP) — Italy, Iran and the United States reported soaring new death tolls as the coronavirus pandemic marched relentlessly across the globe Sunday, prompting a scramble in hard-hit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas also at risk from coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ccca2d0e218411cb6b8aa8d60f8357c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KAMPALA, Uganda (AP) — As the coronavirus infects more people around the world, conservationists are warning of the risk to another vulnerable species: Africa's endangered mountain gorilla....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could peak in 32 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-york-surgeon-warns-coronavirus-015200406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the hospital system at risk of being overwhelmed, Dr. Craig Smith issues a warning: &amp;quot;The hard data has become alarming.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Who lives and who dies': Crisis to test medical ethics
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/03/22/coronavirus-crisis-medical-ethics-guide-decisions-doctors-cant-help-all/2882738001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals might not have enough ventilators to care for coronavirus patients. Ethics could guide doctors' decisions on who gets care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain deploys robots that 'test 80,000 patients a day'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/spain-deploys-coronavirus-robots-test-21733020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Spanish government is planning to test 80,000 patients a day using robots in a bid to fight against the coronavirus outbreak ravaging the country following a surge of cases</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
