<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Florida man arrested, refused to remove obscene sticker from vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://www.wptv.com/news/state/florida-man-arrested-after-refusing-to-remove-obscene-sticker-from-window</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wptv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sheriff's office says a deputy pulled Webb over in Lake City because of a sticker that crudely described his sexual appetites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Royal Baby Makes First Public Appearence...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9026078/meghan-markle-prince-harry-royal-baby-sussex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN Markle and Prince Harry have today beamed as they introduced their “amazing” baby boy to the world – but teased the world by not revealing his name. The new parents appeare…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Person Mired In Boredom 131 Days A Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/no-fun-americans-mired-boredom-131-days-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling bored all too often lately? It seems that many of us might need to get out a bit more and inject some fun into their lives. A survey of 2,000 Americans finds that for the average adult, more than a third of their year is spent mired in boredom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Stern Reveals Cancer Scare, Trump Regrets and Details of New Book...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/howard-stern-reveals-cancer-scare-trump-regrets-details-a-dishy-new-book-1208773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a health crisis that had him "scared  s—less," the $90 million-a-year radio legend opens up about retirement, the one time he lied to his listeners and his metamorphosis from shock jock to insightful interviewer: "I'd feel really f—ing s—ty if I hadn't evolved."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania school drops 'God bless America' after pledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/pennsylvania-school-drops-god-bless-america-after-pledge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pennsylvania school principal will no longer say "God bless America" after leading students in the Pledge of Allegiance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waters' moment in power: Confronting Trump, inspiring Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/12ddaca673d24c05b508932ebd5761b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — She's been called "Kerosene Maxine" and gaveled off the House floor for accusing Republican men of badgering women. She dismissed President Donald Trump and his allies as thugs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER drivers protest around world ahead of IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/08/uber-drivers-strike-over-low-wages-benefits-ahead-of-ipo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers are also expected to stage protests against Uber and Lyft in at least eight cities around the U.S., including New York, Chicago and San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly One in Two Americans Takes Prescription Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2019/05/08/nearly-one-in-two-americans-takes-prescription-drugs-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly One in Two Americans Takes Prescription Drugs: Survey</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax the Rich and More: 2020 Dems Plan New Levies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-08/tax-the-rich-and-more-a-guide-to-potential-democratic-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure builds for FTC to punish Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/442618-pressure-builds-for-ftc-to-punish-zuckerberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pressure is growing for federal regulators to hold Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg personally accountable for his company’s string of privacy scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC faces new debate minefield...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442622-dnc-faces-new-debate-minefield</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic National Committee (DNC) is in a tough spot with just 50 days to go before the first presidential primary debate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Make Money? Work for Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/want-make-money-work-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Photo by Mark Wilson/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1% of Guatemala, Honduras entered USA since September...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/shock-over-1-of-guatemala-honduras-entered-us-since-september</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a shocking demonstration of the latest surge of illegal immigrants border officials are struggling with, over 1% of the populations of Guatemala and Honduras have entered the United States since September, according to the Homeland Security Department chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO SEX, PLEASE: DIGITAL LIFE TO BLAME FOR LACK OF LOVEMAKING?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/07/britain-sex-decline-study-married-cohabiting-couples-digital-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research finds drop in sexual activity steepest for married and cohabiting couples</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Death sells water to tech bros too cool for alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegazette.com/subject/news/nation-and-world/liquid-death-sells-water-to-tech-bros-who-are-too-cool-for-alcohol-20190507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 12-pack of Liquid Death 16.9-ounce tallboys is $21.99 on Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  SALT LAKE TRIBUNE seeks to become nonprofit 'community asset'... </title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/05/08/salt-lake-tribune-seeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of heavy financial losses, The Salt Lake Tribune is pursuing federal approval to become a nonprofit operation sustained by donations large and small.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEB RACE:  FOXNEWS, CNN DEAD HEAT; DRUDGE OVER GOOGLE NEWS; PORN DOMINATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.similarweb.com/top-websites/united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.similarweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 Robots to Work Construction...</title>
      <link>https://www.roboticsbusinessreview.com/construction/more-than-7000-robots-will-work-in-construction-by-2025-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.roboticsbusinessreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worldwide market for construction robotics to reach $226M over six years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen says helped Falwell handle racy photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-falwell-exclusive/exclusive-trump-fixer-cohen-says-he-helped-falwell-handle-racy-photos-idUSKCN1SD2JG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months before evangelical leader Jerry Falwell Jr.’s game-changing presidential ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly mosques receiving threats after video shows children reciting violent poems, songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/muslim-american-society-video-children-philadelphia-20190507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philadelphia branch of the Council on American-Islamic Relations issued an advisory to all Islamic institutions to increase security precautions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET'S MAKE A DEAL:  Trade war cloud over 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trade-war-a-cloud-over-Trump-s-2020-prospects-13827237.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's aggressive trade policies are running headlong into his campaign for reelection.  As Trump prepares to run on the economy, his threat to increase tariffs on imports from China has sent the stock market diving and served to undercut a stretch of positive economic news. U.S. farmers and exporters, already bearing the brunt of China's retaliatory tariffs, now face the prospect of an escalated trade war in which key states that Trump needs to win reelection will be in the crosshairs.  The trade war has also exposed a rift inside the White House and among the president's allies - with some officials pushing for a quick resolution to calm the markets ahead of 2020, and others warning the president that a weak deal with China could leave him politically vulnerable.  "My warning has been, we don't want the 2020 election year to become greatly intensified friction with China over trade issues. We want a deal that works," said Michael Pillsbury, a China expert at the Hudson Institute who has advised the Trump administration on trade. "One way to unite all 21 Democratic primary candidates is if the president gets a quick but flawed deal that inevitably leads to friction when China is caught cheating next year."  However, Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin and National Economic Council Director Larry Kudlow are among a group of Trump aides who have encouraged the president to quickly reach a deal with China and avoid political blowback from a full-scale trade war in 2020, according to people familiar with the internal debate.  White House officials said Trump is prepared to take a hard line with China going into 2020 in part because he intends to keep his 2016 campaign promise to fix what he views as bad trade deals. Trump believes strongly in the power of tariffs to force China and other countries to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheila Nevins Sets Next Act: Launching MTV Documentary Films...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/sheila-nevins-sets-next-act-launching-mtv-documentary-films-1207990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former HBO exec, who departed the premium cable network in 2018 after a 38-year run, will develop new projects for third-party outlets and the Viacom-owned cabler via the MTV Studios division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET ON EDGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/07/trade-war-fears-are-crushing-stocks-and-sell-off-could-keep-going-if-there-is-no-deal-by-friday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An all-out trade war between the U.S. and China could bite into global growth, squeeze profit margins and drive down stock prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD Officers Catch MRSA After Contact With Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/lapd-mrsa-infection-reseda-west-valley-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Gordon of the L.A. Police Protective League confirmed to CBSLA that it was a homeless transient who came into contact with officers at the station.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Computer System Crippled By Ransomware Virus; Residents Not Able To Pay Bills...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/baltimore-city-government-computer-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore City Hall government servers have been infected by a ransomware virus that government officials said is spreading throughout their network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT GETS TRUMP TAX DOCS</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/decade-in-the-red-trump-tax-figures-show-more-than-1-billion-in-business-losses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the time his master-of-the-universe memoir “Trump: The Art of the Deal” hit bookstores in 1987, Donald Trump was already in deep financial distress, losing tens of millions of dollars on troubled business deals, according to previously unrevealed figures from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  After Round of Buyouts, CNN Staffers Brace for Layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/round-buyouts-cnn-staffers-are-worried-whats-next-1208356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Everybody is bracing for a reorganization," a senior producer at the network said. "There are all kinds of rumors about impending layoffs."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSNEWS Internal 'Chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cbs-news-chief-susan-zirinsky-swapping-star-anchors-we-had-shake-things-up-1208317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the network's key shows suffer ratings declines, division president Susan  Zirinsky bets on Gayle King and switches Jeff Glor for Norah O'Donnell and a move to the nation's capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo warns of 'imminent' threat on surprise trip to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190508-usa-pompeo-warns-imminent-iran-threat-surprise-trip-iraq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq has promised to guarantee the safety of US interests from Iran, US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said Tuesday as he paid a surprise trip to Baghdad where he accused Tehran of planning "imminent" attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of killing infant son after losing video game...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2019/05/05/louisville-police-dad-hit-baby-head-after-losing-video-game/1112386001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Trice, 26, is accused of striking his 1-month-old son in the head after losing a video game Friday evening. He's now charged with murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mexico's President threatens critical journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/05/07/mexican-president-to-media-you-know-what-will-happen-for-bad-coverage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the largest and most respected international press freedom organizations called out a series of statements made by Mexico’s President.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG LOSSES</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-taxes/trump-tax-returns-from-1985-to-1994-show-1-billion-in-losses-ny-times-idUSKCN1SD2R4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump's businesses lost a total of more than $1 billi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Catalan leader running for office via SKYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Fugitive-Catalan-leader-wanted-for-rebellion-is-13825574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - Carles Puigdemont once tried to lead Catalonia to independence from Spain. Now his dominion is a house in the suburbs of Brussels.  He fled charges of rebellion after his fall 2017 attempt to split his prosperous province from the rest of the country. And he is adapting to an odd new life where he can travel just about anywhere he wants - except the rolling hills of his native land.  Puigdemont on Monday scored a rare victory against the Spanish state, winning the right to run for European Parliament on May 26 after an election board initially barred the way. The case rose all the way to Spain's Supreme Court.  As long as he seeks to avoid arrest by Spanish police, it will have to be a campaign by Skype and Facetime. He will dial in to rallies in Catalonia from the pink brick building in Waterloo that he and his supporters have dubbed "the House of the Republic."  Meanwhile, some of his rivals and former compatriots will be running from behind bars in Spain, where they are on trial for rebellion, disobedience and misuse of public funds.  Puigdemont defends his self-imposed exile as strategic.  "We decided to live here in order to continue fighting," Puigdemont said in an interview. "If all of us were in jail, the narrative, the version of the Catalan crisis could be very different."  He said it was just a coincidence that his new home and headquarters is located in Waterloo, the site of Napoleon's final defeat. (He cheerfully notes that Napoleon's defeat was the Duke of Wellington's triumph.)  The Waterloo house "is a part of Catalonia," Puigdemont said, looking more tired than he did when he stirred crowds in Barcelona and across his region during the ill-fated independence attempt.  The walls are covered with Catalan art. The shelves are filled with books in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executive Privilege?  White House instructs McGahn not to comply with congressional subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/white-house-instruct-counsel-comply-congressional-subpoena/story?id=62873987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Jerry Nadler sounding off after former White House counsel Donald McGahn was told not to comply with House Democrats' subpoena for Mueller probe documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT GETS TRUMP TAX DOCS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/5-takeaways-from-10-years-of-trump-tax-figures/ar-AAB2BDR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy Hospital Ship Deployed to Aid Refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/05/07/navy-hospital-ship-comfort-deploy-aid-venezuelan-refugees.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy hospital ship Comfort will deploy next month to the Caribbean and Central and South America to provide assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Burglar enters home, pets pup, washes dishes...</title>
      <link>https://klewtv.com/news/offbeat/deputies-say-ohio-burglary-suspect-pet-victims-dog-washed-dishes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;klewtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vinton County Sheriff's Office said a woman is facing a burglary charge after she entered a home, pet the victim's dog and washed the dishes. Cheyenne Ewing is charged with burglary, according to the sheriff's office. Deputies said they received a call about a burglary about 9 a. m. Monday in Hamden. The victim said the suspect entered the home and sat on the couch to pet the family dog. The victim said the suspect then washed the dishes and left the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Censors Musical Short -- About Chinese Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/culture/culture-desk/cbs-censors-the-good-fight-for-a-musical-short-about-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The segment is clear about one of the motives for American self-censorship: China is too big of a market for media corporations to ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive backlash against Seattle woman raped by homeless man...</title>
      <link>https://www.city-journal.org/seattle-elites-homeless-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.city-journal.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seattle elites show little sympathy for a woman raped by a homeless man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools to serve cold food to students who owe lunch money...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/news/20190506/warwick-schools-to-serve-cold-sandwiches-to-students-whose-families-owe-lunch-money</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARWICK — City schools warned parents Monday that they will serve a simple sandwich to children whose lunch money is in arrears, until the balance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchman Arrives In Caribbean After Crossing Atlantic In Big Barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/adventure/outdoors/a27396168/frenchman-crosses-atlantic-ocean-in-barrel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because sometimes adventure beckons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activist faces jail in Poland for posters of Virgin Mary, Jesus with rainbow halos...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/07/world/poland-lgbt-flag-rainbow-halo-black-madonna-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish police say Elżbieta Podlesna put up posters of the revered Black Madonna that showed the Virgin Mary and Jesus with rainbows from the LGBT flag as the halos. Now she could face two years in prison for offending religious feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatigue? DISNEY Announces 3 New 'STAR WARS' Films...</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/entertainment/2019/05/disney-announces-release-dates-for-new-star-wars-avatar-and-marvel-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next "Star Wars" movies after December's "The Rise of Skywalker" will arrive in theaters on 2022, 2024, 2026. Whatever they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese-style surveillance being exported to West...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/may/07/chinese-style-surveillance-exported-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese model is now being exported – and the results could be terrifying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd roars as woman tells Joe 'hug, kiss me anytime!'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/woman-tells-biden-rally-you-can-hug-kiss-me-anytime-n1002986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former VP has been hit with stories from several women who have come forward recently to say he touched them in ways that made them uncomfortable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 'gifts' to voters legal?</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2019/05/07/election-2020-andrew-yang-universal-basic-income-payments-freedom-dividend-iowa-caucuses-president/1120575001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential hopeful Andrew Yang's campaign admitted the error, after the Register began inquiring about it. His campaign plans to amend his financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift fails to dethrone Lil Nas X for No.1 spot...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/music/2019/05/lil-nas-x-holds-off-taylor-swift-no-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the arrival of a new single from pop superstar Taylor Swift, "Old Town Road" rapper Lil Nas X has managed to hold on to his No. 1 spot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic' mushroom decriminalization vote in Mile High City...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8aaa48465b1d42f38014433f61a879df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Voters on Tuesday were deciding whether to make Denver the first U.S. city to decriminalize psilocybin — the psychoactive substance in "magic mushrooms" — and add a new chapter to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn deemed public health crisis by AZ politicians...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/porn-deemed-public-health-crisis-arizona-politicians/story?id=62874408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arizona State Senate voted Monday to declare pornography a public health crisis, but beyond stating such on their resolution, no further action will be taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers who backed uprising face jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190507-venezuela-prosecute-lawmakers-who-backed-failed-uprising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela to prosecute lawmakers who backed failed uprising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great-grandmother with CBD oil arrested at DISNEYWORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/travel/grandmother-cbd-arrested-disney-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney World may be the most magical place on Earth, but it turned into a legal nightmare for a great-grandmother with arthritis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran moving ballistic missiles by boat, USA says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/07/politics/us-iran-transporting-missiles/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence showing that Iran is likely moving short-range ballistic missiles aboard boats in the Persian Gulf was one of the critical reasons the US decided to move an aircraft carrier strike group and B-52 bombers into the region, according to several US officials with direct knowledge of the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Send migrants to Gitmo...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/immigration/442459-trump-should-send-migrants-to-guantanamo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deterring these migrants from coming requires a different approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA star seeks Ramadan fasting advice for playoffs...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/26693616/kanter-texts-olajuwon-ramadan-advice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trail Blazers big man Enes Kanter, with advice from Hall of Famer Hakeem Olajuwon, will fast during Ramadan, meaning no water, food or medication during the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Crashes Lawn Mower Into Cop Car: 'F*** It, I'm Drunk, Take Me To Jail'...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/drunk-florida-man-crashes-lawn-mower-police-car/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police officers have to worry about people driving under the influence or boating under the influence, but now, they'll have to look out for those lawn mowing under the influence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 'Electability' Argument How Dems Lose Elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/05/joe-biden-electability-argument-is-how-democrats-lose-elections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Democrats play it safe and “fall in line,” the results are devastating—as Dukakis, Gore, and Kerry made plain. If Biden wins the nomination next year, it will be because Democrats went with their heads, not their bleeding hearts. But Hillary Clinton’s 2008 campaign is a cautionary tale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union Plans Picket Of Vegas Fundraiser... </title>
      <link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/union-plans-picket-of-joe-biden-fundraiser-hosted-by-kaiser-board-member_n_5cd1c051e4b04e275d510425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Union of Healthcare Workers is battling the health care provider over mental health staffing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz condemns mini skirts with concentration camp photos...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/442526-auschwitz-condemns-redbubble-for-selling-pillows-mini-skirts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Auschwitz Memorial and Museum in Poland on Tuesday condemned Redbubble, an online marketplace for independent artists, for allowing products including throw pillows and mini skirts featuring images of the Nazi concentration and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Dog Thwarts Abduction Of Baby...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/05/07/family-dog-credited-thwarting-baby-abduction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio family believes their pet dog may have prevented the abduction of their infant son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash still king: San Fran to ban credit-only stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e4e95476e4e74756b3973ed23fa3b00e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco is about to require brick-and-mortar retailers to take cash as payment, joining Philadelphia and New Jersey in banning a growing paperless practice that critics...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Chicago police sergeant charged in attack outside gay bar...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-former-chicago-cop-bar-attack-20190507-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Chicago police sergeant once accused of having sexual contact with teenage boys has been charged with a vicious attack at a gay club on the North Side last year that left two men with serious injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer apologizes for 'worst national anthem rendition ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article230112979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentuck Derby winner out of Preakness in Triple Crown debacle...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/07/country-house-out-of-preakness-stakes-in-triple-crown-debacle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be no Triple Crown winner this year. Controversial Kentucky Derby winner Country House will not be running in the May 18 Preakness Stakes after developing a cough, trainer Bill Mott told…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnancy deaths up...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4907da5c58c84a708a548c4ea18fc5c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More U.S. women are dying from pregnancy-related causes, and more than half of those deaths are preventable, government health officials said in a report Tuesday. Although these deaths are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silicon Valley coming for your house...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Silicon-Valley-Is-Coming-for-Your-House-13824737.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today's on-demand digital world, buying and selling a home remains stubbornly, painfully analog. Most sales still begin with a real estate agent (and a 6% commission). Most still end in an office, with the two sides signing page after page of legalese.  Silicon Valley wants to change that. Tech companies have begun to nibble away at the edges of the residential real estate industry, offering virtual open houses, digital closings and other services. Now they are coming straight for the real estate transaction itself through "instant buying," in which companies buy homes, perform some light maintenance and put them back on the market.  Established companies like Zillow and venture-backed upstarts like Opendoor and Offerpad have raised billions of dollars on the promise that they can use sophisticated algorithms to predict the value of individual homes. They contend that those predictions, combined with old-fashioned economies of scale, will allow them to be far more efficient than traditional home flippers.  The companies and their backers say they are doing what tech is best at: bringing efficiency and convenience to a process not known for either. Silicon Valley has already upended the way we hail a cab and order takeout, they argue. Why not improve a transaction that even well-educated professionals find intimidating?  "You should be able to sell a home within a handful of clicks," said Eric Wu, Opendoor's chief executive.  But houses are not taxicabs. A bad Uber ride might set a user back $20 and make her late for a meeting. A house is the largest asset for most Americans and the most expensive purchase they will ever make.  At best, skeptics see instant buying, also known as "iBuying," as an overhyped, capital-intensive business whose explosive growth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine commandos ran military gear theft ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2019/05/06/north-carolina-raider-theft-rings-marines-stole-tactical-gear-vehicle-parts-flashbang-grenades-and-pawned-off-some-of-the-loot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than $300,000 worth of government property was stolen by one group of four Marines in 2017 alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe measles outbreak infects 34,000...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/07/europe-measles-outbreak-infects-34000-travel-advisory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 34,000 Europeans were infected with the measles during the first two months of 2019, most of whom are in Ukraine but who inhabit 42 countries in all. In a new report, the World Health Org…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This anchor doesn't exist, didn't say that...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/deep-fake-videos-intelligence-agencies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video of a seemingly real news anchor, reading a patently false script saying things like the &amp;quot;subways always run on time&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;New York City pizza is definitely not as good as Chicago&amp;quot; gives a whole new meaning to the term fake news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rallies with union members in Vegas... </title>
      <link>https://www.lasvegasnow.com/news/local-news/joe-biden-to-campaign-in-southern-nevada/1982386054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lasvegasnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden will make his first campaign stop in the Las Vegas valley since announcing his 2020 bid for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowfall on Way in Denver...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/07/denver-weather-may-7-snow-fog-thunder-lightning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service has issued a dense fog advisory for the Denver metro area Tuesday morning. As the day progresses the weather conditions will only get more dramatic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro Caught Dancing During Military Uprising...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/05/07/venezuela-nicolas-maduro-danced-on-tv-during-military-uprising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan socialist dictator Nicolás Maduro responded to last week's call for a military uprising by appearing on television and dancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Make America calm again...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/839841/trumps-presidency-puts-america-state-perpetual-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The endless drama in Washington is exhausting â€” and bad for Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals attack, seeking to blunt momentum...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/442378-liberals-attack-biden-seeking-to-blunt-his-momentum </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are taking shots at Joe Biden, seeking to blunt the former vice president’s rise in polls by arguing he is too conservative to be the party's presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple die of bubonic plague after dining on raw marmot...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/couple-die-in-mongolia-of-bubonic-plague-after-eating-raw-marmot-135154552.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists were left stranded for days after a quarantine was introduced following the deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  Russia case NOT closed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48dd7f423f40473a9562fca769104fcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Congress and the special counsel's Russia report (all times local): 11:50 a.m. The White House is instructing former counsel Don McGahn not to comply...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete claims more experience than Trump, Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/buttigieg-claims-more-experience-trump-pence-would-bring-very-different-n1002731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, spoke with NBC News' Craig Melvin while campaigning in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starr Comes For 'Whiny' Mueller!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ken-starr-comes-for-robert-mueller-committed-an-unforgivable-sin-with-whiny-leaked-letter-to-ag-barr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With rare exception, special counsel Robert Mueller has emerged from the past two years unscathed -- seemingly immune to cable news criticism. But on Monday, one man who previously ran a high-profile independent investigation of a president came after him with a blistering take. Appearing on The Story, Ken Starr -- the man who led the investigation into former President Bill Clinton in the late '90s -- shredded Mueller for his letter to Attorney General William Barr, which took the AG to task for his four-page Mueller Report summary. "His letter, that was then leaked on the very eve of Bill Barr's testimony, was essentially, I believe, an unfair, whiny complaint," Starr told Fox's Martha MacCallum. "Whiny" was just the beginning of Starr's blistering critique. The former independent counsel went on to refer to the leaked letter as an "unforgivable sin" against Barr. "Here comes Bob Mueller with this letter which is then leaked. That is, to me, the unforgivable sin," Starr said. "He,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET WAITS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/07/us-stock-market-us-china-trade-tensions-remain-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Tuesday after a top U.S. trade official indicated that higher tariffs on Chinese goods are coming later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company LOSES 58 cents per ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uber-ipo-uber-losing-an-average-of-58-cents-per-ride-and-says-its-ready-to-go-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The profitless company could be valued at up to $90 billion by Wall Street, or roughly twice the market cap of Ford</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  57% of Dems Believe Trump Guilty of Treason...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/57-of-democrats-believe-president-trump-guilty-of-treason/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-seven percent (57%) of Democrats believe that, in his relations with the Russian government, President Trump is guilty of treason. A ScottRasmussen.com national survey found that just 14% of those in Nancy Pelosi's party disagree while 29% are not sure.Republicans reject the notion that the president is guilty of treason by an 82% to 7% margin. Among Independent voters, 30% believe he has committed treason while 44% disagree and 25% are not sure (see full crosstab results).Among all voters, 33% believe the president is guilty of treason while 45% disagree.ScottRasmussen.com releases new public opinion data every day relating to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politician Wants To Ban ALL Bags...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/05/07/new-jersey-politician-wants-to-ban-all-bags-paper-or-plastic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Garden State's plan to ban all grocery store bags could have negative consequences for consumer convenience and the environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sorcerer' promised to help people find love. Instead, orchestrated 'witchcraft extortion scheme'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-sorcerer-promised-to-help-people-find-love-13825060.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The love ritual began with candles, alcohol, vegetables and photographs, all carefully arranged. Then clients were told to send photos and videos of themselves reciting graphic statements and performing sex acts to a Paraguayan business specializing in witchcraft to finish the magic spell aimed at finding a soul mate.  That's when a self-described sorcerer started another familiar rite: extortion.  Ariel Boiteux, an Argentine national who masterminded an international scheme that entangled an estimated 200 victims in at least 12 countries, threatened to post the photos and videos of the intimate acts unless his clients paid "large sums of money," according to authorities, sometimes demanding six-figure payoffs. Boiteux, 31, and associates with his company, Amarres Inmediatos, even posted some explicit content to websites, Facebook and Instagram and forced clients to pay to take down the posts.  But as the alleged warlock of witchcraft extortion learned this week, there were no tricks in his bag of distorted magic that could get him out prison.  The U.S. attorney's office for the Southern District of California announced Monday that Boiteux was sentenced to two years in federal prison for the crime of foreign transmission of an extortionate threat. He pleaded guilty in December after being extradited from Paraguay to San Diego last July, the Los Angeles Times reported.  "This was a despicable scheme that preyed upon people who put their trust in a phony," U.S. Attorney Robert Brewer Jr. said in a news release on Monday. "This defendant used the vulnerability of the lovelorn to humiliate and extort them, and for that he will pay a price."  Authorities in Paraguay said that the estimated 200 victims hailed from the United States, Paraguay, Argentina, Bolivia, Chile, the Dominican Republic, Guatemala, Italy, Mexico, Peru,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Comey in trouble and knows it...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/442278-james-comey-is-in-trouble-and-he-knows-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three internal investigations likely will fully expose Comey’s mishandling of the FBI and legal processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier trampled to death by elephant during mission to protect wildlife from poachers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9019837/brit-soldier-trampled-death-elephant-malawi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRITISH soldier has been trampled to death by an elephant while on anti-poaching duty in Malawi, it emerged today. Guardsman Mathew Talbot, 23, died on Sunday morning during a mission to stop the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rebel priest: 'Gay people in church not going away'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/may/07/rebel-priest-gay-church-campaign-same-sex-marriage </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Rev Andrew Foreshew-Cain says his same-sex marriage cost him his ministry. Now he is launching a campaign for the rights of LGBTQ Christians</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
