<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TRAILER...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5UijUOy0MmE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SPY, starring Sacha Baron Cohen, is inspired by the real-life story of former notorious Mossad agent, Eli Cohen, who successfully goes undercover in Syri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist says eating humans could save earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/6/cannibalism-whacked-scientist-says-eating-humans-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A behavioral scientist from Sweden named Magnus Soderlund argued in a recent presentation that the way to combat climate change, save the planet and secure the earth for scores of upcoming generations is to — get this — eat people. This guy’s whacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure grows to release health records...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/healthcare/pressure-grows-on-biden-to-release-health-records-as-campaign-stonewalls-on-bloody-eye-mishap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic front-runner Joe Biden was speaking at a televised town hall Wednesday when the corner of his left eye appeared to fill with blood, bringing attention away from the issue of climate change at a time when his campaign is already batting back scrutiny about his age and health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAINTS QB Drew Brees defends self after appearing in Bible video...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/saints/2019/09/05/drew-brees-new-orleans-saints-focus-family-video-lgbtq/2226844001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drew Brees appeared in a video promoting National Bring Your Bible to School Day. That video was tied to the anti-LGBTQ group Focus on the Family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spate of clinical trials has scientists hopeful about HIV vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/spate-of-clinical-trials-has-scientists-hopeful-about-a-vaccine/article_aedbf626-41ad-5141-91bb-c531e1923ed8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First there were the drugs that could knock back HIV to undetectable levels, and the virus was no longer synonymous with a death sentence. Then came a treatment that allowed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floodwaters invaded by sharks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9877387/hurricane-dorian-bahamas-floodwaters-sharks-as-dad-is-forced-to-throw-son-5-on-roof/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DAD has told of how he was forced to fling his son onto a roof to save him from sharks that had swum inland after Hurricane Dorian decimated the Bahamas. Adrian Farrington was trying frantically …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE rewrote Siri to 'deflect' questions about feminism, #MeToo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/sep/06/apple-rewrote-siri-to-deflect-questions-about-feminism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: voice assistant’s responses were rewritten so it never says word ‘feminism’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Third Of Parents Say Favorite Child -- Is Pet!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-a-third-of-parents-say-their-favorite-child-is-their-pet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's incredibly common for pet owners to fall head over heels for their companions, but a new survey reveals that many actually favor their pets over their own children!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Star receiver reportedly called GM 'cracker,' avoids punishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/raiders/article/Antonio-Brown-Mike-Mayock-cracker-Broncos-Fantasy-14419290.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oakland Raiders wide receiver Antonio Brown will avoid a suspension after he reportedly apologized to his teammates following an ugly argument with general manager Mike Mayock on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine to allow ranked votes in presidential election...</title>
      <link>https://www.saratogian.com/news/national/maine-to-allow-ranked-votes-in-general-presidential-election/article_6d15269a-3a91-5353-a533-7e024b9eff79.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.saratogian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUSTA, Maine (AP) — Maine is set to become the first state to allow voters to rank candidates in a general presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest self-inflicted wound festers... </title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-drags-sharpiegate-second-day-latest-self-inflicted-wound-festers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump dragged a mini-scandal into a second day Thursday, tweeting a full-throated defense of a doctored Hurricane Dorian map. Democrats howled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm loan delinquencies surge in battleground Wisconsin...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-wisconsin-farmers/farm-loan-delinquencies-surge-in-u-s-election-battleground-wisconsin-idUSKCN1VQ2Y1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farm loan delinquencies rose to a record high in June at Wisconsin's commun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red flag laws spur debate over due process...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/09/04/red-flag-laws-spur-debate-over-due-process</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: POST MALONE 'HOLLYWOOD'S BLEEDING' WEIRD AND WONDERFUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/reviews/album/post-malone-hollywoods-bleeding-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At times he sounds like Julian Casablancas, at others like '70s FM radio. This accomplished record, though, could only come from Post Malone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/refresh/AL052019_3day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/212400_3day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outages increase, flooding spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/weather-news/article234746837.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOODY HELL: NETS SPIKE BIDEN EYE DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/tim-graham/2019/09/06/joe-bidens-bloody-eye-cnn-somehow-spiked-everyone-fox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scary': How AMAZON, Bezos made Washington second home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/king-hill-how-amazon-jeff-bezos-made-washington-second-home-n1033296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many companies have cozied up to the nation's capital, but none have accrued the kind of presence and reach that Amazon will soon boast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CIA spy to publish book about undercover exploits without agency approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/ex-cia-spy-readies-publish-book-without-approval-agency-n1050456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some former CIA agents question the veracity of "Life Undercover: Coming of Age in the CIA," by Amaryllis Fox, which hits stores in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force jet accidentally fires rocket into Arizona desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/air-force-jet-accidentally-fires-rocket-arizona-desert-n1050571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one was injured when an A-10C Warthog "unintentionally released" a phosphorus smoke rocket about halfway between Phoenix and Tucson, the Air Force said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin E now focus of investigation?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/vaping/vitamin-e-now-focus-investigation-some-vaping-illnesses-n1050361</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitamin E oil has been implicated in at least one other vaping-related illness - back in 2000. But the FDA says it's too soon to rule out other contaminants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Strangers step in to help 90% of time...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news/forget-what-you-may-have-been-told-new-study-says-strangers-step-in-to-help-90-percent-of-the-time/ar-AAGU28y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ate a zoo,' murdered enemies..</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/robert-mugabe-ate-zoo-murdered-19574057</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zimbabwe's President Robert Mugabe ate a baby elephant when he celebrated his 91st birthday - but he did plenty worse during a reign of terror lasting almost 40 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why does news seem negative? Human attention may be to blame...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/science/story/2019-09-05/why-people-respond-to-negative-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physiologically, people are more triggered by negative news than positive news. Scientists see it in skin conductance levels and heart rate variability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA deploys facial recognition at LAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-09-05/delta-air-lines-will-use-facial-recognition-cameras-at-lax-boarding-gates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta is starting with one boarding gate but plans to expand. Some privacy rights groups are unhappy about the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE:  Sacha Baron Cohen Amazing in 'SPY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/spy-1237183</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this Netflix limited series' true-life spy story, Sacha Baron Cohen delivers his best dramatic work yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Defends: 'I've Done Everything #MeToo Movement Would Love to Achieve'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/woody-allen-done-everything-metoo-movement-would-love-achieve-1237353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director also predicted 'Rainy Day in New York' may still get a U.S. release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: 'IT: CHAPTER 2' Set For Biggest Opening In Horror History?</title>
      <link>https://www.gamespot.com/articles/it-chapter-2-set-to-have-biggest-opening-weekend-i/1100-6469653/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gamespot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how much money It Chapter 2 is expected to make at the box office during its opening weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's oldest mom' gives birth to twins at age 74...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/worlds-oldest-mom-gives-birth-twins-ivf-hospital-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The title was previously held by a 70-year-old woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>