<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>N.Z. court rejects Kim Dotcom US extradition appeal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/n-z-court-rejects-kim-dotcom-us-extradition-234826993.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand's Court of Appeal ruled Kim Dotcom was eligible for extradition to the United States Thursday in a major setback for the Internet mogul who is accused of online piracy. Dotcom had asked the court to overturn two previous rulings that the Megaupload founder and his three co-accused be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Trolls Trump with Mysterious July 4th Message...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sacha-baron-cohen-trolls-trump-july-fourth-message-1125002 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial comedian teased a new project involving Trump after posting a video of the president criticizing Cohen for being a "third grade character" who needs to "learn about being funny."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco Logs 16,000 Feces Complaints in Week...</title>
      <link>https://newswars.com/san-francisco-logs-over-16000-feces-complaints-in-one-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaultier lights up fashion week with provocative ode to smoking... </title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180704180704-jam8v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASHION-PARIS/HAUTECOUTURE-GAULTIER (PIX, TV):Gaultier lights up fashion week with provocative ode to smoking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson faces casting backlash for playing trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2018/07/04/scarlett-johansson-faces-backlash-again-role-transgender-man/757746002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a controversial decision, Scarlett Johansson has been cast in "Rub &amp; Tug," the true story of Dante "Tex" Gill, a transgender massage parlor owner. She faced a similar flap for last year's "Ghost in the Shell," which cast her as a Japanese manga character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test tube rhino embryos could bring extinct species back from dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/jul/04/first-test-tube-rhino-embryos-could-bring-extinct-species-back-from-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The northern white rhino is essentially extinct – just two females remain – but new research paves the way for its resurrection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY accidentally releases entire film instead of trailer...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/04/sony-pictures-make-huge-faux-pas-release-entire-film-instead-trailer-7683088/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it has already received bad reviews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns of worldwide financial crisis....</title>
      <link>http://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/merkel-warns-of-worldwide-financial-crisis/article_2dff7b52-12a8-5a67-86b0-e4b9324607aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN –– German Chancellor Angela Merkel raised the specter of a new global financial crisis as she warned of the potential fallout from a trade war with the U.S., saying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestor Climbs Statue of Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-live-protester-climbs-statue-of-liberty-liberty-island-evacuated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STRONG ON 4TH OF JULY!</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/results-matter-president-trump-tops-obama-in-approval-numbers-at-same-point-in-his-presidency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats issue bleak statement...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/onpolitics/2018/07/04/democratic-national-committee-july-4th-statement/757585002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Fourth of July statement by the Democratic National Committee cites disputes with President Donald Trump. "Everywhere we look, our most fundamental values are under attack," DNC chairman Tom Perez said in the statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Record-Low Extremely Proud to Be Americans...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/236420/record-low-extremely-proud-americans.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-seven percent of U.S. adults say they are extremely proud to be Americans, a new low in Gallup's trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14,000 immigrants become citizens...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/fourth-july-us-cities-celebrate-americas-newest-citizens/story?id=56326232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On July 4, U.S. cities celebrate nearly 14,000 of America’s newest citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STRONG ON 4TH OF JULY!</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jul04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish for flour? Barter is new currency in collapsing Venezuela... </title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-barter/fish-for-flour-barter-is-the-new-currency-in-collapsing-venezuela-idUSKBN1JT1UM?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the midday sun, dozens of fishermen wait to sell their day's catch by a lagoon in the town of Rio Chico on the Caribbean coast of Venezuela. But they aren't expecting cash in return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowner shocked after finding gold mine in his back garden... </title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/homeowner-gets-surprise-lifetime-finds-12852618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Doolin couldn't believe his eyes when he discovered the ancient shafts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyewear firm shoots ad at WWII death camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/australian-valley-eyewear-firm-shoots-ad-at-jasenovac-death-camp/a-44513768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian company Valley Eyewear has prompted outrage by publishing a sunglasses ad shot at Croatian World War II death camp Jasenovac. The firm told DW the photos were "taken completely out of context."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs can't kiss and make up; Avoid others after disagreement... </title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-5915625/Why-dogs-kiss-make-Researchers-lost-pack-mentality-wolves.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team from the University of Veterinary Medicine in Vienna studied how dogs and wolves reconcile with others of the same species following a disagreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL SHOCK...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/983331/oil-prices-latest-crude-prices-oil-shock-us-west-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OIL prices plummeted sharply yesterday, sparking warnings of an imminent “oil shock” as experts scrambled to come to terms with a wild day in the crude industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police: Gas prices fuel stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/local/article/Police-gas-prices-fuel-stabbing-13047243.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEPORT - A local man is accused of stabbing two people following an argument about the high gas prices. Algie Womack, 54, of Bretton Street, was charged with attempted murder, first-degree assault, second-degree assault, threatening and breach of peace. He was being held in lieu of $200,000 bond. Police said officers were patrolling Main Street Tuesday morning when they heard a woman screaming from the parking lot at St. Vincent's Medical Center. The woman, her dress soaked in blood, complained she had just been stabbed and told officers her assailant had fled on Main Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlusconi, Italy's Original Populist, Fades From Popularity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/berlusconi-italys-original-populist-fades-from-popularity-1530705600?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union’s first populist leader, Silvio Berlusconi, has become a forgotten man in Italian politics, displaced by a new antiestablishment wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social issues roiling USA weigh heavy on Independence Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksl.com/article/46354384/social-issues-roiling-us-weigh-heavy-on-independence-day?print=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In these complex times, a simple question about the quintessential American holiday of fireworks, cookouts and parades isn't always so simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's ambitions in eastern Europe faces scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/china-s-ambitions-in-eastern-europe-to-face-scrutiny-at-summit-10499534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOFIA/BERLIN/BRUSSELS: China meets central and eastern European leaders on Saturday for a summit where Beijing's promises of big infrastructure ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rife With Anxiety, Markets Are Churning at the Fastest Rate Since 2008...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/07/04/rife-with-anxiety-markets-churning-at-fastest-rate-since-2008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors fretting trade war and negative growth revisions, says JPMorgan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Sidelined as Five Powers Set to Give Iran New Assurance...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/07/04/u-s-sidelined-as-five-powers-set-to-give-iran-new-assurance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sidelined as Five Powers Set to Give Iran New Assurance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Demand Surging...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/03/the-heat-wave-has-u-s-power-use-at-the-highest-levels-in-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Heat Wave Has U.S. Power Use at the Highest Levels in Years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists struggle to keep online threats from escalating...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/journalists-struggle-keep-online-threats-escalating-030708079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA, Fla. (AP) — After a Florida radio station's general manager told hosts they didn't have to put an obnoxious repeat caller on the air a couple of months ago, the man stood on the sidewalk outside and vented his irritation with the station through a bullhorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding wildfires in West...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/07/04/exploding-wildfires-in-us-west-derail-holiday-plans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing swath of wildfires in western United States threatens to damper holiday plans as park rangers and fire officials across the region have greatly curtailed accessibility to National Parks and campgrounds to increase public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will tell NATO nations USA cannot be world piggy bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-nato/trump-will-tell-nato-nations-us-cannot-be-the-worlds-piggy-bank-idUSKBN1JT2XD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will tell fellow NATO countries at next week's summit that the United States cannot be "the world's piggy bank," White House spokesman Hogan Gidley said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamic State says leader's son killed in Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/59698eff72214974bc8f91ac17addbd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — The Islamic State group says the son of its leader has been killed fighting Syrian government forces.        The announcement of the death of the young son of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's president-elect shuns guards, asks 'people' for protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-politics-security/mexicos-president-elect-shuns-guards-asks-people-for-protection-idUSKBN1JU04E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador left the country's national palace on Tuesday in the front passenger seat of a white Volkswagen Jetta, swarmed by hundreds of jubilant supporters including one waving a live rooster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, 92, killed 72-year-old son...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/region-northeast-valley/fountain-hills/mcso-92-year-old-refuses-assisted-living-shoots-and-kills-son-in-fountain-hills</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 92-year-old woman is facing multiple charges after she allegedly shot and killed her son in Fountain Hills Monday because she refused to be admitted into an assisted living facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life, liberty and the pursuit of hot dogs...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-birthday-life-liberty-pursuit-hot-dogs-080605135--mlb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fireworks, music and the pursuit of hot dogs will mark the 242nd year of independence for the United States on what is expected to be a steamy Wednesday in much of the country. The Independence Day holiday, which brings out crowds from small towns to big cities, is also a time when law enforcement agencies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART takes heat as it removes 'Impeach 45' shirts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/walmart-takes-heat-removes-impeach-trump-shirts-202917261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart on Tuesday removed shirts and other gear from its online marketplace bearing the phrase "Impeach 45" after supporters of US President Donald Trump lambasted the retail giant on social media. Walmart nixed the items after images of jerseys and baby gear with the anti-Trump slogan went</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans celebrating Fourth of July face scorcher...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-celebrating-fourth-of-july-face-scorcher/ar-AAzz5rn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of vets spells misery for zoo animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/shortage-vets-spells-misery-karachi-zoo-animals-034916299.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Management have been pushing the city council to approve a third veterinary position for the zoo's population, including lions, tigers, elephants, chimpanzees, birds and reptiles. "This is unfortunate, that the zoo is heavily understaffed and thus not able to take good care of the animals,&amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  From cash-strapped roommates to AIRBNB billionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cash-strapped-roommates-airbnb-billionaires-033859101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago a pair of San Francisco roommates decided to make rent money by using air mattresses to turn their place into a bed-and-breakfast when a conference in the city made hotel rooms scarce. The brainwave led to the creation of Airbnb, a startup now valued at more than $30 billion which boasts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare US independence declaration found...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rare-us-independence-declaration-found-uk-archive-111216150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rare parchment copy of the American Declaration of Independence has been found at a British archive among the papers of an aristocrat who supported the rebels, officials have said. The manuscript was discovered at the West Sussex Record Office in the southern English city of Chichester by a team of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns Trump against trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/merkel-warns-trump-against-trade-war-101839767.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel on Wednesday warned US President Donald Trump against unleashing an all-out trade war after he threatened to impose steep tariffs on cars from the European Union. In a speech to the Bundestag federal parliament, Merkel said both sides were effectively locked in a "</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPP 'horrified' over India lynchings, promises action...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/india-slams-whatsapp-over-deadly-rumours-050022052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WhatsApp said Wednesday it was "horrified" by a spate of lynchings in India sparked by false rumours shared on its platform as the government accused the messaging service of irresponsibility. More than 20 people have been killed in India in the last two months, according to media reports,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan to be sworn in with new powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-sworn-monday-powers-105106231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan will on Monday be sworn in for a second mandate as Turkey's head of state after his election triumph last month, assuming sweeping powers granted under a new constitution, a presidential source said. Erdogan, who has dominated Turkey first as premier from 2003 then</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuts may boost male fertility...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nuts-may-boost-male-fertility-study-111927092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eating nuts "significantly" boosted the number and health of sperm in young men in a scientific trial, researchers said Wednesday. The findings "support a beneficial role for chronic nut consumption in sperm quality," they said, but stressed the study participants were all healthy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Becoming Kingmaker In Primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-endorsements-boost-other-left-democratic-candidates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Democratic insurgent candidate has raised the profile of a number of other challengers around the country—leading to significant fundraising boons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK police probing 6 assault claims against Kevin Spacey...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/uk-police-probing-6-assault-claims-against-kevin-103306486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British police are investigating six claims of sexual assault or assault by Academy Award-winning actor Kevin Spacey, three more than previously disclosed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK anti-terror police join 'unknown substance' probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/british-police-2-people-critical-near-poisoned-spy-050512731.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMESBURY, England (AP) — British counterterrorism police were investigating Wednesday after two people were left in critical condition, exposed to an unknown substance a few miles from where a former Russian spy and his daughter were poisoned with a nerve agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US World Cup ratings down 42% without American team...</title>
      <link>https://in.news.yahoo.com/us-world-cup-ratings-down-42-percent-without-143824342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The lack of a U.S. team caused a big viewership drop for World Cup telecasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refugee who fled violence mourns daughter slain in Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/family-friend-says-slain-birthday-girl-mothers-shadow-012909096.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Ruya Kadir had sparkling eyes, a few basic belongings and not much else when she arrived in Boise, Idaho more than two years ago. Bifituu's home was "always a monument to Ruya," full of things the child loved, Schwab said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viral vid of woman's arrest sparks anger, but LAPD says involved in violent kidnapping plot...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-kidnapping-suspect-viral-video-20180702-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many have criticized a viral video that shows several Los Angeles police officers pointing guns at an unarmed woman. Authorities said the woman was involved in a kidnapping and believed to be armed and dangerous.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
