<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Network Boss Pled With Him to Quit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chris-matthews-msnbc-boss-phil-griffin-went-to-dc-to-plead-with-him-to-quit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Hardball” host’s wife had long expressed concerns to MSNBC brass that Matthews’ increasingly controversial on-air antics would ruin him, sources told The Daily Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/2020-election/results/super-tuesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real-time 2020 Super Tuesday election results and live maps by state. POLITICO's primary coverage of 2020 races for President, Senate, House and Governors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELEGATE COUNT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-primary-elections/delegate-count</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Don't Think We Have a Perfect Candidate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/doubts-linger-as-democrats-vote-i-dont-think-we-have-a-perfect-candidate/ar-BB10HjBJ?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Chris Matthews' Sudden MSNBC Departure, Questions Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/chris-matthews-sudden-msnbc-departure-questions-abound-1282369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insiders are wondering: Why now? And who will replace him at 7 p.m. on the network?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HONEYWELL builds world's most powerful quantum computer...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2020/03/03/honeywell-quantum-computer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Honeywell built a quantum computer it says it is twice as powerful as any current device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most loyal dog pushes owner's wheelchair down road...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/worlds-most-loyal-dog-filmed-21623813</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magnus the dog was filmed pushing his 70-year-old master in his wheelchair down a street in Taraz, Kazakhstan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE WINS VT</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/super-tuesday-14-states-democratic-primary-election-live-updates-stream-2020-03-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters are going to the polls in 14 states from Maine to California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts heading down collision course with self...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/485687-chief-justice-john-roberts-heading-down-collision-course-with-himself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critical decisions on health and abortion will decide his future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI PANDEMIC WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/03/top-us-doctor-says-coronavirus-now-an-outbreak-possibly-a-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor on the front lines of battling coronavirus in the US said this week that the rapid spread of the deadly bug has risen to the level of an “outbreak” — and possibly even a “pandemic.” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine could have long-lasting psychological impact...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/being-quarantined-during-coronavirus-outbreak-could-long-lasting-113155998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New UK research has shown how being in quarantine, which is a common situation for many people around the world right now due to the current COVID-19 outbreak, could have a long-term effect on mental health. Carried out by a team from King's College London, the new research looked at 24 previous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/live-blog/super-tuesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest results and updates on Super Tuesday from primary elections in California, Texas, North Carolina, Virginia, Massachusetts, Minnesota, Colorado, Tennessee, Alabama, Oklahoma, Arkansas, Utah, Maine, Vermont and American Samoa on Tuesday, March. 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happens in Vegas if No One Stays in Vegas?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/03/what-happens-in-vegas-if-no-one-stays-in-vegas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This week, thousands of people will travel to Las Vegas for business conferences. The annual South by Southwest festival in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Dem voters made last-minute picks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e752cc0d9c91af8a302cf1b5e637f2f5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Many Democratic voters in Super Tuesday's presidential primaries made up their minds just before casting a ballot — a sign of fluidity in a race recently upended by Joe Biden's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WINS AL, NC, VA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e64410893844bcaf438e11b194c35ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden opened Super Tuesday with a trio of victories in key Southern states, building on momentum that has swiftly revived his Democratic presidential campaign in recent days....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outage hits LAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/power-outage-hits-los-angeles-international-airport-nearby-polling-places-n1148426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outage lasted for about a half-hour at one of America's busiest travel hubs and surrounding neighborhoods in West Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC blocked FDA official from premises...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/03/cdc-blocked-fda-official-premises-119684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sent to help the administration’s coronavirus response, a test specialist was stopped at CDC’s door and made to wait overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO says death rate higher than previously thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/who-says-coronavirus-death-rate-is-3point4percent-globally-higher-than-previously-thought.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World health officials say the case fatality rate for COVID-19 is 3.4% globally, higher than previous estimates of about 2%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran frees 54,000 prisoners to combat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-51723398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judiciary spokesman says the inmates were granted furlough after testing negative for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Opioid Crisis Much Worse Than Believed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/disturbing-study-shows-u-s-opioid-crisis-may-be-much-worse-than-believed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that U.S. deaths related to opioid overdoses may be 28% higher that originally reported due to inadequate death records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 41%...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/politics/trump-job-approval-relapses-amid-coronavirus-threat-ibd-tipp-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign sues WASHPOST for libel over 'false, defamatory statements'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/trump-campaign-sues-washington-post-libel-false-defamatory-statements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump campaign filed a libel lawsuit against The Washington Post for “millions of dollars” on Tuesday for publishing “false and defamatory statements” about an alleged conspiracy with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to WALMART. The doctor will see you now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/03/business/walmart-health-care-clinics-amazon-cvs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Calhoun, Georgia, a city of around 16,000 residents 70 miles outside of Atlanta, Walmart is testing out a new health center. If successful, Walmart may expand its initiative across the United States, potentially upending the way millions of Americans receive medical care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA games may ban fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/marc-lasry-says-nba-games-may-ban-fans-because-of-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marc Lasry, co-owner of the NBA's Milwaukee Bucks, told CNBC on Tuesday that sporting events could possibly ban fans if the coronavirus outbreak worsens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medication fog can mimic or worsen dementia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ef58b341a016590d5996a1c330f959b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claire Dinneen's daughters thought that worsening dementia was causing her growing confusion, but her doctor suspected something else. Dr. Pei Chen asked them to round up medicines in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from the Spanish flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200302-coronavirus-what-can-we-learn-from-the-spanish-flu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After World War One, a flu pandemic swept the world, killing at least 50 million people. What lessons can it teach us about Covid-19?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says he spoke to Taliban leader, had 'good talk'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e142c8d18406fb270ccb2c0cb0872a0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Tuesday that he talked with a Taliban leader, days after the United States and the Taliban signed an agreement that calls for the full withdrawal of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rise as U.S. death toll from coronavirus reaches 9...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dcd130364f2bbec8142d0ae47f805cba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Tensions over how to contain the fast-spreading coronavirus escalated Tuesday in the United States as the death toll climbed to nine and lawmakers expressed doubts about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg: Contested convention 'only way I can win'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/56043f9e91310b0e14ddeab4bad0fb91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Mike Bloomberg acknowledged Tuesday he’s aiming for what some Democrats say would be the party’s worst nightmare: A contested convention. “It’s the only way I can win,” he told...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-year Treasury yield falls below 1% for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/treasury-yields-rise-after-stimulus-hopes-lift-risk-on-sentiment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10-year Treasury yield broke below 1% for the first time ever in the wake of an emergency rate cut by the Federal Reserve to combat the economic effects of the spreading coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Third Of CA Voters Want Michelle O On Ticket...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/03/poll-california-voters-would-like-to-see-michelle-obama-on-democratic-ticket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While California voters go to the polls on Super Tuesday to select their choice for the presidential nomination, a poll done in the days leading up to the primary showed overwhelming support for former First Lady Michelle Obama as a running mate on the Democratic ticket in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'If I do get Coronavirus I'm attending every MAGA rally'...</title>
      <link>https://kdvr.com/news/local/if-i-do-get-coronavirus-im-attending-every-maga-rally-i-can-denver-councilwoman-quotes-solidarity-to-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kdvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER– Denver Councilwoman Candi Cdebaca is getting major blowback over a controversial tweet sent on Friday. Cdebaca quoted a tweet that said, “For the record, if I do get the coronav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security closes facility after illness...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c36518bb11cd81d7e002348d51e50799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The Latest on the virus outbreak (all times local): 3 a.m. The Vatican is insisting Pope Francis is only suffering from a cold, not coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope 'tests negative' but Vatican ups controls...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-tests-negative-coronavirus-vatican-ups-controls-004702909.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis, who is suffering from a cold, has tested negative for the coronavirus, an Italian newspaper reported Tuesday, as Italy battles Europe's worst outbreak. Vatican spokesman Matteo Bruni did not respond to an AFP request for comment on the Messaggero newspaper report and sources said no</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Army on standby as Boris declares war on virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11086449/army-on-standby-coronavirus-boris-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE NUMBER of British coronavirus cases leapt to 51 today – moments after Boris Johnson revealed his battle plan to kill off the deadly bug in the UK. Soldiers could be deployed to guard vita…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears nursing homes will be center of disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/483864/coronavirus-nursing-home-washington-disaster-center-outbreak-seattle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEARS are growing that nursing homes could be at the center of a coronavirus “disaster” in the US after the deaths of four residents at the same Seattle facility. Concern grew as U.S. c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty streets in some of world's busiest cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/coronavirus-fears-empty-streets-some-world-s-busiest-cities-n1147806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eerie quiet has settled upon normally teeming streets and squares as many residents opt to stay home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY man with coronavirus recently traveled to Miami, and Florida didn't know...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article240835481.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donna Brazile Tells RNC Chair 'Go to Hell!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/donna-brazile-shocks-foxs-ed-henry-by-telling-ronna-mcdaniel-go-to-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Democratic National Committee chairwoman Donna Brazile told her Republican counterpart Ronna McDaniel to "go to Hell" with her talking points about how the DNC has "rigged"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: 'I'm Now Nervous'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/im-now-nervous-cnbcs-jim-cramer-predicts-feds-drastic-rate-cut-will-stoke-investor-fear-over-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the eyes of one prominent market observer, the half-point Fed rate cut may actually stoke fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Israel considers placing US travelers under quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/HEALTH-SCIENCE/Israel-could-consider-placing-US-travelers-to-Israel-under-quarantine-619608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of infectious disease at Assuta Ashdod says such a quarantine is under discussion – and he recommends it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient's chilling account of what disease feels like...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/coronavirus-patient-gives-chilling-account-21622276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julie said her lungs went into overdrive after contracting the deadly COVID-19 and she struggled to even walk to the toilet, before she was treated in just nine days</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Offices Closed in Washington State After Employee Falls Ill...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/susan-jones/dhs-offices-closed-washington-state-after-employee-falls-ill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting Homeland Security Secretary Chad Wolf began his congressional testimony on Tuesday with an announcement: One of his own employees is sick, apparently with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO makes urgent plea: 'Supplies rapidly depleting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/who-officials-make-urgent-plea-for-medical-gear-supplies-are-rapidly-depleting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WHO estimates that each month 89 million medical masks will be required for the COVID-19 response.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED CUTS RATES HALF POINT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/fed-cuts-rates-by-half-a-percentage-point-to-combat-coronavirus-slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Markets had been widely expecting the U.S. central bank to take some type of action, with anticipation of a 50 basis point cut by the next Federal Open Market Committee meeting later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON, WALMART battle price gouging... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/03/amazon-walmart-e-retailers-battle-price-gouging-on-coronavirus-products.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, eBay, Walmart and Etsy have all struggled to curb price gouging and products that make unverified claims about the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SWING... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/02/dow-futures-rise-about-150-points-in-early-trading-extending-mondays-huge-comeback-rally.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move follows the Dow's biggest percentage gain since March 2009 and largest-ever point surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Olympics Could Be Pushed To End Of Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/olympics/news/tokyo-olympics-games-can-be-pushed-to-end-of-2020-amid-coronavirus-outbreak-japans-olympic-minister-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The contract doesn't state that the Olympics have to be held in the summer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Tells All Employees To Work At Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/twitter-coronavirus-employees-work-at-home-because-of-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech company said it is "operating out of an abundance of caution" in asking its 5,000 workers to work from home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sense Of Doom And Dread Everywhere'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/03/02/coronavirus-confusion-miami-woman-allegedly-denied-proper-testing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In what may be the first case of coronavirus in South Florida, a woman who recently returned home from Italy says she was told by doctors at Jackson Memorial Hospital that she “likely” has COVID-19, but that they are unable to verify it because state and federal officials refused to conduct the necessary tests to confirm it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN anchor Bobbie Battista dead at 67...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/485080/bobbie-battista-cnn-anchor-dies-cervical-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOURNALIST Bobbie Battista has passed away at the age of 67 after a four-year battle with cervical cancer. The celebrate CNN journalist was one of the original CNN Headline News anchors when the ne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds what killed 1,000 birds in Missouri...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article240833731.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Hollywood Goes for Digital Detox Retreats...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hollywood-goes-digital-detox-retreats-1281209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As overflowing inboxes and constant notifications compound work-related stress and anxiety, seven wellness resorts favored by industry executives and stars offer places to unplug from phones and laptops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orphan monkeys forced to serve beers and play with kids in 'bar jobs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/orphan-monkeys-forced-serve-beers-21584781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baby macaques, whose parents are being killed to order by angry farmers, are been snatched from the streets and made to become human entertainers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones capture devastation...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/breaking-news-deadly-tornado-tears-path-of-destruction-through-nashville-tennessee/694144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>538 FORECAST...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/our-final-forecast-for-super-tuesday-shows-bidens-surge-and-lots-of-uncertainty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden has gotten a lot of good news over the past few days. A huge, almost 30-point win in South Carolina. A series of impressive endo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest meat company linked to 'brutal massacre' in Amazon...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/mar/03/worlds-biggest-meat-company-linked-to-brutal-massacre-in-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation traces meat sold to JBS and rival Marfrig to farm owned by man implicated in Mato Grosso killings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surreal Scene Inside America's Hot Zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/kirkland-washington-is-americas-coronavirus-hot-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus has swept through a nursing home in Kirkland, Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Pence exposed?</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/news/20200302/coronavirus-florida-mother-and-son-at-sarasota-military-academy-under-quarantine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are not showing any symptoms of COVID-19 but came in contact with a patient who the CDC now says tested "positive," the schools says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Election Staffers Quit Over Virus Fears...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/03/02/election-staffers-not-working-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sacramento County Registrar's Office says 10-15 temporary staffers will not be coming in to work the primary Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation H(elpless)? Many Millennials Can't Change Light Bulb...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/generation-helpless-many-millennials-cant-change-a-light-bulb-by-themselves-survey-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey of 2,000 young adults and millennials finds that most still need assistance with the simplest of tasks -- like changing a light bulb!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER TUESDAY HERALDS EPIC DEM CLASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/03/super-tuesday-2020-democratic-primary-battle-119360</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Bernie’s revolutionary zeal pit against Biden’s calls for restoration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After shift to right, Supreme Court to hear major abortion case...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/after-shift-right-under-trump-supreme-court-hear-major-abortion-n1147461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outcome is uncertain following the president's nominees Gorsuch and Kavanaugh joining the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Bloomberg waste $500 million?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Did-Mike-Bloomberg-waste-500-million-running-for-15101124.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the craps table of this campaign, there's a $500 million chip sitting on "Super Tuesday." The bettor's name is mike - small "m," according to the visual design of his campaign, like he's your modest neighbor from the split-level down the block instead of a titan of media and finance with estates in Bermuda and Southampton.  That's Bloomberg. Mayor of New York from 2002 to 2013. Democrat, then Republican, then independent, then Democrat. Purveyor of fancy data terminals. Ninth-richest person in the world. A few months ago Bloomberg saw a moribund field of candidates and thought he could vault his way to the nomination through a delegate grab on Super Tuesday.  So now it's mike, responsible presidential candidate, asking for the car keys as the nation stumbles around.  Is he trying to save the party, or accidentally sabotaging it? Is "mike" just a proxy for Bloomberg as he tries to buy the presidency?  "My first answer to that all the time is: What's the right price to save democracy from Donald Trump?" said Tim O'Brien, a senior adviser to mike, at a Bloomberg house party in McLean, Virginia, Thursday night. There, Northern Virginians sipped Chianti and canned Perrier and whispered about Joe Biden as if he were an uncle in hospice care (this was 48 hours before his defibrillation in South Carolina). They shuddered at the thought of Bernie Sanders, democratic socialist, for his perceived radicalism and dismissed Elizabeth Warren, capitalist reformer, for her vendetta against mike.  What's a democracy worth? A year ago, before mike arrived on the scene, Bloomberg pledged a half billion to vanquishing Trump. In Virginia, over the past three years, he spent $3.5 million to help flip the statehouse to Democrats, whose gun-control advocates now speak of him with reverence. So far this year, Bloomberg has spent $50 million to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Anyone but Trump': The evangelicals who plan to vote Democrat...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200303-anyone-but-trump-the-texas-evangelicals-who-plan-to-vote-democrat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is home to one of the largest evangelical populations in the country, most of which traditionally votes Republican. But some current and former members of the evangelical community have turned…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/00cc158976f9c23e424df524a3487c6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The latest on the Democratic presidential primary and Super Tuesday (all times local): 8 a.m. A super PAC supporting Joe Biden‘s presidential bid is running a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary Could Show Just How Blue Texas Turning...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/03/02/810401130/super-tuesday-could-show-just-how-blue-texas-is-turning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Texas Democrats, the state's Super Tuesday primary could help define the shape of a party that's on the rise after more than two decades of being shut out of power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Children Having Nightmares Over 'Climate Change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/children-climate-change-sleep-nightmares-eco-anxiety-greta-thunberg-a9371191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans continue to vote with their feet towards low-tax states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/485497-how-tax-rates-affect-congressional-apportionment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before we know it, the 2020 census will be in the books and states will know their fates for congressional reapportionment and the electoral college map</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic Navalny says bank accounts frozen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kremlin-critic-navalny-says-bank-accounts-frozen-115221373.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's main opposition leader Alexei Navalny said Tuesday that authorities had frozen all of his bank accounts and those of his family, including his elderly parents. The 43-year-old anti-corruption blogger, who has emerged as President Vladimir Putin's most prominent critic, accused the Russian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chile capital rocked by violent anti-govt rallies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chile-capital-rocked-violent-anti-government-rallies-103847153.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santiago (AFP) - Chile's capital has been rocked by its worst anti-government violence in weeks after stone-throwing protesters clashed with police in running battles across the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek army, police dig in along Turkey border after migrant clashes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200303093733-0z09i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/GREECE (PIX, TV):Greek army, police dig in along Turkey border after migrant clashes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFOs or drones? Time-lapse video at Outer Banks finds mysterious 'red trails' in sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/article240802356.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster: Tornadoes shred 40 buildings around Nashville...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/795688aab981d4e8220042c20e095b55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — At least two tornadoes touched down early Tuesday in central Tennessee, including one that ripped across downtown Nashville and caused about 40 buildings to collapse around...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smiley responds to six PBS employees' accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Smiley-responds-to-six-PBS-employees-accounts-15099830.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - One by one, the voices of six female employees of former PBS talk show host Tavis Smiley sounded in a District of Columbia courtroom, each woman describing incidents in which they claim Smiley requested sex or told a lewd joke while at work.  Some of the women said that they felt pressured to comply with those requests and that they faced retaliation - even losing their jobs - if they didn't. Others described comments or jokes by Smiley that they said made them uncomfortable in the workplace.  During three weeks of trial, Smiley listened to the women's accounts, played in court by video deposition. When he took the witness stand he admitted that he'd had intimate relationships with two of the women. But he said several of the accounts were false and insisted he never acted with retribution and never intended to offend.  "I'm a black man struggling to make it in America. I have laughed at all of this so-called power. I struggled to raise money to keep my show on the air. I never had such power," Smiley, 55, testified. "I have influence, but I don't have power."  The accusations - and Smiley's responses - were detailed as Smiley and PBS squared off in court, with each side arguing that the other was in breach of contract when the network stopped airing his show in 2017 amid the sexual harassment allegations. On Monday, attorneys for PBS and Smiley gave their closing arguments before the jury began deliberations.  For 14 years, PBS distributed Smiley's late-night talk show to 238 stations nationwide, about 72% of its network.  PBS is suing Smiley for about $1.7 million the network says Smiley owes in money it had provided for a season that never aired. Smiley, who says the network terminated his contract without proof of the allegations, is countersuing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials clash over passenger tracking...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Major-airlines-U-S-officials-clash-over-15099881.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - U.S. officials are pressuring airline executives to turn over the email addresses and phone numbers of international passengers as the Trump administration tries to track who may have been exposed to the coronavirus, according to five people briefed on the situation.  Government officials have said they need the data so they can warn local authorities about who might have been exposed to the virus. But the airline industry has balked, saying the federal government should instead share information it already collects between different agencies and come up with a system for obtaining the rest.  The impasse has dragged on for weeks despite concerns about the growing number of people with coronavirus in the United States. It has become a top issue of the Trump administration's virus task force and U.S. lawmakers. Airline executives are slated to meet Wednesday with Vice President Mike Pence.  The airline industry has pushed Congress to intervene, with some lobbyists asking lawmakers to insert a provision in an emergency spending package that would effectively absolve the airlines of having to track some of the data.  The failure to resolve the issue could complicate the government's efforts to contain the outbreak's spread. United Airlines, Delta Air Lines, and American Airlines deferred questions to Airlines for America, a lobbying group that represents the airline industry. Airlines for America said collecting the data shouldn't be the airlines' job since the government already has much of it in existing databases. They also said it would take up to a year for the airlines to set up the tracking system.  Even though both sides have been fighting over the data for weeks, the battle has taken on new urgency in recent days.  The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is asking airlines to collect and - when...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY, PETE ENDORSE JOE...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Democrats-embrace-Biden-as-Sanders-hopes-for-big-15100191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parade of establishment Democrats began coalescing around Joe Biden on Monday, an attempt to bolster the former vice president and stall Sen. Bernie Sanders' ascent as voters in 14 states prepared to cast ballots Tuesday, the most consequential day of the presidential nominating contest.  On a day with cascading developments that rapidly recast the presidential race, Sen. Amy Klobuchar, D-Minn., dropped out and made plans to join Biden at his rally in Dallas on Monday night. In a visual symbol of Biden's attempts to consolidate the moderates in the party, former South Bend, Indiana, mayor Pete Buttigieg - who dropped out Sunday night, and who had an intensely cold relationship with Klobuchar - also scrambled to get to Dallas and endorse Biden.  It was the second straight day that moderates, previously paralyzed over whom to endorse, rushed to join Biden's campaign. Harry Reid, a former Senate majority leader from Nevada, endorsed Biden along with other Democrats including Susan Rice, the former national security adviser to President Barack Obama; political activist and actress Alyssa Milano; Victoria Reggie Kennedy, the widow of Sen. Edward Kennedy, D-Mass.; and Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill.  There are still looming questions about Biden - his propensity for gaffes, the moments when he searches for words or, on Monday, his struggle to come up with well-worn phrases in the Declaration of Independence before shouting, "You know . . . the thing!" - but his campaign has found unmistakable new momentum it is hoping to carry into the elections Tuesday.  Not everyone was playing to his benefit, however. Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., and former New York mayor Mike Bloomberg both vowed Monday to stay in the race.  "I'm in it to win it," Bloomberg said. He has poured hundreds of millions of dollars into the primary...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF 23 YEAR RUN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/02/business/media/chris-matthews-resigns-steps-down-msnbc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Matthews’s show, “Hardball,” has been on the air since 1997.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRIS MATTHEWS QUITS MSNBC 'HARDBALL'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/chris-matthews-announces-retirement-mutually-parts-ways-msnbc-n1147536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthews was due to retire in the near future with the events of the past week playing a factor in the timing of the move, an MSNBC spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'OUT OF TOUCH'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-chris-matthews-msnbc-veteran-retires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Matthews resigned from MSNBC Monday night after more than two decades at the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUSHED?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/chris-matthews-departure-msnbc-hardball-1203521543/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Matthews is abruptly stepping down from MSNBC’s “Hardball” amid scrutiny of recent on-air remarks as well as speculation about behind-the-scenes behavior. The veteran anchor and politic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE BLOWOUT OR DELEGATE SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/a-sanders-blowout-or-a-delegate-split-california-to-shape-outcome-of-2020-primary-race/ar-BB10ECxt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Museum of American Jewish History files for bankruptcy protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia-jewish-museum-bankruptcy-debt-20200302.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In papers filed with U.S. Bankruptcy Court in Philadelphia, the museum said that it owed a little more than $30 million to bondholders and about $1 million to unsecured creditors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What can govt force people to do in name of containing? </title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/coronavirus/sns-what-can-government-force-people-to-do-name-containing-coronavirus-20200302-zwhxf6uclzdcpelyzoyripiqdm-photogallery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q&amp;A: What can the government force people to do in the name of containing the coronavirus?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEGALA: Trump will 'dump Pence' for Haley...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/485562-cnns-begala-trump-will-dump-pence-for-haley-on-day-of-democratic-nominees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime CNN political analyst Paul Begala predicted on Monday that President Trump is "gonna dump [Vice President] Mike Pence in favor of former South Carolina Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMY, PETE ENDORSE JOE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/485510-buttigieg-set-to-endorse-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former South Bend, Ind., Mayor Pete Buttigieg is set to endorse former Vice President Joe Biden in the Democratic presidential race one day after ending his own bid, according to a source close to the Biden campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says MILLIONS of refugees will be released...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/erdogan-warns-europe-share-migrant-burden-113820883.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan warned on Monday that "millions" of migrants would soon head for Europe, drawing accusations from EU leaders that he is trying to pressure them into backing his incursions into Syria. Turkey gave the green light to refugees and migrants on Friday to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top central banks primed to act on coronavirus risk...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200302233859-nyn23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
