<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey's Big Risk (and Opportunity) If  Runs for Gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/politics-news/matthew-mcconaughey-texas-governor-2-1235027824/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the star vaguely embraces the idea of seeking higher office and leads a hypothetical statewide poll, Texas political insiders weigh in and warn: "People will start to hate him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC hotel incurred $70 million in losses while president...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/08/politics/trump-hotel-dc/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump racked up more than $70 million in losses over a four-year period from his Washington, DC, hotel, while publicly claiming that the hotel was making more than tens of millions of dollars, according to documents released by the House Oversight Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mass Surveillance System Set to Spoil Secret Lovers' Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mass-surveillance-system-set-spoil-090019387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Sarah Rogers/The Daily Beast / Photos GettyVENICE—Ah, Venice... The world’s favorite romantic getaway is synonymous with amorous trysts, and not always on the up and up. For centuries, the city—which by no small coincidence is the birthplace of legendary lover Casanova—has been a magnet for romantic affairs by politicians, Hollywood elite, and regular people. Hotels have long offered discreet services, secret entrances and private dining rooms so couples who shouldn’t be se</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING OUTRAGED: ELIMINATE INVADERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-10-07/china-levies-new-threats-at-reports-of-us-commandos-in-taiwan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘See whether the PLA will launch a targeted air strike to eliminate those U.S. invaders!’ the chief of the Chinese Communist Party’s propaganda outlet threatened on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's WALDORF Gets Plush Renovation, Becomes Icon of China's Overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-10-08/waldorf-astoria-inside-the-renovation-slated-for-condos-hotel-owned-by-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storied hotel was bought by Anbang before its Chairman was jailed. Now it’s undergoing a vast renovation overseen by a state-backed enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrote album for her son...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008122653-voy8o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-ADELE/VOGUE (TV, PIX):Adele says she wrote upcoming album for her son</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax chiropractors rising force...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/anti-virus-chiropractors-rising-force-misinformation-02b347767b45cab1d6d532be03c57529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — The flashy postcard, covered with images of syringes, beckoned people to attend Vax-Con ’21 to learn “the uncensored truth” about COVID-19 vaccines. Participants traveled from around the country to a Wisconsin Dells resort for a sold-out convention that was, in fact, a sea of misinformation and conspiracy theories about vaccines and the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French cops board train, arrest tourist for 'wearing wrong type of  mask'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3817270/french-cops-eurostar-arrest-brit-wrong-type-of-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARMED French police boarded a London-bound Eurostar after a Brit was accused of wearing “the wrong type of mask”.  The drama saw the unidentified man being arrested and hauled off the train after i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America Running Out Of Everything...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/america-is-choking-under-an-e2-80-98everything-shortage-e2-80-99/ar-AAPeokg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global supply chain is slowing down at the very moment when Americans are demanding that it go into overdrive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New doubts ahead of next fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article254856897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Chuck Schumer won this game of chicken,” Texas Sen. Ted Cruz told reporters before joining the majority of Republicans to vote against the McConnell agreement on the Senate floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake tech could soon allow anyone to create Hollywood-quality visual effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/deepfake-technology-60-minutes-2021-10-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday on 60 Minutes, Bill Whitaker demonstrates the magic of "synthetic media," allowing for the creation of photo-realistic videos and sound recordings completely generated by computers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden Agenda at Stake, Activists Target Sinema, Dividing Dems...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/08/with-biden-agenda-at-stake-activists-target-sinema-dividing-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — In the days after cellphone camera-toting protesters trailed Senator Kyrsten Sinema of Arizona into a university restroom to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sense Of Purpose Boosts Memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sense-of-purpose-better-memory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People with more purpose also shared more sensory details, recalled their memories in the first-person, and had more positive feelings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing stunning levels of deaths, U.S. and Mexico revamp strained security cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-stunning-levels-of-deaths-us-and-mexico-revamp-strained-security-cooperation/ar-AAPh7fU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly criticized the Merida Intitiative, saying it promoted an ineffective “war on drugs." But the longtime leftist saw few possibilities to renegotiate it with former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Creates  'Mission Center' to Counter...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cia-creates-new-mission-centers-china-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In announcing the changes, the CIA director referred to "increasingly adversarial Chinese government" as the "most important geopolitical threat we face in the 21st century."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing stunning levels of deaths, U.S. and Mexico revamp strained security cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/facing-stunning-levels-of-deaths-us-and-mexico-revamp-strained-security-cooperation/ar-AAPh7fU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has repeatedly criticized the Merida Intitiative, saying it promoted an ineffective “war on drugs." But the longtime leftist saw few possibilities to renegotiate it with former president Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ: Wisconsin incubator for tribal politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/wisconsin-the-incubator-for-america-e2-80-99s-tribal-politics/ar-AAPgKoo </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Hacking Group 'FIN12' Targets Hospitals, Clinics With Ransomware Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cyberattacks-ransomware-hacking-hospitals-target-foreign-groups/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ransomware attacks on hospitals during the pandemic have worsened outcomes for patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read link carefully: Scammers scoop up misspelled crypto URLs to rob wallet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/read-that-link-carefully-scammers-scoop-up-misspelled-cryptocurrency-urls-to-rob-your-wallet/ar-AAPh9mB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Typo URLs, which look similar to the real URLs of cryptocurrency websites, have been used for fake versions of those sites that could steal your password -- and your money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico seek to revamp fight against cartels...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211008-us-mexico-seek-to-revamp-fight-against-drug-cartels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US, Mexico seek to revamp fight against drug cartels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Hockney, lockdown was natural blessing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/david-hockney-lockdown-natural-blessing-061607179.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British artist David Hockney has always been a workhorse, so his months of lockdown in France were a welcome opportunity to devote himself to observing nature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin police investigating 'Havana syndrome' cases at U.S. embassy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211008105911-nbu9t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-HAVANA SYNDROME/BERLIN:Berlin police investigating 'Havana syndrome' cases at U.S. embassy - Spiegel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery lingers around cause of California oil pipeline leak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-los-angeles-california-environment-and-nature-e3b2976b1986e0f4f2908cedc18f2854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNTINGTON BEACH, Calif. (AP) — Investigators searching for the cause of an oil pipeline break off the Southern California coast have pointed to the possibility that a ship anchor dragged the line across the seabed and cracked it, but two videos released so far provide only tantalizing clues about what might have happened 100 feet (30 meters) below the ocean surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blast at Afghan mosque kills many, witnesses and Taliban say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-prayer-religion-2b9d9863da38661ba6fa186a72ac5352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — A powerful explosion in a mosque frequented by a religious minority group in northern Afghanistan on Friday has left several casualties, witnesses and the Taliban's spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catalytic converter thefts surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/catalytic-converter-thefts-have-surged-during-the-pandemic-police-are-fighting-back/ar-AAPgUJX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Takoma Park police have teamed up with RS Automotive to offer free etchings on catalytic converters amid a spike in thefts of the car part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Debt Now Totals $1.3 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/danalexander/2021/10/07/trumps-debt-now-totals-an-estimated-13-billion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The real estate mogul should have no problem paying back his loans in the short term. But come 2024, when he might be running for president again, things could get dicey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She's 51, mother, devout Catholic. She plans to die by euthanasia Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/She-s-51-a-mother-and-a-devout-Catholic-She-16518431.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOGOTÁ, Colombia - It began with a strange feeling in her hand, a weakness in the thumb...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL BLINKS ON DEBT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-congress-mitch-mcconnell-6e330d9fb94b73787ea70e7807b87151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate dodged a U.S. debt disaster Thursday night, voting to extend the government’s borrowing authority into December and temporarily avert an unprecedented federal default that experts warned would devastate the economy and harm millions of Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA MOVES TO TEX</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/07/tesla-moves-its-headquarters-from-california-to-texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's growing dissatisfaction with California has been apparent for some time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe says unpopular Biden is drag on Virginia governor's race...</title>
      <link>https://www.tri-cityherald.com/news/politics-government/national-politics/article254818092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tri-cityherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia gubernatorial Democrat candidate Terry McAuliffe cast President Joe Biden and his party’s lawmakers in Congress as a liability in the final weeks of the campaign, with polls showing a tightening race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IT JUST WASN'T RIGHT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/16357136/adele-busty-display-weight-loss-vogue-cover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADELE last night revealed how her life fell apart when she hit 30 and admitted: “I f***ed up. It didn’t work.” The singer, now 33, said she got divorced, became addicted to exercise and shed seven …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  THISCLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/youngkin-nearly-ties-mcauliffe-in-closest-virginia-poll-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The survey of likely voters shows McAuliffe with only a one point lead over Youngkin (49-48 percent).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers waging guerrilla war on tech companies, revealing secrets and raising fears of collateral damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/hackers-are-waging-a-guerrilla-war-on-tech-companies-revealing-secrets-and-raising-fears-of-collateral-damage/ar-AAPfEry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A resurgence of “hacktivism” seeks to portray cyberattacks as a moral crusade. But everyday users can also end up having their private information exposed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida issues financial penalties to school districts with mask mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-issues-financial-penalties-to-school-districts-with-mask-mandates/ar-AAPfKdz?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chappelle draws criticism for doubling down on jokes about LGBTQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dave-chappelle-draws-criticism-for-doubling-down-on-jokes-about-the-lgbtq-community/ar-AAPfs5q?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Chappelle's new Netflix special "The Closer" has been described by LGBTQ people and advocacy organizations as "blatantly and dangerously transphobic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Authoritarian behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10070335/Google-YouTube-ban-climate-change-deniers-monetizing-content-platforms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google and YouTube sparked controversy after announcing they will prevent anyone who denies climate change from monetizing their platforms with ads or creator payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles sheriff says he will not enforce mandate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/575863-los-angeles-sheriff-says-he-will-not-enforce-vaccine-mandate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles Sheriff Alex Villanueva said he will not force his employees to get vaccinated as required by a mandate the city council passed on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA MOVES TO TEX</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/elon-musk-says-tesla-moving-headquarters-to-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company is moving from Palo Alto, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Soviet-born currency comptroller pick was Young Communists leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10065391/Bidens-new-comrade-Soviet-born-nominee-idolized-Karl-Marx-Moscow-State-University.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden's pick for Comptroller of the Currency was an ardent Young Communist who 'owes money to her friend at Moscow State University after a Soviet-era dorm scam'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Building to Celebrate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/575841-empire-state-building-to-illuminate-in-red-white-and-blue-for-foxs-25th</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire State Building will be illuminated in red, white and blue on Saturday to celebrate Fox News’ 25th anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man plunges 9 stories, lands on BMW -- and survives...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/07/new-jersey-man-survives-9-story-plunge-by-landing-on-a-bmw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man crashed through the roof of the Beemer parked below 26 Journal Square at 10:20 a.m. Wednesday, then stood up with a broken arm and asked, “What happened?” onlooker Christina Smith, 21, told…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas school shooter RELEASED on $75k bond...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10069931/Arlington-shooter-Timothy-Simpkins-pulled-gun-backpack-classroom-brawl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Timothy George Simpkins is in police custody on three charges of assault with a deadly weapon. The 18-year-old opened fire in his classroom at Timberview High School on Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bus driver attacked for asking youths to put on masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/bus-driver-attacked-for-asking-youths-to-put-on-masks-681416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire Tennessee Town For Sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/an-entire-town-in-historic-tennessee-region-is-up-for-grabs-70392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Water Valley was built around 1900, and sits on seven acres of land.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School security officer fired after killing 18-year-old...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2021/10/07/long-beach-school-security-officer-fired-after-killing-18-year-old/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video of the incident, posted on social media, shows him fire two shots as the car begins to pull away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martian Wasteland -- Once a Lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/this-martian-wasteland-was-once-a-lake/ar-AAPftSC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billions of years ago, the view from the edge of Jezero crater would have been “spectacular.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL Reportedly Investigating Player for Using Fake Card...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epnyye/nhl-reportedly-investigating-evander-kane-player-for-using-fake-covid-vaccine-card</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evander Kane is being investigated by the NHL for a multitude of issues, including alleged domestic abuse and submitting a fake COVID vaccine card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toys Tough To Come By...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/10/06/toys-holidays-global-supply-chain-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it's going to be really tight getting access to products for Christmas," said Ryan Petersen, the CEO of Flex Port, a global trade company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-aides told to defy subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/07/trump-jan-6-committees-subpoena-515593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House panel probing the Capitol attack had demanded documents and testimony from the former president's former aides by Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland agrees global tax deal, sacrificing prized low rate...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007180750-48twr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-TAX/IRELAND (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Ireland agrees global tax deal, sacrificing prized low rate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware hackers find vulnerable target in US grain supply...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/ransomware-hackers-find-vulnerable-target-us-grain-supply-rcna2702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least three US grain distributors have been infected with ransomware in recent weeks, raising concerns that hackers have found an easy target in a vital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 133 Cats Rescued From Baltimore Row Home...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/06/133-cats-removed-from-baltimore-home-in-pet-hoarding-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 130 cats were removed from a Baltimore home Tuesday in an apparent case of animal hoarding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diet soda prompts food cravings -- especially in obese...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/10/07/1044010141/diet-soda-may-prompt-food-cravings-especially-in-women-and-people-with-obesity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research adds to growing concern over zero-calorie drinks. Consuming artificial sweeteners may confuse our body, leading to increased hunger and weight gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studies confirm waning immunity -- only 2 months effective?!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/06/health/pfizer-vaccine-waning-immunity/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two real-world studies published Wednesday confirm that the immune protection offered by two doses of Pfizer's Covid-19 vaccine drops off after two months or so, although protection against severe disease, hospitalization and death remains strong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL ratings see big jump in first month of season...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/oct/5/back-where-it-was-nfl-ratings-see-big-jump-first-m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday’s dramatic game between the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and New England Patriots that featured a Brady-Belichick showdown produced a whopping 26.75 million viewers on television and 1.83 million on digital streaming platforms — marking NBC’s second most-watched “Sunday Night Football” broadcast ever, behind only 2012’s Cowboys-Redskins contest that decided the NFC East.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADELE, IS THAT YOU?</title>
      <link>https://www.vogue.co.uk/arts-and-lifestyle/article/adele-british-vogue-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vogue.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her remarkable songs of heartbreak and redemption have won Adele many millions of fans. Now, she tells Giles Hattersley, in her first interview for five years, she is poised to release her strongest album yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hannity's Cable News Career Turns 25  --  Along With FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/exclusive-sean-hannity-takes-mediaites-hot-seat-as-his-cable-news-career-turns-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sean Hannity’s cable news career turns 25 this week. Hannity joined Fox News at its inception in 1996, after a few years on radio (“I was god-awful,” he recalls), and a few more years before that working construction and restaurant jobs. Over the course of two decades, Hannity has gone from being one half of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER shots for kids...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-coronavirus-vaccine-health-b9a0e105be709a4d7a1c7d604e8d05f2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer asked the U.S. government Thursday to allow use of its COVID-19 vaccine in children ages 5 to 11 in what would be a major expansion that could combat an alarming rise in serious infections in youngsters and help schools stay open.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai ruler hacked ex-wife using NSO Pegasus spyware...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/oct/06/dubai-ruler-hacked-ex-wife-using-nso-pegasus-spyware-high-court-judge-finds-sheikh-mohammed-princess-haya</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheikh Mohammed used spyware on Princess Haya and five associates in unlawful abuse of power, judge rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  GROWING ECON THREAT FROM CHINA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/americans-sense-china-eclipsing-us-economically-and-say-protecting-us-jobs-should-be-priority-poll-finds/ar-AAPeJa2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Americans said U.S. foreign policy does not benefit working-class Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES Now Says ALL Workers Must Be Fully Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/american-air-says-workers-must-be-fully-vaccinated-by-nov-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Air Says Workers Must Be Fully Vaccinated by Nov. 24</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France summons archbishop over 'confession above law' stance...</title>
      <link>https://timesofmalta.com/articles/view/france-summons-archbishop-over-confession-above-law-stance.906295</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofmalta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French government on Thursday summoned for explanation a top archbishop who said priests should not go to the police after hearing about child sexual abuse during confession. Archbishop Eric de Moulins-Beaufort made the remark after a government inquiry lifted the lid on "massive" sexual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  44% OF REPUBLICANS WANT HIM TO RUN AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/575678-44-percent-of-republicans-want-trump-to-run-again-in-2024-survey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly half of Republicans want former President Trump to run for office again in 2024, according</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30% of  pilots holding out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-presses-airlines-employees-205316223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines, Alaska Airlines and JetBlue are joining United Airlines in requiring employees to be vaccinated against COVID-19, as the Biden administration steps up pressure on major U.S. carriers to require the shots. The companies say that makes them government contractors who are covered by President Joe Biden's order directing contractors to require that employees be vaccinated. American Airlines CEO Doug Parker told employees late Friday that the airline is still working on details, but “it is clear that team members who choose to remain unvaccinated will not be able to work at American Airlines.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bieber fans 'confused' as Diane Keaton plays love interest in new video...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3807756/justin-bieber-confused-diane-keaton-75-love-interest-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUSTIN Bieber’s fans are “confused” as Diane Keaton appears in his new music video. The 75-year-old actress plays the Canadian singer’s love interest in the video for Ghost. Justin took to Instagra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 former NBA players arrested and charged with defrauding league...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/18-former-nba-players-arrested-federal-authorities-alleged-health-care-n1281022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glen "Big Baby" Davis, who won an NBA title with the Boston Celtics, and former high school sensation Sebastian Telfair are among the defendants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone tourist gets jail time after getting too close to grizzly...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article254825962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, the woman was spotted on video standing within feet of a grizzly bear at the national park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Diaper Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/diaper-shortage-hits-us-amid-covid-19-pandemic-supply-chain-issues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Diaper Bank Network said the country has a diaper shortage with nearly 33% of American families in need of the baby item.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Used To Select Targets From Satellite Photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/10/how-well-can-ai-pick-targets-satellite-photos-army-test-aims-find-out/185916/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Scarlet Dragon exercise is evaluating ways the service might put new tools to use in the very near term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T quietly becomes powerhouse in conservative politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/local/dallas/2021/10/07/att-criticized-funding-conservative-lawmakers-texas-abortion-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T, the world’s largest communications company, has covertly become a powerful player in conservative politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.1 MAG QUAKE JOLTS TOKYO... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211007150806-us98q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Magnitude 6.1 quake jolts Tokyo, causing blackouts but no tsunami warning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATT LABASH</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/welcome-to-slack-tide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Konnichiwa. Or as my English-speaking readers prefer, “hello.” I’m Matt Labash, and welcome to Slack Tide, my brand spanking-new Substack. Just saying those words makes me feel like a honking cliché. Not the Matt Labash part. There aren’t many of us. The only other one who shows up in my Google alerts is a star college lacrosse player. I keep meaning to ask if he’d like to trade lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia wants FACEBOOK held liable for anonymous comments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-scott-morrison-australia-social-media-e68fe4edc2bcdb71f33a9392bb9d5471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia’s prime minister on Thursday described social media as a “coward’s palace” and warned that digital platforms including Facebook should be held liable for defamatory comments posted anonymously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian leader hopes to stay on amid bribery allegations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-austria-0dcdba427328a0de32c17f923bd75fbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Austrian Chancellor Sebastian Kurz denied wrongdoing and made clear he did not plan to step down after anti-corruption prosecutors said he is a target in a bribery investigation. However, the partner party in Kurz's coalition government said Thursday that the probe created a “disastrous” impression and raised questions about the chancellor's “ability to act.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repairs To San Fran's Leaning Tower -- Caused It To Sink MORE!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/10/07/update-despite-warnings-repairs-on-san-franciscos-millennium-tower-caused-additional-sinking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Construction on a fix for San Francisco's leaning Millennium Tower came to a stop in late August because the fix was actually making the tower sink even more. Now it appears some of that damage could have been avoided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT: Russia behind 58% of detected state-backed hacks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-china-europe-united-states-e13548edf082992a735a0af1da39b6c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Russia accounted for most state-sponsored hacking detected by Microsoft over the past year, with a 58% share, mostly targeting government agencies and think tanks in the United States, followed by Ukraine, Britain and European NATO members, the company said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
