<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Vigorously for 4 Seconds. Repeat. Muscles May Thank You...</title>
      <link>https://lightlynews.com/2021/08/11/health/exercise-vigorously-for-four-seconds-repeat-your-muscles-may-thank-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lightlynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exercise Vigorously for four Seconds. Repeat. Your Muscles May Thank You. - LIGHTLYNEWS.COM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Women Muscle In on World of Vintage Cars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/11/more-women-muscle-in-on-the-world-of-vintage-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caroline Cassini, now 29, may have startled some neighbors in West Orange, N.J., when she announced that, rather than applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest Warrants Issued for TX Dems Who Fled Over Voting-Rights Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.texastribune.org/2021/08/10/texas-house-arrest-warrants-democrats-quorum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texastribune.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Texas Supreme Court earlier Tuesday ruled that Democrats who refuse to show up could be detained by law enforcement and brought back to the state Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii to reimpose rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/hawaii-reimpose-covid-19-restrictions-delta-variant-surges-2021-08-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii will re-impose COVID-19 restrictions limiting social gatherings to avert straining the state's healthcare, Governor David Ige said on Tuesday, as the rapid spread of the Delta variant of the coronavirus pushed cases and hospitalizations in the United States to a six-month high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In blistering drought, California farmers rip up precious almond trees...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-08-blistering-drought-california-farmers-rip.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crushed by a devastating drought and new water restrictions, Daniel Hartwig had no choice but to pull thousands of precious, fragrant almond trees from his California farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban now controls two-thirds of Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-taliban-e2c0e7b46c03cebb4fdddca309e005e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban seized three more provincial capitals in Afghanistan and a local army headquarters in a blitz across the country’s northeast, officials said Wednesday, with the insurgents now controlling some two-thirds of the nation as the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQzmCrZ6BUw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US DEBT NEARS $29 TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.usdebtclock.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usdebtclock.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  FOX IN TALKS TO BUY TMZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/warnermedia-in-talks-to-sell-tmz-to-fox/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT&amp;T continues to pare down media assets ahead of WarnerMedia-Discovery merger</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW WORLD ORDER:   Kissinger &amp;  Schmidt Plan Treatise on Artificial Intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/08/10/henry-kissinger-eric-schmidts-big-treatise-on-artificial-intelligence-panned-in-early-important-book-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who knew? Henry Kissinger, age 97, has written a new book. One of his two co-authors is former Google chief Eric Schmidt. Little, Brown has “The Age of A.I.: And our Human Future” set f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean Up After Fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ny-e2-80-99s-first-female-governor-must-clean-up-after-cuomo-fallout/ar-AAN9UUW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Kathy Hochul becomes New York’s governor in two weeks, cleaning up after Andrew Cuomo will be only one of her newfound problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL FACES IMPEACHMENT?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cuomo-may-still-face-n-y-impeachment-to-keep-him-from-running/ar-AANabNj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Governor Andrew Cuomo, who resigned Tuesday in the aftermath of multiple sexual-harassment allegations, may still face impeachment if only to keep him from running for office again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TODD:  CAN MAKE COMEBACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/chuck-todd-suggests-andrew-cuomo-can-make-political-comeback-mere-minutes-after-his-resignation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chuck Todd reacted to Andrew Cuomo's resignation by assessing that the New York governor's decision to step down is a matter of pure political calculus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST 3 GOVS LEFT OFFICE AMID SCANDAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/new-yorks-last-three-governors-democrats-leave-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo will be replaced by Lt. Gov. Kathy Hochul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Cuomo pardon himself?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/andrew-cuomo-pardon-himself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo on Tuesday announced his resignation effective in two weeks, following a damning sexual harassment investigation by the state attorney general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEPSI releasing alcoholic Mountain Dew...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/pepsico-and-boston-beer-co-to-create-alcoholic-mountain-dew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alcoholic Mountain Dew is set to hit shelves in early 2022 in a collaboration with PepsiCo and Boston Beer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire house burns as firefighters battle Dixie Inferno...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/dixie-fire-destroys-fire-station-while-volunteer-crews-battle-blaze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indian Valley Fire Rescue Department was destroyed by the Dixie Fire while the volunteer firefighters were trying to save homes in the Greenville area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE ANDREW FACING MORE ACCUSATIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9881139/Prince-Andrew-seen-Balmoral-supported-ex-wife-Fergie-day-sued-New-York.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York's convoy made a quick entrance to his mother's Scottish Highlands estate just after 6pm, a day he was sued in New York for allegedly sexually abusing Epstein victim Virginia Roberts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO STEPS ASIDE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/politics/andrew-cuomo-resigns/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said that he will resign, relinquishing under extraordinary pressure his decade-long grip on power and heading off a potential impeachment by New York's Democratic-led legislature a week after the release of a report by the state attorney general that found he had sexually harassed 11 women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  EU weighs restrictions on American tourists, while U.S. says avoid Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/So-much-for-post-pandemic-travel-E-U-weighs-16377759.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - The summer started on a hopeful note. Coronavirus cases were falling, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban eye full control of northern Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabnews.com/node/1908666/world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm warnings issued for Caribbean islands; Florida on Alert...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/florida-put-on-alert-for-developing-tropical-system/996922</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just over a month after Elsa struck the Sunshine State, AccuWeather forecasters are saying a strengthening system will approach the state with potential impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOMCBS waiting for other suitors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/10/viacomcbs-waiting-for-other-suitors-sources/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shari Redstone is hitting pause on any potential partnership talks between her media company ViacomCBS and NBC owner Comcast in hopes of lining up more suitors, The Post has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Dynasty Sputters Out...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/10/andrew-cuomo-resigns-as-governor-of-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo resigned amid a barrage of sexual harassment allegations a year after he was hailed for his leadership during the darkest days of COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House escalates battle with DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-house-escalates-battle-with-republican-governors-over-masking-in-schools-224251633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration said Tuesday that school districts across the nation should follow federal masking guidelines, even if that means resisting Republican governors who have enacted measures prohibiting districts from establishing mask mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin blames 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tragic-day-alec-baldwin-blames-180500756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor tweeted his views following the governor’s resignation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hochul to become NY's first female governor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/factbox-cuomos-replacement-kathy-hochul-161638547.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hochul, a former Democratic congresswoman who has served as lieutenant governor since 2015, will take over from Cuomo until his third four-year term in office ends in December 2022. -- Cuomo asked Hochul, a rising star in the Democratic Party, to join the gubernatorial ticket in 2014 after the then-lieutenant governor, Robert Duffy, announced he would not seek another term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell joins Dems to pass Biden infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/mcconnell-joins-democrats-voting-pass-12-trillion-infrastructure-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill moves to the Democratic-led House for consideration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only  Quarter of Office Crowd Now Working From Home...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/only-quarter-office-crowd-now-154801009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In July, roughly 25% of managers and professional workers teleworked at some point because of the pandemic, the lowest since the government started tracking the data in May 2020. It’s a clear sign that the age-old work compact is mostly intact, and that the office model is far from defunct.The July number is down from 41% in January and 57% in May of last year, according to data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, which tallies the number of employed who teleworked or worked at h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Driver bites off man's nipple in road rage...</title>
      <link>https://cwbchicago.com/2021/08/man-bit-off-motorists-nipple-during-road-rage-clash-on-lake-shore-drive-prosecutors-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cwbchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago man battered an off-duty CPD officer and bit the nipple off the cop's buddy during a road rage incident Sunday night on Lake Shore Drive, prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69-30 vote in Senate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-infrastructure-bill-politics-joe-biden-a431f8c9f3f113b661cb3526512fc4e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — With a robust vote after weeks of fits and starts, the Senate approved a $1 trillion infrastructure plan for states coast to coast on Tuesday,  as a rare coalition of Democrats and Republicans joined together to overcome skeptics and deliver a cornerstone of President Joe Biden’s agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAINTAINS INNOCENCE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/andrew-cuomo-resigns-17161f546bb83c32a337036ecf8d2a34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Gov. Andrew Cuomo announced his resignation Tuesday over a barrage of sexual harassment allegations in a fall from grace a year after he was widely hailed nationally for his detailed daily briefings and leadership during some of the darkest days of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did archaeologists find the Trojan Horse?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/did-archaeologists-just-find-the-trojan-horse-676349</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish archaeologists excavating the site of the city of Troy on the hills of Hisarlik have discovered a large wooden structure that they believe are the remains of the famous Trojan Horse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210810-brazil-s-bolsonaro-flexes-muscles-with-military-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-savvy teens falling prey to online scams faster than grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/10/tech-savvy-teens-falling-prey-to-online-scams-faster-than-their-grandparents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of individuals under age 21 reporting that they've been victims of cyber-fraud has surged 156% over the last three years, a study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We rented CA vacation home and got spied on by surveillance camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/California-vacation-rental-surveillance-camera-law-16346246.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you pull up to your vacation rental, you might be greeted by a surveillance camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mask Mandate May Be in Effect Through Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/dc-mask-mandate-may-be-in-effect-through-thanksgiving-if-vaccinations-dont-increase/2767657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;D.C. health officials hope the indoor mask mandate can be dropped by Thanksgiving — but that may not be possible if the numbers don’t improve.  As D.C. enters its second week of a new mask mandate and the delta variant spreads, the number of people getting tested at pop-up testing sites has jumped. The number of new cases is rising…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod man catches Great White Shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2021/08/09/watch-cape-cod-man-catches-great-white-shark/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Pieciak caught a shark while fishing at Nauset Beach in Orleans on Sunday, according to a video he posted on instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBIN COMES OUT AS BISEXUAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/08/10/robin-comes-out-bisexual-dc-comics-batman-urban-legends-series/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin comes out as bisexual in DC Comics series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting Machine Tampering Coming From Inside The MAGA House...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/voting-machine-tampering-is-coming-from-inside-the-maga-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The truth is, these are not very bright guys, and things got out of hand.” – Hal Holbrook After months of being promised by the former President and his stooges that Dominion Voting Systems had RIGGED the election, we finally have our first credible investigation into voting machine tampering. The lede in Monday’s Grand Junction […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going door-to-door dragging out girls as young as 12 to make them sex slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3448281/taliban-grabbing-girls-sex-slaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Taliban are “going to door to door” to round up young girls to be “sex slaves” to fighters in the terror group, reports claim. An inside source suggests that Taliban leaders are att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$611 Million Stolen in Massive Hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/611-million-cryptocurrencies-stolen-massive-hack-1617999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will take legal actions and we urge the hackers to return the assets," Poly Network tweeted in a thread. The hack has been labeled the largest DeFi hack in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China weighs whether to abandon Covid zero-tolerance approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/china-weighs-whether-abandon-covid-zero-tolerance-approach-n1276333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Even if you can lock down all the regions in China, people might still die, and more might die due to hunger," a Yale University health economist says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst governor during pandemic? Lot of candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/melinda-henneberger-the-worst-governor-during-this-pandemic-there-are-a-lot-of-candidates/ar-AAN8Y28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the 18 months since Americans began dying of COVID-19, some of my friends in Missouri, Texas and Florida have been arguing about which of us has the worst wartime governor in the country. Missouri’s Mike Parson got off to a fast start, doing nothing at first, and as little as possible ever since: By April 1, 2020, according to a state compilation of every action taken by every ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon scraps requirement for high school students to read, write...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9879959/Oregon-scraps-requirement-high-school-students-prove-proficiency-math-reading-writing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Oregon has suspended its requirement that high school students demonstrate a proficiency in math, writing and reading in order to receive a diploma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Banana republic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/10/bolsonaro-banana-republic-military-parade-condemned-by-critics-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanks roll through streets of Brasília as congress prepares to vote on plans to change Brazil’s voting system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student proves TWITTER algorithm bias toward lighter, slimmer, younger faces...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/10/twitters-image-cropping-algorithm-prefers-younger-slimmer-faces-with-lighter-skin-analysis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company pays $3,500 to Bogdan Kulynych who demonstrated flaw in image cropping software</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks battle to protect town from ferocious blaze...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/huge-force-struggling-contain-greek-105045534.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers and firefighters are workinground-the-clock, often without masks or helmets, in a desperate bid to stop a violent blaze from reaching a key town on Greece's Evia island, one of hundreds of fires that have raged through the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamblers lifting casino market to its best year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-39f5928cee71d63ba06549e75b5a70fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Gamblers anxious to hit the slot machines and table games in person after a year of coronavirus restrictions are lifting the U.S. casino industry to its best year ever. But the great unknown is whether a new, more contagious variant of COVID-19 will slow an industry that is now winning money at a record pace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-caribbean-brazil-74267e007a4c09417d905b5447d16782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA, Brazil (AP) — Brazil's military staged an unusual convoy of troops and armored vehicles through the capital on Tuesday — an event announced only a day before and that coincided with a scheduled vote in Congress on one of President Jair Bolsonaro's key proposals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of traditional TV happening fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-spiral-spelling-trouble-for-traditional-tv-7a50241a-6c96-4bec-94f7-b81367c86922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a big long-term problem for NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor responds after officers turn backs on her following cop killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wbbm780/news/local/chicago-cops-turn-backs-on-lightfoot-after-officer-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Lori Lightfoot has responded to reports that a group of Chicago police officers turned their backs on her after the murder of a female cop over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire-backed mining firm to seek electric vehicle metals in Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/billionaire-backed-mining-firm-seek-electric-vehicle-metals-greenland-2021-08-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mineral exploration company KoBold Metals, backed by billionaires including Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates, has signed an agreement with London-listed Bluejay Mining (JAY.L) to search in Greenland for critical materials used in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penélope Cruz Movie Poster Featuring Lactating Nipple Censored on INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/penelope-cruz-movie-poster-featuring-lactating-nipple-censored-instagram-1617842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A striking poster for "Madres Paralelas" (Parallel Mothers) was recently unveiled, ahead of it opening the Venice Film Festival in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC investigating 2 deaths, 2 illnesses from rare bacterial disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/melioidosis-us-cases-cdc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The source of the infections remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene for vax tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/tech/twitter-marjorie-taylor-greene/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has suspended Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene's account for one week following another violation of the platform's rules, the company said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviction moratorium forces small landlords to consider selling...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-tenants-who-won-e2-80-99t-pay-or-leave-small-landlords-face-struggles-of-their-own/ar-AAN9niL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many corporate apartment chains catering to white-collar workers are raising rents and booking enormous profits while some small landlords are giving up and deciding to sell as the eviction moratorium stretches on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another city falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldsun.com.au/news/breaking-news/thousands-flee-as-taliban-noose-tightens-around-afghan-north/news-story/54b01324939add545b6ce02d3292b3a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldsun.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban seized another Afghan provincial capital Tuesday -- the seventh in less than a week -- as tens of thousands of people fled their homes in the north for the relative safety of Kabul and other centres.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810140426-j6vax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (PIX, TV):Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Face of Dem Party?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/hakeem-jeffries-nancy-pelosi-speaker-house/619695/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hakeem Jeffries could end up being the first Black speaker of the House—but not all progressives are happy about his rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: War Against Federal Prosecutor...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/andrew-cuomos-war-against-a-federal-prosecutor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A call to the Obama White House that some legal experts say is impeachable fits a pattern of the Governor smearing those who scrutinize him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI system could diagnose dementia in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/3444806/new-ai-system-diagnose-dementia-in-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW artificial intelligence (AI) system could diagnose dementia in just one day, experts have discovered. At present it takes several scans to diagnose dementia and scientists have claimed the ne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL REQUESTS VENTILATORS</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/08/09/florida-sets-another-covid-case-record-as-hospitals-face-sheer-exhaustion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida has again broken a record for new COVID-19 cases, reporting 56,633 of them over the past two days, according to the latest CDC data, an average of more than 28,000 per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot shops opening on Main Street America. And they look like Margaritaville...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90663444/pot-shops-are-opening-on-main-street-america-and-they-look-like-jimmy-buffets-margaritaville</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, cannabis dispensaries tried to channel the sophisticated look of an Apple Store. Now they’re embracing their inner Jimmy Buffett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER: Miami orders residents to evacuate condo...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/miami-orders-residents-evacuate-story-condo-building-79377888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another South Florida condo building is being evacuated some six weeks after the collapse of a Surfside condominium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Distrust In Government Rising Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-burden-distrust-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were also surprised to find that COVID-19 burden does not need additional triggers to motivate political violence,” researchers say. “It is seemingly enough on its own.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Bush admin hid truth about attack targeting Cheney...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2021/08/10/afghanistan-papers-book-dick-cheney-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bush administration hid the truth about an attack targeting Dick Cheney, amid fears it was losing the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to defund agencies following CDC rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/news/rand-paul-covid-cdc-masks-b1899354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial US senator Rand Paul has been blasted after insisting Americans should reject government-mandated regulations, including wearing masks, in a “dangerous” anti-Covid rant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel threatens to kill TV news anchor, claiming unfair coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/azucena-uresti-tv-anchor-threatened-jalisco-new-generation-cartel-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Committee to Protect Journalists considers Mexico the deadliest country in the Western Hemisphere for journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci supports mandates for teachers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/567094-fauci-supports-mandates-for-teacher-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci, the nation's leading infectious disease doctor, on Tuesday, said he supports any effort from local governments to mandate that teachers be vaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid delta surge, confusion again reigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amid-delta-surge-confusion-again-reigns-16376462.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, IDAHO - Ben Lemons, an elementary school principal, received a coronavirus vaccine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Threatens to WithHold Salaries...</title>
      <link>https://npr.org/2021/08/09/1026299001/florida-governor-desantis-school-superintendent-salary-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis ratcheted up a confrontation with school superintendents on Monday, saying anyone who defies his ban on mask mandates might lose a paycheck. Teachers and staff wouldn't be punished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810082158-s7pg3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-CHINA/DRILLS (TV):Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women filmmakers denounce cinema prize for Depp...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-arts-and-entertainment-9b1b8b4ab954f19552c3240e53edc39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain's leading group of women filmmakers on Tuesday condemned the San Sebastian film festival’s decision to award Johnny Depp its highest honor, saying it gave the international event a bad name after a British judge ruled last year that allegations of domestic violence against the actor were “substantially correct".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Sell Fast, Homeowners Making Mansions Move-In Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/corcoran-ceo-pamela-liebman-interview-which-houses-selling-fast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Sell Fast, Homeowners Are Making Their Mansions Move-In Ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals parceling out beds, hunting for doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/delta-strains-hospitals-across-u-s-as-unvaccinated-fill-icus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Strains Hospitals Across U.S. as Unvaccinated Fill ICUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN fears erasure of human rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810111411-58tfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Taliban tighten control of Afghan north as UN fears erasure of human rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings record 10.1 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-4c614d89c69b4afd3504a4d92dd574f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers posted a record 10.1 million job openings in June, another sign that the job market and economy are bouncing back briskly from last year's coronavirus shutdowns. Job openings rose from 9.5 million in May, the Labor Department reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
