<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>8-1 vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/san-francisco-bans-facial-recognition-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first such move by a major city against the use of the technology by police and all other municipal agencies. Civil liberty groups are uneasy about its potential abuse by government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drowning in Debt: Areas with higest taxpayer burden...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/cities-drowning-debt-chicago-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s 10 largest cities, largely Democrat strongholds, are drowning in municipal debt, according to a new report from government watchdog Truth in Accounting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrorism joke gets cops called on comedian Ahmed Ahmed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/14/terrorism-joke-gets-cops-called-on-egyptian-american-comedian-ahmed-ahmed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Egyptian-American comedian had the cops called on him after a stand-up set in Florida over the weekend — when an audience member took his joke about terrorism seriously. Funnyman Ahmed Ahm…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Schmidt defends GOOGLE censored search plan...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/05/14/google-search-china-eric-schmidt-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Google CEO also claimed that employees building the search engine, Dragonfly, knew what they were working on — contradicting what they have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis Ford Coppola Looks Back On Career -- And Next Chapter...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/francis-ford-coppola-apocalypse-now-cannes-40-anniversary-megalopolis-scorsese-godfather-part-ii-re-cutting-godfather-iii-cotton-club-interview-1202613659/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: He was one of the defining voices of the auteur ’70s, having made some of the greatest and most ambitious films ever attempted. The films included The Godfather trilogy, Apocalypse Now a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-year-old girl arrested for DWI after high-speed chase...</title>
      <link>https://www.krqe.com/news/new-mexico/police-video-shows-12-year-old-new-mexico-girl-get-arrested-for-dwi/1999787692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krqe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a disturbing arrest—a 12-year-old girl popped for DWI and leading police on a chase with her friends in the car in Alamogordo. Lapel video obtained by KRQE News 13 shows the end of the situation that could’ve ended very badly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck in equipment, farmer amputates own leg with knife to save life...</title>
      <link>https://www.ketv.com/article/farmer-amputate-own-leg-to-save-his-life/27438602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ketv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local farmer amputated his own leg to save his life after getting stuck in farming equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trackers not sure why Great Whites 'clustering' off NC Outer Banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-tribune.com/news/20190510/great-whites-cluster-off-outer-banks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-tribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OUTER BANKS — A “clustering” of great white sharks off North Carolina’s Outer Banks has grabbed the attention of shark trackers,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,317-lb monster named 'Luna' en route...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article230332489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot aims to keep peace between drivers, cops...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/This-robot-aims-to-keep-the-peace-between-13844425.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Reuben Brewer had been reading tragic news reports about police officers and motorists being killed and injured during traffic stops gone awry.  The root of the problem, he eventually realized, was fear, the powerful, anticipatory anxiety that can overwhelm a hyper-vigilant officer or cause a motorist to behave in ways that arouse suspicion, leading to a violent encounter.  Brewer knew he couldn't take guns from people who shouldn't wield them or single-handedly remove poorly trained police officers from American streets, but he wondered if there was a way to lower the temperature of everyday encounters between jittery police officers and the large numbers of drivers who fear for their lives each time police lights flash in their rearview mirror.  After 16 months of research and development, Brewer - a senior robotics researcher at the nonprofit SRI International in Menlo Park, California - has unveiled his solution: a robot that allows police officers to conduct traffic stops without leaving the safety of their vehicle.  "The main advantage of a robot over a human is that physical danger no longer matters," Brewer wrote after being reached by email. "The robot is purely defensive, so it can't hurt the motorist. If the motorist damages the robot, it's only money to replace it."  "People are more dangerous when they're scared, so the goal is to remove the possibility of being physically hurt so that they're less scared and less dangerous," he added.  Police officers make more than 50,000 traffic stops each day, according to The Stanford Open Policing Project, an effort that has tracked more than 200 million stops in recent years and found significant disparities in policing.  A survey released by the Bureau of Justice Statistics in 2014 found that black motorists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING WARS: DISNEY takes  HULU to challenge NETFLIX, AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-comcast-hulu/disney-takes-control-of-hulu-to-challenge-netflix-amazon-idUSKCN1SK1KI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney Co said it will take full control of the Hulu service in a deal with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next up for COMCAST? Its own service...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/business/comcast/comcast-hulu-disney-philadelphia-nbcuniversal-netflix-fox-20190514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast also agreed to license Comcast-owned NBCUniversal shows and content to Hulu, though NBCUniversal could take those shows off Hulu to stream on its own service. NBCUniversal's streaming service is expected to launch in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. reaches deal to testify with Senate Intel...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/443701-trump-jr-reaches-deal-to-testify-with-senate-intelligence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump Jr. has struck a last-minute deal to comply with a subpoena from the Senate Intelligence Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Journalism has become more subjective...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-05-journalism-subjective.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S.-based journalism has gradually shifted away from objective news and offers more opinion-based content that appeals to emotion and relies heavily on argumentation and advocacy, according to a new RAND Corporation report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran on brink of banning facial recognition... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/SF-could-ban-facial-recognition-software-13842657.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Board of Supervisors is considering a proposal to ban departments from using facial recognition software. While privacy advocates applaud, others say it will restrict a useful tool in solving crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE CHANGE: Ocasio-Cortez Beefs With Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/14/723298209/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-decries-biden-middle-of-the-road-approach-on-climate-ch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I will be damned if the same politicians who refused to act then are going to try to come back today and say we need to find a middle-of-the-road approach to save our lives," the N.Y. Democrat said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe begs critics to CALM DOWN!</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/05/14/joe-biden-defends-his-record-on-climate-change-tells-critics-to-calm-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden defended his record on climate change, asking critics like Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez to "calm down."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Officials Worry Homeless Campers Weakening Levees...</title>
      <link>https://fox40.com/2019/05/13/city-officials-worry-homeless-campers-are-weakening-sacramentos-levees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox40.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO -- Homeless camps along the Sacramento and American rivers are creating a potential problem that could affect thousands. Denise Plescia, who lives nearby, often sees the homeless camps all along the rivers. "They find places to hide, like that bush right there," she told FOX40. Now, some of the campers may be putting Plescia’s home at risk by compromising the structural integrity of the levees themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biscuit heiress defends family's Nazi-era slave labor...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/05/14/choco-leibniz-biscuit-heiress-defends-familys-nazi-era-slave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 25-year-old heiress to the German business behind Choco Leibniz biscuits has been accused of trivialising the company&amp;rsquo;s Nazi past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney rejects judicial pick who smeared Obama...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/14/romney-truncale-1321299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;He made particularly disparaging comments about President Obama. And as the Republican nominee for president, I just couldn't subscribe to that,&amp;quot; Romney says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton beats war drums...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190514-bolton-beats-war-drums-us-iran-standoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolton beats war drums in US-Iran standoff</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive immigration, marriage fraud ring spread throughout Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/immigration/2019/05/14/massive-immigration-marriage-fraud-ring-spread-throughout-texas-feds-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration agents broke up a massive marriage fraud ring in Houston that involved nearly 100 people throughout Texas and overseas accused of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New security flaw in INTEL chips...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8e8543a6813a4540a1eeed5a44a6d25a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA CLARA, Calif. (AP) — Intel has revealed another hardware security flaw that could affects millions of machines around the world. The bug is embedded in the architecture of computer...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank-and-file Dems urge 'second look' at impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/rank-file-house-democrats-urge-second-look-impeachment-n1005496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some members of the House Judiciary Committee think “stronger tools” are needed to force the Trump administration to comply with requests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What helps prevent dementia? Try exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/what-helps-prevent-dementia-try-exercise-not-vitamin-pills-n1005391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although age is the top risk factor, “dementia is not a natural or inevitable consequence of aging,” says the World Health Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto bemoans 'privilege' and 'elitist' campaign launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/beto-the-view-elitist-privilege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O'Rourke, D-Texas, tried rebooting his 2020 campaign on "The View" Tuesday, admitting that he made some missteps in his initial launch earlier in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Extremely Scary' Wild Turkeys Terrorize Boston Neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/05/13/jamaica-plain-residents-fear-wild-turkeys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wild turkeys are going after residents of a Boston neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge skeptical of Trump effort to keep records from House...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ca1d43081d54d96bcc8b5f5038e0ddd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge suggested Tuesday he is skeptical of President Donald Trump's efforts to block Congress from obtaining some of his financial records. Judge Amit Mehta spent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida may create prostitution registry for pimps, johns...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2019/05/14/florida-may-create-prostitution-registry-for-pimps-and-johns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To deter pimps and johns, lawmakers voted to create the “Soliciting for Prostitution Public Database,” which lists the names, addresses and color photographs of people who are convicted or plead no contest to soliciting prostitution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Cuban: Wake-up call for Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/14/mark-cuban-says-hes-not-surprised-by-ubers-disappointing-ipo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Cuban also tells CNBC that Uber's IPO reflects poorly on Silicon Valley's venture capital investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Zombie cells' may play role in aging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6da65f221b6b4d9aba69962c670432e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Call them zombie cells — they refuse to die. As they build up in your body, studies suggest, they promote aging and the conditions that come with it like osteoporosis and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary comic Tim Conway dead at 85...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/legendary-comic-tim-conway-dead-85-n1005486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The venerable actor was best known for his TV work on "McHale's Navy" and "The Carol Burnett Show."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy releases probe into 'sky penis' drawing...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2019/05/14/the-navys-probe-into-sky-penis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time, the tale can be told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traveling carnival worker admits to being serial killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.knoxnews.com/story/news/crime/2019/05/13/carnival-worker-charged-killing-two-tennessee-women-georgia-teen/1193988001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.knoxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Michael Wright, 23, is accused of carrying out the killings near his home in Washington County, Virginia, over the span of three weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70-year-old put dead wife in passenger seat, drove across AZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/nation-world/national/article230376309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Belichick belittles Brady...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/14/how-bill-belichick-belittles-tom-brady-gisele-gq-taunts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Belichick even called out Tom Brady during the Patriots’ 16-0 regular season in 2007. Former New England fullback Heath Evans shared a few telling tales about the relationship between the lege…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain pulls frigate from Gulf build-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/spain-pulls-frigate-us-military-build-gulf-105857435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain has recalled a frigate accompanying a US aircraft carrier to the Middle East because of rising tensions between Washington and Tehran, the defence ministry said Tuesday. "For the moment the frigate Mendez Nunez has left the combat group of the USS Abraham Lincoln," a ministry spokesman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon walks tightrope over 'maximum pressure'... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pentagon-walks-tightrope-over-trumps-maximum-pressure-iran-150137215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon, which has sent an aircraft carrier and B-52 bombers to the Gulf, is hoping to defuse the risks posed to US troops in the Middle East by President Donald Trump's "maximum pressure" strategy on Iran. US National Security Advisor John Bolton cited "a number of troubling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump denies considering 120,000 troops to counter threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-iran-military/trump-denies-u-s-military-considering-120000-troops-to-counter-iran-threat-idUSKCN1SK1YM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Tuesday denied a New York Times report that U.S. offic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians accessed voter records in 2 Florida counties, FBI confirms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2019/05/14/russians-accessed-voter-records-in-two-florida-counties-fbi-confirms-1015760</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hacking did not affect any vote tallying and DeSantis said there is no evidence of 'manipulation.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Revolutionary Communists' descend on UCLA; Advocate overthrow of system... </title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=12223</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overthrow what?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support among young voters drops sharply...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/443547-poll-sanders-support-among-young-voters-drops-sharply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) has seen his support drop sharply among the young voters that have powered his rise in Democratic politics, according to a new poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest breach of personal data...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/whatsapp-hack-latest-breach-personal-data-security-135037749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hacking of WhatsApp -- in which spyware was sneaked into phones, compromising personal data -- is one of the most spectacular of a series of such attacks in recent years. The instant messaging service used by 1.5 billion people worldwide said Tuesday a security breach had allowed sophisticated attackers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE SHUT...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/satellite-images-show-oil-tankers-033939658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oil pipeline that runs across Saudi Arabia was hit by drones Tuesday west of its capital of Riyadh, the Saudi energy minister said, shortly after rebels in Yemen claimed they carried out coordinated drone strikes against the kingdom. The attacks followed reports of sabotage against oil tankers in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC Wants Oscars To Stay Hostless...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/oscars-2020-hostless-abc-jimmy-kimmel-karey-burke-upfronts-1202614386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 92nd Academy Awards may look a lot like the 91st Academy Awards, if ABC has its way. “We’re extremely proud of how the show turned out creatively” ABC Entertainment boss Karey Burke circumspect…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN SAYS U.S. 'FALSE FLAG' DRONE ATTACK ON SAUDI OIL TANKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2019-05-14/yemeni-armed-drones-attack-saudi-oil-pipeline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington named best state in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/articles/2019-05-14/amazon-clean-power-help-fuel-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp hackers install surveillance on users' phones -- just by CALLING...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9069211/whatsapp-surveillance-cyber-attack-glitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HACKERS installed spy software on phones using a major WhatsApp flaw just by calling them, it was revealed last night. Even if the call was not picked up, the software would be installed. It gave h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Men think about sports more than sex!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sun-men/9070497/men-think-about-football-more-than-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT’S a well accepted idea that men typically think about sex every seven seconds. But according to a new study that’s a myth – we’re far more likely to have football on our …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLASTS 'GREEDY AND ARROGANT' TRUMP </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9070365/china-peoples-war-trade-war-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has called for a “people’s war” while hitting out at the “greed and arrogance” of the US amid an escalating trade dispute with Washington. Beijing’s state-run media has went into propaganda o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Turns Down FOXNEWS Town Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/elizabeth-warren-turns-down-fox-news-town-hall-calling-the-network-a-hate-for-profit-racket/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic candidate said that she does not want encourage additional ad dollars for the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Superyacht Showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jimdobson/2019/05/12/billionaire-superyacht-showdown-whos-who-at-the-2019-cannes-film-festival/#5b91ba791a38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's greatest superyachts all convene during the Cannes Film Festival and the Monaco Grand Prix in May. Celebrities like Brad Pitt, Leonardo DiCaprio, and Elton John will all be part of this annual display of the wealthiest individuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN:  Tariffs -- The Taxes That Made America Great...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/patrick-j-buchanan/tariffs-taxes-made-america-great</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shipping container is offloaded from the Hong Kong based CSCL East China Sea container ship at the Port of Oakland on June 20, 2018 in Oakland, California. (Photo by Justin Sullivan/Getty Images)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran says Trump risking 'devastating war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/05/14/iran-trump-bolton-dragging-tehran-devastating-and-unnecessary-war/3664144002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranâ€™s ambassador to the UK said the Trump administration's military deployment because of unspecified Iranian threats risked 'serious miscalculation.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mel Gibson casting in Rothchild comedy sparks outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/may/14/mel-gibson-casting-in-rothchild-comedy-sparks-outrage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of the film, set among the New York super-rich, attracts criticism in wake of the actor’s previous antisemitism controversies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA VOWS 'PEOPLE'S WAR'</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/technology/businessinsider/article/Beijing-calls-for-a-people-s-war-against-the-US-13843480.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getty Images / Thomas Peter-Pool    The US-China trade war has dramatically escalated over the past few days, with both sides announcing tariff increases on billions of dollars' worth of each other's goods.   Chinese state media - which functions as a Communist Party mouthpiece - issued a series of rabble-rousing statements on Monday accusing the US of "greed and arrogance" and calling for a "people's war" against it.   President Donald Trump's administration on Monday night threatened to impose tariffs of up to 25% on another $300 billion worth of Chinese goods.   If such tariffs were to be imposed, almost all Chinese imports to the US would be subject to tariffs.   Trump tweeted on Tuesday that his "respect and friendship" with Chinese President Xi Jinping was "unlimited" but that "this must be a great deal for the United States or it just doesn't make any sense."   Visit Business Insider's homepage for more stories .   The US-China trade war continues to heat up, with Beijing calling for a "people's war" against Washington and President Donald Trump threatening to impose tariffs on another $300 billion worth of Chinese goods.  In a series of editorials and op-ed articles published Monday, Chinese state media slammed what it labeled the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSUMERS PAY PRICE</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-tariffs-consumer-price-effect-20190514-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumer prices on luggage and major appliances such as washing machines have already increased as a result of previous rounds of tariffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes Rolls Out Red Carpet -- But Does Anyone Care?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/cannes-film-festival-diary-does-anyone-still-care-1210424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the fest prepares for the opening night of its 72nd edition, insiders predict a very muted affair, devoid of the glitz and hits of years gone by: "The business is changing, but I don't feel like the festival’s moving along with it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GULF SIMMERS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mystery-shrouds-sabotage-oil-tankers-tense-gulf-110200997.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone attacks claimed by Iran-aligned Yemen rebels shut down one of Saudi Arabia's main oil pipelines Tuesday, further ratcheting up Gulf tensions after the mysterious sabotage of several tankers. Days after the United States deployed bombers and an assault ship to bolster an aircraft carrier in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong 7.7 quake strikes east of Papua New Guinea -USGS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190514130229-2zk6l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUAKE-PAPUA/ (URGENT):Strong 7.7 quake strikes east of Papua New Guinea -USGS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Dusk festival, L.A.'s techno underground heads into the woods...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment/music/la-et-ms-dusk-festival-20190514-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dusk festival, held on a Native American reservation two hours from L.A., provides fans an alternative to large-scale, hyper-branded music events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Tower Now One of NYC's Least-Desirable Luxury Buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-14/trump-tower-is-now-one-of-nyc-s-least-desirable-luxury-buildings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear wasteland: Inside ghost towns of Fukushima...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/nuclear-wasteland-inside-ghost-towns-135129364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was a chilling silence in the town of Tomioka in the days after the March 2011 Fukushima nuclear disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed patriots vow continued patrols as monthly border crossings reach 100,000...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/armed-patriots-vow-continued-patrols-as-monthly-border-crossings-reach-100000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An armed group of citizen patriots patrolling the U.S.-Mexico border in New Mexico have vowed to continue operations to assist Border Patrol despite an eviction from their previous camp. Jim Benvie, spokesman for the newly formed Guardian Patriots, told the Las Cruces Sun News numerous “volunteer patriots” continue to patrol sections of the New Mexico …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record number attacks on gays in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/record-number-attacks-gays-france-report-060709210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assaults in France on lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people hit a new record in 2018, "a dark year" for the LGBT community, French group SOS Homophobie reported Tuesday. The non-profit association registered 231 physical attacks, up from the previous annual record of 188 anti-LGBT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington named best state in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/05/14/washington-top-state-overall-u-s-news-best-states-rankings/1188577001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, home to tech giants such as Amazon and Microsoft, was named the top state in U.S. News &amp; World Report's Best States rankings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes kicks off as clouds of controversy gather...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/may/13/cannes-2019-party-kicks-off-as-clouds-of-controversy-gather-netflix-quentin-tarantino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the film festival’s 72nd edition begins, disputes surrounding gender parity, Netflix and Quentin Tarantino won’t go away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPP flaw let hackers install spyware on phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/whatsapp-flaw-let-hackers-install-spyware-on-cellphones-when-people-made-or-got-calls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Signs point to Israeli company NSO, which works with governments, often to spy on human rights activists; spyware kicked in when people made or got calls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER Blame Game Focuses on MORGAN STANLEY...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/uber-blame-game-focuses-morgan-014218827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now it gets to field the second-guessing after Uber Technologies Inc. tumbled 18% in its first two days of trading. Across Wall Street, questions are flying: Why did bankers including Morgan Stanley’s suggest a $120 billion valuation last year that Uber couldn’t deliver? Did the syndicate led by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First court test arrives in Trump-House showdown over probes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-court-mazars/first-court-test-arrives-in-trump-u-s-house-showdown-over-probes-idUSKCN1SK13A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal court for the first time on Tuesday will step into the intensifying cl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another TESLA Spontaneously Catches Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china-hongkong/tesla-car-catches-fire-in-hong-kong-parking-lot-media-idUSKCN1SK0G1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tesla Inc electric car caught fire in a parking lot in a Hong Kong shopping ma...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eurovision Arrives in Tel Aviv, in Range of Rockets, Focus of Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/14/world/middleeast/eurovision-israel-tel-aviv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hosting an annual international song contest, Tel Aviv has tried to remain an island of secular liberalism divorced from Israel’s troubles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frat busted for 'hazing' dog...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/13/hofstra-fraternity-suspended-dog-drink-beer-keg/1195906001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York university has suspended a fraternity after a video shared on social media showed members forcing a dog to drink fromÂ a beer keg at a party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete has 0% support among South Carolina black voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/politics/the-safe-choice-biden-widens-sc-lead-in-democratic-presidential/article_f727895c-731f-11e9-888a-af4280777b2a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that he's in the race, former Vice President Joe Biden has widened his lead in South Carolina among 2020 Democratic presidential candidates, a new poll found. His support his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYBACK:  Barr Assigns Top Prosecutor to Review Russia Inquiry Origins...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/barr-assigns-us-attorney-in-connecticut-to-review-origins-of-russia-inquiry/ar-AABjF9U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M O N O P O L Y</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/apples-loss-at-the-supreme-court-is-a-big-victory-for-consumers-fighting-big-techs-app-and-platform-monopolies-2019-05-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc. was dealt a major setback in an eight-year-old lawsuit over the app store by the U.S. Supreme Court on Monday, in a decision that could have a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS SEES TRILLION PEOPLE LIVING IN SPACE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7024897/Jeff-Bezos-futuristic-vision-self-sustaining-habitat-house-TRILLION-people-space.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Building off of a concept introduced by physicist Gerard O'Neill – who Bezos himself studied under during his time at Princeton – the Blue Origin founder outlined habitats that could hold cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Spending Sets Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/terence-p-jeffrey/2573708000000-federal-spending-sets-all-time-record-through-april</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Getty Images/Win McNamee)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE IN CROSSHAIRS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/13/why-is-apple-so-vulnerable-to-a-trade-war-with-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is down over 6% on Monday after news of a major escalation in the U.S.-China trade war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GULF TENSIONS FLARE...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/saudi-oil-tankers-hit-sabotage-attacks-gulf-tensions-100602956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four ships, including two Saudi oil tankers, were damaged in mysterious "sabotage attacks" that inflamed Gulf tensions on Monday amid a standoff between the United States and Iran. In the face of growing international concern, US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo scrapped a planned visit to Moscow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costly face tattoo removals on the rise as regret sets in...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/13/costly-face-tattoo-removals-on-the-rise-as-regret-sets-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mauricio Arias wears his past on his face: 11 tattoos cover his skin from his eyelids to his cheeks, down to his neck. Images like a bloodied knife and brass knuckles tell the story of a five-year …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA STRIKES BACK</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/caca73d420354d3497c6b4fe32437687</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Sending Wall Street into a slide, China announced higher tariffs Monday on $60 billion worth of American goods in retaliation for President Donald Trump's latest penalties on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shockwaves in Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/05/13/apples-supreme-court-loss-sends-antitrust-shockwaves-through-silicon-valley</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's loss in a high-stakes Supreme Court case on Monday could expose Silicon Valley to heightened antitrust oversight, threatening a slew of new lawsuits and other legal salvos that challenge the tech industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deploy 120,000 troops' if attacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9069070/us-deploy-troops-middle-east-iran-iraq-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US is planning to deploy as many as 120,000 troops to the Middle East if Iran attacks American forces, a bombshell report claimed last night. In chilling echoes of the invasion of Iraq, US defe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama abortion bill's restrictions weigh on Republicans ahead of vote... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Alabama-abortion-bill-s-restrictions-weigh-on-13842575.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OXFORD, Ala. - On Monday, a day before Alabama lawmakers were scheduled to vote on a bill that would all but ban abortion in the state, Republican Del Marsh, president of the state senate, asked a group of young mothers - toddlers bouncing on their laps - what they want the Legislature to do.  "How do y'all feel about banning abortion, even in cases of rape and incest?" he asked the women, who gathered at tables outside a Southern Girl Coffee truck here, on the edge of Talladega National Forest, about 100 miles from Montgomery.  "I'm praying for y'all, and I wouldn't want your job," sighed Lauren Holland, 32, her 2-year-old daughter climbing on her chest. She said she would have the baby if she were raped, but making that the law? "That there is real hard for women. I'm a Christian. One-hundred percent pro-life. But I don't think I want that in the law."  Marsh asked the women to keep praying for him as he navigates a contentious fight that could put Alabama on the leading edge of the anti-abortion push to get a state law in front of the U.S. Supreme Court. He, like many other Republicans here, has long been against abortion and wants the court to overturn Roe v. Wade - and he embraces the strategy of a bill that will force the issue. But he also long has been accepting of three exceptions to bans on abortion: cases that involve rape, incest or when the mother's life is in danger.  Marsh and some others in the Republican majority here are struggling with Tuesday's vote on an abortion ban, largely because it is so restrictive. Any unborn baby is innocent and deserves a chance at life, the bill's backers argue, even those that are the result of violent or criminal origins.  "It's just, I'm not real comfortable with having a law that forces a woman to carry a baby after rape," Marsh said.  A move to amend the bill last week...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$2 Billion Verdict Against MONSANTO Is Third to Find Roundup Caused Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/13/723056453/california-jury-awards-2-billion-to-couple-in-roundup-weed-killer-cancer-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The verdict represents the third time a California jury has decided in favor of consumers who claimed their cancer was caused by the glyphosate-based Roundup weed killer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Raid on San Francisco reporter's home condemned as 'an attack' on 1st Amendment...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/raid-on-san-francisco-reporter-s-home-condemned-as-an/article_fa172899-09e0-5c25-bde6-b36bd8bf2a63.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco Police Department appears to have violated state and federal laws when its officers searched the San Francisco home of a journalist in an apparent bid to identify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest brothel throws down challenge to sex robots: 'They can't compete'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/778000/sex-robots-world-s-biggest-brothel-sheri-s-ranch-nevada-dena-prostitution-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUMP TREASURIES?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/13/chinas-self-destructive-nuclear-option-in-trade-war-selling-us-treasury-bonds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possibility that China might stop being the world's biggest consumer of U.S. debt again reared its imposing head Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majestic wild horses are being chased, bitten by unleashed dogs roaming Outer Banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article230340449.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House reviews military plans against Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/iran-military-troops-john-bolton-1d4a714c-ea52-483f-b392-2ac2af01f423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan was reportedly ordered by White House national security adviser John Bolton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will political correctness kill classic movies?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/443282-will-political-correctness-kill-classic-movies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to wipe clean questionable content is happening all around us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's most disgusting subway car...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/11/this-is-new-york-citys-most-disgusting-subway-car/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is ‘litter-ally’ the most vile subway car in New York City. Repugnant video posted to Facebook on Tuesday shows a southbound 2 train at the Allerton Avenue stop in the Bronx that looks like it…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigating rappers' ties to shootings around Miami...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d822e9ecfb764848b72da5887be5b8c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A weekend of shootings involving rap musicians and their entourages who were in South Florida for a huge hip-hop festival left two people dead, four wounded and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules against APPLE in App Store antitrust...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9e09bdac11b947b8877613a3a3fb192d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Consumers can pursue a lawsuit complaining that iPhone apps cost too much, the Supreme Court ruled on Monday, adding to Apple's woes that already include falling iPhone sales and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FARMERS FEEL PAIN </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d2c9d14c1de465c96384dda36b61514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — China's announcement Monday of higher tariffs on $60 billion of American exports — retaliation for President Donald Trump's latest penalties on Chinese goods — hit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN OPEN TO BREAKING UP FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71c998ad3b39486ca1dcc220201b68b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMPTON, N.H. (AP) — Joe Biden said Monday that he would be open to breaking up Facebook, a sign of the deep skepticism among many Democratic presidential contenders about the power of massive...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France, New Zealand to launch a call to end online 'extremism'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b844de2f3cb49d69afb9b8604ba7983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The leaders of France and New Zealand will make a joint push to eliminate acts of violent extremism from being shown online, in a meeting with tech leaders in Paris on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrestler dies in ring and crowd thinks it's part of staged bout...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/wrestler-dies-during-match-but-it-was-so-staged-at-first-no-one-knew-anything-was-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A well-known Mexican wrestler who co-starred in the film comedy &amp;quot;Nacho Libre&amp;quot; died in London after he collapsed during a match that a witness described as so elaborately staged it wasn't immediately clear something seriously was wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -617</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190513234255-3mene</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA (WRAPUP 7, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 7-Trump and Xi to meet after defiant China hits U.S. with new tariffs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-minute change of heart foiled secret plot to oust Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Inside-the-secret-plot-to-turn-senior-Venezuelan-13842388.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late one night in April, a week before Venezuela's opposition launched its abortive uprising, four men sat on the terrace of the hillside compound in Caracas belonging to the chief justice of the country's Supreme Court. The dim lights of the capital twinkling below them, they sipped Fiji bottled water as they plotted the ouster of President Nicolás Maduro.  Maduro's spy chief, Gen. Christopher Figuera, and Cesar Omaña, a 39-year-old Venezuelan businessman based in Miami, were trying to seal a deal hashed out over weeks with Maikel Moreno, the chief justice, according to one of the participants in the meeting. Figuera and Omaña were part of the plan to force Maduro out, but they needed Moreno's help.  Moreno, sitting before an ashtray laden with the stubs of Cuban cigars, appeared to be having doubts. The 53-year-old jurist voiced concerns about Juan Guaidó, the U.S.-backed opposition leader who would become the nation's interim president if the plot succeeded.  Then, according to the participant, Moreno offered another candidate to "temporarily" lead the broken country - himself.  "In the end, he was trying to safeguard his own power play," one senior opposition figure said.  This account is based on hours of interviews with three people familiar with the talks: the participant, a senior opposition official who was kept informed on the developments, and a senior U.S. official briefed on the talks. The account also sheds new light on the key question of what went wrong in the Venezuelan opposition's high-stakes move to oust Maduro on April 30.  The three people, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal tactics, said Moreno's hesitant pledge to cooperate - and then his reversal - played a crucial role in the plan's collapse.  The failure of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:  DECIDING ON MORE TARIFFS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/13/trump-says-he-will-meet-with-xi-and-putin-at-g20-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump also confirmed that he plans to meet with Chinese President Xi Jinping and Russian President Vladimir Putin at the G-20 summit in Japan in late June.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
