<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>For first time, spacecraft caught active satellite to extend its life...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/northrop-grumman-mev-2-spacecraft-services-intelsat-1002-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northrop Grumman and Intelsat accomplished a space industry first on Monday, with a small spacecraft docking with an active satellite in orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservationists spreading pathogens to threatened species?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210412-are-conservationists-spreading-pathogens-to-threatened-species</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are conservationists spreading pathogens to threatened species?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER -- but for cannabis delivery...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/uber-ceo-says-company-could-get-into-cannabis-delivery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber could start delivering cannabis once federal regulation allows the company to do so, CEO Dara Khosrowshahi told CNBC on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistook Handgun For Taser?</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/12/holy-st-i-just-shot-him-brooklyn-center-releases-body-camera-footage-of-police-killing-of-daunte-wright/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a press conference Monday afternoon, officials in Brooklyn Center released body camera footage of the fatal police shooting of 20-year-old Daunte Wright.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine President heads to trenches as Russia masses troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/12/europe/ukraine-zelensky-front-lines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of Russian troops gathered across the Ukrainian border are raising fears of an invasion. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky visited troops on the front line and told CNN he wants more support from the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  MICHIGAN NEEDS TO CLOSE</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-michigan-cdc-director-vaccine-3a387859-a6d9-4e17-81d2-56ff6d747d89.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rochelle Walensky said the state can't vaccinate its way out of the surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moby on fame and regret: 'I was out-of-control, utterly entitled drug addict'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/apr/12/moby-on-fame-and-regret-i-was-an-out-of-control-utterly-entitled-drink-and-drug-addict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He declared his intention to go away for a while after pointed criticism of his second memoir. But now the musician is back with a new album - and a visceral documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bogus reporter grilled Jen Psaki for weeks!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/09/lego-gamer-infiltrated-white-house-press-480673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Kacey Montagu" posed as a reporter for the fictitious WHN and managed to fool real correspondents — and even the new Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States growing fewer trees. Forest owners say that's a problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/04/05/states-are-growing-fewer-trees-forest-owners-say-thats-a-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of America’s forestland is privately owned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ROCK Says He'll Run For President If It's 'What The People Want'...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/dwayne-johnson-says-hell-run-for-president-if-its-what-the-people-want-163810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor recently reacted to a poll that found that at least 46 percent of Americans would support his run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's priciest painting may be a Leonardo after all!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worlds-priciest-painting-may-leonardo-143932092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most expensive painting, the "Salvator Mundi", may be the work of Leonardo da Vinci after all, with several media reports contradicting doubts raised in a French documentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Prison threatens to force-feed Navalny...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-prison-threatens-force-feed-134718237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian prison officials are threatening to start force-feeding jailed Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny, his team said Monday, after he lost eight kilograms (18 pounds) since starting a hunger strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran accuses Israel of sabotage at nuclear site, vows revenge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-blames-israel-attack-natanz-090343038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran charged Monday that its arch-enemy Israel was behind an attack on its Natanz uranium enrichment plant and vowed it would take "revenge" and ramp up its nuclear activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers developing blood test to gauge depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/researchers-develop-blood-test-that-could-help-gauge-depression-bipolar-disorder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they found a way to tell from a person’s blood how severe their depression is, the risk of developing severe depression in the future and the risk of future bipolar disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov. says state 'very close' to herd immunity. Data tells different story...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/article/abbott-herd-immunity-texas-16093952.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rallies fizzle...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/unlawful-assembly-declared-white-supremacist-rally-9536047a-f3ab-4faf-b299-580a40164d19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poor showings demonstrate how the white supremacist movement has been driven underground since the U.S. Capitol riots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>536:  Historians pinpoint very worst year EVER to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/historians-pinpoint-the-very-worst-year-to-ever-be-alive/927803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next time you think we have it hard today, remember what life was like during this truly terrible year. Even after it ended, a decade of pain and suffering followed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives fight for leverage amid ever-slimming majority...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/547454-progressives-fight-for-leverage-amid-ever-slimming-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are ascendant in the Democratic-controlled Congress, but they may not have the political leverage to dramatically shape legislative priorities like President Biden’s infrastructure and jobs package as they return to Washington this week with an even slimmer majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE:  Navy destroyer captures mysterious flashing UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2683726/us-navy-filmed-ufo-sky-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Pentagon has admitted the US Navy filmed “pyramid” and “spherical” shaped UFOs buzzing two warships. Startling footage captured by a US Navy destroyer using night vision…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'White Lives Matter' rally ends early as outnumbered marchers chased by counter-protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2681680/white-lives-matter-rally-huntington-beach-counter-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “WHITE Lives Matter” rally in Orange County was cut short after the marchers were outnumbered and chased down by a hundreds-strong swarm of “anti-fascist” counter-proteste…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman high on bath salts claiming to be Harry Potter kills federal judge in hit-and-run...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/new-york-judge-killed-by-erratic-hit-and-run-driver-in-possession-of-bath-salts-police/2992432/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman who claimed she is Harry Potter struck and killed a federal judge visiting from New York and seriously injured a 6-year-old boy after swerving her car onto a sidewalk, officials said. The crash occurred Friday morning in Boca Raton, Florida. According to multiple reports, U.S. District Judge Sandra Feuerstein was walking on a sidewalk when a car…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA NOT:  Gaetz denied audience with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/11/politics/matt-gaetz-donald-trump-denied-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz, who's facing a federal investigation into sex trafficking allegations, was recently denied a meeting with Donald Trump at his Mar-a-Lago estate as the ex-President and his allies continue to distance themselves from the Florida congressman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS RAMPAGES THROUGH INDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/coronavirus-india-becomes-second-worst-hit-country-as-covid-cases-surge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Asian nation reported more than 168,000 new cases over a 24-hour period on Monday, according to health ministry data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes Potential Threat From China's Digital Yuan Plans...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-team-eyes-potential-threat-220001877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Biden administration is stepping up scrutiny of China’s plans for a digital yuan, with some officials concerned the move could kick off a long-term bid to topple the dollar as the world’s dominant reserve currency, according to people familiar with the matter.Now that China’s digital-currency efforts are gathering momentum, officials at the Treasury, State Department, Pentagon and National Security Council are bolstering their efforts to understand the potential implications, the people said.American officials are less worried about an immediate challenge to the current structure of the global financial system, but are eager to understand how the digital yuan will be distributed, and whether it could also be used to work around U.S. sanctions, the people said on the condition of anonymity.A Treasury spokeswoman declined to comment. A National Security Council spokeswoman did not reply to a request for comment.The People’s Bank of China has rolled out trial issuance of a digital yuan in cities across the country, putting it on track to be the first major central bank to issue a virtual currency. A broader roll-out is expected for the Winter Olympics in Beijing next February, giving the effort international exposure.Many key details of the digital yuan are still in flux, including specifics on how it would be distributed. China’s recent establishment of a joint venture with SWIFT, the messaging nexus through which most cross-border settlements pass through today, suggests it is possible a digital yuan could work within the current financial architecture rather than outside of it.U.S. officials are reassured that China’s intentions aren’t to use the digital yuan to evade American sanctions, according to people familiar with the matter. The dollar’s current dominance in cross-border transactions gives the U.S. Treasury the power to cut off much of a business or even a country’s access to the global financial system.China’s officials have said the main intentions of the digital yuan are to replace banknotes and coins, to reduce the incentive to use cryptocurrencies and to complement the current private-sector run electronic payments system -- dominated by Ant Group Co.’s Alipay and Tencent Holdings Ltd.’s WeChat Pay. The PBOC has been working for years on the digital yuan, also called the e-CNY, having set up a specialist research team in 2014.Here’s How a Central Bank Digital Currency Could Work: Chart​​“To provide a backup or redundancy for the retail payment system, the central bank has to step up” and provide digital-currency services, Mu Changchun, the director of the PBOC’s digital-currency research institute, said at an event last month.Beyond seeking a backup to privately run e-payments, Chinese regulators have more broadly been expanding their oversight of the country’s digital champions. Ant Group was told by Beijing to become a financial holding company, which will be regulated more like a bank. China also imposed a $2.8 billion antitrust fine on Ant’s affiliate Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.Read More: Ant to Be Financial Holding Firm in Overhaul Forced by ChinaThe PBOC is also examining the potential for using the digital yuan in cross-border payments, launching a project studying the issue with a unit of the Bank for International Settlements along with the United Arab Emirates, Thailand and Hong Kong’s monetary authority.The Biden administration isn’t currently planning to take any action to counter longer-term threats from China’s digital currency, the people familiar with the discussions said. However, China’s plans have given renewed impetus to efforts to consider the creation of a digital dollar, they said.Members of Congress have also been increasingly interested in a digital dollar, aware of China’s moves, and asked Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell and Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen about the issue in hearings earlier this year.Powell: Need for Digital Dollar Is an Issue for Congress, PublicPowell said in February the Fed was looking “very carefully” at a digital dollar. “We don’t need to be the first. We need to get it right.”Yellen has signaled interest in research into the viability of a digital dollar, a shift from a lack of enthusiasm under her predecessor, Steven Mnuchin.“It makes sense for central banks to be looking at” issuing sovereign digital currencies, she said at a virtual conference in February. Yellen said a digital version of the dollar could help address hurdles to financial inclusion in the U.S. among low-income households.A recent report from the U.S. Director of National Intelligence said the extent of the threat of any foreign digital currency to the dollar’s centrality in the global financial system “will depend on the regulatory rules that are established.”China’s currency makes up little more than 2% of global foreign exchange reserves compared with nearly 60% for the U.S. dollar. Policy decisions, rather than technical developments, will also be necessary to push forward yuan internationalization, as China maintains a strict regime of capital controls.China’s financial system is too “fragile and weak” to pose a real threat to the dollar’s status as the world’s reserve currency, according to Mark Sobel, U.S. chairman for the Official Monetary and Financial Institutions Forum.“At the end of the the day the markets have more confidence in the Fed” than China’s central bank, said Sobel, a former senior U.S. Treasury official for international matters.(Adds reference to China’s regulatory measures in 10th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLORADO NEW HOTSPOT</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/09/colorado-covid-fourth-wave-young-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as Colorado was given its first dose of hope at COVID-19 restrictions being fully lifted, Governor Jared Polis said a fourth wave of COVID-19 cases has arrived in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith 'EMANCIPATION' Pulls Production From Georgia Over New Voting Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/apple-will-smith-antoine-fuqua-runaway-slave-movie-emancipation-georgia-exit-election-law-1234732247/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 6:01 AM: The Georgia exit for Emancipation is now official. Said star Will Smith and director Antoine Fuqua: “At this moment in time, the Nation is coming to terms with its history a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds shroud ID of hacker who forfeited stolen Bitcoin now worth $4 billion!</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/doj-bitcoin-forfeiture-412750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 12--Thanks to the ballooning value of Bitcoin, the U.S. government could liquidate more than $4 billion in cryptocurrency confiscated from a hacker whose identity--despite an array of felonio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith 'EMANCIPATION' Pulls Production From Georgia Over Voting Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/will-smith-antoine-fuquas-emancipation-pulls-production-georgia-voting-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antoine Fuqua and Will Smith's pre-Civil War drama "Emancipation" will move production from Georgia due to the state's new voting restriction laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Pandemic at 'critical point' as cases rise exponentially...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/who-says-covid-pandemic-is-growing-exponentially-at-more-than-4point4-million-new-cases-a-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax Requirements Spread in USA, Sowing Concern on Overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-requirements-spread-in-us-sowing-concern-on-overreach/ar-BB1fvESh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Covid-19 vaccination requirements are fast becoming facts of life in the U.S., spreading business by business even as politicians and privacy advocates rail against them. Brown, Notre Dame and Rutgers are among universities warning students and staff they’ll need shots in order to return to campus this fall. Some sports teams are demanding proof of vaccination or a negative test from fans as arenas reopen. Want to see your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Bay of Pigs has lessons for our time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/547637-bay-of-pigs-has-lessons-for-our-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It forced JFK to take stock, re-evaluate ... and act accordingly — in essence, to learn from his mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits Get Morning Drunk in the Snow to Celebrate Grand Reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brits-morning-drunk-snow-celebrate-134918774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITV NewsIt’s been a long, cold, lonely winter in England.So, as four months of a nationwide lockdown finally came to an end, nothing was going to stop people from enjoying a refreshing pint of beer at the crack of dawn on a Monday morning—not even driving rain, freezing temperatures, and some pretty unseasonal snowfall.Pubs started serving outdoors again as part of a reopening plan that also covers indoor gym sessions, swimming pools, non-essential shops, beauty salons, and, for those who have been gagging to see some sad animals, zoos. Prime Minister Boris Johnson had urged people to “behave responsibly” with their new freedoms, but didn’t explicitly say they shouldn’t get drunk in the snow before having breakfast.One pub in the town of Huddersfield was swamped when it opened at the stroke of midnight. “We didn’t even know if anyone was going to come,” said the pub landlord fittingly named Ian Snowball. “It’s in Huddersfield, it’s midnight, it’s freezing cold—but look, everyone has come.”If you thought you were starting early today… 🍻These drinkers in Huddersfield braved the snow to enjoy a beer garden pint at midnight ❄️https://t.co/UASiR7bXEv pic.twitter.com/i2O79eocSR— BBC Breakfast (@BBCBreakfast) April 12, 2021 One drinker commented matter-of-factly: “It was snowing earlier but I was still going to come out, I just put my coat on.” Another, sitting in a thick jacket next to an icy-looking gin and tonic, made the fair point: “After 14 months of not going anywhere, except funerals, it’s a great place.”Sky News reported that 50 pub-goers headed to the Fox On The Hill pub in south London this morning. The most emotional was perhaps Tony Blake, 59, who gushed to the news network: “I am so happy that it’s open again, it’s unbelievable, I’m so happy.” Student Sasha Carrington, 19, said she planned to stay there for the entire freezing cold day, explaining: “We’ve got our layers on, thermals, we’re going to stay outside.”Pippa Ingram, 51, and Sue Bell, 55, celebrated a chilly seaside pint in Kent, with Ingram describing her first sip in detail. “Absolutely delicious,” she said. “It’s not gonna last long at all! That is banging.” Back in Huddersfield, in footage timestamped at 8.17 a.m., a woman identified only as Sandy was seen having pints with her friends, and she told Good Morning Britain: “It’s not that cold after a while when you’re sat in the sun.”As pub gardens reopen from today, @NickDixonITV talks to some people who have enjoyed a pint since 8am this morning.They discuss how happy they are to be back in pub gardens following the lockdown.Watch GMB 👉 https://t.co/6iQ6ebeOEQ pic.twitter.com/W0yAai1tGD— Good Morning Britain (@GMB) April 12, 2021 One pub in Coventry appears to have taken things slightly too far. Videos posted online showed more than 100 people lining the street outside the Oak Inn after it had publized its grand plans to open a massive outdoor space with heaters, marquees and blankets. The pub is now under investigation for its “unmanageable amounts of visitors.”But, largely, the grand reopening has been welcomed as a major landmark—particularly following the success of the Britain’s vaccine rollout, which has many hoping that there won’t be another lockdown. Nicholas Hair, landlord of the Kentish Belle in south-east London, told BBC News that there was a “sense of celebration” in the country, adding: “I’m hoping this is a sort of rebirth, and that we’re reopen for the foreseeable.”As for Boris himself, government sources confirmed that the prime minister received a long-awaited haircut on Monday—but his planned trip to the pub has been cancelled out of respect for the late Prince Philip.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pints, shopping sprees, hair cuts...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210412073825-mnd81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN (REPEAT, UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):RPT-UPDATE 2-'I'm so excited' - England reopens with pints pulled, shopping sprees and hair cuts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rippling through markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/cars-anyone-how-the-computer-chip-shortage-is-rattling-the-economy-2326719/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. economy rebounds from its pandemic slump, a vital cog is in short supply: the computer chips that power a wide range of products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to zero in on chip shortage in meeting with company officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biden-chips-idUSKBN2BZ118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior White House officials will meet on Monday with top executives from nearly 20 major companies to discuss a global semiconductor shortage that has roiled the automotive industry and technology firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAWKER Set for Relaunch -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/gawker-is-set-for-relaunch-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Gawker writer Leah Finnegan is helming Bustle Digital Group's latest effort to resurrect the website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye sneakers headed for millionaire status in SOTHEBY'S sale...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210412115502-l79ew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCTION-YEEZY/ (PIX):Kanye's Yeezy sneakers headed for millionaire status in Sotheby's sale</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Huge' explosion rocks Caribbean island as volcano keeps erupting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-explosions-evacuations-2c26166fa05e0ec6840669972ea1aaf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINGSTOWN, St. Vincent (AP) — La Soufriere volcano fired an enormous amount of ash and hot gas early Monday in the biggest explosive eruption yet since volcanic activity began on the eastern...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cambodia condemns VICE for edited photos of Khmer Rouge victims smiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/12/cambodia-vice-edited-photos-khmer-rouge-victims-smiling-tuol-sleng-prison-genocide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colourised images from Tuol Sleng prison during 1970s genocide were manipulated, media group says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church issues strict rules after spike in deaths from DIY exorcisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/church-forced-issue-strict-rules-23897310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Church bosses will reveal how to exorcise demons after deaths from DIY rituals in Russia including a nine-year-old boy who died after he was gagged and whipped by his father</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Ukraine 'one step from war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9461199/Putin-spark-war-Europe-invading-Ukraine-ex-ambassador-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is just 'one step away from war' with Ukraine, a news report on state TV said on Sunday, branding the country a 'Nazi' state that may have to be 'de-Nazified' by force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, China carriers in South Sea as tensions simmer...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/12/china/south-china-sea-taiwan-military-tensions-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military activity in the South China Sea spiked over the weekend as a Chinese aircraft carrier entered the region and a US Navy expeditionary strike group wrapped up exercises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soviet cosmonaut made pioneering spaceflight 60 years ago...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-moscow-bbb2cf68c5eb9a724df52c3b13bd0d4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Crushed into the pilot's seat by heavy G-forces, Soviet cosmonaut Yuri Gagarin saw flames outside his spacecraft and prepared to die. His voice broke the tense silence at ground...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Republicans? Some in GOP open to president's agenda...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-ap-top-news-raleigh-north-carolina-7858050374c244239578f00745ba4450</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — Jay Copan doesn't hide his disregard for the modern Republican Party. A solid Republican voter for the past four decades, the 69-year-old quickly regretted casting his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air-Freshener Violation?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mom-minnesota-cops-killed-son-after-stopping-him-on-an-air-freshener-violation/ar-BB1fz0kZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in the Minneapolis suburb of Brooklyn Center fatally shot a Black 20-year-old man during a traffic stop on Sunday afternoon, setting off a string of violent protests amid tensions over the Derek Chauvin murder trial. The victim’s mother spent much of Sunday afternoon at the scene of the fatal shooting, pleading with officers to remove her the body of her son, Daunte Wright, from the pavement. “He got out of the car, and his girlfriend...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests erupt after police shoot Black man in Minneapolis traffic stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9460619/Police-fire-tear-gas-protesters-officer-fatally-shoots-man-near-Minneapolis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police fired tear gas on Sunday to disperse angry protesters after an officer fatally shot Daunte Wright, 20, about 10 miles from where George Floyd was killed in Minneapolis last May.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microchip senses virus in body, extracts from blood?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9460389/Pentagon-scientists-invent-microchip-senses-COVID-19-body-symptoms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists working inside the Pentagon have developed a microchip, contained in green gel (pictured) which is inserted below the skin and senses COVID-19 in the blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/12/us/brooklyn-center-minnesota-police-shooting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds protested Sunday night after a Black man in Minnesota was shot by a police officer and died following a traffic stop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: GOOGLE Founders Join Elite $100 Billion Club...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/google-larry-page-sergey-brin-net-worth-billionaire-wealth-bloomberg-2021-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Page and Sergey Brin are two of eight centibillionaires in the world thanks to surging tech stocks. They join Jeff Bezos, Elon Musk, and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Vows Revenge...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/12/iran-vows-revenge-for-alleged-israeli-attack-on-nuclear-site/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — The Iranian foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, vowed revenge against Israel on Monday morning, a day after a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA probes police who pulled gun, pepper-sprayed Black Army officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/police-accused-threatening-pulling-gun-black-army-lieutenant-during-virginia-n1263731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The town manager of Windsor, where the incident occurred, said one of the two officers involved has already been fired following an internal investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUROPOL: Covid, Cocaine Take Europe To 'Breaking Point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/covid-cocaine-take-europe-to-breaking-point-europol-01618218305</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic could fuel organised crime for years to come in Europe, a continent already at \</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infected man in hospital 5 weeks after receiving J&amp;J jab...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/11/nj-man-in-hospital-with-covid-after-being-fully-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey man is in the hospital with COVID-19 — just five weeks after being vaccinated. Francisco Cosme, 52, was ecstatic when he booked an appointment for the one-dose Johnson &amp; Johnson va…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shady Crypto Start-Up Selling 'Shares' in Celebs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shady-crypto-start-selling-shares-090806622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos via Getty/ReutersIn late March, a 23-year-old named Alex Masmej logged on to Twitter to learn he had been turned into a currency. On a new social networking platform called BitClout, anyone with access to Bitcoin could, in just a few steps, buy something called the “alexmasmej” coin. A handful of people already had—there were about 24 coins in circulation. By BitClout’s metric, a piece of Alex cost about $250.This was not an entirely new experience for Masmej. Last year, after losing his job in the pandemic, he’d minted his own coin called the $ALEX token, selling what amounted to shares in his life. The first $ALEX investors to help Masmej raise $20,000 would get 15 percent of his income for the next three years; at times, they could vote on his everyday decisions. In concept, the BitClout coin was similar, but with a key difference: He’d had nothing to do with it.“BitClout does not ask for consent,” Masmej told the Daily Beast. “[It] is trading on your name without you knowing… People really don’t like this, and that makes sense because it seems almost illegal.”The platform, which has become a source of anger and bemusement in the pockets of the internet that pay attention to new crypto projects, operates sort of like a monetized Twitter. BitClout lets people speculate on prominent social media figures, buying personalized tokens that theoretically rise and fall in value with the person’s popularity. The combination of hype technology and celebrity proved attractive to investors, raising over $165 million from Andreessen Horowitz, the Winklevoss twins, and Reddit co-founder Alexis Ohanian. But the project’s critics, of which there are many, see it as a dystopian ploy to commodify human interaction, in the mode of a “Yelp for people.”Masmej wasn’t the only one to find himself minted into money. When BitClout launched out of private beta on March 24, some 14,000 users had pre-made profiles on the platform, copied from their Twitter accounts and converted into markets for individualized coins, nearly all without approval. Elon Musk, the top-ranked token on the website, runs for about $77,000; Ariana Grande goes for just under $25,000. Donald Trump, who places slightly below Barstool Sports’ Dave Portnoy (about $17,000), trades for nearly $15,700.Masmej found the platform funny, but others were not as entertained. The crypto-focused law firm Anderson Kill sent BitClout a cease-and-desist on behalf of a product manager at the token exchange Radar Relay, calling for his likeness to be removed from the site. “It is well established that a person or company cannot knowingly use ‘another’s name, voice, signature, photograph or likeness…for purposes of advertising or selling...without such person’s prior consent,” the letter reads, citing the right of publicity under California Civil Code 3344. The account was removed, but users can still technically buy its coin by searching for the original username.The premise of BitClout is fairly straightforward. Traders exchange Bitcoin for the site’s native currency, BitClout, which they must spend to register an account, send messages, or post. They can also use the currency to buy “Creator Coins,” individualized tokens issued for prominent personalities. The more people buy a given Creator Coin, the more its value rises, and vice-versa. “It’s literally tokenized clout,” said Brian Fakhoury, a crypto investor who has written about the platform. “The more clout you have, the more your thing is worth.”The site is set up to capitalize on the clout of its users, requiring the most well-known accounts to engage in a bit of unpaid advertising. Figures like Masmej, whose profiles were pre-made on the site, can claim their accounts and issue tokens on their own behalf—but only if they buy BitClout and tweet about the platform. Very few people have done this. One source who reviewed the website’s backend said about 80 profiles on the platform had been claimed.Should I claim my Bitclout?— Snoop Dogg (@SnoopDogg) April 7, 2021 Just joined #BitClout! Excited to be a part of a new platform in the crypto space. Follow me at: https://t.co/XMkeLVV5oC BC1YLiySbpLp3y6q279SQXPgLZPqQoMxKHE9ToqDFk56jE9kwbF4gXE— Tiffany Ariana Trump (@TiffanyATrump) April 7, 2021 BitClout’s launch arrived on the heels of the craze over NFTs, or “non-fungible tokens,” cryptographic units of data stored on a blockchain that can be minted in a range of formats—Jack Dorsey turned his first tweet into an NFT; Kings of Leon released an album as one—and sold off for increasingly outrageous prices. BitClout operates on a similar premise: minting tokens that market hype as a way to directly pay creators. But while NFTs are not mutually interchangeable—the owner of Dorsey’s tweet NFT cannot trade it for another version—BitClout is. Like a dollar, the token can be exchanged for other BitClout. It’s a fungible token.“The underlying force of NFTs is the exact same thing that drives BitClout,” Fakhoury said. “But it’s the same thing at the end of the day. They're kind of worthless assets that people give value to for no underlying reason.”Between NFTs, now BitClout, sometimes I wonder if we’re living in a simulation 🤖 Things will only get weirder from here .. 👽— Abigail Ratchford (@AbiRatchford) April 3, 2021 When it launched, BitClout’s creator tried to remain anonymous, identifying himself only as “Diamondhands”—a slang term for someone who holds onto their financial position fiercely—in the mold of Bitcoin’s pseudonymous inventor, Satoshi Nakamoto. But the attempt at secrecy crumbled quickly, when industry insiders pointed to a man named Nader Al-Naji, who later confirmed his identity to the trade publication, Decrypt. (Al-Naji did not respond to the Daily Beast’s request for comment).A former Google engineer from Alexandria, Virginia, Al-Naji made a splash in the crypto-world back in 2018 with a project called Basis. The idea was to create what’s called a “stable coin”—a token whose value is pegged to a more reliable currency, like the U.S. dollar—but to establish that stability with an algorithm, rather than backing it with actual money. Al-Naji raised a record-breaking $133 million in seed funding, but the concept proved unsustainable. After the Securities and Exchange Commission got involved, Basis shut down and returned its remaining money to investors.The failure left Al-Naji with a mixed reputation: a founder who stumbled, but didn’t steal. And yet the launch of BitClout, which one investor described to Decrypt as “fucked up,” has struck many as a scam. The biggest red flag, beyond the glaring consent issue, is that while users can put money into BitClout, they cannot get it out. Traders send Bitcoin to a single account run by the BitClout team—the exact ownership of which remains unknown—but it’s a one-way transaction. The currency does not trade on any exchanges and there’s no way to cash out on the website.Anyone looking to actually profit from their trades on BitClout has to take more surreptitious measures. Aravind Karthigeyan, a high school student and moderator of a BitClout subreddit, told The Daily Beast he’s gotten around this by reselling his tokens at a discount to individual buyers on the messaging app, Telegram.For James Prestwich, a crypto engineer and founder who has been publicly critical of BitClout, this represents a clear indication that the currency is a shitcoin—crypto jargon for a scam. “The only way to get Bitcoin or dollars out is to find another person and to negotiate a bespoke deal with them,” he said. “So BitClout users, once they get in, they're trapped. There's no way out.”“There is a secondary market that’s developed on Telegram. On Telegram, OTC (over-the-counter) BitClout is usually a 40 to 50 percent discount,” Prestwich said. “So if you want to get out, you’re taking a 40 percent haircut, and the only way to do it is to manually send the BitClout to someone and hope they pay you.”Critics have also cast doubt on the platform’s security. “They are very opaque,” Masmej said, “It’s very hard to get to the BitClout website… and even then, it’s really hard on the platform to know how much they’re getting in fees or what exactly to do to sign up. We have to pay Bitcoin, but we don’t really know what it’s for. I think a lot of communities in crypto are really pissed off.”Most crypto projects issue users a “private key”—often a long phrase or string of random characters—to access their accounts. Unlike a password, private keys can’t be changed. The risk is that if someone else figures out a private key, the user can’t make a new one to keep them out of the account. “If somebody gets your private key, you literally can't do anything with your account,” Fakhoury said. “It is just forever compromised.”BitClout also issues private keys, but when users log in, it caches the keys in whatever browser they’re using. As a result, the keys are more vulnerable to theft—if the user clicks on a scammy pfishing link and signs in, their key could be stolen. “There's a big security risk in the private keys just sitting directly in your browser,” Fakhoury said.For Prestwich, the more jarring revelation was that BitClout also stores the keys on its own server, uploading the data after every transaction. “It’s not just that they’re insecurely storing keys, but they’re sending them to themselves,” Prestwich said. “They could take all of the BitClout at any time or make arbitrary purchases on your behalf. Any BitClout you have, any employee that has access to that server can take it at any time.”Rather than launching the platform on a ready-made blockchain like the Bitcoin-rival Ethereum, which has templates for minting new tokens using its own infrastructure, BitClout chose to develop their protocol from scratch. As a result, it was not initially a blockchain—where multiple servers run the same algorithm and register transactions simultaneously—but a single block or “node” operated off one server.In its white paper, BitClout claims that other users are running nodes. And the project maintains that it is open-source, meaning anyone interested could theoretically download the source code, create a node of their own, and extend the chain. But BitClout’s creator has not released the source code. “There does seem to be a blockchain there,” Prestwich said, “a poorly constructed, poorly thought out blockchain. I would suspect that there are other people who have a close relationship with BitClout who are running other nodes.”As an investor, Fakhoury was skeptical of the project’s execution, but found the concept exciting.“I think it's a genius idea,” he said. “BitClout just opened Pandora's box. It opens the door to now ‘Oh, I see this YouTuber is getting popular. I know they're gonna get more popular now and I have a way to financially benefit from that.’”Masmej, who has not claimed his profile because he only uses Ethereum, said his peers were less impressed. “I asked my friends in crypto and they were like ‘Dude, this is a chain for boomers,’” he said. “They are only on Bitcoin, this is not going to work, and they are impersonating people’s Twitter accounts.’”Prestwich agreed: “This is not the cool, hot crypto-startup. This is people who are part of the establishment trying to imitate some of the hot crypto-startups in order to make money.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot, killed during Minnesota traffic stop sparks unrest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/police-minnesota-minneapolis-shootings-1ad1b12b77f35f9fa01e680b73add7d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKLYN CENTER, Minn. (AP) — Crowds of mourners and protesters gathered in a Minnesota city where the family of a 20-year-old man say he was shot by police before getting back into his car and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>536:  Historians pinpoint very worst year EVER to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en /severe-weather/historians-pin point-the-very-worst-year-to- ever-be-alive/927803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Four gray whales found dead in San Francisco Bay area...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Four-gray-whales-found-dead-in-eight-days-in-San-16093159.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the span of eight days, four gray whales were found dead in the San Francisco Bay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden on track to accept FEWER refugees than Trump!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-administration-on-track-to-accept-fewer-16093228.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Since his days on the campaign trail, President Joe Biden has tried to cast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'coffeehouse style' seating to more comfortable economy class; Redesigned airplane cabins...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/11/crystal-cabin-awards-future-of-redesigned-airplane-cabins.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the pandemic, leaders in the aviation industry stretched their imaginations to design new concepts for airplane cabins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intimate portrayal of marginalized Americans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/migration-saga-nomadland-among-favourites-021650658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US road movie "Nomadland" triumphed at the Bafta film awards on Sunday, with Chinese director Chloe Zhao's intimate portrayal of marginalised Americans winning in four categories including best film, best actress and best director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhao becomes 1st woman of color to win top DGA honor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-sam-mendes-academy-awards-kathryn-bigelow-emerald-fennell-5680ca5f57957cc4798d2e49078a76e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chloé Zhao’s “Nomadland” continued its tour of dominance through awards season Saturday night, when Zhao took top honors at the 73rd annual Directors Guild Association Awards. She is the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mom Arrested for Stabbing 3 Kids to Death...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-arrests-los-angeles-california-9e05ca3e92211a3eca572dd0995c0ee8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The woman arrested on suspicion of killing her three young children at her Los Angeles apartment had been involved in a custody dispute with their father, according to a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOMADLAND' wins best film, director, actress at BAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hugh-grant-tom-hiddleston-priyanka-chopra-coronavirus-pandemic-chloe-zhao-fd6ce441111615517945a5fed6358336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Gig-economy Western “Nomadland” won four prizes including best picture on Sunday at the British Academy Film Awards, which were handed out during a pandemic-curbed ceremony that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOMADLAND' wins best film at BAFTA, best director, actress...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/04/11/updating-bafta-winners-point-to-possible-oscars-daniel-kaluuya-yuh-jung-youn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAFTA, the British Academy, is handing out their awards now live in London. The show won’t air in the US until 9pm on the BBC. Who cares? The whole thing is being done on social media, so why…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French audiences develop a taste for window theatre...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210411160628-jmw28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-ACTORS (TV, PIX):French audiences develop a taste for window theatre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's futuristic transport loop in Vegas blasted as 'slow cars and flashy lights'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2679290/musk-vegas-tunnel-blasted-slow-cars-flashy-lights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk’s “futuristic” $55M Las Vegas public transit loop has been panned as “just humans driving cars slowly in a tunnel”. Plans had promised to whisk passengers in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disappointed' In Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-reportedly-unleashes-in-bonkers-closed-door-rant-for-rnc-donors-torches-son-of-a-btch-mcconnell-full-of-crap-fauci-and-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump absolutely scorched the earth on Saturday night, according to multiple accounts, in a bonkers rant behind closed doors at a Republican donor retreat at Mar-a-Lago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden returns POW flag to top of White House that Trump had moved...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/biden-returns-prisoner-of-war-flag-to-pole-on-top-of-white-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden has restored the prisoner-of-war/missing-in-action flag to its former location atop the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil now has more young than old Covid patients in ICUs...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/brazil-now-has-more-young-than-old-covid-patients-in-icus-01618159805?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Covid-19 patients under 40 in intensive care in Brazil surpassed older groups last month, a researcher said Sunday, amid a deadly surge driven partly by a new coronavirus variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He heeded MAGA's call to fight. Now a Georgia teen awaits consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/he-heeded-trumps-call-to-fight-now-a-milton-teen-awaits-the-consequences/HBIEZ7C2SRHTDAPGGW52DKJLTY/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruno Joseph Cua is the youngest of the nearly 400 defendants so far arrested in the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol, and among the Georgians arrested, faces among the most serious crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>536:  Historians pinpoint the very worst year ever to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/ en/severe-weather/historians- pinpoint-the-very-worst-year- to-ever-be-alive/927803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
