<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>As Trump appointees flout Hatch Act, civil servants who get caught get punished...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/To-punished-workers-Hatch-Act-not-a-joke-15523350.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A Defense Logistics Agency employee was suspended for 30 days without pay last fall after giving his office colleagues a PowerPoint presentation that displayed the words, "Vote Republican."  An Energy Department worker was forced to resign in January after admitting she gave a woman running for Congress a tour of a federal waste treatment plant so the candidate could show her expertise to potential voters.  Another civil servant began a 120-day suspension without pay from the Food and Drug Administration in July after creating a Facebook page with his name and photograph to solicit political donations and then co-hosting a fundraiser.  These were some of the recent consequences for federal workers who illegally mixed government employment with partisan politics in violation of the Hatch Act, the anti-corruption law Congress passed in 1939.  The New Deal-era law applies, on paper at least, to civil servants and political appointees alike. But the top Trump administration officials showcased in prime-time appearances and speaking slots at the Republican National Convention this week serve as a reminder that when it comes to flouting the separation between governing and politicking, there appears to be a two-tiered system of consequences.  Watchdog groups complained that acting homeland security secretary Chad Wolf and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo violated the Hatch Act this week when Wolf led a taped naturalization ceremony for newly minted citizens on White House grounds and Pompeo gave a speech from Israel.  "Convention events were planned and executed by the Trump Campaign and RNC," White House spokesman Judd Deere said in a statement. "Any government employees who participated did so in their personal capacities and in compliance with the Hatch Act."  The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE NUMBERS RISE AGAIN IN EUROPE </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Case-numbers-rise-again-in-Europe-15522078.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases are surging again in Europe after months of relative calm, but the second wave looks different from the first: Fewer people are dying, and the newest and mostly younger victims of the pandemic need less medical treatment.  Unlike the initial hit of the pandemic this spring, which overwhelmed hospitals and turned nursing homes into grim mortuaries, the European resurgence of recent weeks has not forced as many people into medical wards.  But the increase is widespread, and it is unsettling societies that had hoped the worst was behind them. Paris on Friday joined some other French jurisdictions in imposing a citywide mask requirement, with cases spiking. France, Germany, Spain and others posted caseloads in recent days that had not been seen since April and early May. Spain has been hit particularly hard, with per capita cases now worse than in the United States - a notable marker in Europe, which after the initial springtime spike had generally controlled the virus more successfully than America.  And with almost every European country planning a return to in-person schooling, many starting next week, public health officials are holding their breath for the impact.  The surge is a first test of the efforts Europe has made to improve its resilience in the half-year since the pandemic unleashed a wave of suffering across the world. Most European countries have improved their testing capacity. They have hired contact tracers to combat big outbreaks. They have masks and gloves for their doctors and nurses.  Many countries, including Italy, endured grinding lockdowns this spring. Now citizens are exhausted, and economies are still flagging.  "I don't think the country can survive another lockdown. And to be frank, there is no reason to," said Ranieri Guerra, a World Health Organization assistant director...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE makes 'privacy' change, and advertising companies cry foul... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Apple-makes-a-privacy-change-and-Facebook-and-15522035.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming weeks, Apple plans to change its iPhone software to make it more difficult for advertisers to track Apple customers, an effort that will help further one of the company's long-standing goals: Protecting the privacy of its customers.  But with Apple under the antitrust spotlight, its privacy move has also been called a power move by an advertising industry that is scrambling to adjust to the changes, expected to be included in iOS 14, the company's latest mobile operating system expected to go live next month.  On Wednesday, Facebook became the latest organization to speak openly about the changes, telling investors and users that Apple's move will hurt the social network's bottom line because it will limit the kind of personalized targeting that makes Facebook's ads so valuable to advertisers. "This is not a change we want to make, but unfortunately Apple's updates to iOS14 have forced this decision," the company said in a blog post.  Some in the advertising industry see the moves as part privacy, part self-interest on the part of Apple. Apple also offers advertising, and by limiting the amount of data outside marketers collect, Apple's access to the data becomes more valuable.  "I think there's probably 30 percent truth in that they're doing it for privacy reasons and it's 70 percent that they're doing it because it's what's good for Apple," said Nick Jordan, founder of Narrative I/O, which helps companies gather data for advertising. "It's a question for regulators and courts whether they should be able to wield the power they do over this ecosystem," he said. "They created it, but can they rule it with an iron fist?"  In an interview with The Washington Post, Apple director of privacy engineering Erik Neuenschwander said the changes were part of Apple's privacy road map. When asked whether Apple...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEURALINK PUTS COMPUTER CHIPS IN ANIMAL BRAINS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828231238-ikq23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECH-NEURALINK/MUSK (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-'Three little pigs': Musk's Neuralink puts computer chips in animal brains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palin CAN sue NYT for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828224738-q2qkg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PALIN/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Sarah Palin can sue New York Times for defamation -court ruling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACTOR BOSEMAN DEAD AT 43...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5f4352111fdead278da3651b44d311b8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Actor Chadwick Boseman, who played Black icons Jackie Robinson and James Brown with searing intensity before finding fame as the regal Black Panther in the Marvel cinematic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tests providing results in 20 seconds trialled at Heathrow...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1387642/covid-19-tests-heathrow-eplace-quarantine-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 tests that produce results in just 20 seconds are being trialled at Heathrow airport to replace the current quarantine system. The airport plans to mass-screen the 78 million travellers th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSKENSTEIN!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/28/elon-musk-unveils-working-prototype-of-brain-implant-device/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney for accused Kenosha protest gunman says teen acted in self-defense...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828234039-68iot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-RACE/USA (WRAPUP 9, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 9-Attorney for accused Kenosha protest gunman says teen acted in self-defense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOOKING FOR VOLUNTEERS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aacbb0ff7a66b64faa375e22694425ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk isn't content with electric cars, shooting people into orbit, populating Mars and building underground tunnels to solve traffic problems. He also wants to get inside your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College towns growing alarmed over outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d36c40584bc1c9730654b589f672f79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — As waves of schools and businesses around the country are cleared to reopen, college towns are moving toward renewed shutdowns because of too many parties and too many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, at NH rally, sows fears about 'thugs,' 'anarchists'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6ca2a7999c107d682dc21b8a0dfad4f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDONDERRY, N.H. (AP) — Fresh off accepting the Republican Party’s nomination, President Donald Trump said Friday he was the only thing standing between “democracy and the mob,” as he lashed out...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  GOP portrayal of urban mayhem doesn't always match reality...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6a983b159cb0a20468e0c0a19dd93a31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At almost every turn at the Republican National Convention, speakers from the president on down portrayed American cities like Portland, Oregon, New York and Chicago as lawless Democratic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's charts slower course on reopening...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/253ce3fcdc81b2b7960cd3ab40b208ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — With the hope of preventing another virus surge, California Gov. Gavin Newsom announced a new process Friday for reopening businesses that's more gradual than the first...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Regrets Maskless Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gop-senator-thom-tillis-says-he-regrets-maskless-night-at-trumps-white-house-rnc-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I fell short of my own standard,” Sen. Thom Tillis (R-NC) said in a statement after he was photographed without a mask during Trump’s RNC speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service copes with infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-Trump-travels-Secret-Service-copes-with-15523103.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When President Donald Trump gave a speech to a group of sheriffs in Tampa late last month, his decision to travel forced a large contingent of Secret Service agents to head to a state that was then battling one of the worst coronavirus surges in the nation.  Even before Air Force One touched down on July 31, the fallout was apparent: Five Secret Service agents already on the ground had to be replaced after one tested positive for the coronavirus and the others working in proximity were presumed to be infected, according to people familiar with the situation.  The previously unreported episode is one of a series of examples of how Trump's insistence on traveling and holding campaign-style events amid the pandemic has heightened the risks for the people who safeguard his life, intensifying the strain on the Secret Service.  In the past two months, dozens of Secret Service agents who worked to ensure the security of the president and Vice President Mike Pence at public events have been sickened or sidelined because they were in direct contact with infected people, according to multiple people familiar with the episodes, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the incidents.  Despite that, Trump has continued to hold large gatherings - most dramatically at the White House on Thursday night, when he delivered his acceptance speech at the Republican National Convention before a crowd of 1,500 people seated closely together on the South Lawn, with few masks in sight. The vast majority were not tested for the coronavirus ahead of time.  Trump's actions rebuff the scientific consensus that the best way tamp down the spread of the virus is to avoid large gatherings and close quarters. Critics say his refusal to abide by those guidelines is imposing unnecessary risk on the Secret Service staff, who have no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Republicans weaponized impeachment and Dems ignored it...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/28/democratic-republican-conventions-trump-impeachment-404342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It seems like history,” said House Judiciary Chairman Jerry Nadler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC suspended from App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/28/apple-suspends-fortnite-maker-epic-games-app-store-account.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are disappointed that we have had to terminate the Epic Games account on the App Store. We have worked with the team at Epic Games for many years on their launches and releases," Apple said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems will try to repeal ban on federal money for abortions...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/house-democrats-try-repeal-longstanding-190200300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats say they will put up a fight in 2021 to end a long-standing ban on federal funding of abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN BEATS TRUMP IN TV AUDIENCE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828204832-lodex</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TV RATINGS (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Trump convention speech attracts smaller TV audience than Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart Disease Detected From Selfies...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/selfies-help-diagnose-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists using a computer algorithm can detect coronary artery disease (CAD) using four pictures of a person’s face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg slams APPLE 'monopoly' in leaked comments...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/28/zuckerberg-slams-apples-app-store-monopoly-in-leaked-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg poured gasoline on his simmering feud with Apple on Friday, slamming the company’s “stranglehold” on the iPhone’s App Store, saying it charges “monopol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9.9 Million Watch on FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/republican-convention-tv-viewership-donald-trump-joe-biden-1203026084/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s acceptance speech on the final night of the Republican National Convention drew 19.9 million TV viewers across six networks, falling short of the 21.8 million who watched Joe B…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP GENERAL: MILITARY WON'T RESOLVE DISPUTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a979ad8beceacd77c692e42448cf7b82</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. armed forces will have no role in carrying out the election process or resolving a disputed vote, the top U.S. military officer told Congress in comments released...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorce rates in America soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8674001/Divorce-rates-America-soar-34-percent-COVID-19-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data collected by Legal Templates found that there has been a 34% increase in sales for divorce agreements during the coronavirus pandemic - indicating soaring divorce rates in the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American jets intercept military aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/28/politics/us-jets-intercept-russians-alaska/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US F-22 fighter jets intercepted Russian military aircraft in international airspace off the coast of Alaska late Thursday, according to North American Aerospace Defense Command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada man becomes first in USA to catch COVID-19 twice...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/28/nevada-man-becomes-first-in-the-us-to-catch-covid-19-twice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nevada resident is thought to be the first person in the United States to be infected twice by the coronavirus, according to findings released this week. The 25-year-old man, of Reno, experienced…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton wants her kids to 'erode' their white privilege...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/chelsea-clinton-says-she-wants-her-children-erode-their-white-privilege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It still isn't, kind of, easy, fair or equal for many Americans to vote and I think it's really important that my children understand that," Clinton said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK celebs criminally charged after LA house parties...</title>
      <link>https://federalnewsnetwork.com/entertainment-news/2020/08/tiktok-celebrities-criminally-charged-after-la-house-parties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;federalnewsnetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say TikTok celebrities Bryce Hall and Blake Gray are facing criminal charges after they hosted recent parties in the Hollywood Hills held despite a ban on large gatherings during the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Trump Hotel operator files for bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://bc.ctvnews.ca/vancouver-s-trump-international-hotel-closes-as-operator-files-for-bankruptcy-1.5083142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bc.ctvnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears the days of having the controversial Trump name emblazoned on a prominent hotel tower in downtown Vancouver are coming to an end, with a staff member at the Trump International Hotel confirming Friday that the hotel is closing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior CIA official died by suicide...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/08/26/cia-national-intelligence-official-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Schinella, the National Intelligence Officer for Military Issues and a longtime CIA official, killed himself at his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health agencies' credibility at risk after week of blunders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b9b6dc204d780fac7e6a79c1dbf21b8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The credibility of two of the nation’s leading public health agencies is under fire this week after controversial decisions that outside experts say smack of political pressure...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGM Resorts to Lay Off 18,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/mgm-resorts-to-lay-off-18000-employees</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary to shut its borders again... </title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/hungary-to-shut-its-borders-again-over-virus-fears-01598628904</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hungary said Friday that it would close its borders again next month because of new coronavirus fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandal could weigh on president's white evangelical fanbase...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/28/jerry-falwell-jr-fall-grace-influence-trump-voters-liberty-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex scandal surrounding ex-head of Liberty University could weigh on president’s white evangelical fanbase in run-up to election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What was it like to ride out Cat 4 hurricane? Survivors tell their stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/what-was-it-like-to-ride-out-the-storm-survivors-of-hurricane-laura-tell-their-stories/803204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO TV RATINGS BUMP? DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2020/08/28/tv-ratings-republican-convention-night-4-president-trump-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the latest TV ratings, the 2020 Republican National Convention’s grand finale did not appear to enjoy any major Trump bump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifeguard Catches Shark With Bare Hands On Beach!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/27/shark-sighting-long-island-jones-beach-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of onlookers formed around 10:15 AM last Friday at Robert Moses Field Two as a dorsal fin poked out of the water followed by a long pointed tail and of course, a set of shark teeth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming Middle East Arms Race Sparks Fear of Regional War...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/looming-middle-east-arms-race-sparks-fear-of-unprecedented-regional-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impending expiration of an international weapons ban on Iran threatens to flood the Middle East with high-tech Russian and Chinese military equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC DAYBREAK CHART... </title>
      <link>https://election.usc.edu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;election.usc.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sperm Quality Lower In Men Who Use Smartphones, Tablets At Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sperm-quality-worse-smartphones-tablets-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research just released by the American Academy of Sleep Medicine notes a correlation between nighttime digital media use and poor sperm quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JK Rowling returns award over trans comments criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200828-jk-rowling-returns-award-over-trans-comments-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JK Rowling returns award over trans comments criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer-Spending Rebound Cools, Hinting at More Risk Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-spending-rebound-cools-130322665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The rebound in U.S. consumer spending slowed in July amid a surge in virus cases, and now faces another roadblock after the government cut unemployment benefits.Household outlays rose 1.9% from the prior month following an upwardly revised 6.2% rise in the prior month, a Commerce Department</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cope in anxious age: Hitchcock, Munch, Poe...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/How-to-cope-in-an-anxious-age-Try-Hitchcock-15521450.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French film director François Truffaut, who conducted a famous series of interviews with Alfred Hitchcock in 1962, said afterward that he had found Hitchcock to be a "fearful" and "deeply vulnerable" man, but that this was precisely what made him an "artist of anxiety." Hitchcock's biographer Peter Ackroyd concisely summed up the theme of most of his films: "Ordinary people, living in a familiar setting, are suddenly plunged into a 'chaos world' where no one is safe."  This can hardly be improved upon as a description of our own world since March. It may not be clear what to call the Hitchcock movie we seem to have been plunged into - "Housebound" instead of "Spellbound"? Perhaps "The Man Who Knew Too Little?"  Yet the feeling of being immersed in one of Hitchcock's movies can also induce a desire to watch them, or to consume anything comparably tense and dark and riveting. Friends of mine, from rural Wisconsin to the south of France, from Texas to Tel Aviv, have written to say that during the long coronavirus siege they have been devoting themselves to film noirs and classic Hitchcock and Clouzot thrillers, or to Poe and Kafka and Raymond Chandler stories.  In a small New England town, I've been doing the same. A tenet of homeopathic medicine is that "like cures like." I'm not sure that's true, but perhaps it can at least alleviate it (as, admittedly, can pure, carefree escapism, like the screwball comedies about mostly rich people during the Depression). The art of anxiety may deflect real-life anxiety and simultaneously put it into better focus. Anxiety involves a sharpening of the senses, a heightened awareness. In any kind of treacherous landscape, it helps us keep our balance and see what is hidden.  Like the news, Hitchcock's movies and Franz Kafka's stories are often about innocent people falsely accused of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashierless Stores Popping Up At Gas Stations, Stadiums, Even DUNKIN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/cashierless-stores-are-popping-up-at-gas-stations-stadiums-and-even-dunkin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept popularized by Amazon Go may be getting a lot bigger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University says it caught outbreak before started. Its secret weapon: poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/The-University-of-Arizona-says-it-caught-a-dorm-s-15521359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As 5,000 students prepared for move-in day at the University of Arizona this week, the school warned they will periodically be tested for Covid-19. One test, though, doesn't involve a nose swab. The university is regularly screening the sewage from each dorm, searching for traces of the virus.  On Thursday, officials said the technique worked - and possibly prevented a sizable outbreak on campus. When a wastewater sample from one dorm came back positive this week, the school quickly tested all 311 people who live and work there and found two asymptomatic students who tested positive. They were quickly quarantined.  "With this early detection, we jumped on it right away, tested those youngsters, and got them the appropriate isolation where they needed to be," said Richard Carmona, a former U.S. Surgeon General who is directing the school's reentry task force, in a news conference.  Researchers around the world have been studying whether wastewater testing can effectively catch cases early to prevent Covid-19 clusters. There are programs in Singapore, China, Spain, Canada, and New Zealand, while in the U.S., more than 170 wastewater facilities across 37 states are being tested. Earlier this month, officials in the U.K. announced testing at 44 water treatment facilities. The Netherlands has been collecting samples at 300 sewage treatment plants.  With colleges battling large outbreaks around the country, the University of Arizona -- which is trying a mix of online and in-person courses -- elected to test sewage from all 20 residence halls. Other schools are doing the same, including the University of California, San Diego and Syracuse University.  On Tuesday, that screening process found signs of the virus in the wastewater from a dorm called Likins Hall. Although all students living in the dorm had to pass antigen tests...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*ck You Up,' 'Kill You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/08/28/rand-paul-threats-from-dc-mob-were-f-you-up-kill-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday on Fox News Channel's "Fox &amp; Friends," Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) relived his experience from a night early having been confronted by a mob of protesters near the White House after the conclusion of the Republican National Committee. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 350 faith leaders endorse Biden, citing 'need of moral leadership'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/514110-more-than-350-faith-leaders-endorse-biden-citing-need-of-moral-leadership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coalition of more than 350 faith leaders endorsed Joe Biden for president late Thursday, citing a "need of moral leadership" and "hope for a better future."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk set to reveal device that connects brain to computer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-implant-v2-demo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk tweeted that his “V2” update will blow our minds. But how close is he to putting computer chips in them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flying Car' Gets off Ground -- With Person Aboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2020-08-28/japans-flying-car-gets-off-ground-with-a-person-aboard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands arrested for 'virus-related crimes' in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200828-thousands-arrested-for-virus-related-crimes-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands arrested for 'virus-related crimes' in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer creates 'AI Jesus' which goes on to make apocalyptic prophecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/engineer-creates-ai-jesus-writes-22592469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was designed by engineer George Davila Durendal and told to write about just three topics, The Plague, Roman emperor Ceasar and The End of Days. The artificial intelligence has so far produced 60,000 words</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece starts more training exercises amid Turkey tension...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greece-starts-more-training-exercises-100435625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece and the United Arab Emirates have begun joint air force training exercises in the eastern Mediterranean, in the latest build-up of military forces in the region where Greece and Turkey are at odds over seabed mineral rights. The training flights started Friday, a day after the UAE completed the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron emerges as potent political force ahead of election...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828091114-oioqo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/JAMES (PIX):NBA star LeBron James emerges as potent political force ahead of November U.S. election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam ends 'experiment' with mandatory masks...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828085743-j55aj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AMSTERDAM-MASKS (URGENT):Amsterdam ends "experiment" with mandatory face masks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets Brace for Election Drama Like Never Before...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/volatility-markets-brace-election-drama-100000689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Traders across major asset classes are sending the same message: Prepare for what could be the most-contentious U.S. presidential elections in decades.One measure of hedging in the stock market is higher than at any point in the past three presidential elections. In the interest-rates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian navy conducts major maneuvers near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f6c6dceba65e893aeeee9dfa814ef8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The Russian navy conducted major war games near Alaska involving dozens of ships and aircraft, the military said Friday, the biggest such drills in the area since Soviet times....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Flagship Carrier EL AL Set for Unprecedented UAE Flight...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/israels-flagship-carrier-el-al-set-for-unprecedented-uae-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Office Is Adrift. Divinity Consultants Are Here to Save It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/28/the-office-is-adrift-divinity-consultants-are-here-to-save-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the beginning there was Covid-19, and the tribe of the white collars rent their garments, for their workdays were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best and Worst Moments...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/28/republican-convention-best-and-worst-moments-from-trumps-big-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Opinion’s commentary for the last night of the Republican National Convention. In this special feature, Times Opinion writers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan officials decry robocall that dissuades mail voting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f754971cb5cc10942bd383ca69b3dc3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Michigan's attorney general and secretary of state on Thursday were investigating what they called a racist robocall that falsely warns residents in majority-Black Detroit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands expected at March on Washington commemorations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e99f9bfcca9cb388054486fa41192194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Capping a week of protests and outrage over the police shooting of a Black man in Wisconsin, civil rights advocates will highlight the scourge of police and vigilante violence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns coronavirus situation to get more difficult over winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20200828/merkel-virus-fight-will-be-more-difficult-in-autumn-winter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But New Study Suggests Polls Missing Shy Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/new-study-suggests-polls-are-missing-shy-trump-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Study Suggests Polls Are Missing Shy Trump Voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American warship sails near disputed islands...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-warship-sails-near-disputed-090856776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American warship sailed near the disputed Paracel Islands in the South China Sea, the US Navy has said, challenging Beijing&amp;#39;s claims on the resource-rich waterway and prompting a warning from the Chinese military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bullet' plane to revolutionize travel...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/celera-500l-plane/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, the mysterious bullet-shaped Celera 500L has been officially revealed. The super-efficicient six-person plane might hit skies by 2025 and could revolutionize private travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggressive BLM protesters heckle guests leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8672681/BLM-protesters-gather-outside-White-House-Trumps-RNC-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kentucky senator Rand Paul and his wife were attacked by a mob of protesters as they left the White House Thursday/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul Harassed..</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/08/28/rand-paul-attacked-outside-white-protesters-trumps-speech-rnc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul was harassed after leaving the White House where President Trump delivered his speech for the Republican National Convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe to resign over health issues... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23a3685932db83a826360280e5e5435f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan's longest-serving prime minister, Shinzo Abe, intends to leave office because of declining health, according to his political party. In a country once known for its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Pans: 'Surprisingly Flat'... 'Lack of Fireworks'... 'Far Too Long'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-chris-wallace-pans-trump-speech-as-surprisingly-flat-it-was-far-too-long/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Chris Wallace said Thursday night that while President Donald Trump's RNC convention speech had some effective lines, it was "surprisingly flat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70-minute marathon!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/donald-trump-republican-convention-review-final-night-joe-biden-covd19-china-1203025652/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump delivered a Republican Convention acceptance speech that was a 70-minute marathon of attack lines against Democrats, superlative trumpeting of his own accomplishments and dir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=56BzAQFB9T0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald J. Trump's Full Remarks at the 2020 Republican National Convention. #RNC2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowded party on South Lawn mostly devoid of virus precautions...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-celebrates-at-crowded-party-mostly-devoid-15520959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump celebrated his renomination Thursday with a crowded party at the White House that offered a jarring contrast with a nation that is still widely shut down over fears of the coronavirus pandemic whose spread remains uncontrolled.  More than 1,500 supporters poured onto the South Lawn for his formal acceptance speech to cap the Republican National Convention, and most were not wearing masks, even though they were seated closely together in white folding chairs.  The overwhelming majority of guests were not administered rapid coronavirus tests, Trump campaign and RNC officials said, despite their relative proximity to the president and other White House officials. A White House official said it would have been logistically unfeasible to test such a large number of people.  Two attendees said in interviews that they were not offered tests and were not even put through a more basic screening, such as being questioned whether they had any symptoms, such as coughs, or taking their temperature. They spoke on the condition of anonymity to talk frankly.  The spectacle offered Trump a reasonable facsimile of the traditionally raucous nominating convention that was canceled this year because of the pandemic. A large stage was set up just beyond the White House portico, lined with dozens of American flags - a dramatic backdrop that allowed the president to wield the visual power of his office at a campaign event despite federal regulations that seek to limit such activities.  But the program also projected the image to millions watching on television that a president whose public approval ratings have fallen over widespread disapproval of his handling of the pandemic has returned to business as usual, even if most Americans have not.  Medical...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
