<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>White Nationalists Stage Rally in DC, Find Themselves Stranded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/white-nationalists-stage-bizarro-rally-in-downtown-d-c-find-themselves-stranded/ar-AARts8x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Shady Billion-Dollar Phone Sex Industry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-shady-billion-dollar-phone-095800604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyIn 2019, when I was asked by three award-winning filmmakers to host and co-write a podcast called Operator, which would explore phone sex in the 1990s, of course I responded, “Yes! Yes! YES!” As soon as I learned the basics about American Telnet, a company that made billions off of adult pay-per-call lines, I was chomping at the bit to fly down to Florida to interview everyone involved. What I found is that the more sex work changes,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany advises against Christmas travel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-travel-d5cb2d658afec5aeb84c3a028cba0c44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's incoming transport minister is advising people against traveling over Christmas as the country tries to stem a wave of coronavirus infections. Federal and state leaders on Thursday announced tough new restrictions that largely target unvaccinated people , preventing them from entering nonessential stores, restaurants, sports and cultural venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anime Convention Goer Says 15 Friends Sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/man-who-had-omicron-says-friends-also-got-sick-after-nyc-anime-convention/ar-AARto86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak on cruise ship approaching New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-louisiana-new-orleans-1f8edb74567df1abdbc29161d800056f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Ten people aboard a Norwegian Cruise Line ship approaching New Orleans have tested positive for COVID-19, officials said Saturday night. The Norwegian Breakaway had departed New Orleans on Nov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon chief says China ops near Taiwan resemble 'rehearsals'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-china-taiwan-pentagon/chinese-military-flights-near-taiwan-look-like-rehearsals-pentagon-chief-idUSKBN2IJ0NQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin on Saturday said Chinese military flights near Taiwan look like "rehearsals" though he did not indicate that he expected Beijing actually to carry out such operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The woman who could bring down Roe...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-woman-who-could-bring-down-Roe-v-Wade-16674783.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soon after the U.S. Supreme Court agreed to consider Mississippi's 15-week abortion ban,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm grows over smash-and-grab robberies amid holiday season...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/584057-smash-and-grab-crimes-raise-alarms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in smash-and-grab robberies across the U.S. has jolted businesses, prompting owners and leaders to take precautions to protect brick-and-mortar shops amid a busy holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes break out in Jerusalem after Palestinian who stabbed Israeli killed by police...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/clashes-break-out-in-jerusalem-after-palestinian-who-allegedly-stabbed-israeli-is-killed-by-police/ar-AARsFd4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli flight forced to reduce altitude due to spy plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/israeli-flight-to-russia-forced-to-reduce-altitude-due-to-spy-plane-687816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden, Putin set video call...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-83e399de3cd43eee751553aafb543052</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Presidents Joe Biden and Vladimir Putin will speak in a video call Tuesday, the Kremlin said, as tensions between the United States and Russia escalate over a Russian troop buildup on the Ukrainian border  that's seen as a sign of a potential invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More omicron detected...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-new-york-city-kathy-hochul-5129e53128a7a249d36790402220aecc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York announced three more cases of the omicron variant of the coronavirus Saturday, bringing the number of state cases linked to the new variant to eight. “The omicron variant is here, and as anticipated we are seeing the beginning of community spread," state Health Commissioner Mary Bassett said in a news release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Erupts as Top Diplomats Face Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/u-s-russia-tension-on-ukraine-erupts-as-top-diplomats-face-off-1.1691101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken and Russian Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov had a testy exchange over Ukraine at a dinner with dozens of their colleagues this week, according to people familiar with the discussions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio Cancels New Year's Eve Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/rio-de-janeiro-cancels-new-year-s-eve-party-on-omicron-fears-1.1691095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC nurse charged for making fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/584343-south-carolina-nurse-charged-for-allegedly-making-fake-vaccine-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury on Friday indicted a South Carolina nurse on two counts of producing fake vaccine cards, the U.S. Attorney's Office in South Carolina announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Psychedelics Next Big Treatment for Depression?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/psychedelics-next-big-treatment-depression-050022986.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyIn 2019, the FDA made a groundbreaking decision to approve a form of ketamine as a clinical treatment for patients suffering from treatment-resistant depression, a condition which is estimated to affect nearly three million Americans. The drug, called Spravato, is the first psychedelic drug to be approved for the treatment of mental illness. This approval, along with large-scale clinical trials of LSD, MDMA, and psilocybin (the active co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Economic Collapse, Afghanistan Gripped by Starvation...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/facing-economic-collapse-afghanistan-is-gripped-by-starvation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAH WALI KOT, Afghanistan — One by one, women poured into the mud brick clinic, the frames of famished children</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotify Removes Top Comedians From Service In Royalty Payments Dispute...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/12/spotify-removes-top-comedians-from-service-royalty-payments-dispute-1234884794/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Mulaney, Jim Gaffigan, Tiffany Haddish and Kevin Hart are among the big name comedians whose work has been removed from streaming service Spotify in a fight over royalty payments. The Wall St.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 33-year-old lives on $88 a day in S Africa after moving from NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/04/how-this-33-year-old-lives-in-south-africa-on-88-a-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanisha Colon-Bibb says “nothing has really changed” about her routine in South Africa despite the emergence of a new coronavirus variant there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Plunges in Another Sign of Global Market Nerves...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-plunges-over-20-another-063422558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin plunged along with other cryptocurrencies on Saturday, in another indication of the risk aversion sweeping across financial markets.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female Founders‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsAutomating the War on Noise PollutionReliving the New York Subway Map DebateThe largest digital token fell as low as $42,296 before paring some of the tumble. It was trading at about $48,300 as of 10:31 a.m. in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee as Indonesia volcano erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/04/asia/indonesia-mount-semeru-eruption-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mount Semeru, a volcano on Indonesia's East Java Province, erupted on Saturday, spewing a column of smoke and ash while displacing thousands from the area, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France First Female President Could Be Right-Wing Pecresse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/france-s-republicans-pick-pecresse-as-presidential-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s Republicans Pick Pecresse as Presidential Candidate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodox priest shouts 'Pope, you are heretic' at Francis in Athens...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211204145529-cfa0h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-GREECE/ARCHBISHOP-PROTESTER (PIX, TV):Orthodox priest shouts 'Pope, you are a heretic' at Francis in Athens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugstores squeezed by jab demand, staff shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-science-business-health-b02158b1530871161f3c78d0ca915b67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rush of vaccine-seeking customers and staff shortages are squeezing drugstores around the U.S., leading to frazzled workers and temporary pharmacy closures. Drugstores are normally busy this time of year with flu shots and other vaccines, but now pharmacists are doling out a growing number of COVID-19 shots and giving coronavirus tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern-day slavery uncovered in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/this-has-been-happening-for-a-long-time-modern-day-slavery-uncovered-in-south-georgia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — A yearslong human trafficking operation trapped migrant workers in “modern-day slavery” on South Georgia farms, according to a federal indictment unsealed last week. Victims include over one hundred laborers smuggled from Mexico and Central America into “brutal” and “inhumane” working cond...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIOLENT CRIME SHAKES LA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/brutal-brazen-crimes-shake-la-leaving-city-at-a-crossroads/ar-AARsCHd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearing Repeat of Jan. 6, Congress Eyes Changes to Electoral Count Law...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/fearing-a-repeat-of-jan-6-congress-eyes-changes-to-electoral-count-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Members of the select congressional committee investigating the Jan. 6 attack at the Capitol are pressing to overhaul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denzel Washington, Man on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/04/denzel-washington-man-on-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Denzel Washington and Frances McDormand began rehearsing to play the Macbeths, he asked her how she thought the couple</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Households with married couple and children falls to record low...</title>
      <link>https://www.nny360.com/news/number-of-u-s-households-with-married-couple-and-children-falls-to-record-low/article_3dc0544b-cfcf-50ee-a83d-ad09927e38cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nny360.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The number of U.S. homes with a married couple and kids fell to a record low, according to new government data, as the pandemic further delayed weddings and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine defense keeps 'spotlight' on Epstein, other powerful men...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/ghislaine-maxwells-defense-keeps-spotlight-epstein-powerful-men-rcna7516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell is the one accused of sex trafficking, but during the first five days of testimony in a New York City courtroom her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala staff exodus reignites questions about her leadership -- and future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-kamala-harris-staff-exodus-reignites-questions-about-her-leadership-style-e2-80-94-and-her-future-ambitions/ar-AARshLP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shares genetic code with common cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-possibly-more-infectious-because-it-shares-genetic-code-with-common-cold-coronavirus-study-says/ar-AARscA9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRYPTO CRASHES; BITCOIN DOWN 17%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/04/cryptocurrencies-bitcoin-and-ether-prices-drop-sharply.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a 24-hour period spanning Friday morning to Saturday morning, bitcoin's price went from about $57,000 to $47,000, losing $10,000, or more than 17%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal experts on Baldwin risky interview: 'No-upside situation'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/legal-experts-alec-baldwins-risky-004841420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin's decision to speak on national television during an active criminal investigation into the 'Rust' shooting was highly risky, legal experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amish Hold Key To Healthier Heart? Gene Linked To Lower Disease Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gene-heart-disease-amish/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, study authors say fewer than one person in 10,000 has this particular gene -- B4GALT1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blizzard warnings in effect for Hawaii as potent storm wallops islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/blizzard-warning-hawaii-flood-watch-kona-low/1056085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vigorous storm system known as a Kona low is expected to bring a widespread flood threat to the drought-stricken islands, while also blasting the highest elevations of the Big Island with snow and winds up to 100 mph.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
