<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory Implantation of Microchips in Employees?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/kevin-mccandless/mandatory-implantation-microchips-employees-uk-govt-says-it-would</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds like the stuff of eschatological literature, but the idea of companies forcibly implanting their employees with microchips is making waves in Britain – although the government says it doubts the practice would be legal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece 'like war zone' with police brutality riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7924330/greece-riots-athens-police-brutality-killing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIOTERS torched cars and hurled flares at cops to mark the tenth anniversary of a ‘police brutality’ killing. Hundreds of demonstrators marched through Athens in tribute to 15-year-old …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE NAP:  Why I don't believe it's fishing expedition...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/judge-andrew-napolitano-why-i-dont-believe-that-mueller-is-on-a-fishing-expedition-or-is-about-to-go-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am not of the view that Mueller is on a fishing expedition or is about to go home. First, he has a few dozen defendants whom he has indicted and needs to try -- even though most are Russians indicted for hacking and interfering with the 2016 election campaign and will be tried in absentia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to reveal secrets in Cohen, Manafort filings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/mueller-to-release-new-details-on-ex-trump-aides-manafort-cohen.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, federal prosecutors in New York will be filing a sentencing memo detailing Cohen's  cooperation after his guilty plea in their separate case against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High intrigue surrounds Mueller filing in Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/420107-high-intrigue-surrounds-mueller-filing-in-manafort-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller on Friday is expected to file a bombshell report that describes how former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort eviscerated his plea agreement with federal prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP set to grill Comey...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/420160-house-gop-set-to-grill-comey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are poised to grill former FBI Director James Comey on Friday in what could be the final act in a dramatic effort to probe allegations of bias at the Justice Department before Democrats take over the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift snubbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/07/grammys-2019-taylor-swifts-reputation-snubbed-for-album-of-the-year-because-of-american-music-awards-appearance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grammy nominations are out. And Taylor Swift, previously a Grammy favorite, has been snubbed. I predicted this when Swift appeared on the American Music Awards and performed from her “Reputat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar king of GRAMMYS with eight noms...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/entertainment/entertainment-news/Kendrick-Lamar-Leads-Grammy-Noms-Where-Women-Make-a-Comeback-502158311.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music of 'Black Panther,' with Kendrick Lamar in its starring role, officially owns the 2019 Grammy Awards, where women are heavily represented in the major four categories following a year where their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE BRACES FOR RIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-macron/france-braces-for-trouble-macron-to-address-yellow-vest-anger-idUSKBN1O60I8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France hunkered down for another wave of potentially violent protests on Saturda...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Fatigue Killing Any Movie, Show With Political Edge?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-fatigue-killing-movie-show-political-murphy-brown-front-runner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's risky, especially since the real unfolding drama on cable is more compelling," political reporter and documentarian Jonathan Alter says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Latin America, Awash in Crime, Citizens Impose Their Own Brutal Justice...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-a-continent-awash-in-crime-citizens-impose-their-own-brutal-justice-1544110959</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latin America has the world’s highest murder rate. With little faith in the police or courts, mobs routinely kill suspected lawbreakers in spontaneous attacks. Many lynching victims are innocent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic 'object' spotted towering over Earth from ISS; NASA live feed CUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/746841/NASA-conspiracy-alien-news-iss-international-space-station-blue-object-cut-live-feed-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI CONFUSION: America has three coasts -- 'North, South and West'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/pelosi-confusion-america-has-three-coasts-north-south-and-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nancy? The next Speaker of the House struggled with U.S. geography on Thursday as she once again announced her opposition to a wall along the border with Mexico. ﻿ “We, most of us, speaking for myself, consider the wall immoral, ineffective and expensive, and the President said – he promised – he also promised Mexico …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most modified youth: 40 ops...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7921478/worlds-most-modified-youth-operations-split-tongue-eye-tattoos-belly-button-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A YOUNG Australian man who went through more than 40 body modification procedures claims to be “the world’s most modified youth”. Ethan Bramble from Melbourne has had a string of body modifications…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coup?</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/445836-france-radicals-weapons-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As France braces for a new wave of protests, a government spokesman warned that radicals are using the Yellow Vest movement to pursue their own goals and one of them is to topple the current leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eye-Scanning Lie Detector...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-05/blade-runner-eye-scanning-lie-detector-may-be-coming-dystopian-future-near-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3.9 billion people now using Internet...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/more-half-global-population-now-115946999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 3.9 billion people are now using the Internet, meaning that for the first time more than half of the global population is online, the United Nations said Friday. The UN agency for information and communication technologies, ITU, said that by the end of 2018 a full 51.2 percent of people around</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot skills will make surgeons out of nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/robot-skills-will-make-surgeons-out-of-nurses-gds3t0tw3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caesareans and other routine operations will be done by nurses as the rise of robots means common procedures do not need a hands-on surgeon, according to an expert review. Nanorobots will fix the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man posed as doctor, gave meds to unsuspecting patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.postcrescent.com/story/news/crime/2018/12/05/appleton-man-charged-posing-doctor-held-200-k-bond/2216983002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postcrescent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using the pseudonym "Doctor Kyle Ellis,"Â a man posing as a doctor treated patients and gave them medications, a criminal complaint states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rages in Anti-Mueller Tweetstorm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-rages-in-anti-muelller-tweetstorm-big-time-conflicts-of-interest-and-destroyed-peoples-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outcry over mass teen roundup...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/outcry-over-mass-teen-roundup-france-braces-more-090606857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images of dozens of high-school pupils kneeling with their hands behind their heads during mass round-ups sparked an outcry Friday as France braces for more violence at "yellow vest" protests this weekend. Leftwing politicians have expressed outrage at the videos, which have gone viral on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/frances-macron-astride-the-globe-overlooked-swelling-anger-at-home-1544178601 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron has tended to respond to outrage over high fuel taxes with lectures rather than sympathy. After the weekend’s violence, he had to back down, postponing a tax increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest known wild bird to become mother 37th time...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/07/worlds-oldest-bird-lays-egg-wisdom-albatross </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisdom, a 68-year-old Laysan albatross, has laid another egg with her longtime lover at the Midway Atoll national wildlife refuge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little town that pot built...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2018/12/04/the-little-town-that-pot-built</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like horror film'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Like-a-horror-film-The-efforts-to-contain-13449195.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NAIROBI, Kenya - The medical anthropologist was in the shower when she heard the first pops of gunfire. Initially, she thought it might be the action movie she'd left playing on high volume. Then the wall shook. The violence in eastern Congo, which has stymied the international response to a growing Ebola outbreak in the region, had arrived at the guesthouse used by many of those working to prevent the disease's spread. Terrified, Julienne Anoko dropped to the floor and crawled into the corridor outside her room. She and five others from U.N. agencies, Congo's health ministry and the World Health Organization, which she works for, hid in another bathroom for three hours until a U.N. peacekeeping force arrived and gave the all-clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola spreads to major city...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/86fd89fa73594ed0aa098c6c5a063300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — The second-largest Ebola outbreak in history has spread to a major city in eastern Congo, as health experts worry whether the stock of an experimental vaccine will stand up to the demands of an epidemic with no end in sight. Butembo, with more than 1 million residents, is now reporting cases of the deadly hemorrhagic fever. That complicates Ebola containment work already challenged by rebel attacks elsewhere that have made tracking the virus almost impossible in some isolated villages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  HOST CHRIS ROCK SHOCK: ONLY GAYS WATCH OSCARS...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A33625-2005Feb17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO WILL REPLACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/07/kevin-hart-steps-down-from-oscar-host-job-after-scandal-about-homophobic-tweets-reaches-peak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart has just Tweeted: “I have made the choice to step down from hosting this year’s Oscar’s….this is because I do not want to be a distraction on a night that should …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Flies Plane Over Ukraine in Warning to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-military-plane-flies-over-ukraine-in-warning-to-russia-1544136754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon said it carried out a rare flight over Ukraine under the international Open Skies Treaty to “reaffirm U.S. commitment to Ukraine” amid heightened Russia-Ukraine tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Making President's Bed, A Housekeeper Without Papers... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/making-president-trump%E2%80%99s-bed-a-housekeeper-without-papers/ar-BBQAYz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm tired of being humiliated and treated like a stupid person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-housekeeper-new-jersey-golf-club-immigration-20181206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman working as a housekeeper at President Trump's golf club in Bedminster, New Jersey revealed that she is an unauthorized immigrant in a NYT interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation-hit Chernobyl wolves 'spreading mutant genes across Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911846/the-european-grey-wolf-population-has-boomed-at-the-site-since-the-human-population-moved-out-and-it-became-a-virtual-wildlife-preserve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS fear wolves living in Chernobyl’s radioactive forbidden zone may be spreading mutant genes across Europe. The European grey wolf population has boomed at the site since the human p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President lawyers, Special Counsel in talks following written submission...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-lawyers-special-counsel-discussions-following-written-submission-president-s-n945061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s lawyers have resumed discussions with the office of special counsel Robert Mueller in recent days, the first time that's been acknowledged since President Donald Trump submitted written responses to questions regarding the possibility of collusion between his 2016 campaign and Russia, two people familiar with the matter told NBC News on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOPES Fact-Checker Botches Fact Check...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/06/snopes-facebook-google-fact-check/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is quite literally insane fake news'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Legal 'proctological examination' hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/roger-stone-gripes-about-legal-proctological-examination-this-has-been-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR DRAMA: HOST HOMOPHOBIA HEADACHE</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-harts-past-anti-gay-tweets-creates-problem-academy-1167191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next Oscars host faces a backlash over hundreds of homophobic jokes. Said Billy Eichner: "There's real truth, anger &amp; fear behind these."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They're All Too Old': Dems Face Generational Reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/democrats-face-a-generational-reckoning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The choice in the 2020 primary ultimately comes down to one thing: who is best prepared to beat Trump at a time when Trump owns the culture? Someone who actually understands culture would be a start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers who ingested Mexican cartel cash profits busted...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-colombia-crime/smugglers-ingested-mexican-cartel-cash-say-colombia-police-after-arrests-idUSKBN1O600D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombia has arrested 27 people accused of belonging to four smuggling networks ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Heather Nauert Next UN Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-07/trump-to-pick-heather-nauert-as-next-un-ambassador-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep in mind, I'm not homophobic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/kevin-hart-deletes-old-anti-gay-tweets-after-landing-oscar-hosting-gig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart has been busy scrubbing his Twitter account of his old anti-gay tweets since he was tapped as Oscar host earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gig in jeopardy?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/should-the-oscars-fire-host-kevin-hart-over-his-homophobic-jokes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past homophobic and anti-gay jokes and tweets the comedian made, including calling someone’s picture a “gay billboard for AIDS” have resurfaced. Are they a fireable offense?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Hart Scrambles to Delete Anti-Gay Tweets After Being Named OSCARS Host...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/michaelblackmon/kevin-hart-homophobic-tweets-gay-oscars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a since-deleted tweet, Hart joked that he would break a dollhouse over his son’s head if he were caught playing with the toy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador: Enough UK guarantees for Assange to leave embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0b95cddbe0614d47b71c07c827710210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Ecuador's president has ramped up pressure on Julian Assange to leave his country's embassy in London, saying that Britain had provided sufficient guarantees that the WikiLeaks founder won't be extradited to face the death penalty abroad. Lenin Moreno's comments in a radio interview Thursday suggest that months of quiet diplomacy between the U.K. and Ecuador to resolve Assange's situation is bearing fruit at a time when questions are swirling about the former Australian hacker's legal fate in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doorstop vigilantes fight porch pirates with booby traps, dog poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/porch-pirates-are-trying-to-steal-christmas-but-doorstep-vigilantes-are-on-high-alert/2018/12/06/cbf694ea-f966-11e8-8c9a-860ce2a8148f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans fight back with booby traps, hidden cameras and even dog poop against the scourge of online commerce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Ready for 'Inevitable' Clampdown on Tech, Media?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/12/06/are-you-ready-for-the-clampdown-on-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Apple's CEO Tim Cook says "the free market is not working," bad things are coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham lied to discredit alleged rape victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ct-life-stevens-thursday-how-not-to-apologize-lena-dunham-1206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Girls" actress and director should be better at apologizing by now, but her Hollywood Reporter note to Aurora Perrineau is little more than terrible performance art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns embezzle $500,000 from school to gamble, take trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.presstelegram.com/2018/12/05/nuns-improperly-took-as-much-as-500000-from-torrance-catholic-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.presstelegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were an ATM and people know it and they won’t ask for justice,” one parent said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sits on victim naked, bashes with brass plate...</title>
      <link>https://www.komu.com/news/columbia-woman-arrested-for-domestic-assault-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.komu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested Amy Parrino after an incident in northeast Columbia on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman chases, beats man who refused to perform oral sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.columbiatribune.com/news/20181204/columbia-woman-charged-with-sex-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbiatribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Columbia woman is accused of attempting to force a man to perform oral sex on her.Boone County prosecutors on Monday charged 43-year-old Amy Nicole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC election fraud probe shines light on 'ballot harvesting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/north-carolina/north-carolina-race-shines-light-on-ballot-harvesting/884597359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) - An investigation into whether political operatives in North Carolina illegally collected and possibly stole absentee ballots in a still-undecided congressional race has drawn attention to a widespread but little-known political tool called ballot harvesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firms in China vulnerable after HUAWEI arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/us-firms-in-china-vulnerable-after-huawei-arrest-ex-us-trade-advisor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a good chance the Chinese will retaliate for the arrest of Huawei CFO Meng Wanzhou by targeting American businesses in China, says former assistant U.S. trade representative Jeff Moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE AirDrop Assaults On Rise As Criminals 'Cyber Flash' Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/airdrop-assaults-on-the-rise-as-criminals-cyber-flash-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As technology infiltrates every aspect of our lives criminals and creeps are figuring out creative ways to abuse it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ride from Hell': Carpooling in Age of UBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ride-from-hell-carpooling-in-the-age-of-uber-can-beawkward-1544112559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shared ride services become more popular, passengers clash over music, temperature and talking. Exasperated drivers try to referee; ‘They had no shame.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIATCHRYSLER to open new Detroit factory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/fiat-chrysler-reportedly-plans-to-open-new-assembly-factory-in-detroit-to-build-suv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSKINS QB facing 'devastating complications' after surgery...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/12/06/reports-alex-smith-dealing-with-post-op-infection-in-leg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington quarterback Alex Smith’s recovery from the broken tibia and fibula he suffered last month is reportedly being complicated by an infection. Eric Bickel of 106.7 The Fan reports that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDNY Chief removed over 'inappropriate behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/06/fdny-chief-james-leonard-removed-from-post-over-inappropriate-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDNY’s top uniformed member was removed from his post Thursday amid a probe into his alleged mistreatment of the department’s highest-ranking woman, the FDNY and sources said. Chief of Departme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece plans crowdfunding for new warships...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1845b762915c4de7bb71d6568fb73d51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece's defense minister is appealing to his austerity-battered countryfolk for a crowdfunding effort to raise money for new warships, promising to donate part of his own salary. Panos Kammenos says he will open a bank account on Jan. 1 where members of the public can make donations "for new frigates and a flagship." He addressed his appeal to Greece's wealthy shipowning industry, as well as ordinary Greeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>89,000 security forces deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-security/france-to-deploy-89000-security-personnel-ahead-of-saturday-protests-idUSKBN1O52BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe said 89,000 members of the security force...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Conversion Exorcisms on the Rise in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/islamic-exorcisms-aim-to-cast-out-lgbt-demons-in-worlds-largest-muslim-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's even a TV show...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after Wisconsin Republicans approved a package of bills intended to restri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next big security risk: Children's video-game habit...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-next-big-risk-to-your-security-is-your-kids-video-game-habit-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers are increasingly targeting video games, new report finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY:  3 new docs may show what ex-Trump aides told Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/friday-3-new-documents-may-show-some-what-ex-trump-n944801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sentencing memos for Michael Cohen and a document detailing Paul Manafort's alleged "crimes and lies" are due to be filed Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/eiffel-tower-close-saturday-due-planned-paris-protests-n944876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several other cultural sites and attractions will also close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi rejects funding wall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3fd315c66554c22bfdf97710e0df711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi is rejecting the idea of paying for President Donald Trump's border wall in exchange for a deal to help hundreds of thousands of young immigrants avoid deportation. Pelosi said Thursday that wall funding and legal protections for so-called "Dreamers" should not be linked, saying "they're two different subjects." Pelosi, who is seeking to become House speaker in January, said Congress should pass appropriations bills that key committees have already agreed on, along with a separate measure funding the Department of Homeland Security, which oversees the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Marriage Easiest In Old Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/marriage-easier-old-age-laughter-replaces-bickering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever feel like your marriage is losing its luster and all the romance is being replaced with petty bickering? Don't worry, there's light -- and lightheartedness -- at the end of the tunnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Net Oil Exporter for First Time in 75 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-06/u-s-becomes-a-net-oil-exporter-for-the-first-time-in-75-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Flight Skids Off Runway At Burbank Airport... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/12/06/southwest-flight-skids-burbank-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines flight arriving at Burbank Airport from Oakland skidded off the runway after landing Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Murder Rate on Track for Big Drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/upshot/us-murder-rate-for-2018-is-on-track-for-a-big-drop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murders are down so far in a sample of large American cities, typically a good indicator for national numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bones tossed like trash at cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fc144b8bb3c04f96b95634f7f645415e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the 1990s, Cheryl Jansen had noticed junk and tree limbs piling up at the once oasis-like Park Cemetery, just north of downtown Bridgeport, Connecticut, and wondered where the money families had paid for perpetual upkeep was going. What she learned after finally taking her case to a judge shocked the conscience. Gravestones and remains moved without permission to make way for the newly dead. New graves simply stacked on top of old ones, separated by a new layer of dirt. Worst of all, human bones, casket pieces and old headstones tossed in the woods like trash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65,000 security forces deployed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edfebfba2beb486d8d1e48da4cb6834e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France will deploy more than 65,000 security forces amid fears of new rioting at protests Saturday in Paris and around the nation, despite President Emmanuel Macron's surrender over a fuel tax hike that unleashed weeks of unrest. Police unions and local authorities held emergency meetings Thursday to strategize on how to handle the weekend protests, while disparate groups of protesters did the same thing, sharing their plans on social networks and chat groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer who documented dark side of communist state mysteriously vanishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911948/chinese-photographer-dark-side-communist-state-vanishes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN award-winning Chinese photographer who candidly documented the dark side of the country’s booming economy has mysteriously vanished. Lu Guang, a three-time World Press Photo award winner, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX Lands Most TV Nominations... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/golden-globes-tv-fx-most-nominations-network-prime-video-streamers-hbo-netflix-1202515092/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FX is closing its chapter as a 21st Century Fox network on a high note, edging awards juggernauts HBO and Netflix to top the list of networks with most Golden Globes nominations, 10. It was a very …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encryption-busting powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.itnews.com.au/news/australia-gets-world-first-encryption-laws-as-labor-folds-516601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itnews.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor passes bill without changes it claimed were needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO CORTEZ:  Climate Governance Will Create 'Economic, Social, and Racial Justice'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-inevitable-global-warming-governance-will-crea </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It’s inevitable that we can use the transition to 100% renewable energy as the vehicle to truly deliver and establish economic, social, and racial justice in the United States of America’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elementary school bans Santa, candy canes, red and green items...</title>
      <link>http://eagnews.org/elementary-school-bans-santa-candy-canes-reindeer-elf-on-the-shelf-red-green-items-to-be-inclusive-and-culturally-sensitive/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manchester Elementary School Principal Jennifer Sinclair just landed on Santa’s naughty list, which means she probably won’t get any presents from the big man this year. The Nebraska educator apparently tripped on a “big rock” and fell on her face, all the while attempting to rob her students of the joyous Christmas season. It’s like a bad Hallmark movie come to life, happy ending and all. “It seems that I have stumbled upon a ‘big rock’ that I hadn’t anticipated,” Sinclair wrote to her legion of teachers in her “week ahead” newsletter for Dec. 3-7. “I know that you are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest snubs, surprises...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/golden-globes/2018/12/06/golden-globes-nominations-snubs-4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2019 Golden Globes nominations are out. Let's first hit some surprises, because there were some rather huge ones on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6467875/Elizabeth-Warrens-advisers-want-APOLOGIZE-DNA-stunt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats blasted the liberal Massachusetts senator in October for drawing attention to her biggest political liability in the middle of a tense midterm election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval rating crashes to 18%...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7915541/emmanuel-macron-predicts-violence-france-weekend-approval-rating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL Macron’s approval rating has crashed below 20 per cent today as he predicts more “major violence” across France this weekend. The beleaguered head of state is locked in a law and order cri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY, ZUCKER, DRUDGE NAMED 'MOST INFLUENTIAL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/mediaites-most-influential-in-news-media-2018/8/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES CHAOS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d47620b3896e4f47b82aac1ec5069554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Adam McKay's Dick Cheney biopic "Vice" seized control of the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards with a leading six nominations, narrowly edging Bradley Cooper's tear-jerking revival "A Star Is Born," the interracial road-trip drama "Green Book" and the period romp "The Favourite." "Vice" topped all contenders Thursday, in nominations announced at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California, including best picture, comedy and best actor nominations for Christian Bale's nearly unrecognizable performance as the former vice president. It also earned nominations for Amy Adams' Lynne Cheney, Sam Rockwell's George W. Bush and both the screenplay and direction by McKay, the veteran comedy filmmaker who once skewered politicians as a "Saturday Night Live" writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amal Clooney accuses Trump of 'giving green light' to autocratic regimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/amal-clooney-accuses-trump-giving-green-light-autocratic-regimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amal Clooney has claimed Donald Trump gives the &amp;quot;green light&amp;quot; to autocratic regimes during a speech in which she warned against the US president's attacks on the press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/elizabeth-warren-stands-by-dna-test-but-around-her-worries-abound-/18043961/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The plan was straightforward: After years of being challenged by President Donald Trump and others about a decades-old claim of Native American ancestry, Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., would take a DNA test to prove her stated family origins in the Cherokee and Delaware tribes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student protests intensify alongside tax revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181206-french-student-protests-intensify-alongside-yellow-vest-revolt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French student protests intensify alongside 'yellow vest' revolt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Spoilers?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/811016/5-republicans-who-could-challenge-trump-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of them can win. But they could play spoiler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatters Diversity Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-shatters-diversity-record-4-10-best-picture-nominees-non-white-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Crazy Rich Asians," "BlacKkKlansman," "Black Panther" and "If Beale Street Could Talk" all break into the top categories</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
