<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Landfall with 140mph winds and 165mph gusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT4+shtml/280240.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/aug/27/wall-street-hits-new-highs-after-fed-extends-covid-stimulus-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head of US central bank Jerome Powell had been expected to announce the programme would be tapered off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS propaganda app uses AMAZON Web Services...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/ISIS-propaganda-app-that-touted-Kabul-attack-16417641.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A propaganda arm of ISIS that celebrated the suicide bombing that killed at least 170...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio mandates vaccines for tourist spots, public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rio-mandates-vaccines-tourist-spots-185803462.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio de Janeiro announced Friday it will require proof of vaccination against Covid-19 to enter public spaces including movie theaters, stadiums and iconic tourist spots like the Christ the Redeemer statue and Sugarloaf Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Lifts All Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/denmark-scrap-all-covid-19-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREPARES TO STRIKE BACK</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/us-prepares-to-strike-back-after-kabul-airport-attack-grxfh5qkf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is drawing up plans for retaliatory strikes against Isis militants in Afghanistan after the killing of as many as 200 people in the Kabul airport suicide bombing.President Biden’s vow to avenge the deaths of the 13 US Marines who were among those to die in the attack raises the prospect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knocks out more oil than Katrina...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/update-5-extremely-dangerous-hurricane-ida-knocks-out-more-oil-than-katrina/ar-AANOdln</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ENERGY (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-'Extremely dangerous' Hurricane Ida knocks out more oil than Katrina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOSTAGE FEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934589/Britain-pulls-plug-Kabul-airlift-UK-start-getting-soldiers-Airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ministry of Defence (MoD) has said the UK's ability to process more evacuations from Afghanistan's Kabul airport will be 'extremely reduced'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Seagal on Hook for SEC Crypto Fine Despite Move to Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/steven-seagal-hook-sec-crypto-180957482.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Steven Seagal who starred in the film “Beyond the Law” found out that even relocating to Russia doesn’t mean he’s beyond the reach of U.S. courts as the Securities and Exchange Commission won a judgment against him.A federal judge in Brooklyn, New York, said the SEC can go through Seagal’s business manager to try and collect more than $200,000 that the actor owes the U.S. government for failing to disclose he was being paid to promote a digital token.U.S. District Judge William Ku</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel seeks records from tech companies in riot probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-riots-capitol-siege-michael-pence-d0324bd4b8122220e181147725078733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House panel investigating the riot at the U.S. Capitol issued sweeping document requests on Friday to social media companies, expanding the scope of its investigation as it seeks to examine the events leading to the Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders sells big govt virtues in red states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-election-2020-bernie-sanders-a3760ba452dcd0fd8014a115461e8ef5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST LAFAYETTE, Ind. (AP) — Bernie Sanders has long argued — but not proved — that his big government populism can win over voters in the largely white, rural communities that flocked to Republican Donald Trump in recent elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine Commander Fired After Blasting 'Inept'  Leadership...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/marine-battalion-commander-blasts-inept-military-leadership-over-afghanistan-withdrawal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sitting Marine battalion commander on Thursday blasted the “ineptitude” of U.S. military leadership over the disastrous Afghanistan withdrawal, saying he was willing to risk losing his 17-year career and future retirement pension in order to “demand accountability” from top military brass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Religious Broadcasters fires spox after pro-vax comments...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2021/08/27/nrb-spokesman-dan-darling-fired-after-pro-vaccine-statements-on-morning-joe-evangelical-covid-hesitancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — Daniel Darling, senior vice president of communications for the National Religious Broadcasters, was fired Friday (Aug. 27) after refusing to recant his pro-vaccine statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders parents to pay $45K for tossing son's porn, sex toy collection...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/judge-orders-parents-to-pay-45k-for-tossing-sons-porn-collection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because they threw out some X-rated material, these parents will now have fork over thousands in cash. A Michigan couple will have to pay $45,000 in a smut-fueled family feud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK assassin Sirhan wins parole with support of 2 Kennedys...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/crime-shootings-california-los-angeles-san-diego-acfc333ba40e6853c6e2874281685d0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — U.S. Sen. Robert F. Kennedy's assassin was granted parole Friday after two of RFK's sons spoke in favor of Sirhan Sirhan’s release and prosecutors declined to argue he should be kept behind bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cancel culture' show in Warsaw stirs controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210827-cancel-culture-show-in-warsaw-stirs-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Cancel culture' show in Warsaw stirs controversy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid pandemic, CDC gets serious -- about gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/27/health/cdc-gun-research-walensky/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in decades, the director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention -- the nation's top public health agency -- is speaking out forcefully about gun violence in America, calling it a "serious public health threat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban kill squad hunting down Afghans --  using American biometric data...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/taliban-kill-squad-hunting-afghans-with-americas-biometric-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban has mobilized a special unit, called Al Isha, to hunt down Afghans who helped US and allied forces — and it’s using US equipment and data to do it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. intel split on origins, offer no high-confidence conclusions in new report...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/27/covid-origin-report-us-intelligence-agencies-are-divided.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May, Biden ordered a closer intelligence review of what he described as two likely scenarios of the origins of the Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission impossible: To rescue Tom Cruise's stolen luggage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mission-impossible-rescue-tom-cruises-162905111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission for British police on Friday, should they choose to accept it, was to recover the luggage of Hollywood superstar Tom Cruise after his bodyguard's car was stolen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  NEWSOM COULD BE IN REAL TROUBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/gavin-newsom-california-recall/619848/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gavin Newsom's struggles could spell trouble for Democrats everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riddle as Pentagon now says there was only ONE explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9934007/Pentagon-says-ONE-explosion-Kabul-suicide-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army General Hank Taylor said on Friday: 'I can confirm that we do not believe there was a second explosion at or near the Baron hotel' and blamed the 'confusion' on the dynamics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of Young Patients Struggling to Breathe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/at-a-children-s-hospital-a-wave-of-young-patients-struggling-to-breathe/ar-AANOZfV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a Children’s Hospital, a Wave of Young Patients Struggling to Breathe By Noah Weiland and Erin Schaff NEW ORLEANS — Helpless to improve her infant son’s breathing as he was about to be intubated, Catherine Perrilloux did the only thing that came naturally to her in that moment, the worst of her life: She looked away and prayed. The boy, known as Junior, was two months old and gravely ill with Covid-19. Sign up for The Morning newsletter from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: Nearly 100 Cats Removed From Feces-Covered Home...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2021/08/26/mather-greene-county-cats-rescued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of cats were removed from a home in Greene County Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T. Rex Was 'Foodie,' Scientists Find...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avmap/scientists-find-t-rex-was-a-foodie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dinosaur had “a delicate side like other animals. It’s not a monster.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani admits liking Scotch but denies being alcoholic...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/politics/rudy-giuliani-says-u-s-has-gone-off-the-rails-denies-he-has-alcohol-problem/3243586/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 20 years after being dubbed America’s Mayor, Rudy Giuliani says he knows that people think he’s gone off the rails. He also doesn’t care, and instead believes it’s the country that has gone off the rails</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans evacuations ordered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/hurricane/article_c59648f6-0756-11ec-858a-874da06021ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Tropical Storm Ida heads toward the Gulf coast, some parish officials in southeast Louisiana have called for voluntary and mandatory evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark Lifts All Restrictions Except Entry Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidnikel/2021/08/27/denmark-lifts-all-coronavirus-restrictions-except-entry-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From September 10, Denmark will remove all domestic restrictions related to Covid-19. Travel restrictions remain in place for the time being, although many people can now travel to Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7y-lpFQ-XLs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594Follow my Twitter for more fre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro says everyone should buy a rifle...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-08-27/brazils-bolsonaro-says-everyone-should-buy-a-rifle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organizer of TX 'Freedom Rally' hospitalized with Covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-anti-mask-freedom-rally-045722778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His pregnant wife said this week that the hospital was "out of options" for her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL JUDGE OVERTURNS DESANTIS MASK MANDATE BAN...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/27/florida-judge-overturns-desantis-school-mask-mandate-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida Circuit Court judge has overturned Gov. Ron DeSantis’ mask mandate ban for Florida schools, ruling the governor overstepped his authority by issuing an executive order banning the mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans inmate sues prisons over surgery denial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-prisons-virginia-4bc8a1f7c9ba60a554d099e40129c8b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTESVILLE, Va. (AP) — A transgender man held at a women's prison in Virginia is suing state prison officials after being denied breast removal surgery. Jason Yoakam, who is serving sentences for murder, conspiracy to commit murder and a firearm offense, says the denial by the state Department of Corrections violates his constitutional protection against cruel and unusual punishment and his rights under the Equal Protection Clause of the 14th Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landfall with 120mph winds and 150mph gusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT4+shtml/271516.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repairs Of Leaning San Francisco Skyscraper Put On Hold...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/26/repairs-sinking-san-francisco-skyscraper-on-hold-engineering-expert-blasts-plan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A geotechnical engineer and professor at UC Berkeley says the current plan to fix the leaning Millennium Tower in San Francisco is "incorrect" and should be abandoned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 In 5 People Worldwide Have Suffered Sleeping Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nearly-3-in-5-suffered-sleep-problems-during-covid-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study involving people from 79 countries around the globe reveals that 56.5 percent experienced some kind of sleep disturbance in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBT NEARS $29 TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.usdebtclock.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usdebtclock.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ON ALERT FOR MORE ATTACKS</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/western-nations-race-complete-afghan-evacuation-deadline-looms-2021-08-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. forces helping to evacuate Afghans desperate to flee new Taliban rule were on alert for more attacks on Friday after an Islamic State attack killed 92 people including 13 U.S. service members just outside Kabul airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court blocks eviction moratorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-blocks-biden-administration-s-eviction-moratorium-n1277765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Congress never gave the CDC the staggering amount of power it claims," a group of landlords argued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped Ally: 'Will Never Regret it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/afghan-ally-trapped-in-kabul-says-even-if-he-dies-i-will-never-regret-it-in-emotional-and-harrowing-fox-news-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A segment on Fox News’ America’s Newsroom on Friday was emotional as an Afghan ally who was only identified as “Carl” was connected with someone trying to help Afghan interpreters evacuate Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION 30 YEAR HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/27/key-inflation-gauge-rises-3point6percent-from-a-year-ago-to-tie-biggest-jump-since-the-early-1990s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inflation measure the Federal Reserve uses to set policy rose 3.6% in July from a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/26/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks rose Friday as Fed Chair Jerome Powell prepared the markets for the central bank start tapering its $120 billion in monthly bond purchases this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANETTA:  US troops will need to return for combat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/27/leon-panetta-says-us-troops-will-need-to-go-back-to-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Defense Secretary Leon Panetta says US troops will need to go back into combat in Afghanistan — as the region remains on high alert for more suicide attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MOBILE CEO says 'truly sorry' for hack of 50 MILLION users' data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-hacking-fce56107ed5982bbbbc6b1acdefb5ebc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BELLEVUE, Wash. (AP) — T-Mobile says it has notified nearly all of the millions of customers whose personal data was stolen and that it is “truly sorry” for the breach. CEO Mike Sievert said in a written statement Friday that the company spends lots of effort to try to stay ahead of criminal hackers “but we didn’t live up to the expectations we have for ourselves to protect our customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus surge pummels Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-hawaii-097137d852609f37e4aada899da5938f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Kuulei Perreira-Keawekane could barely breathe when she went to a Hawaii emergency room. Nausea made it difficult for her to stand and her body throbbed with pain. Like many Native Hawaiians, she was not vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBERTY announces campus-wide quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-a62698ebad644853caaff077fd578cf5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LYNCHBURG, Va. (AP) — Liberty University announced a temporary campus-wide quarantine Thursday amid a spike in COVID-19 cases. The quarantine is set to begin Monday and last until Sept. 10, news outlets report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED KEEPS PUMPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-5540a3115d041e10327bfcad2be043e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve will start dialing back its ultra-low-rate policies this year as long as hiring continues to improve, Chair Jerome Powell said Friday, signaling the beginning of the end of the Fed’s extraordinary response to the pandemic recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New urgency to airlift from Kabul after blasts kill dozens...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bombings-evacuations-kabul-bb32ec2b65b54ec24323e021c9b4a553</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — Evacuation flights from Afghanistan resumed with new urgency on Friday, a day after two suicide bombings targeted the thousands of people desperately fleeing a Taliban takeover and killed dozens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellish summer in Tahoe: Choked in smoke with fire closing in fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/a-hellish-summer-in-lake-tahoe-choked-in-smoke-with-the-caldor-fire-closing-in-fast/ar-AANOjOx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the destructive Caldor fire creeps closer to the popular resort area, the boaters, hikers and beach-goers who typically descend on South Lake Tahoe have all but vanished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long COVID's daunting toll seen in study of pandemic's earliest patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/long-covids-daunting-toll-seen-in-study-of-pandemics-earliest-patients/ar-AANOkT3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study of more than 1,200 COVID survivors who were once hospitalized finds that about half have at least one symptom a year later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special forces vets launch own mission to get allies out...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9932809/Afghanistan-evacuation-continues-day-ISIS-bomb-kills-13-troops-90-Afghans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now just four days until the Taliban's August 31 deadline to get the remaining US citizens, troops and equipment out of Kabul and the mission has become even more dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama reports large spike in child cases...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/569684-alabama-reports-large-spike-in-child-covid-19-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama has reported a surge of COVID-19 cases among children as the academic school year gets underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could be Cat 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-orleans-storms-hurricanes-tropical-storms-science--d4b3399437cc5ccb7e76aa270a63f724</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — Tropical Storm Ida swirled toward a strike on Cuba on Friday showing hallmarks of a rare, rapidly intensifying storm that could speed across warm Gulf waters and slam into Louisiana as a Category 3 hurricane on Sunday, the National Hurricane Center warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Sea Drone Activity Prelude to Major Naval Movement?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42154/japanese-fighters-intercept-three-chinese-drones-in-as-many-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It isn't clear if the surge in Chinese drone presence over the East China Sea is indicative of a new trend or prelude to a major naval movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliwa mayoral candidacy radical shift in NYC politics..</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-local-correspondents/the-mayoral-candidate-with-a-mouth-that-roars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curtis Sliwa, the Republican nominee, expects his opponent to paint him as racist, sexist, and homophobic. But he’s ready to strike back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How deadliest ever female sniper 'Lady Death' shot 309 Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3550775/sniper-lady-death-world-war-2-nazis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AS GERMAN troops poured into the Soviet Union in the midst of World War 2, Lyudmila Pavlichenko rushed to join the Red Army. Out-of-touch recruiters found the prospect of a 24-year-old woman joinin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One person turns up at anti-lockdown protest in Auckland...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/27/new-zealand-police-break-up-one-person-anti-lockdown-protest-in-auckland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram account had called on people to get involved in the Queen Street demonstration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darthgator nearly ripped trainer's arm off. She can't wait to work with him again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-alligator-named-darthgator-nearly-ripped-his-trainer-e2-80-99s-arm-off-she-can-e2-80-99t-wait-to-work-with-him-again/ar-AANOewg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m the one that made a mistake,” the trainer said. “Darthgator was just an alligator doing alligator things.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
