<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Burned-out millennials quitting lucrative jobs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/25/millennials-are-bailing-on-their-high-paying-jobs-to-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Solomon had a pretty sweet life. The 20-something publicist was always out at fashion events, dinners and parties — and even hung out with John Legend during Fashion Week. “It was definitely …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DEATH SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/us-markets-earnings-trade-ecb-and-data-on-the-agenda.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech-heavy Nasdaq Composite and S&amp;P 500 opened lower on Thursday after a sharp decline in Facebook sent tech shares lower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mercury in retrograde': Expect 3 weeks of bad luck?</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/07/26/mercury-in-retrograde-should-expect-3-weeks-bad-luck.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're experiencing a spell of bad luck, many people may ask you the same question: is Mercury in retrograde?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5995211/Facebook-shareholders-try-fire-Mark-Zuckerberg-chairman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shareholders are trying to fire Mark Zuckerberg as chairman of Facebook because of the social media giant's 'mishandling' of recent scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL ST STUNNED OVER PROFITABILITY PLUNGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/26/wall-street-is-stunned-over-facebooks-coming-profitability-plunge-do.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several analysts are downgrading Facebook shares after the company's disappointing sales and profitability forecasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer Snaps Photo Of Mother Duck Swimming -- With 76 Ducklings!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/07/25/mama-duck-76-babies-brent-cizek-new-york-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mama duck in Minnesota has captured hearts across the nation after a Bemidji photographer snapped an image of her leading an astonishing 76 ducklings across a lake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK OF AMERICA Customers Find Safety Deposit Boxes Vanished; No Explanations...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/26/safe-boxes-stolen-drilled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman says her bank let her safety deposit box vanish. And she's not the only one. Susan Nomi says when she went to open her Bank of America safe deposit box of 16 years, the entire box was gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betsy DeVos yacht untied from dock, set adrift...</title>
      <link>http://www.toledoblade.com/local/2018/07/25/DeVos-40-million-yacht-vandalized-at-Huron-dock-npr.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occupy ICE Protesters Leave Heaps Of Trash, Human Waste For City To Clean...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/occupy-ice-pdx-protesters-leave-heaps-of-trash-human-waste-for-city-to-clean-at-taxpayers-expense/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City leaders say they found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU: AMAZON face ID tool mismatched 28 members of Congress to mugshots...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180726120000-51gft</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON.COM-FACIAL RECOGNITION/ (PIX):Amazon's face ID tool mismatched 28 members of Congress to mugshots: ACLU</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Average Person Has Just 15 'Perfect' Days A Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/best-day-ever-survey-15-perfect-days-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What makes a day "perfect?" Of course, the answer can be markedly different from person to person, but a recent survey sought to find out common characteristics of an ideal day for the average person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can She Turn Georgia Blue?</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5349541/stacey-abrams-georgia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I am coming for you, Georgia! Help me get there!'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>http://www.newser.com/story/262480/a-harsh-letter-a-168b-loss-and-a-plan-to-fire-zuckerberg.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did you just lose $16.8 billion?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi war threat: Oil tankers bombed; Kingdom bans exports through Red Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/994441/saudi-arabia-news-iran-houthi-movement-oil-tankers-donald-trump-exports-red-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-BACKED Yemeni rebels aligned have launched an attack on two oil tankers passing through the strategically important Red Sea shipping lane of Bab al-Mandeb – prompting Saudi Arabia to announce that was “temporarily halting” all oil shipments along the route.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson wildfire forces entire California town to evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47e6296ea13043c68fcd0147acddc544/Arson-wildfire-forces-entire-California-town-to-evacuate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IDYLLWILD, Calif. (AP) — A fast-moving wildfire — believed to have been sparked by arson — tore through trees, burned five homes and forced evacuation orders for an en</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech blasts snoozing workers with AC...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180726-thats-cold-japan-tech-blasts-snoozing-workers-with-ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence as migrants storm Morocco-Spain border fence...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-5994709/Violence-migrants-storm-Morocco-Spain-border-fence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 400 migrants from sub-Saharan Africa reached Spain Thursday after storming a double barrier between Morocco and the Spanish territory of Ceuta, with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian general warns Trump: 'War will destroy everything you own'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180726094015-595zf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-USA/TRUMP-SOLEIMANI (URGENT):Iranian general warns Trump:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Small bomb set off outside US Embassy in Beijing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/26/us-embassy-incident-beijing/839835002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos posted on Twitter showed a large amount of smoke and what appeared to be police vehicles surrounding the embassy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO THE HEAVENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/07/26/welcome-to-the-new-space-age#gs.t=jDLaI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the New Space Age</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Outflows Swell as Investors Seek Refuge in Bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/outflows-from-u-s-stocks-swell-as-investors-seek-refuge-in-bonds-1532597401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are fleeing U.S. stocks at a rapid clip as the possibility of a protracted trade dispute between the world’s two largest economies pushes them to seek safety among less risky assets such as U.S. Treasurys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mission to Sample Comet Going 84,000MPH -- and Return...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/07/26/the-mission-to-sample-a-comet-going-84-000-miles-per-hour-and-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mission to Sample a Comet Going 84,000 Miles Per Hour—and Return</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan newspaper closures leave coverage in state's hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-media-coverage/venezuelan-newspaper-closures-leave-coverage-in-states-hands-idUSKBN1KG18G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost three-quarters of Venezuela's newspapers have closed during five years of recession in the once-prosperous OPEC member country, according to the national journalism association, leaving El Nacional as the last independent national daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAREHOLDERS DRAW UP NEW PLANS TO OUST...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/facebook-shareholders-new-proposal-fire-mark-zuckerberg-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BI PRIME: Facebook investor Trillium Asset Management has drawn up a new proposal to oust Mark Zuckerberg as chairman. Trillium wants to appoint an independent chairman, citing Facebook's 'mishandling' of scandals like Cambridge Analytica.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK RECORD HEATWAVE BRINGS OUT THE RATS!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6865890/weather-37c-july-record-rat-sharks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN is set for the hott­est days of the year so far, with a sweltering high of 37C (99F) predicted. Thermometers are expected to register 35C (95F) on Thursday as the longest scorcher since 197…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE THURS:  Once 'punching bag,' Cohen takes swing...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-lashes-out-at-Michael-Cohen-after-release-13103460.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the past decade, Michael Cohen worked as Donald Trump's personal lawyer and fixer. He was an eager supplicant, executing the wishes of his celebrity boss and forever seeking his attaboy affection. He said he would take a bullet for Trump and, even after the president passed him over for a White House job, Cohen still professed his eternal loyalty. But in Trump's world, eternity has limits. By releasing audio of his covertly recorded conversation with Trump about purchasing the rights to a Playboy centerfold's story of an extramarital affair, Cohen made a decisive break from his longtime client.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble Sleeping? High-Tech Mask Resets Body Clock... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trouble-sleeping-high-tech-masks-can-help-1532535248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These eye shades use light therapy to help reset your body clock so you can rest easy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Age of Tattoos: Inked Man As Likely to Fly Private Jet as Ride HARLEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/too-old-for-a-tattoo-not-these-ceos-1532540138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new tattooed man is just as likely to get around by private jet as by Harley-Davidson. How to ink elegantly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTA PORN SHAME AS SECRET SEX HASHTAGS REVEAL SMUTTY VIDEOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6860954/instagram-porn-hashtags-sex-explicit-videos-age-rating/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INSTAGRAM is awash with hardcore porn videos despite being aimed at children as young as 13, The Sun can reveal. The popular image-sharing app has a strict “zero tolerance” policy on se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial intelligence begins diagnosing patients in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegazette.com/subject/news/health/coralville-iowa-university-of-iowa-hospitals-and-clinics-diabetes-and-endocrinology-center-artificial-intelligence-diagnosis-20180725 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORALVILLE - The University of Iowa Hospitals and Clinics has become the first to employ new technology - developed by a company rooted in the university's research engine - that uses artificial intelligence to diagnose an eye disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Starts Paying a Price for Scandals... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/25/technology/facebook-revenue-scandals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social network said that advertising and user growth slowed in the second quarter, and that efforts to improve privacy would stunt profits further. Its stock price tumbled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men Panicking About Sperm Count... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/25/style/sperm-count.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study suggests that sperm counts have been dropping for decades. Is this how the big dystopia begins? Silicon Valley is at hand to help men get their mojo back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT AGAIN? EXCITEMENT BUILDS FOR GDP READING... </title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/get-ready-for-the-gdp-hot-takes-2018-07-25 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the GDP report arrives, so will a round of “yes, but,” and finger pointing and “won’t you ever give Trump at least some credit?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL PREVIEW:  Dallas Cowboys players MUST stand for anthem...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/dallas-cowboys-players-must-stand-for-anthem-jerry-jones-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has yet to finalize a policy for player behavior during the national anthem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rattlesnake on lake had family screaming -- and then it climbed aboard!</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article215474215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screams erupted on a family’s boat as a venomous timber rattlesnake slithered toward them and then briefly climbed aboard. ‘Univited rattlesnake boards our boat on Fontana Lake’ in Western North Carolina, Wayne Robbins titled his Instagram video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE: 'MISSION' OPENING FRANCHISE RECORD?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/tom-cruise-mission-impossible-fallout-worldwide-opening-1202432976/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arguably the last tentpole huzzah of the summer before New Line/Warner Bros.’ Conjuring series title The Nun takes us into the fall on Sept. 7 is Paramount/Skydance’s Mission: Impossibl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOZILLA exec says GOOGLE slowing YOUTUBE on non-Chrome browsers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/mozilla-exec-says-google-slowed-youtube-down-on-non-chrome-browsers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A redesign allegedly made it more dependent on Chrome's architecture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants bash YELP health scores: 'Another way to profit from terrorizing?'</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/dining/ct-food-chicago-restaurants-yelp-health-scores-20180724-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yelp rolled out new health scores on its restaurant review pages, and Chicago restaurants sound off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster of quakes off California sparks 'Big One' fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6865838/california-earthquakes-spark-fears-big-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CLUSTER of earthquakes off the California coast could mean ‘the Big One’ could strike at anytime, devastating the West Coast of the USA, it has emerged. ‘The Big One’ refe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo: NKorea making bomb fuel despite denuclearization pledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-usa/north-korea-making-bomb-fuel-despite-denuclearization-pledge-pompeo-idUSKBN1KF2QT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea is continuing to produce fuel for nuclear bombs in spite of its pledge to denuclearize, U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said on Wednesday, even as he argued that the Trump administration was making progress in talks with Pyongyang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS 'Strong Solidarity' With CNN After WH Bars Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/fox-news-president-declares-strong-solidarity-with-cnn-after-wh-bars-kaitlan-collins-from-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind-controlled robo-arm lets do two things at once...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2175126-this-mind-controlled-robotic-arm-lets-you-do-two-things-at-once/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Need a hand? Eight people have reliably used a mind-controlled robotic third arm to perform two tasks simultaneously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD UNION:   64% Of Female Writers Have Been Sexually Harassed On Job...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/writers-guild-female-writers-sexual-harassment-survey-wga-west-hollywood-1202433690/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A survey of more than 2,000 WGA West members has found that 64% of female writers say they’ve experienced sexual harassment sometime in their careers, and that “a significant amoun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Scrutinize NATIONAL ENQUIRER Dealings...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/national-enquirers-years-long-dealings-with-trump-lawyer-fall-under-federal-scrutiny-1532534115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen and the tabloid publisher traded favors over many years, including helping mediate a lawsuit threat by former “Apprentice” star Omarosa Manigault-Newman and tackling emerging stories potentially unfavorable to the president. Authorities are trying to determine whether the publisher and Mr. Trump’s team violated campaign-finance laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California City Threatens Waiters With Jail For Serving Straws...</title>
      <link>https://www.newswars.com/california-city-threatens-waiters-with-jail-for-serving-straws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Californian waiters are already struggling to make ends meet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC HOST: I'd Like to Cover Climate Change, But It's a Ratings Killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/scott-whitlock/2018/07/25/liberal-chris-hayes-id-cover-climate-change-its-ratings-killer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal MSNBC journalist Chris Hayes admitted reality on Tuesday and tweeted that haranguing people about global warming is a “ratings killer.” This is the same man who once starred in an ad where he biked to work in order to save the planet. Now, he can’t be bothered. After tweeting about the “disaster” that is climate change, he was called out for not doing stories on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Dead baby found in plane toilet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6864430/dead-baby-found-in-plane-toilet-after-underage-mum-gave-birth-on-board-stuffed-its-mouth-with-toilet-paper-and-dumped-it-for-cabin-crew-to-discover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DEAD baby was found abandoned inside the lavatory of an AirAsia India flight that landed in New Delhi on Wednesday, police and the airline said. The mother of the infant, who is believed to be un…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USERS VANISH...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-results/facebook-misses-estimates-on-monthly-active-users-idUSKBN1KF2U5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc's stock fell as much as 24 percent after hours on Wednesday over concerns about the impact of privacy issues on the social media company's business, with executives warning that revenue growth would slow and expenses would rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DEATH SPIRAL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/25/tech-stocks-poised-for-bloodbath-on-thursday-with-facebook-on-track-fo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech-heavy Nasdaq was set for a big down day Thursday after disappointing quarterly results from Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG LOSES $16,800,000,000 IN MINUTES!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/25/zuckerberg-loses-16-8-billion-in-a-snap-as-facebook-plunges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zuckerberg Loses $16.8 Billion in a Snap as Facebook Plunges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You're allowed to say something untrue, as long as you an authentic person'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/facebook-asked-to-justify-infowars-and-fox-news-tca-1202433578/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook faced renewed questions about its handling of noted conspiracy site Infowars, and its decision to place Fox News alongside other news organizations at a time when the social media site has…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECS BITCH OVER CONTENT, CENSORSHIP, BLOCKING...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/25/facebook-fox-news-infowars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook executives promoting their video-on-demand service got into a combative exchange with reporters while at the Television Critics Association's press…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Economy Flailing: Need Bread, Butter... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/we-need-bread-and-butter-iranians-under-pressure-in-flailing-economy-1532548684</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian leaders are pushing to contain a deepening economic crisis that is slashing the buying power of Iranians and pressuring Tehran’s ruling elite even before the bite of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stressed rich people retreat with sensory-deprivation tanks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/luxury-homeowners-retreat-with-sensory-deprivation-tanks-1532528989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wealthy residents are spending tens of thousands of dollars installing pods that let them float free of gravity and the stresses of daily life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect offers cops donuts to let go, faces bribery charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.fredericknewspost.com/news/crime_and_justice/police-man-tried-to-bribe-officers-with-doughnuts/article_9ce22b91-c227-5f6a-986d-b81732baa8a8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fredericknewspost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Frederick man didn’t do himself any favors when city police said he tried to bribe several officers with doughnuts in exchange for letting him go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran looks to ban free lunch at tech giants!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/san-francisco-looks-to-ban-free-lunch-at-tech-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary Silicon Valley perk is keeping local restaurants empty, leading to complaints they can't compete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAL-MART chauffeuring shoppers in self-driving cars...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/07/25/technology/waymo-walmart-groceries/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some customers picking up groceries in Chandler, Arizona, will get a free ride in a self-driving car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti gets judge to bar media from his testimony...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-avenatti-bankruptcy-20180725-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels' lawyer, who appears almost daily on cable news, convinced a U.S. Bankruptcy Court judge in Santa Ana to block reporters from covering his testimony about his law firm's bankruptcy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA finds 'many' non-compliance issues in data handling...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/national-security/398853-nsa-watchdog-finds-many-issues-of-non-compliance-in-agencys-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency's (NSA) inspector general issued a rare report Wednesday condemning the administration for insufficiently protecting data gathered from U.S. citizens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Secures Concessions from EU to Avoid Trade War... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ahead-of-eu-meeting-trump-rails-at-domestic-critics-1532524795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union delegation meeting with President Trump Wednesday agreed to some concessions in an effort to avoid a trade war with the U.S., according to a European official in the room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked man found doing jumping jacks in MCDONALD'S women's bathroom...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/mcdonalds-huffer-popped-684309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 25--A naked man who police found doing jumping jacks in the women’s bathroom of a McDonald’s in Tennessee was arrested Monday on public indecency, trespass, and public intoxication charges. Poli</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attached electric wires to nipples, penis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6859452/german-serial-killer-electrocuted-dead-cell-sex-act/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A GERMAN serial killer who murdered five female hitchhikers accidentally killed himself performing a strange solo sex act in his prison cell over the weekend, reports claim. Egidius Schiffer, dubbe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German serial killer accidentally kills self in jail during sex act...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/25/serial-killer-accidentally-kills-himself-in-jail-during-sex-act/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German serial killer who murdered five female hitchhikers accidentally killed himself while performing a strange solo sex act in his prison cell over the weekend, reports claim. Egidius Schiffer,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt Workers Chant 'Lock Him Up' To President...</title>
      <link>https://ntknetwork.com/government-employees-chant-lock-him-up-referring-to-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ntknetwork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House, citing Mueller, says next Putin meeting delayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/25/white-house-says-trump-wont-meet-putin-until-next-year-740492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will not host Russian President Vladimir Putin in Washington until 2019, White House national security adviser John Bolton said Wednesday, because it is Trump’s preference not to do so until “the Russia witch hunt is over.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB used as brothel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/couple-who-rented-out-home-12978844</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The couple arrived back at their Amsterdam house to find odd stains on the carpet and furniture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Tapper Went 'Bananas' on Staff Over Botched Clips...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnns-jake-tapper-went-ballistic-at-staff-over-botched-clips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE REMOVES ALEX JONES VIDEOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/7/25/17613492/youtube-alex-jones-strike-hate-speech-child-endangerment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video site removed four of Jones’ videos on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researcher under fire for risque photos at turtle, fish conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/25/metoo-risque-photos-fish-turtle-conference/835252002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Dick Vogt was harshly criticized for showing inappropriate photographs of female field researchers in a presentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMV worker slept 3 hours a day on the job for 4 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/article/California-DMV-worker-slept-3-hours-a-day-on-the-13101363.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — A state Department of Motor Vehicles worker slept at least three hours a day on the job for nearly four years, slowing down processing times in an agency known for its long waits, a state audit said Tuesday. According to the state auditor’s report, the DMV worker napped at her desk for an estimated 2,200 hours of work time between February 2014 and December 2017, costing the state more than $40,000. The employee’s name was not released. The employee’s supervisors failed to discipline her, despite noting in her performance evaluations that she routinely slept on the job, the audit said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occupy ICE Keeps Cops Out -- With Border Wall...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/25/portland-occupy-ice-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walls work?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman finds cougar in living room, says telepathy got it out...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/pacific-northwest-news/index.ssf/2018/07/oregon_woman_finds_cougar_in_l.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ashland woman says she used "feline-speaking eye blinking," drumming to calm the cat and encourage it to depart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER 'shadow banning' prominent Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://news.vice.com/en_us/article/43paqq/twitter-is-shadow-banning-prominent-republicans-like-the-rnc-chair-and-trump-jrs-spokesman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several conservative Republican Congressmen no longer appear in the auto-populated drop-down search box on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEASE FIRE OVER:  Exchange of fire near Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/BREAKING-IDF-soldiers-fired-on-near-Gaza-border-563425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coen Brothers surprise entry at Venice film fest...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/coen-brothers-surprise-entry-venice-film-fest-171050729.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Offbeat American filmmakers the Coen Brothers were the surprise entry in the 2018 Venice Film festival line-up, unveiled Wednesday, making their new western a contender for the Golden Lion award. "The Ballad of Buster Scruggs" is competing for the coveted gong alongside 20 other films featuring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese baseball team takes over Texas minor league club...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/567beba8c985424c878d74fd8ce17b16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRAND PRAIRIE, Texas (AP) — The starting lineups are announced in English and Spanish at home games for the independent Texas AirHogs, and then the Chinese national anthem is play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS claims attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/no-evidence-back-claim-deadly-toronto-attack-police-151240115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian authorities said Wednesday they have no evidence to substantiate a claim by the Islamic State group that the gunman who killed two people in a Toronto rampage was an IS soldier. The group's Amaq news agency said the gunman, identified by police as 29-year-old Faisal Hussain, was an IS &amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR DETECTS LAKE ON MARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-lake-liquid-water-discovered-mars-143322689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive underground lake has been detected for the first time on Mars, raising the possibility that more water -- and maybe even life -- exists there, international astronomers said Wednesday. It is the largest body of liquid water ever found on the Red Planet. It was home to plenty of liquid water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man accused of murdering 101-year-old neighbor...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/101-year-old-neighbor-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man accused of killing a 101-year-old neighbor in western New York has pleaded not guilty to murder charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey vows to keep buying Iranian oil: 'We will not obey'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/turkey-vows-to-keep-buying-iranian-oil-we-will-not-obey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkey plans to keep purchasing Iranian oil in defiance of American sanctions on the rogue regime, according to the NATO ally’s top diplomat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet ablaze ...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6859588/deadly-wildfires-and-killer-heatwaves-are-ripping-through-the-planet-from-athens-and-sweden-to-los-angles-and-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE planet is ablaze as it was gripped by a mammoth killer heatwave which has left hundreds dead. Across Europe, North America and Japan, searing heat and devastating wildfires have also left tens …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multibillion Dollar Weather Satellite Malfunctioning...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/07/noaas-next-gen-weather-satellite-still-malfunctioning-and-may-not-be-fixable/149995/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second satellite in NOAA’s $11 billion GOES program continues to experience issues with its most important instrument and officials still aren’t sure what’s wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Koreans eat dog meat to beat summer heat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e4cc8823492487ba94f9fb163126fb2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PYONGYANG, North Korea (AP) — In North Korea, summer is not a good time to be a dog.        With the sizzling heat upon the country, North Korea's biggest brewery is pumpin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Band Of Female Thieves Hit LULULEMON...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/07/24/video-female-lululemon-thieves-hit-a-dozen-stores-across-the-bay-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a dozen Lululemon stores in the Bay Area have been hit in the same way and police say the suspects are still on the loose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men Swipe $30K In Electronics From APPLE Store...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/24/apple-store-robbery-costa-mesa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thieves hit an Apple Store in Costa Mesa, making off with expensive electronics. Stacey Butler reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TAPES COMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/michael-cohen-trump-tapes-lanny-davis-f14f46c7-2856-4dc2-99d8-45c1014c61c8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Michael Cohen has made a turn. This is on the record."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE RAT</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5990807/Trump-unloads-Michael-Cohen-kind-lawyer-tape-client.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Why was the tape so abruptly terminated (cut) while I was presumably saying positive things?' Trump asked on Twitter. 'I hear there are other clients and many reporters that are taped.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Truth on our side'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/398714-lanny-davis-on-trump-cohen-audio-we-have-truth-on-our-side</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen's lawyer Lanny Davis on Tuesday insisted "the truth is on our side" after releasing audio of a conversation between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Film Festival to host NETFLIX movies, unfinished Orson Welles work...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venice-film-festival-host-netflix-movies-unfinished-orson-134019944--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From westerns to the space race and the latest offerings from Oscar-winning directors, this year's Venice Film Festival will present a rich line-up of premieres, including a host of Netflix movies and an unfinished Orson Welles work, the organisers said. Unlike May's Cannes Film Festival, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/underground-lake-found-mars-raising-possibility-life-140133549.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Will Dunham WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Using a radar instrument on an orbiting spacecraft, scientists have spotted what they said on Wednesday appears to be a sizable salt-laden lake under ice on the southern polar plain of Mars, a body of water they called a possible habitat for microbial life. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not seeking pardon...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-tape-lies-truth-cohens-lawyer/story?id=56805521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attorney for President Donald Trump's former lawyer speaks out on tape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-MILE-WIDE RESERVOIR?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-lake-found-mars-water-polar-cap-life-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 12-mile-wide reservoir could solve a Martian mystery—and offer a new target in the hunt for extraterrestrial life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR DETECTS LAKE ON MARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/25/world/mars-subsurface-water-lake-evidence/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lake of liquid water has been detected by radar beneath the southern polar ice cap of Mars, according to a new study by Italian researchers from the Italian Space Agency, published Wednesday in the journal Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish student stops plane deporting Afghan man from leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/25/swedish-student-elin-ersson-stops-plane-deporting-afghan-man-leaving/832071002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elin Ersson has been applauded by many for her courage, but critics have called her selfish for singlehandedly making a decision on the country's deportation stance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
