<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Jussie Smollett Loses at NAACP Image Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jussie-smollett-already-lost-at-the-naacp-image-awards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Empire" star Jussie Smollett was up for an NAACP Image Award for his role on the Fox musical drama, but he ultimately did not take home the prize</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Air Force Does Fly-by Over Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/27206/the-russians-just-did-a-fly-by-of-area-51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's specially equipped Tu-154M Open Skies aircraft is doing a grand tour of America's most sensitive military installations out west.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring surge shocks system...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/spring-brings-surge-of-migrants-stretching-border-facilities-far-beyond-capacity/ar-BBVqhmt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockets from Gaza Strip hit Israel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b907a134c5b246d7bac1f3be0f687e28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Five rockets were fired from the Gaza Strip into Israel early Sunday, the Israeli military announced, following a day of mass protests that saw Israeli troops kill...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet  Cracking...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2019/mar/30/furious-tory-mps-tell-theresa-may-they-will-block-snap-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cabinet ministers join warning on poll as Amber Rudd leads bid to halt shift to the right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve McQueen's Son Sues TOM FORD Over 'McQueen' Cardigan Line...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/steve-mcqueens-son-sues-tom-ford-cardigan-line-1198320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late actor's heir says the fashion brand is trying to capitalize on McQueen's iconic status to sell sweaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump seeks to cut foreign aid for 3 Central American nations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/962e59315df9438eb2a2f846fd0804e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Taking drastic action over illegal immigration, President Donald Trump moved Saturday to cut direct aid to El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras, whose citizens are fleeing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Investigation Claims Saudis Obtained His Private Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeff-bezos-investigation-finds-the-saudis-obtained-his-private-information</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Enquirer’s lawyer tried to get me to say there was no hacking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH RICHARDS:  Mick, we are always there for you!</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/03/30/keith-richards-responds-to-mick-jagger-illness-rolling-stones-tour-postponement-things-need-to-be-taken-care-of-mick-we-are-always-there-for-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keith Richards has responded on Twitter to news of Mick Jagger’s illness and the postponement of the Rolling Stones’ upcoming tour. Richards writes: “A big disappointment for ever…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6868939/Mystery-illness-causes-Mick-Jagger-75-halt-Rolling-Stones-200million-tour.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer was told by doctors he needs urgent medical treatment and shouldn't go on stage. More than a million fans were due to watch the band at 17 venues across the US and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONOPOLIES INCREASINGLY DOMINATE BUSINESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/iowa-country-of-monopolies-7de113b7-2860-4fa2-83ea-32c5b6766c15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are going down the same road as the Russians with the collective farm system."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo set to launch fashion brand from prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.thisisinsider.com/el-chapo-convicted-drug-lord-is-launching-a-fashion-brand-from-prison-2019-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thisisinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clothing bearing the drug lord's signature could soon be available in the US and Mexico after El Chapo signed company documents from his federal cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump intervenes in case of Navy SEAL charged with murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/03/30/trump-intervene-navy-seal-1244374</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s message follows a request by 40 members of Congress to the Navy on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/30/us/border-migrants-el-paso-bridge-spring-surge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migration along the southern border typically increases in the spring, but authorities said the current numbers have reached “unmanageable” levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1 million acres of U.S. cropland ravaged by floods...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/exclusive-more-than-1-million-acres-of-us-cropland-ravaged-by-floods/ar-BBVoRKX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConaughey Hits Bottom...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/03/dumbo-box-office-results-disney-us-jordan-peele-weekend-1202584883/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, SATURDAY AM 2nd Update: Refresh for updates Dumbo doesn’t stink like the elephant pen at the zoo, but his estimated $15.2M Friday and $46.1M isn’t a skyrocket in flight either. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: What is hip hop enough?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D5wKs6kPFNA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following news that Lil Nas X's viral hit "Old Town Road" was removed from the Billboard country charts due to a "mistake" Ebro in the Morning decided to dis...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brunei defends tough new Islamic laws against growing backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brunei-islamiclaws/brunei-defends-tough-new-islamic-laws-against-growing-backlash-idUSKCN1RB0E1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brunei has defended its right to implement Islamic laws that would allow death b...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman held 33 immigrants in home in forced labor scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/03/29/us/33-immigrants-forced-labor-scheme/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was arrested and faces forced labor charges after she was accused of keeping 33 immigrants in her Illinois home, forcing them to work and pay her thousands of dollars, federal court documents state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Projected to Add 1.5 Million Illegal Aliens This Year...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/27/u-s-projected-to-add-1-5m-illegal-aliens-to-population-this-year/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is projected to add about 1.5 million illegal aliens to the American population by the end of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEXICO WARNS:  'Mother of all caravans' pushes north...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/597b194af93c473aa4f041a4462788d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico is bracing for the possible arrival of the "mother of all caravans," even as doubts arise over whether the group of Central American migrants will be all that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Texas rallies, Beto seeks to reclaim 2020 star status...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-rallies-orourke-seeks-reclaim-2020-star-status-134911758.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Democrat Beto O'Rourke, the young-looking Texan who has spent two weeks campaigning for president in early-voting states, holds a hometown kickoff rally Saturday in El Paso, aiming to raise his profile in an increasingly crowded field. The 46-year-old former congressman and onetime punk rocker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton warns Russia on military presence in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190329133831-cw8pj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/USA (URGENT):Trump adviser warns Russia on military presence in Venezuela</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Prepares to Elect First Black Woman as Mayor...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chicago-prepares-to-elect-first-black-woman-as-mayor-11553950800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before voters are set to elect Chicago’s first black woman mayor, the two candidates sparred over how best to tackle the city’s faltering finances, pervasive violence and distrust of local police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh documents keep up pressure on Trudeau over scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-politics/fresh-documents-keep-up-pressure-on-canadas-trudeau-over-scandal-idUSKCN1RA2LA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former cabinet member at the heart of a crisis that could cost Canadian Prime ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/breaking-rolling-stones-cancel-tour-14208092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The legendary rock group have been forced to cancel their upcoming dates in the US and Canada after Mick was advised against performing by doctors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence Erupts at Gaza Border on Anniversary of 'Return' Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.euronews.com/2019/03/30/violence-erupts-again-on-anniversary-of-gaza-s-border-protests-with-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.euronews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions have mounted along the Israel-Gaza border this week ahead of the commemoration of the 'Great March of Return' border protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans aren't getting enough sleep -- and it's killing us...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/436555-americans-arent-getting-enough-sleep-and-its-killing-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who usually slept six or fewer hours increased their risk of death by stroke or heart failure by nearly 10 percent over a 7.8-year period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONES postpone tour as Jagger receives medical treatment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc106647558b4081a1b81a6c720b914c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Rolling Stones are postponing their latest tour so Mick Jagger can receive medical treatment. The band announced Saturday that Jagger was told by doctors "he cannot go on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jews scared to speak out as antisemitism spreads in Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/world/jews-remain-silent-as-antisemitism-spreads-in-orban-s-hungary-s29vsmdrs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The image on the front page of the Hungarian pro-government magazine could easily have been propaganda from Nazi Germany: a portrait of Andras Heisler, president of the Federation of Hungarian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists pinpoint moment 66 million years ago life nearly wiped off Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-fossils-show-asteroid-impact-on-earth-66-million-years-ago-20190330-54n74loaevhljou2uffmof66ci-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;scientists pinpoint moment when dinosaurs were wiped off Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission to find never contacted Amazon tribe to stop 'catastrophic' jungle war...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/mission-find-never-contacted-amazon-14106577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's indigenous affairs agency believes tensions between the Korubo and Matis tribes are about to flare up again with disastrous consequences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothel offers 'digisexual therapy' to cure robot addiction...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/768387/Sex-robot-addiction-cure-digisexual-therapy-Sheris-Ranch-worlds-largest-brothel-Nevada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems tailoring 2020 message to appeal to rural voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d8f0810fa5a349278f7f0a4b21762b0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Several Democratic presidential candidates will make their case to Iowa farmers on Saturday — part of a broader effort to win over rural voters who have drifted to...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
