<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PLAYING GOD:  'Daddy shortlegs' insect created by gene-hacking scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3491138/daddy-shortlegs-experiment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUTANT ‘daddy shortlegs’ have been created in a laboratory experiment. The common household pests are usually known for their long legs but scientists have worked out a way to turn thei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow &amp; MSNBC Beat OAN $10M Defamation Suit -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/rachel-maddow-msnbc-beat-oan-lawsuit-appeal-robert-herring-1234816713/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow is still talking with MSNBC about a new contract, but the primetime host and her current cabler newser home just scored what may be a bonding TKO against One America News Newtork Reaf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL QAEDA MOCKS</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/week-asia/politics/article/3140706/al-qaeda-mocks-us-withdrawal-afghanistan-taliban-continues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the US troop withdrawal, the Taliban says it will not allow al-Qaeda to operate in the country – but analysts say this is not the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Governor Abbott Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/17/texas-governor-greg-abbott-tests-positiver-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Governor Greg Abbott has tested positive for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Taliban using to 'fish for legitimacy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/tech/services-and-software/how-the-taliban-is-using-twitter-to-fish-for-legitimacy-as-it-reclaims-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounts suspected to belong to Taliban representatives reach nearly 900,000 followers on the social platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER testing way to report 'misleading tweets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/twitter-is-testing-a-way-to-report-misleading-tweets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Misinformation is still a big problem on social networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  FBI investigating Deshaun Watson...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/08/17/tony-buzbee-says-fbi-has-contacted-him-regarding-deshaun-watson-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months ago, attorney Tony Buzbee tried to spark a federal investigation of Texans quarterback Deshaun Watson. It apparently worked. “Deshaun Watson reaches out to a woman in Atlanta, Georgia, while he’s in Houston,” Buzbee said at a press conference in early April. “Hear what I’m saying. He reaches out to a woman via direct message [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired vax expert denies sending dog muzzle to herself...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/17/tennessee-vaccine-expert-fired-dog-muzzle-michelle-fiscus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Michelle Fiscus says muzzle was sent anonymously, perhaps as a warning, before she was fired over efforts to vaccinate teenagers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing to harvest sun's energy in space -- beam it to Earth for power...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3145237/china-aims-use-space-based-solar-energy-station-harvest-suns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civilian and military researchers will look at applications for the technology amid concerns about radiation and the potential for beams misfired from space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg, husband become parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/celebrities/2021/08/17/pete-buttigieg-chasten-buttigieg-to-become-parents/8167248002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg and husband Chasten are going to be dads. "We’re overjoyed to share that we’ve become parents!" the transportation secretary said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration embroiled in internal blame-shifting amid chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/17/politics/biden-afghanistan-blame-shifting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bus driver shortage causes districts to pay parents to drive their own children...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/568203-school-bus-driver-shortage-causes-districts-to-pay-parents-to-drive-their-own</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;School bus driver shortages are causing schools to take extreme measures, including paying parents stipends to drive their kids to campus for the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces threat in volatile borderlands after Taliban takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-faces-threat-in-volatile-borderlands-after-afghanistan-falls-to-the-taliban/ar-AANpifd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has long feared the militant group’s radicalization effects on Muslims in the vast Xinjiang region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney's bizarre naked INSTAGRAM posts as family feud rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3490387/inside-britney-spears-wildest-most-naked-instagram-posts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears has rocked wild and revealing Instagram looks over the past several months during her battle to end her decades-long conservatorship. The pop sensation has denied having a boob job a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says U.S. will not be harmed from Afghan soil...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/taliban-announces-amnesty-urges-women-join-government-n1276945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We don’t have any grudges," spokesman Zabihullah Mujahid said in a news conference in Kabul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHOCK AND AWE' TALIBAN STYLE</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/568108-shock-and-awe-taliban-style</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The staggering speed and manner of the takeover will remain a permanent stain on the administration, leaving Afghans to an uncertain and probably dire fate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Escalates Fight With NASA...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/08/blue-origin-spacex-fight-nasa-moon-lander-contract-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bezos said in 2019 that only losers would sue the federal government because they didn’t win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Conversation Key To Healthy Mind...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/someone-to-talk-to-brain-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conversely, those in their 40s and 50s with no one to talk to displayed a cognitive age at least four years older than their peers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow Released By JAGUARS After Embarrassing Preseason Game Gaffe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tim-tebow-released-by-jaguars-ending-tight-end-experiment-im-grateful-for-the-chance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow released by Jaguars, issues formal statement following move: 'I'm grateful for the chance'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to honor women's rights but within Islamic law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-taliban-kabul-1d4b052ccef113adc8dc94f965ff23c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban vowed Tuesday to respect women's rights, forgive those who resisted them and ensure a secure Afghanistan as part of a publicity blitz aimed at convincing world powers and a fearful population that they have changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Prince Andrew 'person of interest' in Epstein probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/prince-andrew-a-person-interest-epstein-probe-source-2021-08-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. prosecutors probing the activities of British socialite Ghislaine Maxwell and others linked to U.S. financier Jeffrey Epstein consider Prince Andrew a person of interest in the investigation, a source familiar with the U.S inquiry said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variant could push Israel back into lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/coronavirus-in-israel-new-travel-restrictions-cap-on-weddings-676840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One million Israelis receive booster, as Pfizer submits first data to the FDA • School year start may be postponed if morbidity doesn’t drop, Health Ministry D-G says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travelers Once Again Canceling Long-Awaited Trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-delta-variant-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Delta variant fuels another spike in COVID-19 numbers, people longing to see friends and loved ones are struggling with what to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France battles blaze near Saint-Tropez...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817112313-bwu9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-WILDFIRES/FRANCE (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Campsites evacuated as France battles wildfire near Saint-Tropez</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much money person needs to earn to get by in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/17/income-a-single-person-needs-to-get-by-in-every-us-state.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT's Living Wage Calculator estimates how much a single person needs to earn in order to stay above the poverty line without outside assistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If Could Become Invisible to Mosquitoes?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/17/what-if-you-could-become-invisible-to-mosquitoes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you could have just one superpower, flight or invisibility, which would you choose? And would your answer change if</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American' trophy hunter sparks fury after butchering beloved lion at Zimbawee park...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3488040/american-shooting-mopane-lion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FOREIGN trophy hunter has sparked outrage after shooting a beloved lion dead with a bow and arrow – just yards from where Cecil was killed in 2015. The hunter – thought to be American…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat Helps Rescuers Find 83-Year-Old Owner Who Fell Down Ravine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cats-meowing-helps-rescuers-find-83-year-old-owner-after-she-falls-down-a-ravine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman fell 70 feet, and her persistent cat stayed above the ravine until help arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Violent Gang Of Teens 'Attacking People At All Hours' Amid Rash Of Robberies...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/08/16/downtown-loop-south-loop-chicago-robberies-teens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Police on Monday night were warning anyone walking downtown or in the South Loop to stay alert after a series of attacks and robberies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surreal Footage Shows Militants Driving Bumper Cars, Lifting Weights...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5gng4/taliban-bumper-cars-afghanistan-kabul</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one clip, a group of men are trying out exercise equipment as one person holds a rocket launcher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders requiring fans to be vaccinated in first for NFL team...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/568132-raiders-requiring-fans-to-be-vaccinated-in-first-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Las Vegas Raiders this week announced that all fans attending home games will be required to provide proof of their vaccinations against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants swap AK-47s for made-in-America rifles...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817080253-r1u0o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ARMS:As Taliban takes over, some swap iconic AK-47s for made-in-America rifles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Percentage of Americans who have tried marijuana new high...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/353645/nearly-half-adults-tried-marijuana.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of Americans who have tried marijuana has increased to a new high of 49%, as younger generations have been more likely than older generations to have tried it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human remains in tomb are best-preserved ever found in Pompeii...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/17/human-remains-in-tomb-are-best-preserved-ever-found-in-pompeii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former slave who rose through the social ranks was interred at necropolis of Porta Sarno before AD79</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We aren't all dumb hillbillies': How virus caused rift in country music...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/aug/16/we-arent-all-dumb-hillbillies-covid-rift-country-music</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country stars such as Jason Isbell have received backlash for insisting on safety at their concerts, exposing an age-old political divide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runners' High: More Incorporating Marijuana Into Workouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/marijuana-while-exercising/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey reveals more than two in five exercise enthusiasts who use marijuana during their workout have turned to even more products during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese State Media Says USA Will 'Abandon' Taiwan, Too...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/international/patrick-goodenough/chinese-state-media-outlet-says-us-will-abandon-taiwan-too</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese state mouthpiece reacted to the fall of Kabul to the Taliban Monday by saying the crisis has dealt a severe blow to U.S. “hegemony,” and suggesting allies like Taiwan should be careful about placing their trust in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge spending costing Americans $765 more month...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/17/post-covid-revenge-spending-is-costing-americans-765-more-a-month.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between dining out and travel, Americans are spending an average of $765 more a month compared to last year, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72 hours at Camp David: Inside Biden's lagging response to fall of Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/72-hours-at-Camp-David-Inside-Biden-s-lagging-16391851.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Marine One lifted off Friday at 1:36 p.m. for Camp David bearing a leader...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man caught in landing gear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9901013/Horrific-video-Afghan-caught-landing-gear-c-17-clambering-plane-emerges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage which appears to have been taken from a C-17 military plane leaving Kabul shows a man's legs protruding from the wheel arch and failing against the side of the plane as it cuts through the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghans scramble to delete digital history, evade biometrics...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817111442-4d73x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are fears that government offices and aid agencies may fail to secure databases, leaving people vulnerable to attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As murders surge, Dems find new message: Fund the police...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817110011-4y0w0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-POLICE/DEMOCRATS (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-As murders surge, Democrats find a new message: Fund the police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Star mothers' hearts ache after takeover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817100004-snltv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/GOLDSTAR (PIX, TV):Gold Star mothers' hearts ache after Taliban takeover of Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSE: China holds assault drills near Taiwan after 'provocations'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210817050008-3oull</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-TAIWAN/SECURITY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China holds assault drills near Taiwan after 'provocations'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this beginning of end of American gas station?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/aug/17/end-american-gas-station-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A movement in California seeks a moratorium on new pumps – and a transformation of the US transportation system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Giant Purple Nipple Digital Nose of Future?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-08-17/replicating-our-sense-of-smell-is-one-of-the-hardest-problems-in-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new generation of companies is homing in on one of the hardest problems in tech: replicating our sense of smell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Newsom Keep Job? Recall Effort Shows Dead Heat...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/17/can-gov-newsom-keep-his-job-a-recall-effort-in-california-shows-a-dead-heat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden sent an urgent message last week to the most populous state in the nation: Keep Gov. Gavin Newsom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces even greater test in preventing extremist resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/after-taliban-triumph-biden-faces-even-greater-test-in-preventing-extremist-resurgence-in-afghanistan/ar-AANosZZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the Taliban in power and no neighboring countries willing to permit U.S. bases, the administration will be forced to rethink its strategy for monitoring and targeting extremists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants announce 'amnesty,' urge women to join govt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-joe-biden-middle-east-kabul-taliban-1d4b052ccef113adc8dc94f965ff23c7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban declared an “amnesty” across Afghanistan and urged women to join their government Tuesday, seeking to convince a wary population that they have changed a day after deadly chaos gripped the main airport as desperate crowds tried to flee the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel requests international aid amid masive wildfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jerusalem-area-blaze-continues-for-second-day-residents-evacuated-676852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency services have evacuated thousands of residents from a number of towns as the fires continue to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Trump 'peace' plan released 5,000 Taliban from prison...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5794643/trumps-disgraceful-peace-deal-taliban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Afghanistan peace plan will strengthen the Taliban and make America less safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan sued for allegedly sexually abusing 12-year-old girl in '65...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/08/16/bob-dylan-sued-for-allegedly-sexually-abusing-12-year-old-in-1965/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dylan allegedly used his star status to groom, gain the trust of and control the victim “as part of his plan to sexually molest and abuse” her, according to the Manhattan Supreme Co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REALLY?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/08/16/bob-dylan-hit-with-bogus-lawsuit-claiming-molestation-in-nyc-april-may-1965-not-possible-he-wasnt-there</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On April 26, 1965 Bob Dylan arrived in London. He didn’t return to the United States until June 2nd. In April. he was mostly on the West Coast. All of this is recorded in calendars tracking D…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges dropped for man who crashed autopilot TESLA into cop car while watching movie...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/car-crash/tesla-crash-pass-659230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla owner who was watching a movie when his car, traveling in autopilot mode, struck a North Carolina police cruiser has walked away from the crash legally unscathed, records show. Prosecutors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks double from pandemic bottom -- fastest rally since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/16/sp-500-doubles-from-its-pandemic-bottom-marking-the-fastest-bull-market-rally-since-wwii.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broad equity benchmark has rallied 100% on a closing basis from its Covid trough of 2,237.40 on March 23.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
