<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Vaccine Sommeliers' Go to End of Line in Brazil Town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-sommeliers-go-to-the-end-of-the-line-in-one-brazilian-town/ar-AALFv61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Brazilian town is taking action against people who are pick and choosing which Covid-19 vaccine they want to take, a move that’s delaying a mass immunization campaign in one of the hardest-hit countries in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federally Protected Birds Terrorizing Passersby, Leaving Some Bloodied In TX...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/hit-head-pair-birds-harassing-people-southlake-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of seemingly angry birds have people ducking, dodging and generally avoiding a section of sidewalk in Southlake in order to stay away from the sudden aerial attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock injuries of woman 'raped &amp; punched in genitals' by DODGERS star...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3197915/trevor-bauer-accuser-injuries-claims-raped-punched/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TREVOR Bauer’s accuser says the baseball star raped and repeatedly punched her in the genitals, according to shocking legal documents. In disturbing images, the woman, identified by her lawye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chef dies after falling into boiling vat of soup...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/01/chef-dies-after-falling-into-boiling-vat-of-soup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iraqi chef tragically died last week after falling into a vat of soup, which left him severely scalded across large swathes of his body. The horrific accident had occurred June 15 while Issa Ism…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Rogan Too Big to Cancel...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/01/joe-rogan-is-too-big-to-cancel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other comics called him “Little Ball of Anger” — semi-affectionately, never to his face — a man flammable by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein, Ghislaine gain confidence they'll be freed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3198376/bill-cosby-me-too-harvey-weinstein-ghislaine-maxwell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILL Cosby’s release is a “huge blow” to the #MeToo movement, experts claim, as Harvey Weinstein and Ghislaine Maxwell’s lawyers say their cases should also be overturned.  The disgraced TV st…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Companies Revolt Against AMAZON, Shut Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7ez5x/amazon-delivery-companies-revolt-against-amazon-shut-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent shutdown of two Amazon delivery companies in Portland appears to be the first public example in the United States of such companies using their leverage to protest against Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER revamps misinformation labels...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-election-2020-misinformation-technology-37cee761758f1072f91e1a362f769f5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last May, as Twitter was testing warning labels for false and misleading tweets, it tried out the word “disputed" with a small focus group. It didn't go over well. “People were like, well, who’s disputing it?" said Anita Butler, a San Francisco-based design director at Twitter who has been working on the labels since December 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK untouchable? It's complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/facebook-untouchable-complicated-rcna1323</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook won a major battle against government regulators this week, but the war isn't over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The social media giant's &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA debt to hit $3 trillion THIS YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/us-deficit-to-hit-243-trillion-in-2021-then-fade-as-stimulus-relief-expires-cbo-says/ar-AALFGpo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The deficit is projected to remain historically high this year but then quickly shrink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Covid cases up 10% this week...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-covid-cases-10-percent-hypertransmissible-delta-variant-spreads-n1272895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lagging vaccination rates coupled with the rise of the delta variant could account for the uptick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>130 nations agree to global tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/01/nations-agree-to-support-us-proposal-for-global-minimum-tax-on-corporations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of 130 nations has agreed to a global minimum tax on corporations, part of a broader effort to overhaul international tax rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sick as Dog? Pets Often Catch From Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-07-01/sick-as-a-dog-pets-often-catch-covid-from-humans-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin DiAngelo Very Disappointed in White People Making Her Rich...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/01/robin-diangelo-is-very-disappointed-in-the-white-people-making-her-rich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nice Racism—and the "anti-racism" consulting business—rakes in the bucks while losing hearts and minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: French fries GOOD for blood pressure?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/potatoes-fries-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study authors explain that increasing dietary potassium from foods like baked and boiled potatoes helps to reduce sodium retention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fukushima: Radioactive boars create mutant hybrid species decade after disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/fukushima-radioactive-boars-create-mutant-24439268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade after the Fukushima disaster, wild boars have been mating with domestic pigs in the nuclear wasteland and creating a new mutant species, DNA researchers have determined</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach residents debate leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/haunted-tragedy-safety-fears-surfside-212144655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chiara Mauriziano rolled a suitcase into Champlain Towers East in Surfside, Florida on Wednesday morning, returning home nearly a week after a condo tower a few hundred feet away collapsed, killing at least 16 and leaving scores missing. Mauriziano, like many of her neighbors in Champlain Towers East and other nearby buildings, awoke to a nightmare last Thursday. Around 1:30 am, Champlain Towers South, which sits on the same strip of beachfront as the building in which Mauriziano's family has owned a condo for two decades, partially collapsed into a smoldering mound of twisted metal and fragmented concrete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby release infuriates survivors; Lawyers hail win for Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/bill-cosbys-prison-release-provokes-202921475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;- "What happened to Cosby should never happen to any American in any social strata...the Constitution won today," former prosecutor Bruce Castor said in an interview. Castor made a deal with Cosby's attorneys in 2005 not to bring criminal charges and, as a result, he was unable to avoid testifying in a civil lawsuit brought against him by his accuser Andrea Constand. - “Today’s majority decision regarding Bill Cosby is not only disappointing but of concern in that it may discourage those who seek justice for sexual assault in the criminal justice system from reporting or participating in the prosecution of the assailant or may force a victim to choose between filing either a criminal or civil action,” Andrea Constand said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infection Changes Structure Of Blood Cells, May Explain 'Long-Hauler' Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-19-changes-blood-cells/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests reveal the size and deformability of red blood cells differs greatly between those contracting COVID and those who have not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  MCCAIN QUITS 'VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/01/meghan-mccain-says-leaving-to-live-in-l-a-but-the-view-had-no-emmys-noms-this-year-for-the-first-time-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan McCain says she’s leaving “The View” because she likes living in Washington, DC. “When I said goodbye to all of you in the studio, I found out I was pregnant,” McCain said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorka claims NSA spied on him and Bannon!</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2021/07/01/trumpers-go-spy-crazy-now-seb-gorka-claims-nsa-spied-on-him-and-steve-bannon-in-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump aide, echoing Tucker Carlson, claims NSA surveilled him, Steve Bannon and other White House insiders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC hotel industry 'depression,' room revenue down 60%...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/nyc-hotel-industry-in-a-depression-room-revenue-down-60-report-says/3134878/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hotel industry is in a recession or worse in 21 of the top 25 U.S. markets, and New York City is one of the worst off of all, according to a new report released Thursday by a lodging trade group. The American Hotel &amp; Lodging Association said the city has lost about a third of its hotel rooms since…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: French fries GOOD for blood pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/eating-french-fries-could-be-good-for-blood-pressure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you want to lower your blood pressure? How does a plate of French fries sound?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shows Massive Explosion After LAPD Botches Detonation Of Illegal Fireworks; 10 Cops Injured...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/01/it-felt-like-a-really-hard-earthquake-9-people-injured-in-botched-illegal-firework-detonation-by-police/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 16 people, including 10 law enforcement officers, were injured and several cars and structures were damaged Wednesday evening when police attempted to safely detonate illegal fireworks that were seized in South Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA County Orders Inspection Of 3-Building Condo Complex In Marina Del Rey!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/exclusive-county-orders-inspection-of-marina-city-club-towers-in-marina-del-rey-after-tragic-florida-condo-collapse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County officials have ordered an inspection of the Marina City Club Towers, a condominium complex with three buildings in Marina Del Rey, after the tragic Champlain Tower collapse in Florida last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWBIZ:  MCCAIN QUITS 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3195499/meghan-mccain-quits-the-view-on-air/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN McCain quit The View live on-air after saying she’s “done” with her co-star clashes and joked they have “four weeks of fighting left.” The host will reportedly …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wally Funk was supposed to go to space 60 years ago. Now she's going with Bezos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/wally-funk-was-supposed-to-go-space-60-years-ago-now-she-s-going-with-jeff-bezos/ar-AALF7FT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At 82, the Mercury 13 pioneer is poised to become the oldest person to reach space when the first crewed Blue Origin rocket takes flight this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Announces Liz Cheney to Sit on 1/6 Committee, Despite Threats of Revenge From McCarthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/just-in-pelosi-announces-liz-cheney-to-sit-on-1-6-committee-despite-threats-of-revenge-from-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) announced Thursday that Rep. Liz Cheney (R-WI) will serve on the January 6 select committee, despite threats from House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-CA)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastated condo community looks to Biden visit for comfort...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-fl-state-wire-surfside-building-collapse-government-and-politics-cc101831be50a82fb9968bbe5c5df8c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — President Joe Biden is set to offer comfort and support Thursday to the families of the dead and missing after last week's collapse of a high-rise condo building along the Florida coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as Bitcoin 'billionaire' 'drowns in sea'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3195065/bitcoin-billionaire-mircea-popescu-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MYSTERY surrounds the fate of Bitcoin billionaire Mircea Popescu amid reports he drowned off the coast of Costa Rica. The widely reported death of the controversial investor has now sparked specula…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel scrambles to curb jump in infections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-health-02cb24a60d6aa5d3fe0ebf713219e37f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Israel, a world leader in coronavirus vaccinations, reported its highest daily infection rate in three months as it scrambles to contain the spread of the new delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies request to remove Britney Spears father from conservatorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/jul/01/britney-spears-judge-denies-request-to-remove-father-jamie-from-conservatorship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision comes a week after Spears delivered dramatic testimony calling the conservatorship ‘abusive’ but addresses a petition from November</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Anti-MAGA Trolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2021/07/meet-anti-maga-trolls/619332/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inside the Reddit communities that can’t leave the right-wing internet alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman passes out in pain after receiving 100 lashes for having pre-martial sex under Sharia law...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9741529/Moment-woman-passes-pain-receiving-100-lashes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman and her male lover each received 100 lashes for having premarital sex in the city of Lhokseumawe on Monday. The city is in the only region with the autonomy to enforce sharia law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive Israeli army unit dispatched to find victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9738929/Israeli-commander-describes-harrowing-Florida-condo-rescue-operation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The maps are intended to show where some of the many unaccounted people in the disaster might be in an effort to streamline the search-and-rescue process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippine volcano belches dark plume, villagers evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/philippines-environment-and-nature-0360df2a2d4d37f10dc9e255d88cb507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — A small volcano near the Philippine capital belched a dark plume of steam and ash into the sky in a brief explosion Thursday, prompting officials to start evacuating thousands of villagers from high-risk areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass evacuation underway as Philippines raises danger level for volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/mass-evacuation-underway-philippines-raises-danger-level-taal-volcano-n1272881</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite standing at only 1,020-feet, Taal can be deadly and an eruption in 1911 killed more than 1,300 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katzenberg emerges as figure in LA homelessness debate...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hollywood-mogul-jeffrey-katzenberg-wants-031238251.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Famed Hollywood executive Jeffery Katzenberg has discussed the homeless crisis in L.A. with several members of the City Council, as well as aides to Mayor Eric Garcetti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 Wounded After Seized Explosives Blow Up in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/least-9-injured-blast-after-los-angeles-police-seized-illegal-n1272868</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three civilians had moderate injuries, and the rest of those hurt, which included nine LAPD officers, had minor injuries, the fire department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcism saw woman 'levitate' with so much force she nearly smashed ceiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/terrifying-exorcism-saw-woman-levitate-24422535</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julia started rasping in an unearthly voice and speaking in Latin and Spanish before she rose above the ground and supposedly started to levitate during a terrifying exorcism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia races Tom Cruise, Musk for first movie in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210701-russia-races-tom-cruise-and-musk-for-first-movie-in-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia races Tom Cruise and Musk for first movie in space</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg 'WEST SIDE STORY' going to get him canceled?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/30/steven-spielbergs-west-side-story-adaptation-is-going-to-get-him-canceled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than four decades, screen mavens have been eagerly awaiting the time when Steven Spielberg would bite the bullet and make a full-blown movie musical. Now he’s done it. It comes out at Chri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden stunned by rare shooting of police officer as gang violence worries grow...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210701100908-lobtq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SWEDEN-POLICE/SHOOTING (PIX):Sweden stunned by rare shooting of police officer as gang violence worries grow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP congressman flouts mask rules on flight to Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tx-state-wire-texas-airlines-business-health-15fbd5c0b5247fe96cc9ae3635b36ebe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A Texas congressman who has been an outspoken critic of COVID-19 mask mandates went without a mask for at least a portion of a commercial airline flight Tuesday evening, an apparent violation of federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy ditches futuristic railgun, eyes hypersonic missiles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-a67d3200fad72488ebb37ce1b46bce5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATH, Maine (AP) — The U.S. Navy pulled the plug, for now, on a futuristic weapon that fires projectiles at up to seven times the speed of sound using electricity. The Navy spent more than a decade developing the electromagnetic railgun and once considered putting them on the stealthy new Zumwalt-class destroyers built at Maine's Bath Iron Works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are so many whales dying on CA beaches?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90650909/why-are-so-many-whales-dying-on-california-beaches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s an epidemic of whales washing up on the West Coast. Scientists are piecing together exactly why to try to find a solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAYS CHINA WILL BE DOMINANT WORLD POWER...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/xi-jinping-says-china-become-dominant-world-power-within-30-years-1605848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Only socialism could save China. Only socialism with Chinese characteristics can develop China," President Xi Jinping declared amid celebrations in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobs report poised to boost or hinder Biden's agenda...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/561043-jobs-report-poised-to-boost-or-hinder-bidens-agenda</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is looking for fireworks in the June jobs report due out Friday as the White House makes a renewed push for its economic agenda heading into the long Fourth of July weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Wide Web source code NFT sells for $5.4 million...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-wide-source-code-nft-230950540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Berners-Lee's source code for the World Wide Web sold Wednesday for $5.4 million in the form of non-fungible token (NFT).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Men hit harder...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/delta-variant-gains-ground-u-175056234.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The following is a roundup of some of the latest scientific studies on the novel coronavirus and efforts to find treatments and vaccines for COVID-19, the illness caused by the virus. The highly transmissible Delta variant of SARS-CoV-2, first identified in India, has become the most prevalent variant among new COVID-19 cases in the United States, according to California-based genomics company Helix. The company's computer models indicate that Delta now accounts for around 40% of new U.S. cases, Dr. William Lee, vice president of science at Helix, said in a statement provided to Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reaction to death deeply divided...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/reaction-rumsfelds-death-deeply-divided-211811884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) -Donald Rumsfeld, the former U.S. defense secretary who was the main architect of the Iraq war, died at age 88, his family said Wednesday. For the next five years, he was in steady service as a wartime secretary of defense – a duty he carried out with strength, skill, and honor. A period that brought unprecedented challenges to our country and to our military also brought out the best qualities in Secretary Rumsfeld.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Trump Debuts As Lowest-Ranked Living President...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/donald-trump-lowest-ranked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just like in 2000, 2009, and 2017, Abraham Lincoln ranks as the greatest president in terms of leadership qualities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, Japan hold war games amid escalating tensions between China and Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.baysidenews.net/us-japan-hold-war-games-amid-escalating-tensions-between-china-and-taiwan/'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baysidenews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's covid death toll could be 60% higher than official count...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-registers-351-376-excess-182805604.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (Reuters) -COVID-19-related deaths in Mexico likely exceed the confirmed toll by about 60%, health ministry data released on Wednesday showed. Authorities have previously said the fatalities likely far exceed the official count, and the latest figure is in line with data published in March. According to the latest data, Mexico registered 351,376 excess deaths associated with COVID-19 from the start of the pandemic through the 20th week of this year, which would be May 23.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On what would be her 60th birthday, Princess Diana statue unveiled by feuding sons...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/her-60th-birthday-princess-diana-231849823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Princes William and Harry will put their differences aside on Thursday to unveil a statue to their late mother Princess Diana on what would have been her 60th birthday. The statue in honour of Diana, who was killed in a Paris car crash in 1997, will be revealed in the Sunken Garden of Kensington Palace in central London, her former home. "I think it's going be very awkward," royal commentator Penny Junor told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's largest psychedelic therapy trial underway...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/compass-pathways-completes-target-administration-192143789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compass Pathways (Nasdaq: CMPS), a biotech company in the psychedelics space, announced it has completed a key milestone on its path to obtaining FDA approval for psilocybin in the treatment of depression. The company reported that it had completed psilocybin administration to all 216 patients that were targeted for Compass’ phase IIb clinical trial for treatment-resistant depression. The trial, which is using a proprietary version of isolated psilocybin known as COMP360, is the world’s largest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine law restricts facial recognition technology statewide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maine-technology-government-and-politics-cbf6207f15d13b8e647615e251157774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUSTA, Maine (AP) — A bill touted as the country's strictest statewide regulation on the use of facial recognition technology has become law in Maine. While several states regulate facial recognition as a surveillance tool, the Maine law represents a broad prohibition of the technology at the state, county and municipal government levels, with limited exceptions for law enforcement purposes, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/refresh/AL052021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/212906_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Henry Sues FOXNEWS CEO Suzanne Scott, Alleging Cover-Up of Extramarital Affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ed-henry-sues-fox-news-ceo-suzanne-scott-alleging-she-covered-up-affair-between-network-president-and-employee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News anchor Ed Henry is filing suit against Fox News CEO Suzanne Scott, accusing her of "defam[ing] him as a sex criminal."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Mayoral Race: Embattled Board Of Elections Releases New Numbers Showing Same Razor-Thin Margins...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/nyc-mayoral-race-democratic-primary-board-of-elections-ranked-choice-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Adams wants a judge to oversee the vote count and preserve the integrity of the ballots, while the BOE is trying to save face after a mistake that one political pundit called a "train wreck."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas has biggest one-day virus case spike in 4 months...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ar-state-wire-arkansas-coronavirus-pandemic-health-4692603de02d4683ad2291588bd27e95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas reported its biggest one-day spike in coronavirus cases in four months Wednesday, an increase the state's governor said was being fueled by the delta variant of the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not healthy environment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/30/kamala-harris-office-dissent-497290</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is dysfunction inside the VP’s office, aides and administration officials say. And it’s emanating from the top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapidly developing tropical system taking shape over Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/potential-tropical-cyclone-5-takes-shape-over-atlantic/971809</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AccuWeather forecasters are monitoring two different features in the Atlantic basin, and one may soon become the fifth named storm of the season.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
