<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>With most adults now vaccinated, Israelis are busting loose...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/with-most-adults-now-vaccinated-israelis-are-busting-loose/ar-BB1fSzTN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People are having a ball. People at the beaches … it’s like, wow!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA weighs ban on menthol cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-weighs-ban-on-menthol-cigarettes-which-disproportionately-addict-e2-80-94-and-kill-e2-80-94-black-americans/ar-BB1fQIa3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Menthol cigarettes are more addictive and 85 percent of Black smokers smoke menthol. The FDA will decide later this month whether to ban them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs new law that makes sesame major food allergen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-signs-new-law-that-makes-sesame-the-ninth-major-food-allergen/ar-BB1fZrc6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA mandate expires soon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-tsas-mask-mandate-expires-soon-airline-industry-leaders-and-politicians-are-calling-for-an-extension/ar-BB1fZoBq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Transportation Security Administration announced in January that it would require people to wear a mask at airports and on planes, trains and other forms of public transportation, the announcement included a sunset date: May 11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNT OR SERIOUS?  Jenner officially running for CA gov...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/caitlyn-jenner-california-governor-run-710153ef-7a89-460d-b9ec-9efed2a9399f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will officially announce her bid later today, her campaign tells Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian hospitals plead for oxygen, country sets virus record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-hospitals-oxygen-tanks-coronavirus-surge-eeed59f1a8574e34353c046ca80419b1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — India put oxygen tankers on special express trains as major hospitals in New Delhi begged on social media on Friday for more supplies to save COVID-19 patients who are struggling to breathe. More than a dozen people died when an oxygen-fed fire ripped through a coronavirus ward in a populous western state. India’s underfunded health system is tattering as the world’s worst coronavirus surge wears out the nation, which set a global record in daily infections for a second straight day with 332,730. India has confirmed 16 million cases so far, second only to the United States in a country of nearly 1.4 billion people. India has recorded 2,263 deaths in the past 24 hours for a total of 186,920.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ activists shun...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/23/lgbtq-activists-shun-caitlyn-jenner-over-trump-sup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though Caitlyn Jenner is one of the most famous transgender people in America, the announcement of her candidacy for California governor was greeted hostilely by one of the state’s largest LGBTQ-rights groups and by many trans activists around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER LIVES!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/uncategorized/2763088/golf-tiger-woods-leg-brace-dog/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIGER WOODS has revealed he is on the mend as he posted a picture in a leg brace while stood next to his dog. The golf legend sustained serious injuries in a horror car accident in February with fe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Albuquerque refers $211K Trump campaign bill to collection agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/city-of-albuquerque-refers-211k-trump-reelection-campaign-bill-to-collection-agency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Albuquerque, New Mexico, has sent an unpaid bill for former President Donald Trump’s reelection campaign to a debt collection agency, officials said. The bill stems from an event in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Styles to perform 'realistic' gay sex scenes in new film...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/23/harry-styles-gay-sex-scenes-to-look-as-real-as-possible/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harry Styles’ sex scenes with another man in the upcoming Amazon Studios film “The Policeman” will “look as real as possible,” an insider said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Pounces...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/newsom-raise-money-tying-caitlyn-jenner-to-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom’s campaign team wasted no time coming after Caitlyn Jenner as she entered the recall race to take his seat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Climate' Kerry Scoots After White House Meet...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/ClimateEnvoy/status/1385704140211429376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Faces Barrage of Criticism by Ex-Aide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-faces-barrage-of-criticism-by-ex-aide-cummings/ar-BB1fYPTm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson, facing an onslaught of criticism from the man he until recently relied on as his most powerful adviser, denied he’d blocked an inquiry into leaks of sensitive information from within his government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz probe includes scrutiny of potential public corruption tied to medical marijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/23/politics/gaetz-probe-public-corruption-medical-marijuana/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities are looking into whether a 2018 trip to the Bahamas involving Republican Congressman Matt Gaetz and several young women was part of an orchestrated effort to illegally influence Gaetz in the area of medical marijuana, people briefed on the matter told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US diplomatic missions to fly LGBTQ Pride flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/23/blinken-authorizes-us-diplomatic-missions-to-fly-pride-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Tony Blinken has authorized US diplomatic missions to fly the LGBTQ pride flag on the same pole as the American flag at embassies and consulates, a department official confirmed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer complains about jail treatment: 'Epstein effect'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-not-guilty-new-sex-trafficking-charges-203305963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 59-year-old British socialite has been held without bail in Brooklyn’s Metropolitan Detention Center since her arrest last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SULLIVAN:  Face-Masks The New Condoms?</title>
      <link>https://andrewsullivan.substack.com/p/are-face-masks-the-new-condoms-f8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;andrewsullivan.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some thoughts on plagues, rationality and recovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frail Ghislaine Maxwell pleads not guilty to new charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9503995/Ghislaine-Maxwell-pleads-NOT-GUILTY-two-counts-sex-trafficking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell, 59, pleaded not guilty Friday to new sex trafficking charges added to an indictment three weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family indicted, accused of selling bleach as cure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-coronavirus-5f9c2732411f3a14cd6cffd04d787b16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — A family accused of selling a toxic industrial bleach as a coronavirus cure through their Florida-based church has been indicted on federal charges. A federal grand jury in Miami returned an indictment Thursday charging Mark Grenon, 62, and his sons, Jonathan, 34, Jordan, 26, and Joseph, 32, with one count each of conspiracy to commit fraud and two counts each of criminal contempt, according to court records. They face possible life sentences if convicted. Mark Grenon is the archbishop of the Genesis II Church of Health and Healing, based in Bradenton, Florida. The church sells chlorine dioxide as a “Miracle Mineral Solution,” officials said. The Grenons claim the solution can cure a vast variety of illnesses ranging from cancer to autism to malaria to COVID-19. A Miami federal judge last April ordered the church to stop selling the substance, but the order was ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL draftees could hug, dap up vaccinated Roger Goodell
...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/draft/2021/04/23/nfl-draft-roger-goodell-vaccinated-against-covid-19-bro-hugs/7350561002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With NFL commissioner Roger Goodell vaccinated against COVID-19, bro hugs, daps and handshakes could make their return at the 2021 draft next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The dogs that stayed in Chernobyl...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210422-the-guards-caring-for-chernobyls-abandoned-dogs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The descendants of pets abandoned by those fleeing the Chernobyl disaster are now striking up a curious relationship with humans charged with guarding the contaminated area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More risks to pregnant, newborns than known before...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-pregnant-women-stu-idUSKBN2CA1E9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pregnant women infected with COVID-19 and their newborn children face higher risks of complications than was previously known, a study by British scientists showed on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tells Erdogan He'll Call Armenian Massacre Genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-tells-erdogan-he-ll-call-armenian-massacre-a-genocide/ar-BB1fZ04f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden told Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Friday that he intends to recognize the early-20th century massacre of Armenians by Ottoman Empire forces as a genocide, according to people familiar with a call between the leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Rush Return To CA? Company Working To Reopen Mine Untouched Since '56...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/04/22/gold-rush-return-to-grass-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been decades since gold country in California has been actively mined, but a Canadian company wants to change that in Grass Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising actor, fake HBO deals. One of Hollywood's most audacious Ponzi schemes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-04-23/zachary-horwitz-hollywood-film-ponzi-scheme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Zachary Horwitz collected $690 million from investors for movie deals the FBI says were fictitious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say no safer indoors at 6 feet or 60 feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/23/mit-researchers-say-youre-no-safer-from-covid-indoors-at-6-feet-or-60-feet-in-new-study.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC and WHO guidelines fail to factor in the amount of time spent indoors, which increases the chance of transmission the longer people are inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small black hole, dubbed 'Unicorn,' discovered near Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/04/23/black-hole-dubbed-the-unicorn-may-smallest-one-discovered-yet/7349740002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The black hole was given the nickname because it's so rare but also because it was discovered in the constellation Monoceros, which means unicorn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New malaria vaccine proven 77% effective...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210423-landmark-advance-as-malaria-vaccine-first-to-hit-who-goal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Landmark' advance as malaria vaccine first to hit WHO goal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech execs to testify at Senate hearing on algorithms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/23/facebook-youtube-twitter-testify-senate-484456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aides said they hoped to draw bipartisan interest by focusing the session on structural issues in how companies approach content moderation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owner says he won't dismantle shooting center as ordered...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ny-state-wire-shootings-business-gun-politics-c28092be0da198c2bb465ecc5562e35d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST PAWLET, Vt. (AP) — The owner of an unpermitted firearms training center that has rattled neighbors in a southern Vermont town says he won't comply with a judge's order to dismantle much of the facility he has built. Daniel Banyai said he is looking for “the proper constitutional attorney" to appeal a Vermont Environmental Court order that he dismantle all structures on the property that were built without permits in the town near the New York border. He has until May 5 to appeal. “We are not going to do that," Banyai said when asked about the order during a weekend event at the center he calls Slate Ridge Vermont. “We have not done anything wrong, we haven’t done anything illegal."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist Who Says He Created Bitcoin Can Sue Mystery Website...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/scientist-who-says-he-created-bitcoin-can-sue-mystery-website/ar-BB1fYzuA?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Australian scientist who says he created Bitcoin won the backing of a London court to pursue the mystery owners of the bitcoin.org website for allegedly infringing his copyright over the world’s largest cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich face tax hike with anger, denial and grief...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rich-americans-face-biden-tax-hike-with-anger-denial-and-grief/ar-BB1fWKNm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeatedly Misgendered on 'THE VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/joy-behar-apologizes-after-repeatedly-misgendering-caitlyn-jenner-in-segment-on-governor-stunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joy Behar repeatedly misgendered Caitlyn Jenner on Friday's The View, using the incorrect pronouns in a segment covering her bid for Governor of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actors Unload On Rudin: Hundreds Take To Streets Demanding His Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/04/22/scott-rudin-protest-new-york-city-march-on-broadway-actors-equity-association/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Broadway actors and theater workers came out Thursday for a "March on Broadway."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashlessness May Have Gone Too Far in Norway, Govt Warns...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/news/economy/cashlessness-may-have-gone-foo-far-in-norway-government-warns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALDS offers $50 just to show up for job interview!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/florida-mcdonalds-offers-50-just-to-show-up-for-job-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McDonald's location is so desperate for workers that it has offered people $50 just to show up for a job interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art or activism? The Oscars' identity crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/23/art-v-activism-can-the-oscars-survive-its-identity-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s awards will be a battle between political propriety and cinematic excellence. But will medium or message finally triumph?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More flushed wipes are clogging pipes, sending sewage into homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-nasty-pandemic-problem-more-flushed-wipes-are-clogging-pipes-sending-sewage-into-homes/ar-BB1fYvix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stepped-up cleaning and people seeking alternatives during toilet paper shortages have led to increased wipes usage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe sees record approval among young...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/549913-biden-sees-record-approval-among-college-age-americans-in-harvard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 6 in 10 college-age Americans approve of President Biden’s job as president thus far, according to a new youth poll from the Institute of Politics at Harvard Kennedy School, representing the highest figure for any president in the h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat dies after catching from owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2757937/cat-dies-covid-catching-bug-uk-owner-breathing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CATS have caught Covid from their owners in the UK, a new study has found – leading to fears of a pet pandemic. Two kitties were found to have contracted the virus, including a four-month-old…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study Shows Many Kept Traveling Normally -- Despite Feeling Symptoms!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/what-pandemic-people-traveling-despite-covid-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say this is the first report during COVID to trace movement patterns among people with possible symptoms of infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorkin's Lucy-Desi Movie Scraps Chateau Marmont Shoot Amid Boycott...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/aaron-sorkin-lucy-desi-movie-chateau-marmont-shoot-scrapped</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gets help from MAGA Brad Parscale...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/08/caitlyn-jenner-gets-help-from-brad-parscale-with-potential-run-for-ca-gov/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump 2020 campaign manager Brad Parscale is assisting Caitlyn Jenner as she mulls a potential challenge to California Gov. Gavin Newsom in this year’s recall, a source familiar with t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning to pre-covid life turning out to be hard for some...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-returning-pre-covid-life-120051678.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We seem to be on the cusp of returning to normal life, but for many people, transitioning back to Before Times is proving to be a lot more fraught than we expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where COVID kills young: Brazil shows what may await others...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/where-covid-19-kills-the-young-brazil-shows-what-may-await-others</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are many causes for the alarming shift but one appears to be that the young have trouble accepting they are at risk.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN MOVES TO TAX THE RICH!</title>
      <link>https://www.investing.com/news/stock-market-news/biden-aims-at-top-03-with-bid-to-tax-capital-gains-like-wages-2483253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Aims at Top 0.3% With Bid to Tax Capital Gains Like Wages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron crisis: Le Pen surges as French election panic sets in for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1427058/Emmanuel-macron-marine-le-pen-french-election-poll-latest-france-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL MACRON is facing an unexpectedly tight French election next year after a new poll showed rival Marine Le Pen hot on his heels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEALTHY FLEE ON PRIVATE JETS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-rips-icu-india-suffers-113653505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BENOIT TESSIEREight private jets carrying India’s super wealthy—and potentially the coronavirus—landed in London ahead of the U.K.’s 4 a.m. ban on travel from India, according to the London Times. The U.K. added India to its “red list” of pandemic-stricken countries. As of Friday, any Britons returning from India must quarantine for ten days in a government-approved hotel. All non-British or non-Irish citizens will be banned entirely from entering the country if they have been in India in the previous 10 days. British Prime Minister Boris Johnson had to cancel his own state visit to India scheduled for next week as a “precautionary measure.”The last of the luxury airliners to arrive, VistaJet Bombardier Global 6000, which left Dubai Thursday to collect passengers in Mumbai, landed at 3:15 a.m., just 44 minutes before the restrictions took place.The private jet passengers were fleeing unimaginable horror back home. At least 14 COVID-19 patients perished in a devastating fire that ripped through an ICU ward in one of India’s overcrowded hospitals about 70 miles outside Mumbai. The fire that broke out around 3 a.m. Friday morning was contained and extinguished, but not before 14 patients—many who were intubated and hard to evacuate—had died. “Around 90 patients were admitted to the hospital at the time of the incident,” Dilip Shah, the head of the Vijay Vallabh Hospital where it happened said in a statement Friday. Black Market Hospital Beds and Price-Gouged COVID Drugs Selling on Indian TwitterOne eyewitness, Avinash Patil, told reporters outside the hospital that no doctors were present at the time. “I got a call at around 3 am from a friend whose mother-in-law was admitted to the hospital,” he said. “As I reached the hospital, I saw fire engines outside. The ICU on the second floor was engulfed in smoke. Only two nurses were there, and I couldn’t see a doctor. It took firefighters about half an hour to put out the flames. We could see eight-ten bodies there.”Shah, the hospital chief, insisted all safety norms were followed and that “doctors were present,” according to local media reports. Earlier in the week, an oxygen leak in Maharashtra state, near where the fire broke out, resulted in the death of 24 COVID-19 patients who were on ventilators.To make terrible matters even worse, India reported its highest one-day number of cases, recording 332,730 new infections in a 24-hour period. In the same period, 2,263 people died with COVID-19.India has been overwhelmed by new cases coupled with a critical shortage of oxygen, hospital beds and now ventilators. Many desperate families have been forced to turn to black market price gougers who have been able to buy hospital space from corrupt administrators.The spike in cases comes as political rallies are still being held and after a month-long religious ceremony continues to bring millions of people to the Ganges River.India Prime Minister Narendra Modi has been criticized for not calling a national lockdown to try to mitigate the spread and for hosting rallies ahead of elections in May. Government officials have said the previous lockdown at the beginning of the pandemic was economically devastating to many manual laborers who then traveled by foot from home cities to their villages, carrying the virus with them. The fire at a COVID-19 hospital in Virar is tragic. Condolences to those who lost their loved ones. May the injured recover soon: PM @narendramodi— PMO India (@PMOIndia) April 23, 2021 Modi called the ICU fire “tragic” and offered condolences over Twitter. Many of the comments on his tweet begged him to call a national lockdown to try to save lives. In a shocking expose published in Time magazine, Indian journalist Rana Ayyub paints a horrific picture from the ground, writing about states essentially hijacking oxygen trucks and stealing supplies for their own hospitals, and disturbing allegations of underreporting deaths. Ayyub lays the blame for the debacle squarely on Modi’s shoulders, accusing him of ignoring the fact that his Trump-style rallies are super-spreader events, and for letting the ball drop on vaccines.“Why was India caught unprepared as the second wave ravaged a cross-section of Indian society?” Ayyub writes. “The responsibility lies with a strongman regime that has ignored all caution.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIGHT FOR OXYGEN</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/india/oxygen-gets-armed-escort-india-supplies-run-low-covid-crisis-2021-04-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sirens wailing, a police convoy escorting a tanker carrying oxygen reached a hospital in India's capital just in time, to the huge relief of doctors and relatives of COVID-19 patients counting on the supply to stave off death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning photos capture launch to ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/trending/spacex-launch-10-stunning-photos-captured-by-skygazers/SPUJ6JNR7ZHRPFYOOIQAMGBSMI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four astronauts lifted off Friday morning from Florida’s Kennedy Space Center on a SpaceX flight to the International Space Station. Skygazers took to social media to share their photos. Here are some of our favorites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over $200 billion wiped off crypto market in day as bitcoin plunges below $50,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/23/bitcoin-btc-price-plunges-as-260-billion-wiped-off-cryptocurrencies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin and other digital currencies plunged on Friday as U.S. President Joe Biden's proposed capital gains tax hike led to a wave of selling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed Kremlin critic Navalny says he will start ending hunger strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210423111142-4uyd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Jailed Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny says he will start ending hunger strike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC probes new death, hospitalization after J&amp;J shots...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210423104338-cgp31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JOHNSON&amp;JOHNSON-USA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-U.S. CDC probes new death, hospitalization after J&amp;J vaccine shots - officials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER HOSPITAL FIRE KILLS PATIENTS</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Fire-kills-covid-patients-in-second-India-16123254.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire that broke out at a hospital in western India killed at least 14 coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
