<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The fall of QUIBI: How did starry $1.75 billion NETFLIX rival crash so fast?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2020/jun/28/quibi-netflix-jeffrey-katzenberg-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Katzenberg’s short-form content platform has struggled to make an impact with bad reviews, lack of interest and legal issues swirling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun Belt time bomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/29/sun-belt-coronavirus-trump-reelection-343694</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising Covid-19 caseloads in Florida, Arizona and Texas raise fresh doubts about the president's reelection prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could he drop out?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-polls-republican-gop-operatives-possible-drop-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stretch of lackluster polling for President Trump has some Republican operatives nervous about the president’s reelection prospects in November – with some even floating the possibility that Trump could drop out if his poll numbers don’t rebound</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild moment St. Louis couple draws firearms on protesters outside home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8467075/St-Louis-couple-point-firearms-protesters-outside-home-marching-demand-mayors-resignation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Husband and wife, Mark and Patricia McCloskey could be seen aiming the guns at demonstrators who walked by their property in St. Louis at around 6pm on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singers criticize Chase Rice for concert in front of hundreds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Country-singers-criticize-Chase-Rice-as-selfish-15373220.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country singer Chase Rice played his first in-person concert in months on Saturday night and appeared thrilled to do so. "We back," he wrote in an Instagram story with a smiley face sunglasses emoji, accompanied by video of hundreds of people singing along to his recent hit, "Eyes On You."  But on social media, many were horrified to see images of a packed crowd, with no masks and no social distancing - especially as the concert took place in Tennessee, which is experiencing a significant spike in coronavirus infections. As the videos started circulating on Twitter, other country singers took the unusual step of calling out Rice by name.  "Imagine being selfish enough to put thousands of people's health at risk, not to mention the potential ripple effect, and play a NORMAL country concert right now. @ChaseRiceMusic," Kelsea Ballerini tweeted to her million followers. "We all want (and need) to tour. We just care about our fans and their families enough to wait."  Mickey Guyton responded and included Rice's Twitter handle: "An absolute selfish act. Shame on him." Maren Morris replied to one of Guyton's tweets and simply said, "No masks," with head-exploding and frowning-face emojis.  Bobby Bones, the format's most powerful radio personality, tweeted the video and wrote, "Aside from the obvious .... probably also heavy liability here. Just talked to two different attorneys about this."  The concert took place at Historic Brushy Mountain State Penitentiary, a former prison turned tourist destination that has a distillery, paranormal tours and a concert series called "Live at Brushy" - it's located in Petros, Tenn., a 2½-hour drive from Nashville. Brian May, vice president of the Brushy Mountain Group, said in a statement Sunday evening that fewer than 1,000 people attended Rice's show, even though the venue's maximum...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft Prostitution Case Heads to Appellate Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/sports/new-england-patriots/2020/06/28/robert-kraft-case-update</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The case will be argued via videoconference and livestreamed on the court’s website because of coronavirus concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I saw devil': Patients have terrifying delirium...</title>
      <link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/spotlight/06/29/20/i-saw-the-devil-many-covid-patients-have-terrifying-delirium</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Called hospital delirium, the phenomenon has previously been seen mostly in a subset of older patients, some of whom already had dementia, and in recent years, hospitals adopted measures to reduce it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food Bank Lines Reemerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/food-bank-lines-reemerge-covid-paralyzes-households</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash cliff spells trouble for unemployed, and everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-cliff-analysis-idUSKBN24014U?taid=5ef9c889d50dbc00016bc39d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judith Ramirez is bracing for July. That's when the hotel housekeeper and her electrician husband - who have both been out of work for three months - expect their combined unemployment benefits to drop by more than half, and their deferred $1,500 monthly mortgage payment on their Honolulu home to come due.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China forces birth control on Muslims to suppress population...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/269b3de1af34e17c1941a514f78d764c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese government is taking draconian measures to slash birth rates among Uighurs and other minorities as part of a sweeping campaign to curb its Muslim population, even as it encourages some...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former MVP QB Cam Newton signs 1-year deal to join PATRIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/it-s-official-cam-newton-signs-1-year-deal-to-join-patriots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cam Newton has been without a NFL home since March. That finally changed Sunday night. The 2015 MVP quarterback has agreed to terms on a one-year deal to join coach Bill Belichick and the New England Patriots, NFL Network Insider Ian Rapoport reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers will lose paid sick leave if they travel to states with high infections... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8469051/New-Yorkers-lose-sick-leave-benefits-travel-states-high-COVID-19-infection-rates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers will lose their paid sick leave benefits for voluntarily traveling to states which have a COVID-19 positive test rate of 10 per cent or more under an order made by Gov. Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From sleepy to senile: Inside  campaign's effort to rebrand Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-campaign-biden-branding-43b2c6a5-3a06-4b20-b18f-38429b0faf28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's aides say it will be harder to make Biden widely despised than it was with Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil has record week for virus cases...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-record-week-virus-cases-005920593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil had its worst week yet of the coronavirus pandemic in terms of new cases, registering 259,105 infections in the seven days through Sunday, according to health ministry figures. Brazil, the country with the second-highest number of infections and deaths worldwide after the United States, has struggled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears worse to come...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5a06549049a5471d510ddde7188eeae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The world surpassed two sobering coronavirus milestones Sunday -- 500,000 confirmed deaths, 10 million confirmed cases -- and hit another high mark for daily new infections as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies and Commandos Warned Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/spies-and-commandos-warned-months-ago-of-russian-bounties-on-u-s-troops/ar-BB164Uci?li=BBnb4R7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX GOV:  Has taken very dangerous turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mike-pence-in-dallas-as-gov-abbott-says-covid-19-has-taken-very-dangerous-turn-in-texas/ar-BB164Lm2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLY 5% SAY THINGS GOING 'VERY WELL'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/only-5-25-of-americans-in-survey-say-things-are-going-very-well/ar-BB164UX2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB CEO: 'Travel will never, ever go back to the way it was'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/airbnb-travel-coronavirus-3f7ac17c-89d7-4ba6-9b5b-8905e4aa888a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Chesky tells Axios in an interview that global travel may never fully recover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working-class white women turning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/working-class-white-women-turning-164806378.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2016, Trump held the support of a key group — white women without college degrees. This spring, they've turned against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House denies knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200628131939-u3umc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AFGHANISTAN/RUSSIA:Trump denies being told about Russian bounties to kill U.S. troops in Afghanistan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi takes step toward dropping rebel image from flag...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1d4969cb533fb6ab7fe381fb5855c256</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Mississippi lawmakers voted Sunday to surrender the Confederate battle emblem from the state flag more than a century after white supremacist legislators adopted the design a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMPAIGN SCRAMBLES TO BOOST REELECTION</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Analysis-Trump-campaign-scrambles-to-boost-15372432.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump and his campaign team are grappling with how to resuscitate his imperiled reelection effort amid a wave of polling that shows him trailing presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden and losing traction even among core constituencies.  Some Trump advisers and allies are privately pushing for sweeping changes to the campaign, including the idea of a major staff shake-up and trying to convince the president to be more disciplined in his message and behavior.  But so far, the campaign has settled only on incremental changes - such as hiring and elevating several operatives who worked on Trump's upset victory in 2016 - and has yet to settle on a clear message for his reelection. Campaign officials and other advisers are also still struggling with how to best focus their attacks on Biden, which so far have been scattershot and have failed to curb his rise among voters.  And then there's Trump himself, who has derailed his team's desired themes on an almost daily basis - deploying racist rhetoric and mounting incendiary attacks on critics amid a surging coronavirus pandemic, an economic crisis and roiling protests over police brutality.  Numerous national polls show Trump losing significant ground with seniors and among white voters, including those with and without four-year college degrees. He has also slipped among white evangelical voters. According to new New York Times/Siena College polls, Trump is at least slightly behind Biden in six states that he won in 2016 and are pivotal to his reelection path - including Michigan, Pennsylvania and Wisconsin, where he trails by double digits.  "You can't win with these numbers. They're atrocious numbers," said Edward Rollins, co-chairman of the pro-Trump super PAC Great America and the former campaign manager for Ronald Reagan's 1984 reelection...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L'OREAL vows to remove 'whitening' from skin products...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1051036/loreal-remove-whitening-word-skin-products/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L’OREAL has today vowed to remove phrases like ‘whitening’ from their skin products in the wake of racism protests. The beauty company announced it had decided to remove the words…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS OUT OF CONTROL:  'Window closing for us to take action'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/28/politics/hhs-alex-azar-coronavirus-rise-in-cases-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Alex Azar warned Sunday that the "window is closing" for the United States to get the coronavirus pandemic under control, as confirmed cases are surging in a majority of the country and some states are dealing with record numbers of hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TWEET DISASTER</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/06/28/seniors-protesting-the-village-florida-donald-trump-white-power/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, Donald Trump loves his white supremacists, because he just gave his stamp of approval on a protest where one of his loudest supporters is screaming "white power."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS PULLS ADS FROM SOCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/06/28/starbucks-latest-company-to-pause-ads-across-social-media-platforms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks is the latest company said it will pause advertising on "all social media platforms" and promises to have discussions internally and with media partners and civil rights organizations to stop the spread of hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign targeting evangelical voters in bid for November surprise...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/biden-campaign-confident-they-can-peel-evangelical-voters-away-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The battle for the soul of our nation deeply resonates with evangelicals,” says John McCarthy, deputy national political director for the Biden Campaign. “They would be open to Joe Biden’s message as well.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WHITE POWER'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7eea48b80f14474b7057967a9654c4f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Sunday tweeted approvingly of a video showing one of his supporters chanting “white power," a racist slogan associated with white supremacists. He later...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accidental Discovery Leads to Parkinson's Disease Cure in Mice...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/accidental-discovery-leads-to-parkinsons-disease-cure-in-mice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A discovery by researhers in California has led to the development of a treatment that eliminates symptoms of Parkinson’s disease in mice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half million back in lockdown as Beijing fights new cluster...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-puts-half-a-million-people-in-lockdown-as-beijing-fights-new-cluster/ar-BB163Mig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallout in college towns could last 'for next decade'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/we-could-be-feeling-this-for-the-next-decade-virus-hits-college-towns/ar-BB163B6P</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Promotes Video of Supporter Yelling 'White Power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-promotes-video-of-his-supporters-yelling-white-power-great-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump praised "great people" on Sunday by sharing a video of one of his supporters shouting "white power"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis council members calling to defund police hire private security...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/minneapolis-city-council-members-private-security-detail-death-threats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Minneapolis City Council members who have received death threats following their calls to defund the police after the death of George Floyd have been assigned private security details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 2 states reporting decline in new cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/06/28/health/us-coronavirus-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two US states are reporting a decline in new coronavirus cases compared to last week -- Connecticut and Rhode Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Players To Put Social Justice Statements On Backs Of Jerseys...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-players-will-be-allowed-to-put-social-justice-statements-on-the-back-of-their-jerseys-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move will be made with Nike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 1 injured at Breonna Taylor protest park in Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/1-dead-1-injured-breonna-taylor-protest-park-kentucky-n1232351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is a tragedy that this area of peaceful protest is now a crime scene," Louisville Mayor Greg Fischer tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Orders US-Based Christian TV Channel Off Air...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-cancels-evangelical-christian-channel-god-tv-633054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Council for Cable and Satellite Broadcasting threatened to suspend Shelanu TV’s license, pending a review by the council.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'STAY HOME': County Residents Receive Emergency Text Order...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/06/27/texas-residents-emergency-alert-covid-19-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in one Texas county received an emergency alert about COVID-19, urging them to stay home and avoid gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114-year-old monk survives coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jun/28/tilahun-woldemichael-ethiopian-orthodox-monk-said-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ethiopian Orthodox monk whose family says he is 114 years old has survived the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern states report record surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/06/27/southern-states-coronavirus-surge-342267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has also seen a record number of cases nationwide, according to the latest figures released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church of Scientology tried to silence Danny Masterson's alleged rape victims: suit...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/06/27/church-of-scientology-tried-to-silence-danny-mastersons-alleged-rape-victims-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danny Masterson, who made a wisecracking name for himself on “That ’70s Show,” was arrested and charged June 17 on multiple counts of rape against three women. But it’s not just the actor who is on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simmering doubts in 'God &amp; guns' country...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/god-guns-trump-country-simmering-224335706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mohave County, Arizona, which went 73% for Donald Trump in 2016, some residents are starting to question their support for the president.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
