<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HOW THE LEFT IS OUTSOURCING CENSORSHIP OF THE INTERNET...</title>
      <link>https://www.powerlineblog.com/archives/2018/08/how-the-left-is-outsourcing-censorship-of-the-internet.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.powerlineblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberals control every newspaper in America, as far as I know, except the Manchester Union Leader. They control CBS, ABC, NBC and every cable network except Fox News. They control what is left of the news magazines, and pretty much every other magazine, too. Only talk radio and the pesky internet lie outside their grasp, so that is where they seek to impose censorship. But they have a problem: the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Ring of Underground Wrestling...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/18/style/wrestling-underground-new-york.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A community of New Yorkers has formed around controlled, costumed combat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vitamin D, the Sunshine Supplement, Has Shadowy Money Behind It...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/18/business/vitamin-d-michael-holick.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The doctor most responsible for creating a billion-dollar juggernaut has received hundreds of thousands of dollars from the vitamin D industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They are closing down opinions of many on right...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6073647/President-Trump-accuses-social-media-companies-totally-discriminating-against-Republicans.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Speaking loudly and clearly for the Trump Administration, we won’t let [censorship against conservatives] happen,' the president tweeted early Saturday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Maher criticizes social media bans: 'Alex Jones gets to speak'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/technology/402450-bill-maher-on-social-media-bans-alex-jones-gets-to-speak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO talk show host Bill Maher spoke out in defense of controversial right-wing host Alex Jones after Jones was suspended from several social media platforms, saying that everyone has a right to free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP BLASTS SOCIALS; WON'T ALLOW CENSORSHIP</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-social-media-discriminating-republican-conservative-voices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Speaking loudly and clearly for the Trump Administration, we won't let that happen," POTUS says in Saturday tweet-storm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former UN chief Kofi Annan dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b36471b5018640379c5d431ea0738ef5/Former-UN-Secretary-General-Kofi-Annan-dies-at-age-80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Kofi Annan, one of the world's most celebrated diplomats and a charismatic symbol of the United Nations who rose through its ranks to become the first black African</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let 'good and bad' voices speak...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/402449-trump-let-good-and-bad-voices-speak-on-social-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Saturday charged that social media is “totally discriminating against Republican/Conservative voices" and argued that the platforms should allow both "good and bad" content online amid an ongoing debate over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor says emails were 'gay-coded,' not sex harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nyu-professor-says-emails-were-gay-coded-not-221305983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A prominent New York University professor who is being sued by a former student who accuses her of sexual harassment said that her relationship with him was not sexual and that affectionate emails they exchanged were just "gay-coded" correspondence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News outlets challenge Maryland online ad law...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/news-outlets-challenge-maryland-online-ad-law-214936741--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREENBELT, Md. (AP) — News outlets filed a lawsuit on Friday challenging a Maryland law meant to fight foreign meddling in online political advertising because they say it creates unfair burdens on media sites that publish such ads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest made in more than 100 synthetic pot overdoses in park...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/arrest-made-more-100-synthetic-pot-overdoses-park-211859789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the victims identified John Parker, of New Haven, as one of the people who was dealing K2 on the New Haven Green, where most of the overdoses occurred Wednesday and Thursday, Police Chief Anthony Campbell said. Parker, who was arrested Wednesday, was charged with drug crimes after being found</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant named after Jimmy Buffett served protected game fish...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/business/fl-bz-protected-fish-served-jimmy-buffett-restaurant-permit-fish-margaritaville-20180815-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JWB Prime Steak and Seafood, a restaurant at Hollywood's Margaritaville resort, served speared permit fish to customers. Permit are protected game fish that are illegal to sell commercially. Now, the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission is investigating the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, McConnell forge partnership as midterms approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-mcconnell-forge-partnership-as-midterms-approach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their relationship hasn't always been a smooth one, but they have a Senate and House to protect</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy:  Boom or blip?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d69297fd7a874d54a58674623e0a2e2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Is the latest pickup in U.S. economic growth destined to slow in the years ahead as most analysts say?        Or, as the Trump administration insists, is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump backs CEOs, proposes easing corporate reporting rules...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/sec-asked-study-six-month-filing-system-companies-114212485--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK/WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump asked securities regulators to explore replacing quarterly reporting requirements with half-yearly filings at the urging of executives including PepsiCo Chief Executive Indra Nooyi, reigniting a debate about how often companies should give financial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Republican opens up about Russia probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a968f26df3a64667afe108107daebc4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For much of the last two years, Senate Intelligence Committee Chairman Richard Burr has been the Russia investigator who is seen but rarely heard on Capitol Hill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Speeches Feature Mystery Men the White House Won't Name...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/16/trump-s-speeches-feature-mystery-men-the-white-house-won-t-name</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's Speeches Feature Mystery Men the White House Won't Name</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No one is ever really ready': Aid-in-dying patient chooses his last day...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/no-one-is-ever-really-ready-aid-in-dying-patient-chooses-his-last-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its expansion to Hawaii this year, medical aid-in-dying is now approved in eight U.S. jurisdictions. Even when legal, the controversial practice of choosing to die after a terminal diagnosis i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look how astronauts may live on missions to deep space...</title>
      <link>http://www.orlandosentinel.com/business/os-lockheed-space-habitat-20180815-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Kennedy Space Center Thursday, Lockheed Martin gave a first look at what an astronaut habitat may look like for future deep space missions. The aerospace giant is under contract with NASA to build a prototype of the living quarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez Defends Barring Press From Town Hall So People Would 'Feel Safe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/reporters-fire-back-after-ocasio-cortez-defends-barring-press-from-town-hall-so-people-would-feel-safe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>148 years jail for man who broke into motel rooms, forced couples to have sex at gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.mycentraljersey.com/story/news/crime/2018/08/16/elizabeth-linden-man-rasheed-powell-robbery/1002672002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mycentraljersey.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rasheed Powell, 43, was sentenced to 148 years in state prison for terrorizing, robbing and sexually assaulting four couples at motels in Linden and Elizabeth in 2012.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative Page Claims 'Shadow Ban', Cites 99.9999% Drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/17/shadow-ban-prageru-reveals-immediate-99-9999-drop-in-facebook-reach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative non-profit group PragerU appears to be facing Facebook censorship, as many recent posts from group are suffering from a 99.9999 percent drop in engagement based on Facebook's own dashboard. The Social Media Masters of the Universe also pulled down two PragerU videos, which it labeled "hate speech."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt for aliens boosted by discovery of hundreds of 'water worlds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/08/17/hunt-aliens-boosted-discovery-hundreds-water-worlds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chances of finding alien organisms have been boosted by the discovery of hundreds of &amp;ldquo;water worlds&amp;rdquo; capable of supporting life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate of anti-Semitism shakes UK Jewish community...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/17/uk/uk-anti-semitism-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For months, accusations of anti-Semitism have dogged Britain's Labour Party and its leader, even as incidents of anti-Semitism are near record levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special ops blast John Brennan: 'You put your politics before us'...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/17/special-ops-shoot-down-brennan-and-his-defenders-put-your-politics-before-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Brennan rallied numerous high-powered defenders to his corner over his security clearance clash with President Trump, but some well-known special ops heroes are firing back suggesting the former CIA director got what he deserves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: Not just audio, Omarosa prepping VIDEO releases?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e2b8967b8b0c47638cf16b2d2285c519/AP-source:-It's-not-just-audio,-Manigault-Newman-has-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It's not just audiotapes.        Omarosa Manigault Newman has a stash of video, emails, text messages and other documentation supporting the claims in her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Execs 'Misled Staff' On Censored Search...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/17/internal-meeting-reveals-how-google-bosses-misled-staff-on-their-china-censorship-plan-here-are-the-questions-they-must-answer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-founder Sergey Brin said he didn’t know about the China plans, which CEO Sundar Pichai said are “in an exploration stage” — despite previous reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs NKorea planning big September: Blocked visas, parade practice, haircuts...</title>
      <link>www.washingtonpost.comhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2018/08/17/signs-that-north-korea-is-planning-something-big-september-blocked-visas-parade-practice-haircuts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady strips, breaks SUV window with rock during 'tresspassing' dispute with neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://triblive.com/local/westmoreland/13983373-74/troopers-accuse-derry-twp-woman-with-open-lewdness-during-neighborhood-argument</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;triblive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State troopers allege a Derry Township woman left it all out there -- including her clothes -- during a recent, late-night argument with neighbors. Brianna ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort jurors sent home for the weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-jury-begins-2nd-day-manafort-deliberations-140938481--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. (AP) — The Latest on the trial of Paul Manafort (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. govt seeks FACEBOOK help to wiretap 'Messenger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-encryption-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-government-seeks-facebook-help-to-wiretap-messenger-sources-idUSKBN1L226D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government is trying to force Facebook Inc to break the encryption in its popular Messenger app so law enforcement may listen to a suspect's voice conversations in a criminal probe, three people briefed on the case said, resurrecting the issue of whether companies can be compelled to alter their products to enable surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter kills bear biting leg -- and jaws stays clamped!</title>
      <link>https://www.krqe.com/news/new-mexico/new-mexico-man-explains-how-he-survived-a-bear-attack/1366347597</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krqe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Mexico man is sharing his story of survival after he was attacked by a bear while walking his dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmaker: 'Cold day in Hell' before put up monument...</title>
      <link>https://www.thv11.com/article/news/religion/sen-rapert-says-very-cold-day-in-hell-before-baphomet-statue-allowed-on-capitol-grounds/91-584967664</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thv11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A self-described Satanic Temple drove a statue of Baphomet to the gathering, hoping to someday see it placed on the same grounds as the state's Ten Commandments monuments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SATANISTS RALLY AT ARKANSAS CAPITOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox16.com/news/local-news/satanic-temple-rally-at-state-capitol-targets-arkansas-lawmaker/1376928022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox16.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly four months after crews reinstalled the Ten Commandments monument on state capitol grounds, the Satanic Temple came back Thursday with a statue of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE FEARS MANAFORT JURY SAFETY</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/17/manafort-judge-threatened/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I had no idea this case excited this emotion in the public'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Internment Camps Swell Beijing Widens Dragnet...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-uighur-camps-swell-as-beijing-widens-the-dragnet-1534534894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has sharply expanded an internment program that initially targeted ethnic Uighur extremists but is now confining vast numbers of the largely Muslim minority group, including the secular, old and infirm, in camps across the country’s northwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fisherman tossed into water as whale capsizes boat...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/monmouth/index.ssf/2018/08/retired_firefighter_rescues_fishermen_after_whale.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were knocked into the water when a whale hit their boat during a fishing trip Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Won't Air National Anthem on 'MONDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2018/08/17/espn-president-jimmy-pitaro-no-national-anthem-mnf-telecast-nfl/1019642002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN president Jimmy Pitaro told reporters that the network does not plan to televise the national anthem on its 'Monday Night Football' broadcasts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC, WASH POST Fight Over Russia 'Election Hack' Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/bill-nelson-wasn-t-making-things-when-he-said-russians-n901701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bill Nelson, who is in a tough re-election fight, was blasted for saying 10 days ago that Russians had penetrated his state's election systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Suggestion Senator Leaked Classified Info'...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/GlennKesslerWP/status/1030546609556398081</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Our Four-Pinocchio rating stands. Everything in this article was noted in our piece, except for the suggestion that Nelson leaked classified information. https://t.co/j7To5lj1k5”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most ancient' solid cheese found in jar...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Substance-in-dug-up-Egyptian-jar-most-ancient-13163270.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAIRO (AP) - For thousands of years beneath Egypt's desert sands a solidified whitish substance sat in a broken jar. Scientists now say it's "probably the most ancient archaeological solid residue of cheese ever found." Archaeologists came across the finding while cleaning the sands around a 19th dynasty tomb at the vast Saqqara necropolis of the ancient city of Memphis. The tomb of Ptahmes, the mayor of ancient Memphis, was initially discovered in 1885 but had been swallowed by shifting sands until its rediscovery in 2010.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Young Thug Arrested At Own Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/rapper-young-thug-booked-on-weapons-charge-in-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Rapper Young Thug was arrested in Los Angeles after officers found a concealed firearm inside his car, authorities said Friday. The rapper, whose real name is Jeffery Lamar Williams, was booked on a weapons possession charge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss America slams pageant, Gretchen Carlson: 'Silenced me, reduced me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2018/08/17/miss-america-cara-mund-leadership-bullied-manipulated-silenced-me/1019920002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reigning Miss America says she has been bullied, manipulated and silenced by the pageant's current leadership, including Gretchen Carlson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELLISON: EX-GIRLFRIEND SHOULD RELEASE VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/government/2018/08/ellison-pressed-over-abuse-allegation-takes-it-to-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Minnesota Rep. Keith Ellison is answering calls to quit his state’s attorney general race following allegations of domestic abuse by hitting the campaign trail. Ellison is visiting…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calif. giant swamp rat problem worse than thought...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/nutria-California-invasive-rodent-Delta-river-rat-13155943.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the spring, the Department of Fish and Wildlife began to warn the public about the dangers of nutria, the destructive rat-like mammal currently burrowing into central California's wetlands. But in the past few months, only 200 nutria have been exterminated, 100 of which were found in a pond on a single private farm in central California.  And as the agency prepares for an intensive survey of the Sacramento-San Joaquin River Delta, officials say they have no idea what the actual numbers will look like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expected to break for weekend without verdict...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/17/manafort-verdict-latest-news-updates-783089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the jurors exited for a nearby conference room, Ellis acknowledged the trial “might end soon”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison says he won't quit race amid abuse claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/The-Latest-Ellison-says-he-won-t-quit-race-amid-13163855.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) - The Latest on Minnesota Rep. Keith Ellison's response to an allegation of domestic abuse (all times local): 12:20 p.m. Democratic Rep. Keith Ellison says he won't abandon his run for Minnesota attorney general amid allegations from an ex-girlfriend that he once physically abused her, "because I didn't do it." Ellison made his most expansive comments about the allegations Friday before joining supporters for a campaign outreach event in Minneapolis. Karen Monahan has accused the six-term congressman of dragging her from a bed while screaming at her in 2016. She has claimed to have video but says she won't release it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL turns to yoga...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/yoga-more-beneficial-stretching-nfl-players-172543870--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — During the mandatory rookie camp back in June, the New York Giants required players to take a yoga class. Running back Robert Martin walked in, looked around at his new teammates and thought, man, this is crazy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Technical error' blamed for 1,000 attorney-inmate jail recordings...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-oc-pivileged-phone-calls-20180817-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Orange County Sheriff’s Department employee revealed this week during a court hearing that the department improperly recorded more than 1,000 privileged phone calls between county jail inmates and their attorneys over a three-year period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New CA Bill To Mandate Only Milk, Water With Kids' Meals...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/08/16/kids-soda-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Bill 1192 would make water or milk the default drink for kids meals in a push to reduce obesity and access to sugary drinks for children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Half-naked woman 'trying to get to heaven' punches officer...</title>
      <link>http://www.onlineathens.com/news/20180817/half-naked-athens-woman-punches-officer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 32-year-old Athens woman was arrested early Wednesday after she created a disturbance on Bray Street and then fought with a police officer, Athens-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim couple denied Swiss citizenship over handshake refusal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/muslim-couple-denied-swiss-citizenship-over-handshake-refusal-165220137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Swiss city of Lausanne has blocked a Muslim couple's bid to become Swiss nationals over their refusal to shake hands with members of the opposite sex. The municipality said it refused to grant the couple's citizenship application over their lack of respect for gender equality, Lausanne mayor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPE COD SUMMER OF SHARKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/cape-cod-beaches-close-following-shark-sightings/22755039</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beach goers along Cape Cod are being told to use caution after a shark attack and multiple shark sightings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels drops out of UK reality show at last minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewstribune.com/entertainment/celebrities/article216886850.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stormy Daniels, the adult film actress and nemesis of U.S. President Donald Trump, has pulled out of a British reality-TV show at the last minute after a dispute with producers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank robber returns to crime scene 60 years later -- for lunch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/ottawa/bank-robber-riviera-1.4787029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1958, Boyne Johnston stole $260,000 from the Sparks Street bank in Ottawa where he worked as a teller. Six decades later, he dined at the restaurant now in its place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez Bans Media From Town Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-banned-the-media-from-her-latest-town-hall-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst-case scenario for Republicans is 70-seat wipeout...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/402329-worst-case-scenario-for-house-gop-is-70-seat-wipeout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic enthusiasm and a GOP malaise surrounding President Trump has set the stage for a potentially devastating midterm election for the House Republican majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sleeper Cell' Militants Hibernating in USA, Positioned for Attack...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iranian-backed-sleeper-cell-militants-hibernating-u-s-positioned-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian-backed militants are operating across the United States mostly unfettered, raising concerns in Congress and among regional experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  3 times the evidence for Manafort's NEXT trial...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/08/16/app-politics-section/mueller-manafort-evidence-next-trial/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Special Counsel's Office has almost three times the number of exhibits it wants to show a jury in Paul Manafort's next criminal trial compared with what it used in his Virginia case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant busted for serving protected tarantulas on tacos...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/restaurant-busted-over-protected-tarantula-tacos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fancy a tarantula taco for a cool $27? Not so fast, Mexican authorities say. A Mexico City market restaurant recently put the arachnids on its menu and posted a video on Facebook showing a chef torching one until blackened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor bitten by deadly snake during service, leaving him drenched in blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7040148/horror-moment-us-pastor-is-bitten-by-a-deadly-snake-during-a-service-leaving-him-drenched-in-blood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the horror moment a snake bit – and almost killed- a controversial American pastor who was performing a bizarre service with the reptile in Kentucky. Drenched in his own blood, Cody C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod Beachgoers Panic As ANOTHER Shark Spotted Near Shore...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/08/16/race-point-beach-shark-sighting-provincetown-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shark sighting off Provincetown closed Race Point Beach for one hour Thursday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PILLS, THE PAIN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/17/musk-details-excruciating-personal-toll-of-tesla-turmoil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk, choking up, spoke about how his health has suffered and that, from a personal standpoint, he believes “the worst is yet to come.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argument Over Aretha Franklin Leads To Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/08/16/argument-shooting-over-aretha-franklin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An argument over Aretha Franklin led to a shooting, witnesses told police in one Virginia town Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran General 'Ready for Jihad'; Posts White House Explosion Pic...</title>
      <link>http://cjlab.memri.org/lab-projects/iran-cyber-initiative-lab-projects/irgc-qods-force-commander-qassem-soleimani-designated-by-u-s-treasury-dept-is-active-on-instagram-posts-include-image-of-white-house-exploding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cjlab.memri.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge 'optimistic case might end soon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/08/17/paul-manafort-trial-jury-resumes-deliberations-tax-bank-fraud-case/1017802002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jury resumed deliberations Friday in the fraud trial of Paul Manafort, while the judge in the case against the former Trump campaign chairman said he was "optimistic" the case might end soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 20 illegals skip hearings, disappear into shadows each day...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/16/illegal-immigrant-children-skip-deportation-hearin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On any given day, nearly 20 illegal immigrant children skip their deportation hearings and disappear into the shadows, the Trump administration said Thursday, putting contours on the difficulty the government faces in trying to stop the flow and protect the children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA SHARES TUMBLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/17/tesla-tumbles-3point5-percent-ahead-of-elon-musks-reported-meeting-with-sec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of Tesla took a hit in early trading Friday after reports that CEO Elon Musk will meet with Securities and Exchange Commission officials next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam Wants You: Treasury Depends More on Domestic Bond Buyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/funding-secured-for-the-u-s-government-that-means-domestic-bond-buyers-1534507201 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government has been issuing more debt, but it’s not getting more foreign buyers in the door. As a result, U.S. investors have so far financed all of this year’s increase in the federal government’s borrowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there a friendship crisis?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/is-there-a-friendship-crisis-2018-08-17</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why do so many friendships end? How you can preserve them or know when to let go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man, 39, Battered Girlfriend, 78, Over Unpaid DirecTV Bill...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/bryceville/twice-his-age-collar-520931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 39-year-old Florida man battered his 78-year-old girlfriend during an argument over an unpaid DirecTV bill, according to police. Investigators charge that David Mann and the victim quarreled Tuesd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says cancelled military parade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/735cfcd91ce9458189ab13ecc204f140/President-Trump-says-he-has-cancelled-military-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Friday he had canceled plans for a Veterans Day military parade, citing the "ridiculously high" price tag — a day after U.S. of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON BLOODBATH: Four children stabbed; Boy 'disembowelled'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/08/17/four-children-stabbed-south-london-one-boy-disembowelled-7850208/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six teenagers have been arrested over the quadruple stabbing that has left one boy fighting for his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREAKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/elon-musk-confronts-a-fateful-tweet-and-an-excruciating-year/17775134/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk was at home in Los Angeles, struggling to maintain his composure. “This past year has been the most difficult and painful year of my career,” he said. “It was excruciating.”</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
