<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>City to make gun owners carry liability insurance, pay violence fee...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/30/san-jose-california-to-make-gun-owners-carry-liabi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Jose officials have passed a new law that requires gun owners to carry liability insurance and pay a fee to cover taxpayers’ costs associated with gun violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitism rising in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/30/us/american-anti-semitism-students-soh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young Americans say they are seeing a new face of anti-Semitism among their progressive college classmates who are bullying and shunning them purely for their Jewish faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Babbitt killed by member of Pence's Secret Service detail...</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/killed-ashli-babbitt-capitol-riot-secret-service-pence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cockburn’s sources tell him a member of VP Mike Pence’s protective detail may have been responsible for the shooting of Ashli Babbitt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPOST Media Columnist Keith Kelly Steps Aside...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ny-post-media-columnist-keith-kelly-to-retire-after-23-years-exclusive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keith Kelly is planning to retire on July 23 after more than 20 years at the tabloid, according to an individual with knowledge of his plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phylicia Rashad Applauds: 'Terrible Wrong Being Righted'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/30/phylicia-rashad-comes-out-swinging-for-bill-cosby-a-terrible-wrong-is-being-righted-a-miscarriage-of-justice-is-corrected</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claire Huxtable has come out swinging. Actress Phylicia Rashad, who defended Bill Cosby in this very column a few years ago, has expressed her support for her friend and former co-star on The Cosby…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to establish committee to investigate Jan. 6 Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-vote-creation-committee-probe-jan-6-riot-n1272624</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Republicans — Cheney and Kinzinger — joined the Democrats in approving the new panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary under both Ford and W. Bush...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/30/former-defense-secretary-donald-rumsfeld-has-died-at-the-age-of-88-497239</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rumsfeld served as secretary of Defense under both Presidents Gerald Ford and George W. Bush.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China building 100+ new missile silos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-is-building-more-than-100-new-missile-silos-in-its-western-desert-analysts-say/ar-AALDiuX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite images point to a construction spree for ICBM launch tubes that could a signal a major expansion of Beijing’s nuclear capabilities, though some could be decoys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCUSERS SPEAK OUT: 'Serial rapist'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1002148/cosby-accusers-speak-out-against-injustice-after-conviction-is-overturned-hes-a-serial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much is Cabinet post worth?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/30/cabinet-post-bribery-banker-trial-497178</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bribery trial of Paul Manafort’s banker could hinge on a debate about the value of top federal jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phylicia Rashad Applauds: 'Terrible Wrong Being Righted'...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/30/phylicia-rashad-on-bill-cosbys-overturned-conviction-a-terrible-wrong-is-being-righted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 73-year-old Rashad, who played Clair Huxtable on the long-running "The Cosby Show," has long stood by Cosby throughout the slew of sexual assault allegations against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene therapy to regenerate cardiac muscle passes key test in pigs...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/30/gene-therapy-to-regenerate-cardiac-muscle-after-heart-attack-passes-key-test-in-pigs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The approach, described in a paper published Wednesday, led to new cell growth and improved heart function in pigs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundred Arrested For Setting Billionaire Neighborhood on Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wx5xam/arson-arrests-bahria-town-pakistan-billionaire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrested are mostly poor villagers who allege their land was grabbed to build the posh neighbourhood for Pakistan's rich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns ISIS still world threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2021/06/28/us-warns-that-islamic-state-extremists-still-a-world-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coalition is hoping to stabilize areas liberated from the Islamic State, repatriate and hold foreign fighters accountable and combat extremist messaging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Blames FAA After SPACEX Scrubs Falcon 9 Mission at Last Second...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/06/spacex-scrub-transporter2-satellite-launch-elon-musk-blame-faa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The current regulatory system is broken,” he tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Justices Seem To Think CDC's Eviction Moratorium Is Illegal. Supremes Left It in Place Anyway...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/30/at-least-5-justices-seem-to-think-the-cdcs-eviction-moratorium-is-illegal-scotus-left-it-in-place-anyway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brett Kavanaugh, who provided a crucial fifth vote, said he agrees that the CDC does not have the authority to override rental contracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz calls for inspector general probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/matt-gaetz-calls-inspector-general-investigation-tucker-carlson-nsa-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN TAUNTS USA, DECLARING WORLD DOMINANCE OVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15444852/putin-taunts-us-saying-their-world-dominance-is-over-threatens-to-strike-back-if-any-boundaries-are-crossed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUTIN has taunted the US, saying their world dominance is “over” and threatened to strike back if any “boundaries are crossed”. The Russian president issued the stark warning during a televised Q&amp;a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: DeSantis feuds with Trump over Florida rally amid condo collapse search...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/politics/desantis-feud-trump-florida-rally-condo-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  LA No Longer Worst Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2021/06/29/worst-traffic-los-angeles-new-york-newark/7803449002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles was ranked as having the worst traffic for over 28 years, but stay-at-home orders resulted in it no longer being at the top.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED and VICE 'Last Resort' Efforts to Go Public...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/buzzfeed-vice-spac-plans-1234975467/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the venture capital-funded digital media boom of the 2010s, startup founders often voiced world-conquering ambitions. In 2014, Vice Media co-founder Shane Smith bragged: “We won’t be the nex…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designer aims to build air-purifying car that you can meet, sleep and eat in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/30/thomas-heatherwick-on-his-an-air-purifying-airo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British designer Thomas Heatherwick tells CNBC that IM Motors is planning to build around 1 million Airo vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Break-Ins Skyrocketing In San Fran; Up 700% In Parts Of City...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/06/28/car-break-ins-skyrocketing-as-thieves-target-unsuspecting-tourists-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Car break-ins have skyrocketed in San Francisco, increasing by more than 700 percent in some parts of the city. With more people visiting after county and state restrictions were lifted, thieves are taking advantage of tourists by breaking into rental cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Miguel County Longest Life Expectancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/slideshows/longest-life-expectancy-by-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Average life expectancy is longest for people born in these 25 places in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S:  Home sales rebound to highest level since '05...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/30/may-home-sales-rebound-to-highest-level-since-2005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a surprising rebound, pending home sales jumped to the highest level since 2005.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Internet Is Rotting...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2021/06/the-internet-is-a-collective-hallucination/619320/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Too much has been lost already. The glue that holds humanity’s knowledge together is coming undone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA wildfire grows to 13,000 acres, threatens pot farms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/560873-california-wildfire-grows-to-13000-acres-threatens-marijuana-farms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of Northern California’s wildfires that erupted from mountain thunderstorms last week has grown to cover more than 13,000 acres as of Tuesday, potentially threatening a massive network of marijuana farms in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widower Seeking New Start in Florida Missing in Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2021-06-30/widower-seeking-new-start-in-florida-is-missing-in-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York City man bought a beachfront condo in Florida to start a new chapter of his life after his wife and parents died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark leaps out of water to bite parasailer!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3187570/sharks-leaps-water-bites-parasailers-foot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the shocking moment a shark leaps out of the water and bites a parasailer’s foot, at a resort in the Red Sea. Footage of the horrifying incident shows the tandem paraglider, a 37-year-old J…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first elderly sex robot with 'wrinkles and silver hair'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3182902/old-male-sex-robot-realdoll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN ‘ELDERLY male’ sex doll has been created by sex robot company RealDoll. The grey haired robot has been made at the request of a customer and was posted on the firm’s Instagram …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIANA BONES: Harrison Ford Shoulder Injury to Delay Filming 3 Months...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3184238/harrison-ford-signed-off-filming-indiana-jones-serious-injury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HE’S taken on the Nazis, overcome the evil Thuggee cult and found the Holy Grail. But when it comes to nasty shoulder injuries, Harrison Ford has had to finally admit defeat. I can exclusively reve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy's shock tests caused collapse?</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-06-29/shock-tests-condo-collapse-1995288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People continue to pine for answers after last week’s horrific condo collapse in Surfside, Fla. It may be weeks or months before the actual cause is known — but that doesn’t stop non-experts coming up with their own hypotheses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lava Fire erupts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/lava-fire-erupts-in-northern-california-amid-stifling-heat-wave/ar-AALAQpe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blaze has consumed more than 13,000 acres and may be a harbinger of a serious fire season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active-Duty Marine Plotted to Bomb DNC, Feds Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/right-wing-death-squad-active-duty-marine-plotted-to-bomb-dnc-murder-black-people-feds-say/ar-AALANYM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An active-duty U.S. Marine came under federal investigation for allegedly plotting with at least two others to assassinate minorities, drug users, and employees of the Democratic National Committee with explosives, rocket launchers, and automatic rifles. That’s according to a newly unsealed FBI search warrant affidavit obtained by The Daily Beast, which indicates USMC Private First Class Travis Owens and his partners in the unrealized murder...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Sue Me Like That: Anatomy of Copyright Troll...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/don-t-sue-me-like-that-anatomy-of-a-copyright-troll/ar-AALyIRK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How rock photographer Larry Philpot perfected a perfectly legal way to extract settlements from his images of Tom Petty, Willie Nelson, Ted Nugent, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENTLEY Tests Futuristic Biofuel By Climbing Pike's Peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/autos/news/bentley-s-renewable-fuel-continental-gt3-earns-2nd-place-pikes-peak-time-attack-finish/ar-AALypht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Driver Rhys Millen set out to break the Time Attack record, but a problem with the car -- and the course -- kept that from happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throwable military robots sent to assist...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Throwable-military-robots-sent-to-assist-with-16283702.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First responders on the ground at the Miami Beach-area condo that partially collapsed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines hopes all-female Coast Guard unit will keep Chinese ships away...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-Philippines-hopes-this-all-female-Coast-Guard-16283600.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With tensions rising in the South China Sea, the Philippines is turning to an unusual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal team expects charges in coming days...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-organization-charges-expected-manhattan-district-attorney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Organization's legal team anticipates the company will be accused of tax crimes, attorney Ronald Fischetti said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARINGS 20S: Inflation Eats at Surging Wages...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/inflation-eats-at-surging-u-s-wages-with-biden-agenda-at-stake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation Eats at Surging U.S. Wages With Biden Agenda at Stake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying car completes test flight between airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-57651843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vehicle runs on regular fuel and can travel up to 1,000km while airborne, its creator says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>112-year-old Puerto Rican Becomes World's Oldest Living Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/112-year-old-puerto-rican-becomes-world-s-oldest-living-man-01625048107</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emilio Flores Marquez from Puerto Rico has become the world's oldest living man at an age of 112 years and 326 days old, Guinness World Records announced on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whose rocket is bigger? How Musk, Branson, Bezos space stuff stacks up...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/musk-branson-and-bezos-in-race-to-conquer-space-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeff Bezos announced that he would fly into suborbit with his brother, the winner of an auctioned seat and another crew member on July 20, Richard Branson countered with a flight plan of his …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYTIMES editor says he suffered from burnout, wished for death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/ex-new-york-times-styles-editor-says-he-suffered-from-burnout-wished-for-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choire Sicha quit his high-profile job as editor of the New York Times Styles section in April because he was so burned out that he sometimes cried at work. In a recent blog post to promote a pal&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion grips NYC mayor race after vote 'discrepancy'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/29/eric-adams-narrowly-edges-garcia-in-preliminary-ranked-choice-results-boe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Borough President Eric Adams’ lead in the Democratic primary shrank to just two percentage points Tuesday as Kathryn Garcia vaulted past Maya Wiley into second place under …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA TURNS INTO DEATH VALLEY:  121-DEGREES!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scores-dead-heat-wave-grips-222446237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scores of deaths in Canada's Vancouver area are likely linked to a grueling heat wave, authorities said Tuesday, as the country recorded its highest ever temperature amid scorching conditions that extended to the US Pacific Northwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate ads by conservatives, for conservatives, shift views...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210630113113-dvenb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows online ads by leading political conservatives talking about their concerns about climate change boosted worry about the issue among other conservative voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: SUPPORT FOR JOE ERODES AMONG DEMS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210630084859-v7v7b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/POLL (POLL, PIX, GRAPHICS):POLL-Support for Biden erodes among Democrats as U.S. looks past pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart inflammation after shots higher-than-expected in military study...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210629173730-oxieu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-VACCINES (PIX):Heart inflammation after COVID-19 shots higher-than-expected in study of U.S. military</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satellite's impending fiery demise shows how important it is to keep space clean...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/satellites-impending-fiery-demise-shows-120052408.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small satellite is speeding to its demise in a test that could help clean up space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA SPYING ON TUCKER?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/tucker-carlson-nsa-spy-claim-jen-psaki-fox-news-1234783858/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency has given Tucker Carlson a lesson in spycraft and fake news. One which looks certain to crank up the volume in the now war of words, real and imagined. In a rare social…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Teen Drowned His Father In Pool To Baptize Him, 'Exorcise Demons'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/29/jack-callahan-duxbury-massachusetts-father-murder-exorcism-baptism-island-creek-pond-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Callahan was ordered held without bail after pleading not guilty to a murder charge Tuesday in Plymouth District Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice to World Premiere 'HALLOWEEN KILLS'...</title>
      <link>https://bloody-disgusting.com/movie/3672032/venice-world-premiere-halloween-kills-honor-jamie-lee-curtis-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bloody-disgusting.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first official reviews for Halloween Kills will arrive this September when the David Gordon Green-directed sequel World Premieres at the 78th Venice Film Festival, which runs September 1-11 on the Lido. The festival will this year award a Golden Lion for Lifetime Achievement to American actress Jamie Lee Curtis, add Deadline who says the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William, Harry to unveil Diana statue as royal rift simmers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-entertainment-royalty-50f64f8f06ef4a481fbafe1a93fb9558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — They were once so close. Princes William and Harry grew up together, supported each other after their mother’s untimely death and worked side by side as they began their royal duties — two brothers seemingly bonded for life by blood, tradition and tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error mars count...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eric-adams-lead-shrinks-nyc-democratic-mayor-primary-0c92450b5dbb57018e2f8e15d8471a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Democratic primary for mayor of New York City was thrown into a state of confusion Tuesday when election officials retracted their latest report on the vote count after realizing it had been corrupted by test data never cleared from a computer system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy dies after being repeatedly slammed in judo class...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-coaching-taiwan-judo-sports-47392a250cfb597c395f3a227889bc23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — A 7-year-old Taiwanese boy has died after being repeatedly slammed by his coach and others at a judo class. The boy, identified only by his surname, Huang, was taken off life support on Tuesday night after being in a coma since the April 21 incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKEDIN breach reportedly exposes data of 92% of users, including salaries...</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2021/06/29/linkedin-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;9to5mac.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second massive LinkedIn breach reportedly exposes the data of 700M users, which is more than 92% of the total 756M users. The database ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
