<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Mayor infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/atlanta-mayor-keisha-lance-bottoms-tests-positive-for-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"COVID-19 has literally hit home," Bottoms said in a tweet. "I have had NO symptoms and have tested positive."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania's former right hand coming out with another tell all...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2020/07/stephanie-winston-wolkoff-book-melania</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania’s former right hand will write, among other things, about her “abrupt and very public” departure from the East Wing after inauguration chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Capitol shutters after lawmaker tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/california-capitol-closes-after-l-a-lawmaker-tests-positive-for-covid-19/ar-BB16pl2Q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West company...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8494965/U-S-Treasury-small-businesses-took-pandemic-aid-says-51-1-mln-jobs-supported.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Monday revealed how a firehose of $521.4 billion in taxpayer cash washed across the landscape of America's small businesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent researcher of jihadi groups shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/06/middleeast/baghdad-iraq-hisham-al-hashimi-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prominent Iraqi expert on jihadi groups in the Middle East, including ISIS, was shot dead by unknown gunmen late Monday in front of his home in central Baghdad, media director of the Iraqi Ministry of Interior, Major General Saad Maan, told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign pupils must leave USA if classes go online...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/768c2bf5c9615a15a1397f4cd1c32500</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International students will be forced to leave the U.S. or transfer to another college if their schools offer classes entirely online this fall, under new guidelines issued Monday by federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White woman charged after racist Central Park confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/White-woman-charged-after-racist-Central-Park-15389218.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A white woman who called the police during a videotaped dispute with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's intel briefer breaks her silence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/06/trump-intelligence-briefer-breaks-silence-349936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In rare public remarks, the veteran intelligence officer tip-toed around the complexities of her job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit council staffer killed in apparent murder-suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2020/07/06/deandree-watson-detroit-policy-staffer-apparent-murder-suicide/5384803002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeAndree Watson, 30, was found shot to death in his vehicle on Sunday in Westland, the victim of what police called a murder-suicide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors warn country in 'free fall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/06/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With rates of infection soaring in most states, "we can't really keep going at this rate," one doctor says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia gov to deploy 1,000 National Guard troops after bloody weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/kemp-deploy-000-national-guard-troops-after-violent-weekend/nuGXOOMNsj0zkkoO9GLNPL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Of Investment Advisors, Portfolio Managers Received Bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/here-are-thousands-investment-advisors-and-portfolio-managers-who-received-bailout-grants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-year commitment!</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29418825/sources-chiefs-patrick-mahomes-agree-10-year-extension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chiefs and quarterback Patrick Mahomes have reached agreement on a 10-year contract extension that ties him to Kansas City through the 2031 season, league sources tell ESPN's Adam Schefter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech start-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/ppp-loans-to-tech-start-ups-bird-mixpanel-grindr-on-the-list.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several tech start-ups were among the companies that received loans under a program intended to blunt the economic damage from Covid-19, according to a list released Monday by the Trump Administration. Bird, Mixpanel, Grindr and Zendrive were on the list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political orgs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/coronavirus-stimulus-list-of-ppp-small-business-loan-recipients-released.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Paycheck Protection Program was set up as part of the CARES Act relief law to help companies retain employees during coronavirus lockdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick, DISNEY announce partnership deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/29417850/colin-kaepernick-disney-announce-partnership-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick will be featured in an exclusive docuseries produced by ESPN Films as part of a first-look deal with The Walt Disney Co. The deal between Kaepernick's production arm, Ra Vision Media, and Disney was announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit strip club linked to outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/wayne-county/2020/07/05/romulus-strip-club-linked-13-covid-19-cases/5381144002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virus cases of 12 patrons or staff at the Playhouse Club in Romulus and one Checkers employee have been linked to club, health department says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth management firms got bailouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/wealth-management-firms-have-taken-ppp-loans-amid-coronavirus-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many businesses, the government's PPP loans offered terms that were too good to pass up. That includes many wealth management firms across the country, according to government data. But whether those firms should have taken those loans is the subject of controversy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formula One drivers take knee, wear 'End Racism' shirts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/506038-formula-one-drivers-take-a-knee-wear-end-racism-shirts-at</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Formula One drivers wore shirts that said “End Racism” and took a knee ahead of Sunday's season-opening Austrian Grand Prix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids suffer mysterious brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/06/some-kids-suffer-mysterious-brain-damage-from-coronavirus-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus may be causing scary neurological issues in some children. Youth may help beat the novel virus itself, but kids may be more vulnerable to a secondary, brain damage-causing ailment w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals reserve tickets to NH rally to make venue look empty...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/liberals-reserve-tickets-trumps-nh-rally-try-making-venue-look-empty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group Blue Revolution is sharing an RSVP link to Trump's rally in Portsmouth, N.H. Saturday on social media telling followers to reserve spots and not show up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Camp Vows to Protect Brazil Iconic Statue From Left Wing Mobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-camp-vows-to-protect-brazils-most-iconic-statue-from-left-wing-mobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new ad warns that the famous Christ the Redeemer statue in Rio de Janeiro is under threat. It’s unclear if this is even true or how the president would actually save it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 million gig workers getting unemployment, 41% of the total...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/06/pua-unemployment-benefits-being-paid-to-about-13-million-americans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are about 13 million people getting unemployment benefits through a program meant for previously ineligible groups of workers, and the share is rising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Announces Kaepernick Docuseries Deal...</title>
      <link>https://espnpressroom.com/us/press-releases/2020/07/the-walt-disney-company-announces-overall-first-look-deal-with-colin-kaepernick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;espnpressroom.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASCAR 'TRUMP 2020' WRECK...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/06/corey-lajoie-nascar-trump-2020-brickyard-400-race-pit-road-wreck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Corey LaJoie's "Trump 2020" car barely made it out of the garage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. COVID DEATHS PASS 130,000... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2020/jul/06/coronavirus-live-news-india-sees-record-new-cases-as-texas-warns-of-overwhelmed-hospitals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s handling of US crisis under microscope; Israel reimposes restrictions after infections spike</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters boycott WHOLE FOODS over BLM masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1093168/boycott-whole-foods-black-lives-matter-masks-massachusetts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROTESTERS are boycotting a Cambridge Whole Foods after workers wearing Black Lives Matter masks were sent home, reports say. People have picketed outside the Massachusetts store every day since Ju…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami restaurants, gyms closing AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article244024192.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Noose' made of bread dough gets JIMMY JOHN'S workers fired...</title>
      <link>https://www.macon.com/news/nation-world/national/article244022002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel blamed for explosion at Iran nuclear site...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/israel-blamed-for-explosion-at-iran-nuclear-site-report-634013</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IRGC member told the 'NYT' that the possibility a cyberattack was behind the incident at Natanz has been ruled out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Expert Offer Grim Outlook:  'We'll Be Living With Masks For Years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/living-with-masks-for-years-covid-19-through-the-eyes-of-a-pandemic-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the summer of 2019, I've been speaking with one of the world's leading pandemic experts about what a global outbreak could look like. Now, as the world enters a grim new phase, he says we're in a whole new ball game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick Signs First-Look Deal With DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/colin-kaepernick-walt-disney-first-look-deal-espn-1234698911/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colin Kaepernick’s journey from San Francisco 49ers quarterback to civil-rights activist will be chronicled in a documentary series developed by ESPN Films as part of a first-look deal betwee…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House hopes Americans will grow numb to toll...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/923821/white-house-reportedly-hoping-americans-grow-numb-covid19-death-toll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As new COVID-19 cases and deaths continue to rise in the United States, White House officials are reportedly crossing their fingers that Americans will simply get used to it. President Trump's advisers are looking to 'reframe' his coronavirus pandemic response, and they want to 'convince Americans that they can live with the virus,' with White House officials hoping 'Americans will grow numb to the escalating death toll and learn to accept tens of thousands of new cases a day,' The Washington Post reports. One senior administration official said Americans will have to 'live with the virus being a threat,' while a former official told the Post, 'They're of the belief that people will get over it or if we stop highlighting it, the base will move on and the public will learn to accept 50,000 to 100,000 new cases a day.' Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, recently said the U.S. could soon reach this shockingly high number of 100,000 new cases a day while also warning that the final death toll will be 'very disturbing.' The U.S. has reported almost 130,000 deaths from COVID-19 and has been setting records for the number of new cases per day. NBC News similarly reports the White House is preparing a new message on COVID-19 that the country must 'learn to live with it.' Trump has faced a declining approval rating during the pandemic, with Bloomberg reporting on Monday that support for Trump 'is slipping fastest in the 500 counties where the number of cases have been more than 28 coronavirus deaths per 100,000 people.' Meanwhile, the Post reports that presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden's campaign plans to keep attacking Trump for his COVID-19 response, arguing that, as one adviser put it to the Post, 'the country would be in a much different place today ... if Joe Biden had been the president in January.' Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President slams Bubba Wallace over 'hoax'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/77f320f49331e17ca4ddce5ee4b3bed0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After a weekend spent stoking division, President Donald Trump on Monday blasted NASCAR for banning the Confederate flag and wrongly accused the sport's only Black driver, Bubba...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Struggles to Resume Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/as-pandemic-worsens-hollywood-struggles-to-salvage-reopening-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"For a big-budget studio film, COVID testing and safety could increase a budget by 15-20%," producer Shaun MacGillivray says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY'S BOOK NEXT WEEK</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/publisher-of-mary-trumps-book-pulls-release-date-forward-to-july-14-after-extraordinary-interest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Due to high demand and extraordinary interest in this book” by Trump’s niece it will now be published on July 14, the publisher says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West Used His 'Presidential Announcement' as Lure to Sell Merchandise Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/06/kanye-west-used-his-presidential-announcement-as-a-lure-to-sell-merchandise-online-this-afternoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West’s “presidential announcement” wasn’t followed up on Instagram with more information about his important campaign to make America great again. No, the next Instagr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SURVIVAL CONDO': Inside The Luxury Nuclear Bunker Protecting The Mega-Rich From Apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/features/inside-the-survival-condo-nuclear-bunker-protecting-the-ultrarich-hacking-the-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A climbing wall, a waterslide, a gun range... preparing for nuclear war just got deluxe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Employees More Trouble Than Worth...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/coronavirus/employers-find-testing-employees-more-trouble-than-its-worth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From nursing homes in New York and a landfill in Utah to Disney World and the Las Vegas Strip, employers are wrestling with workplace safety in the age of Covid-19 and making fraught calculations about how to safeguard both their businesses and their employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If She Tells All, Will Fallout Be Too Much Even For U.S. Government?</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/ghislaines-last-stand-if-epstein-s-accomplice-tells-all-will-the-fallout-be-too-much-even-for-u-s-8fc87089da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sensational arrest of Ghislaine Maxwell, alleged madam for sex fiend Jeffrey Epstein, is the end game in The Justice Department’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120 DAYS UNTIL VOTE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8513ec966d26d1c850e7cab0b269997c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Not long after noon on Feb. 6, President Donald Trump strode into the elegant East Room of the White House. The night before, his impeachment trial had ended with acquittal in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Anyone Watching QUIBI?</title>
      <link>https://www.vulture.com/2020/07/is-anyone-watching-quibi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vulture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming platform raised $1.75 billion and secured a roster of A-list talent, but it can’t get audiences to notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticking Time Bomb of HIV in Plagued South...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-ticking-time-bomb-of-hiv-in-covid-plagued-mississippi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dire situation in Mississippi—where disease surveillance for HIV has succumbed to coronavirus chaos—could send the larger region into a death spiral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How second half of 2020 could be even 'messier' than first...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-second-half-2020-pandemic-unemployment-election-20200706-nk6ji4s5x5buxozcj7ixwt7qea-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year 2020 hasn't been great, but here's how the rest of it could shape up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attacks Bubba Wallace...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8494303/Trump-launches-attack-Bubba-Wallace-demanding-NASCAR-star-apologize-noose-hoax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump launched an attack on Bubba Wallace, demanding the only Black NASCAR driver apologize to those who supported him when it was reported a noose had been found in his garage stall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions believe allergic to modern life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/04/millions-of-americans-believe-they-are-allergic-to-modern-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Welsh was a respiratory therapist living in Muskegon, Michigan, when, in the space of a few years, his life began to fall apart. It started when he developed an allergic reaction to certain f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: TRUMP APPROVAL 38%; RECORD PARTISAN GAP...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/313454/trump-job-approval-rating-steady-lower-level.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval rating remains lower than his earlier 2020 readings, with 38% currently approving of the job he is doing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How LINCOLN PROJECT got into his head...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/how-lincoln-project-anti-trump-republicans-got-his-head-spoiler-n1232669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With clever ads and searing social media attacks, the group has drawn notice. But what that means for the election is up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Crops Trump Out of Epstein, Maxwell Pic...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-crops-trump-out-of-jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-photo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News appeared to scrub President Donald Trump out of a photograph with Jeffrey Epstein on Sunday during the network's coverage on the arrest of Ghislane Maxwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Camp Sees 'Desperation' in Trump's Ever-Changing Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/biden-camp-sees-desperation-in-trump-s-ever-changing-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Camp Sees â€˜Desperationâ€™ in Trumpâ€™s Ever-Changing Attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for fewer laws...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/894138/case-fewer-laws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many Americans regard America as 'a nation of laws.' But, more and more, the United States is becoming a nation of too many laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo drags British royal family into scandal once again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/04/ghislaine-maxwell-kevin-spacey-once-sat-on-buckingham-palace-thrones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a newly surfaced 2002 photo, the just-captured accused Jeffrey Epstein madam sits on Queen Elizabeth II’s throne during a private Buckingham Palace tour — with actor Kevin Spacey at her side.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel launches spy satellite...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-satellite/israel-launches-spy-satellite-to-keep-a-better-eye-on-enemies-idUSKBN2470KK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel on Monday launched a new spy satellite that it said would provide high-quality surveillance for its military intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL: Clubs, bars, cultural shows, gyms closing immediately...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/coronavirus-israel-passes-30000-cases-634021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country passed 30,000 coronavirus cases on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Employees More Trouble Than Worth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/employers-find-testing-employees-more-trouble-than-it-s-worth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employers Find Testing Employees More Trouble Than Itâ€™s Worth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampa ICUs at maximum capacity...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/505959-four-tampa-area-hospitals-at-maximum-icu-capacity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four hospitals in the Tampa area were at maximum Intensive Care Unit capacity over the weekend as the number of coronavirus cases in Florida continued to spike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odds on Winning Slashed From 500/1 to 50/1...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/07/06/odds-on-kanye-becoming-president-slashed-from-500-1-to-50-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polls show it's more likely he would take votes away from Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway Star Dead at 41 After Long Battle...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/05/nick-cordero-broadway-star-of-waitress-and-a-bronx-tale-dead-at-41/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Broadway and music communities celebrated a man that many have worked with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When illness robs sense of smell...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-robs-sense-smell-032158364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris (AFP) - "What I miss most is the smell of my son when I kiss him, the smell of my wife's body," says Jean-Michel Maillard. Anosmia -- the loss of one's sense of smell -- may be an invisible handicap, but is psychologically difficult to live with and has no real treatment, he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt arrests doctors, silences critics over outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf9528ebff1d5dd7e3b95d467d7e9418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor arrested after writing an article about Egypt’s fragile health system. A pharmacist picked up from work after posting online about a shortage of protective gear. An editor taken from his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woof Warning: Dog alerts owner to house fire next door...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8994f0b665e68ff3607a554599ef5f97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKLIN, Tenn. (AP) — A dog in Tennessee became a hero on the Fourth of July by alerting her owner to a house fire next door. Roux, a 3-year-old Belgian Malinois, woke her owner Jeff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-connected lobbyists reap windfall in COVID-19 boom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2edf8670a491a702ecfb7312f507f83a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Forty lobbyists with ties to President Donald Trump helped clients secure more than $10 billion in federal coronavirus aid, among them five former administration officials whose...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Is the Statue Shit Going to Work?'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-wont-stfu-about-confederate-statues-heritage-as-advisers-wonder-is-the-statue-shit-going-to-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shockingly, there are some in Trump’s political orbit who aren’t convinced his strategy will move voters as much as he seems to think it will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China detains leading critic of President Xi...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/China-detains-leading-critic-of-President-Xi-15388052.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan - Chinese police on Monday seized the Tsinghua University professor and essayist Xu Zhangrun, silencing one of the last voices within China's besieged intellectual circles who dared to openly and persistently criticize President Xi Jinping's leadership.  Xu's arrest in Beijing's outskirts came five months after he published a lengthy essay pleading with political leaders to conduct an open investigation into the coverup of the covid-19 outbreak in Wuhan and reverse the country's spiral into tyranny. What began as a local outbreak was exacerbated by a political system that stifled whistleblowers and "a rot that goes right up to Beijing," Xu wrote in his February piece, which he predicted would be "the last piece I write."  Friends in Beijing, some speaking on the condition of anonymity for fear of reprisals, said Xu was taken away early Monday. A widely circulated statement on social media from Xu's friends, which could not be independently confirmed, said Xu's home was surrounded by 20 police officers, who took away Xu and his computer.  Tsinghua University's Law Department, where Xu taught constitutional law until he was demoted last year for his political writing, said Monday it was "not clear" about Xu's situation. Beijing's public security department declined to comment.  One friend who met Xu on Saturday said the professor was in high spirits as he gathered with friends after weeks of isolation; Xu had been barred from leaving his home during the politically sensitive month of June, when some dissidents commemorate the anniversary of the bloody Tiananmen Square crackdown in 1989, but did not seem to be under an unusual degree of pressure.  But Xu's arrest was not wholly unexpected, coming at a time when the Communist Party is forcefully reasserting itself not only globally - over territorial disputes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Support Withering in Hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-support-withering-in-areas-where-virus-cases-are-rising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Support Withering in Areas Where Virus Cases Are Rising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Employees More Trouble Than It's Worth...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-07-06/employers-find-testing-employees-more-trouble-than-it-s-worth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-ever online Paris fashion week clicks off...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-ever-online-paris-fashion-week-clicks-off-083935938.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris haute couture and men's fashion weeks have been rolled into one, with labels making films to showcase their clothes instead of staging sometimes extravagant shows. The virus has not just made the traditional catwalk format -- where a few hundred globetrotters are crammed into an overlit, overheated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Cam Newton Be Superman Again?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/06/can-cam-newton-be-superman-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Third-and-10 is traditionally a passing situation, but just outside the red zone on that down, Cam Newton took the shotgun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran claims built underground 'missile cities' along Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/iran-brags-that-new-missile-cities-are-nightmare-for-enemies-634017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments were made Sunday by Brig. Gen. Alireza Tangsiri who said that Iran has “underground cities which house vessels and missiles.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese city issues epidemic warnings for plague...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8493307/Chinese-city-issues-epidemic-warnings-PLAGUE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bubonic plague, known as the 'Black Death' in the Middle Ages, is one of the most devastating diseases in history, having killed around 100million people. The new case was found in Inner Mongolia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHANGED SOUND OF CINEMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-19626787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The versatile Italian composer's film scores that were an integral part of the cinema experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump base begins to crack?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/505926-juan-williams-trumps-base-begins-to-crack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPINION: Even white evangelicals are now having doubts about a president they have backed until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate outlook slides for GOP...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/505490-senate-outlook-slides-for-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are within striking distance of retaking the Senate majority in November as Republicans face an increasingly difficult electoral map.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENNIO MORRICONE DEAD IN ROME...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscar-winning-composer-ennio-morricone-dead-91-083845169.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ennio Morricone, one of the world's best-known and most prolific film composers, died in Rome on Monday at the age of 91. Morricone died in hospital where he was being treated for a fractured femur following a fall, according to a statement from a lawyer and family friend. A statement issued by</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash-Free Future Getting Closer...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/06/our-cash-free-future-is-getting-closer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — On a typical Sunday, patrons at Julien Cornu’s cheese shop used to load up on Camembert and chèvre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia to shut state border as Melbourne infections surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fdee12c97b5dba09feb1b4d9c362ec0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia (AP) — Australian authorities were preparing to close the border between the country's two largest states, as the country's second-largest city, Melbourne, recorded two deaths...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAESTRO OF SPAGHETTI WESTERN...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/66a1b5ad5716402a09dbcb4279cb1c00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Oscar-winning Italian composer Ennio Morricone, who created the coyote-howl theme for the iconic Spaghetti Western “The Good, the Bad and the Ugly” and often haunting soundtracks for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUB PARTY OF THE CENTURY</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12039335/second-coronavirus-wave-sunday-drinking-super-saturday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COP has warned of a second coronavirus wave after revellers carried on the party today after Super Saturday. The social distancing regulations were ignored by many partygoers as pubs and bars thr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL DISTANCING TURNS SOCIAL DRINKING IN LONDON!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8491821/English-drinkers-return-pubs-night-bar-closures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking footage from Millfields Park in Hackney captured dozens of partygoers as they gathered for a late-night rave in the capital on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UdkiB6dqbH4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;#trump #blacklivesmatter #trumpsupporters Trump Supporters Paint Over Black Lives Matter Mural. A couple attempt to paint out city sanctioned messaging on Co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 People Paint Over Black Lives Matter Mural...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/07/05/california-police-white-people-vandalized-black-lives-matter-mural/5381285002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are looking for two white people who vandalized a Black Lives Matter mural in downtown Martinez, California, on the Fourth of July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Duckworth emerges as serious contender...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Duckworth-emerges-as-contender-for-Biden-running-15387527.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As Joe Biden pushes ahead with his search for a running mate, Sen. Tammy Duckworth, D-Ill., has quietly emerged as a serious contender, according to three people with knowledge of the selection process, one of several developing dynamics as the search enters its final weeks.  Duckworth is a Purple Heart recipient and veteran of the Iraq War, the only finalist with military combat experience - and as a woman of Thai and Chinese descent, one of several candidates of color under consideration. While she has a lower profile than some rivals, she is being taken seriously by Biden's team, according to the people with knowledge of the search, one of whom said she has lately received strong consideration.  Former Senate majority leader Harry Reid, who has been in direct contact with the Biden campaign about its search, said in a recent interview that there was a "lot of attention" lately on Duckworth, whom he called "a highly decorated woman."  Reid suggested Duckworth's qualifications are getting more attention. "You had all the other names there, and it was as if she didn't exist," Reid said. "And suddenly people began to look at her - this highly decorated woman, member of Congress, senator."  Two others with knowledge of the search said Duckworth has been attracting notable interest from the campaign, including one who said Duckworth had left a strong impression on at least part of the Biden team. They spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private deliberations.  The Biden campaign declined to comment.  Duckworth's emergence comes as some Biden allies say former senator Chris Dodd, D-Conn., a close friend of Biden's, is taking a primary role in the search process. It is also unfolding as Republicans prepare to launch fierce attacks on whoever is chosen as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI nearly flubbed... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8492641/FBI-agents-blew-4-9M-covert-operation-storm-Ghislaine-Maxwells-New-Hampshire-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI agents preparing to storm the New Hampshire hideout of Ghislaine Maxwell, the former girlfriend of Jeffrey Epstein and alleged madam, nearly blew the $4.9M covert operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  As with all things Trump-related, there can be no middle ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Trump-turned-July-4-into-a-partisan-event-and-15387416.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, with two speeches in two days, has turned the Fourth of July from a joyful and unifying patriotic celebration of America's founding values into a partisan political event. The damage could outlast his presidency.  From near the base of Mount Rushmore on Friday night and from the South Lawn of the White House on Saturday night, Trump tried to write himself into the history of America as an implacable wartime president. His enemy, however, is not the Nazis of the 20th century or terrorists of the 21st century. Instead, it appears to be those in America who disagree with him - a caricatured blue America.  Trump knows his reelection campaign is in trouble. He sees the fight against this enemy of his creation as his pathway to victory in November. His political weapon of choice is exaggerated and at times racist rhetoric designed to pit Americans against Americans. Never in our lifetimes has the Independence Day holiday been used for such divisive and personal ends.  He put it this way on Friday night: "Our nation is witnessing a merciless campaign to wipe out our history, defame our heroes, erase our values and indoctrinate our children." On Saturday night, he said this: "We will never allow an angry mob to tear down our statues, erase our history, indoctrinate our children or trample on our freedoms. We will safeguard our values, traditions, customs and beliefs."  The president speaks for and to a portion of the country. People can debate how large or small his base is at this point, but the rhetoric of these recent days resonates as much as it divides. Political polarization is real. Identity politics - on both sides - is real.  The culture war, broadly defined, rages across the country, whether the issue is masks or statues. The pandemic seems to have added fuel to that bonfire, and the president...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Trends data shows 'Sleepy Joe' name-calling isn't generating buzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-biden-sleepy-joe-culture-wars-499e1334-4609-4fb6-ad6c-fd33c0054b55.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's quest for a viral attack line against Biden may be driving him to diverge even more politically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans leave large cities for suburban areas and rural towns...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/505944-americans-leave-large-cities-for-suburban-areas-and-rural-towns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several factors have forced residents to move from urban areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 men arrested after allegedly harassing Black family on beach...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/505945-7-men-arrested-after-allegedly-harassing-black-family-on-oregon-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Lincoln City, Ore., said this weekend that they arrested seven men on various charges after a group of white people they were a part of allegedly harassed a Black family on Independence Day by using racial s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring coronavirus cases, hospitalizations overshadow July 4 celebrations...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200705173724-gg24y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 2, GRAPHIC, PIX):UPDATE 2-Soaring U.S. coronavirus cases, hospitalizations overshadow July 4 celebrations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Invokes 'Fake News' Law to Defend Migrant Workers' Tests...</title>
      <link>https://crywnews.com/business/singapore-invokes-fake-news-law-to-defend-migrant-workers-tests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;crywnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore’s government defended its stand on the testing of migrant workers, the biggest cluster of its coronavirus outbreak, issuing five corrective directions under its fake-news [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Says Fire at Nuke Site Caused Significant Damage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fire-irans-natanz-nuclear-facility-172709822.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire at Iran's underground Natanz nuclear facility has caused significant damage that could slow the development of advanced centrifuges used to enrich uranium, an Iranian nuclear official said on Sunday. Iran's top security body said on Friday that the cause of the fire that broke out on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Deepens..</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6738eb091a5a26500f45c01d019c0fc9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran on Sunday confirmed that a damaged building at the underground Natanz nuclear site was a new centrifuge assembly center, the official IRNA news agency...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
