<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NASA chief latest official to suggest UFOs have otherworldly origins...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/579303-nasa-chief-bill-nelson-latest-official-to-suggest-ufos-have</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asked to speculate about the nature of recent UFO sightings , Bill Nelson responded, “Who am I to say that planet earth is the only location of a life form that is civilized and organized like ours?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spurns Catholic hospital appeal over trans patient...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211101134206-0348z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TRANSGENDER (PIX):U.S. Supreme Court spurns Catholic hospital appeal over transgender patient</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Pulls Episodes In Philippines Over South China Sea Map...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/netflix-pulls-episodes-in-philippines-over-south-china-sea-map-01635773408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has removed two episodes of an Australian spy show from its streaming service in the Philippines after Manila objected to scenes showing a map with Beijing's claims to the disputed South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL AFTER  AA CANCELS 2,000+ FLIGHTS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211101131805-m62o0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-AIRLINES/AMERICAN AIRLINE:American Airlines cancels more flights; total now over 2,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Stealth Drone Spotted Over Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/42949/secret-rq-180-stealth-drone-photographed-over-area-51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was the third photographic encounter with the secret flying wing drone, leaving little doubt as to its existence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Deprivation Affects Ability to Walk...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencetimes.com/articles/34264/20211101/sleep-deprivation-more-dangerous-thought-affects-ones-ability-walk.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's commonly known that deep deprivation has effects on one's physical and psychological health alike, and such effects are very negative if it is missing or disrupted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal contractors get broad flexibility to enforce jab order...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/01/federal-contractors-will-have-broad-flexibility-to-enforce-covid-vaccine-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the new guidance, federal contractors will have leeway to determine how they enforce the vaccination requirements for workers who refuse to be vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 70 years, Christmas trees were family business. Then came drought. And fire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/70-years-christmas-trees-were-120050307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For three generations, farming trees has brought joy and heartbreak. Now their livelihood is at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Souring view of president looms large...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/virginia-biden-mcauliffe-youngkin/2021/10/31/aa8c6d62-384b-11ec-8be3-e14aaacfa8ac_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Souring views of the president loom over hotly contested race for governor and signal trouble ahead for the party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL AFTER  AA CANCELS 2,000+ FLIGHTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/01/business/american-airlines-flight-cancellations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines has canceled another 250 flights Monday, continuing a days-long chain reaction of cancellations that started last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huma Abedin Has Been to Hell and Back. Now She's Gingerly Telling Tale...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/01/huma-abedin-has-been-to-hell-and-back-now-shes-gingerly-telling-the-tale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Huma Abedin was a young, single aide to Hillary Clinton, she was already a subject of great fascination. “Hillary’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Go back to L.A.': Urban transplants threaten to price out locals in SoCal desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/go-back-l-urban-transplants-threaten-price-locals-southern-california-rcna4153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once a hamlet for cowboys and homesteaders, the Morongo Basin is undergoing rapid change amid an influx of urbanites seeking to escape city life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Gulf Stream leads parade of 400 private jets into climate summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10152027/Hypocrite-airways-Jeff-Bezoss-48m-gulf-stream-leads-parade-400-private-jets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some activists at COP26 will be urging others to cut down on air travel, but apparently it is fine for billionaires to fly in on their own planes on routes already served by commercial airlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran SAFEWAY Cuts Hours Due To 'Off The Charts' Shoplifting...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/10/31/safeway-in-castro-cuts-hours-due-to-off-the-charts-shoplifting-its-sad-upsetting-and-frustrating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet another major retailer in San Francisco has made the decision to close earlier due to excessive theft particularly at night. The Castro Safeway on Market and Church Streets has cut back its hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis voters to decide on scrapping police dept after Floyd murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/minneapolis-voters-decide-scrapping-police-department-18-months-after-george-2021-10-31/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Harrelson points toward a blue angel painted on the pavement, marking the spot where a Minneapolis police officer murdered her nephew George Floyd and ignited a national police reform movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Charles, once dismissed as plant-talking oddball, takes environmental bona fides to COP26...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/prince-charles-once-dismissed-as-a-plant-talking-oddball-takes-his-environmental-bona-fides-to-cop26/ar-AAQbrrt </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisons face staff shortages as officers quit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-texas-prisons-d367722492d903e9299fd66ea3518998</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a Georgia state House of Representatives hearing on prison conditions in September, a corrections officer called in to testify, interrupting his shift to tell lawmakers how dire conditions had become.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Locks 34,000 Guests Inside DISNEYLAND for Covid Tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/locking-guests-inside-disneyland-shows-chinas-extreme-covid-tactics/ar-AAQaNOC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While thousands of visitors to Shanghai Disneyland on Sunday were queuing for roller coasters and watching fireworks above the fairytale castle, staff quietly sealed the amusement park. People in Hazmat suits streamed in through the gates, preparing to test everyone for Covid-19 before they could leave for the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Belies 'Best for Business' -- by Trailing California...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/texas-belies-best-for-business-by-trailing-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Belies `Best for Business' by Trailing Major States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS HALLOWEEN SPOOKED: FEAR VIRGINIA DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-richmond-campaigns-virginia-election-2020-484e32f4b802da309f4d8a62325b078b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin are set for a final day of campaigning at a frenetic pace ahead of Tuesday’s finale in the competitive and closely watched race for governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems face monster December collision...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/579209-democrats-face-monster-december-collision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are setting up a massive December cliff as they punt several key deadlines to the back of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Supersonic Air Travel Fly Again?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/01/can-supersonic-air-travel-fly-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the promise of two-hour flights from New York to Los Angeles, the supersonic airline industry never really got off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Chokes Up as He Praises Pope for Friendship...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/united-states/biden-chokes-up-as-he-praises-pope-francis-for-his-friendship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US President spoke passionately about the support the Pope has provided over the years.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABOR SHORTAGES LOOM FOR HOLIDAYS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/american-airlines-e2-80-99-canceled-flights-portend-messy-holiday-travel/ar-AAQaft7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The razor-thin staffing that contributed to thousands of canceled U.S. passenger flights in October doesn’t bode well for smooth holiday travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  AA CANCELS 2,000+ FLIGHTS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/e2-80-98deja-vu-all-over-again-e2-80-99-american-airlines-cancels-hundreds-more-flights-sunday/ar-AAQa25o?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines has canceled nearly 700 flights so far Sunday, adding to more than 1,000 already called off as the airline struggled to recover from slowed operations caused by weather on Thursday and Friday. Nearly a quarter of the mainline operations for the Fort Worth-based carrier were sidelined Sunday after major cancellations on Friday and Saturday were blamed on bad weather as far ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia's borders open up after 590 days!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10150569/Australians-hug-Sydney-Airport-quarantine-scrapped-international-flights-resume.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International travellers have embraced their loved ones for the first time in months after the first of the quarantine-free flights touched down at Sydney airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC PLAGUED BY CONFUSED MESSAGING ON BOOSTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cdc-messaging-coronavirus-masks-vaccines-boosters-212616596.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics say that the CDC has struggled to communicate clearly to the American people the fine points of late-stage pandemic policy, in particular when it comes to mask guidance and the need for booster shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian police kill 25 people in warlike operation against criminal group...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazilian-police-kill-25-people-in-warlike-operation-against-criminal-group/ar-AAQamVx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll Sunday underscored the extraordinary violence Brazilian police are willing to use during police operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Knifeman dressed as 'Joker' goes on train rampage in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/31/deranged-man-stabs-10-people-aboard-tokyo-commuter-train/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A knife-wielding man went on a crazed rampage aboard a Tokyo commuter train Sunday, stabbing at least 10 people and starting a fire before finally being taken into custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 5 million have died of covid since start of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/covid/2021-10-31/nearly-5-million-deaths-covid-19-pandemic-3442858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly a quarter billion cases of the coronavirus have been reported. Despite the rollout of vaccines, global health experts warn that the pandemic is set to continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST faces criticism for pilot's anti-Biden chant...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/southwest-airlines-to-investigate-pilot-s-purported-anti-biden-chant/ar-AAQ9xUx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Southwest does not condone Employees sharing their personal political opinions while on the job serving our Customers, especially when comments are divisive and offensive,” the airline said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26,000 NYC workers refusing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/nyc-vaccine-rule-may-leave-workers-unpaid-and-services-unmet/ar-AAQ9LPy?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) --</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Starts Moving Earth for Its Futuristic Linear City...</title>
      <link>https://www.arabianbusiness.com/industries-construction/470376-saudi-arabia-starts-moving-earth-for-its-futuristic-linear-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arabianbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Announced in 2017, Neom is the crown jewel of Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's programme to overhaul the economy of the world's largest oil exporter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Wants Proof $6 Billion Can Solve World Hunger...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-wants-proof-6-164343999.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elon Musk, the world’s richest man, challenged a United Nations official’s claim that just a small percentage of his wealth could help solve world hunger.Most Read from BloombergInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideCan a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?The Terrifying Rise of Haunted TourismThe Best New Restaurants in Washington, Chosen by Top ChefsIn Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing Is at StakeMusk was responding to comments by David Beasley,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS HALLOWEEN SPOOKED: FEAR VIRGINIA DISASTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-elections-virginia-terry-mcauliffe-b956177300be965ec34b1ddb75bb5042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — For four years, nothing rallied Democrats like the push to get Donald Trump out of office. Now, they're not sure what to do without him. Democrats in Virginia are scrambling to stave off disaster in the state's governor's race — the most competitive major election since Trump left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American B-1B bomber flies over Mideast amid Iran tensions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/africa-iran-israel-egypt-middle-east-b88f8ce6747fcb420ecea3e09ed856dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The U.S. Air Force said Sunday it flew a B-1B strategic bomber over key maritime chokepoints in the Mideast with allies including Israel amid ongoing tensions with Iran as its nuclear deal with world powers remains in tatters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Kaepernick copares NFL Draft to SLAVERY in new NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3969736/colin-kaepernick-nfl-draft-slavery-netflix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLIN Kaepernick has been branded “the lowest of the low” by outraged viewers after comparing the NFL Draft and training camp to SLAVERY in his new Netflix special. A clip from the form…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People Naturally Pessimistic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pessimism-naturally-optimistic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our experiments show that the method commonly used to evidence such optimism is flawed," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS LOW LIKE TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-poll-numbers-nbc-approval-960fec42-d0aa-4f0d-8a17-9191dfe37524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The numbers come as Biden tries to close the deal on a historic expansion of government.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
