<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI HERALD Journalist Sued by Epstein Victims...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-herald-journalist-julie-brown-235511651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo by Drew Angerer/Getty ImagesWhen Miami Herald reporter Julie K. Brown published her book on the Jeffrey Epstein case last year, she dedicated it to Courtney Wild and other victims of the wealthy sex-trafficker.Now Wild and fellow accuser Haley Robson are suing the star journalist, whose 2018 Herald series about Epstein’s shady plea deal for abusing scores of girls led to his indictment. The duo allege she defamed them in her book.In a stunning lawsuit, Wild and Robson say Brown published “</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Mayor called white cops 'crackers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/mayor-eric-adams-called-white-nypd-officers-crackers-in-2019/ar-AATu4KD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  Trump 'wrong' to say election could be overturned...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-elections-donald-trump-election-2020-electoral-college-84ff467d9ff5bfaad084e274f69ac521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Mike Pence on Friday directly rebutted Donald Trump's false claims that Pence somehow could have overturned the results of the 2020 election, saying that the former president was simply “wrong.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to gun down feral cattle spurs concern among ranchers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-travel-environment-and-nature-new-mexico-lifestyle-e968f6270da210b15313a6e98f6ad293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — A plan by U.S. Forest Service officials to put a dent in the population of feral cattle on national forest land near the New Mexico-Arizona border is drawing fire from ranchers who say gunning down the animals from helicopters is a violation of federal law and won’t help to solve the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staffers Move to Unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/02/04/congressional-staffers-launch-push-to-unionize-00005742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes one day after Speaker Nancy Pelosi endorsed a union, but the House and Senate would have to approve a right to codify a union by certain workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German anger as Russia shuts DEUTSCHE WELLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60257581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany and the EU condemn a decision to shut down Deutsche Welle's bureau in Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardi B Case May Have Ended Gossip Pages...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awqwp/what-does-cardi-bs-lawsuit-against-tasha-k-mean-for-youtubers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapper’s libel case against Tasha K will change the way the internet engages with attention-seeking celebrity commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti convicted of stealing $300K from Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/michael-avenatti-convicted-of-stealing-300k-from-stormy-daniels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney-turned-criminal Michael Avenatti was convicted Friday of swiping nearly $300,000 in book-advance money from his then-client Stormy Daniels. The now-twice-convicted felon — and one-ti…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JACKASS FOREVER' a 'masterpiece'? Critics rave 'tonic we all need'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/jackass-forever-reviews-1235087315/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics declare the latest stunt-filled gross-out spectacle "the tonic we all need" after years of pandemic and political division.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Shocked at California's 'Third World' Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/02/04/clueless-newsom-shocked-at-californias-third-world-conditions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor needs to leave his fancy Sacramento-area compound more often to see what's going on throughout the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin 'falls asleep' at Olympics as Ukraine team introduced...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/vladimir-putin-falls-asleep-at-beijing-olympics-as-ukrainian-team-is-introduced/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world leader was caught on camera slumped in his chair with his eyes closed as the athletes were introduced and their national anthem blared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC school lunch menu going vegan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-new-york-education-new-york-city-nyc-state-wire-bca2dcfd0dda46cb08160baf6ecfcc86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Forget mystery meat or cheese pizza. Instead, chickpea wraps and veggie tacos will be on the menu for New York City public school students as the nation's largest school district shifts to “Vegan Fridays” in school cafeterias.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perth police stop church service to check masks...</title>
      <link>https://7news.com.au/news/wa/community-furore-after-police-stop-st-bernadettes-glendalough-church-service-to-check-masks-c-5567846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;7news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Churchgoers were left stunned when their Thursday night service was halted by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SQUID GAME' VIBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3ab5d8/beijing-olympics-2022-bubble-winter-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those living inside China’s Winter Olympics bubble describe shopping malls for athletes and being served by robot waiters. The only catch—they can’t leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's security men: Elite group who 'fuel anxieties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/04/putin-security-elite-siloviki-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s growing isolation has strengthened the ‘siloviki’ who surround the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside community where pedophiles live surrounded by gator-infested waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4549320/miracle-village-restoration-destination-sex-offender-community-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HUNDREDS of sex offenders live in a 24-acre private, isolated community along a miles-long Florida road lined by gator-infested waters and surrounded by thousands of acres of sugar cane. The commun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC votes to censure Cheney, Kinzinger...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/592841-rnc-votes-to-censure-cheney-kinzinger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Committee (RNC) on Friday voted formally to censure both GOP Reps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES USED TO 'WHITEWASH' BRUTAL REGIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4614277/china-winter-olympics-torture-executions-human-rights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has been accused of using the Winter Olympics to try to “whitewash” the regime’s disturbing record of torture and executions. The world’s eyes have descended on Beijin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/discovery-ceo-david-zaslav-reveals-he-sees-cnn-as-the-leader-in-news-to-the-left</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive who is soon to take over CNN made a candid admission about where he sees the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC rapper gunned down hours after signing record contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/rapper-tdott-woo-shot-dead-in-brooklyn-reports-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Tdott Woo was shot and killed on Avenue L in Canarsie, Brooklyn on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How machines stole our privacy...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/how-covid-stole-our-privacy/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have outsourced morality to machines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW BOSS DECLARES: CNN LEADER 'IN NEWS TO THE LEFT'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/04/discovery-ceo-calls-cnn-leader-in-news-to-the-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discovery CEO David Zaslav made a frank admission regarding CNN’s ideology on Friday, describing the news network as the leading source for left-leaning viewpoints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Caliph Without a Caliphate...</title>
      <link>https://newlinesmag.com/reportage/a-caliph-without-a-caliphate-the-biography-of-isiss-new-leader/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newlinesmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents and pictures, made public in English by New Lines for the first time, that indicate Qardash was in fact a leading figure among Iraqi jihadist groups over the past two decades who has steadily worked his way up the security and religious hierarchy within the Islamic State group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEIJING PROJECTS POWER</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/winter-olympics/as-olympics-begin-beijing-projects-shared-future-of-undisputed-chinese-power/ar-AATtygT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside his secret life...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/who-abu-ibrahim-al-hashimi-26131550</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of the ISIS group has been killed during an overnight raid of north-western Syria by US special forces. Here’s what we know about Abu Ibrahim al-Hashimi al-Qurayshi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese security drags reporter away during live shot at Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2022/02/04/watch-chinese-security-thug-drags-dutch-reporter-away-during-live-shot-genocide-games/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch reporter was bodily dragged away by a Chinese security officer outside the arena during a live broadcast of the Beijing Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: A defense of bothsidesism...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/feature/opinion/1009757/a-defense-of-both-sides-thinking-about-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A call for equanimity in a polarized time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LABASH:  How highchair fight at the GOLDEN CORRAL is mirror for our souls...</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/high-steaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a highchair fight at the Golden Corral is a mirror for our souls (which aren't pretty)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tripling economists' forecast...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/coming-up-u-s-jobs-report-for-january-11643980058</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy added 467,000 jobs in January and hiring was much stronger at the end of 2021 than originally reported, indicating businesses did a better...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT COVID? JAN JOBS BLOWOUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/04/jobs-report-january-2020-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase 150,000 in January, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas-powered leaf blowers face moment of reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/gas-powered-leaf-blowers-face-a-moment-of-reckoning-205028611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outcry over leaf blowers has grown so loud that in October, California Gov. Gavin Newsom signed a bill that will spell an end to the use of gas-powered devices in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening Review: Propaganda Fireworks; NBC Balances Sports &amp; Geopolitics...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/02/opening-ceremony-beijing-olympics-2022-review-nbc-1234926598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOILER ALERT: This story contains details of this morning’s Beijing Olympics Opening Ceremony live on NBC. A Chinese-hosted Winter Olympics in the Year of the Tiger should having been roaring, ins…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW BOSS DECLARES: CNN LEADER IN NEWS 'TO THE LEFT'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/discovery-ceo-david-zaslav-reveals-he-sees-cnn-as-the-leader-in-news-to-the-left/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The executive who is soon to take over CNN made a candid admission about where he sees the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to dismantle bridge forr Bezos yacht sparks anger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-environment-and-nature-netherlands-north-sea-a24e8696be86eb3ae5f56d8e7a648c04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROTTERDAM, Netherlands (AP) — A plan to temporarily dismantle a recently restored historic bridge in the heart of Dutch port city Rotterdam so that a huge yacht, reportedly being built for Amazon founder Jeff Bezos, can get to the North Sea is unlikely to be plain sailing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Aggressive HIV Strain That Leads To AIDS Twice As Fast Discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/more-aggressive-hiv-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients with VB had a viral load between 3.5 and 5.5 times higher than the typical HIV strain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul promises investigation of Fauci if Republicans take Senate...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/592761-paul-promises-investigation-of-fauci-if-republicans-take-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul (R-Ky.) says he plans to subpoena Anthony Fauci's records if Republicans retake the Senate in November's midterm elections and he becomes chairman of a committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scandal on Wealthy Island: Priest, Murder, Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/04/scandal-on-a-wealthy-island-a-priest-a-murder-and-a-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not much happens of note on Shelter Island, all 8,000 bucolic acres of it. Sandwiched between Long Island’s North and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal and Corporate Tensions Collide After Exit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/04/at-cnn-personal-and-corporate-tensions-collide-after-jeff-zuckers-exit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One by one, the name-brand news anchors filed in: Wolf Blitzer, Jake Tapper, Dana Bash and some two dozen of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous testimonials about workplace culture grip Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2022/02/04/dear-white-staffers-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A viral Instagram account has become a safe space for congressional aides to anonymously call out lawmakers and share their experiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beating of 49ERS fan outside SoFi Stadium kept secret for days, raising questions as Super Bowl nears...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2022/02/03/sports/apparent-beating-of-49ers-fan-outside-sofi-stadium-kept-secret-for-days-raising-questions-as-super-bowl-nears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES &gt;&gt; Officials faced mounting questions today about why they didn’t inform the public about the apparent beating of a San Francisco 49ers fan outside SoFi Stadium on Sunday and whether more security measures are needed before the Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'highly virulent' HIV strain discovered in Netherlands...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/new-highly-virulent-strain-of-hiv-discovered-in-the-netherlands-2748390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oxford researchers announced Thursday the discovery of a highly virulent strain of HIV that has been lurking in the Netherlands for decades, but because of the effectiveness of modern treatments, is "no cause for alarm."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Meltdown' on Downing Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amid-e2-80-98meltdown-e2-80-99-on-downing-street-fifth-boris-johnson-aide-quits/ar-AATsCmP </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Americans united in worry over political divisions, but not much else...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/02/03/civility-downhill-biden-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civility has gone downhill since Biden took office, voters say in a new Georgetown University’s Institute of Politics and Public Service poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth the Steadfast: Queen marks 70 years on throne...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/queen-elizabeth-ii-70-years-ab40326fbd7bdca7a536ece0497f2da7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Elizabeth Alexandra Mary Windsor wasn’t born to wear the crown. But destiny intervened. The woman who became Queen Elizabeth II will mark 70 years on the throne Sunday, an unprecedented reign that has made her a symbol of stability as the United Kingdom navigated an age of uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS 'ghost' of leader was plotting comeback when U.S. commandos cornered him...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2022/02/03/islamic-states-ghost-of-a-leader-was-plotting-comeback-when-u-s-commandos-cornered-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abu Ibrahim al-Qurayshi was the second person to lead the Islamic State in its current incarnation, and his death was nearly identical to that of his predecessor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Fed, MIT unveil model for electronic cash as policymakers mull whether to launch it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/boston-fed-mit-unveil-model-for-electronic-cash-as-policymakers-mull-whether-to-launch-it/ar-AATs01l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot patrol dogs deployed on US border...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/terminator-dog-robots-deployed-border-26134041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users have reacted in terror to Ghost Robotic's metal dogs that have been deployed on the US border, as they resemble the robot from the 'Metalhead' episode of Netflix's Black Mirror</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalio Sees USA on Path to Civil War as Political Polarization Rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bridgewater-s-ray-dalio-sees-u-s-on-path-to-civil-war-as-political-polarization-rises-1.1718043</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ray Dalio warned Thursday that the U.S. appears to be on a “classic path” toward “some form” of a civil war amid a dangerous combination of large deficits, high taxes, inflation and gaps in wealth and values that lead to political polarization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games begin -- with lockdowns and boycotts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-begins-1c252fa7706cd54a083a46062fa7d321</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country where the coronavirus outbreak emerged two years ago launched a locked-down Winter Olympics on Friday, proudly projecting its might on the most global of stages even as some Western governments mounted a diplomatic boycott over the way China treats millions of its own people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Texts Say He 'Destroyed' Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jeff-zucker-cnn-legacy-leaked-texts-destroyed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Cover the news. Don’t f--- your subordinates. Jesus, how hard is that, anyway?” one former CNN staffer writes in leaked text</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blew self up?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4603497/isis-leader-the-professor-killed-by-us-special-ops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE leader of ISIS blew himself and his family up after using his own children as human shields during a bloody raid by US special forces, it emerged today.  ISIS boss Abu Ibrahim al-Hashimi a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$252,000,000,000 WIPED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/facebook-owner-meta-set-for-200-billion-wipeout-among-worst-in-market-history/ar-AATqEvu </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIGGEST IN HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/facebook-owner-meta-set-for-200-billion-wipeout-among-worst-in-market-history/ar-AATqEvu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil prices climb to new seven-year high above $91 a barrel...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/oil-prices-climb-to-new-seven-year-high-above-91-a-barrel-11643971736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crude prices are poised to gain more than 5% this week, as risks to U.S. and global crude supplies have driven higher prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCK BLAMES TIKTOK</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10471227/Facebook-loses-users-time-Zuckerberg-blames-TikTok-boom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook reported a nearly half-million drop in users during the last three months of 2021, with only 1.93 billion users logging in daily. Zuckerberg attributed the decline to the TikTok boom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE CRASH OF FACEBOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/facebook-shares-plummet-22percent-after-reporting-weak-guidance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other tech stocks were down Thursday following Facebook's plunge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China push back against USA in pre-Olympics summit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-putin-xi-meet-0e9127176250c0cab19b36e75800052e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin on Friday arrived in Beijing for the opening of the Winter Olympic Games amid growing Chinese support for Moscow in its dispute with Ukraine that threatens to break out into armed conflict</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'ISIS leader' killed in Syria raid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-says-us-raid-syria-killed-islamic-state-group-leader-ca598136de014e008f746a35f6f721b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATMEH, Syria (AP) — The leader of the Islamic State group blew himself up along with members of his family as American forces raided his Syria hideout Thursday, the U.S. said — the second time in three years the United States has taken out a leader of the violent group that has been struggling for resurgence with deadly attacks in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump facing multiple criminal investigations; Court buildings bracing for violence, chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/donald-trump-is-facing-multiple-criminal-investigations-for-his-conduct-court-buildings-are-bracing-for-violence-and-chaos/ar-AATrVPa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg net worth down $30 billion -- in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/mark-zuckerbergs-net-worth-fell-30-billion-as-meta-shares-tank.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 26% drop was Meta's biggest single-day plunge ever, and wiped more than $200 billion off of its market cap — also a record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP rockets as much as 57% on first-ever profit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/snap-q4-2021-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snap reported earnings for the fourth quarter Thursday that beat analyst estimates on earnings, revenue and user growth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
