<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico officials order governor, aides to hand over phones amid scandal...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190723230543-k5741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PUERTORICO/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Puerto Rico officials order governor, aides to hand over phones amid scandal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP MORGAN Warns: Dollar Could Lose Status As World's Dominant Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/jp-morgan-warns-dollar-could-lose-status-as-worlds-dominant-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's largest bank sounds alarm in face of skyrocketing debt, rise of China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Sheds $24 Billion in Value Days After Growth Miss...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/netflix-sheds-24-billion-value-six-days-growth-miss-1226463</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heavy volume of trading over the past nine days suggests many investors are cashing in on their big gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vowed millions of immigration arrests in dramatic raids. ICE caught 18 family members....</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/President-Trump-vowed-millions-of-immigration-14117006.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Donald Trump vowed to deport "millions" of immigrants from the United States, he was telegraphing an Immigration and Customs Enforcement operation that targeted migrants with final deportation orders. The real list had about 2,100 families on it, with the goal of deterring Central American migrants from trying to cross the southern border.  The final tally from the operation, according to federal officials: 18 family members were arrested, not enough to fit into a school bus. Immigration officials arrested another 17 undocumented immigrants they encountered in their searches, what are known as collateral arrests.  ICE announced the data Tuesday morning, tucking it into a news conference that included information about worksite enforcement and routine criminal arrests. Aside from the 35 immigrants apprehended in the much-anticipated family operation, immigration agents separately picked up nearly 900 adults - most of them convicted criminals - and delivered more than 3,000 notices to companies nationwide that authorities will audit their records to ensure that workers are in the United States legally.  Acting ICE Director Matthew Albence called the criminal operation successful and said the family operation, Operation Border Resolve, will continue, though the number of arrests were lower than in the past. The first such operation over New Year's weekend in 2016 under the Obama administration led to the arrests of 121 adults and children in Georgia, Texas and North Carolina.  Officials would not say where the arrests were made during the recent operation, nor when the operation took place, and immigration arrests are not public record. Families were not separated during the arrests, Albence said.  Albence said public blowback and publicity surrounding the raids likely dampened their numbers, but he said the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 HOUR GRILL ON HILL</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/in-high-stakes-mueller-hearing-there-are-big-risks-for-everyone-1.1290910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP STRATEGIST:  2020 WILL BE THISCLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/454323-top-strategist-projects-narrow-electoral-college-victory-for-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Democratic strategist on Tuesday projected his party would win a narrow Electoral College victory over President Trump if the election were held today, but cautioned that the contest could go either way depending on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAACP calls for Trump impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/454333-naacp-calls-for-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the NAACP are calling for President Trump's impeachment, the latest effort to push members of Congress to pursue impeachment against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE seeks tariff exemption after moving Mac production to China...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-seeks-mac-pro-parts-170038851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for Next China, a weekly email on where the nation stands now and where it's going next.Apple Inc. has asked the Trump administration to exclude components that make up the forthcoming Mac Pro high-end desktop computer from import tariffs, weeks after planning to re-locate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread investigation?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/90b8142ea4b84910a5cd4ad1923fa70b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER TAKES STAGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/868ccd3a04a94bf19afe40e4a9fc2e54</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2019/7/23/20707658/justice-department-antitrust-big-tech-review-google-apple-investigations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s separate from the Google and Apple investigations that were announced earlier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has College Gotten Too Easy?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/education/archive/2019/07/has-college-gotten-easier/594550/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time spent studying is down, but GPAs are up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  ONLY 35 ARRESTED IN ICE RAIDS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/more-than-2000-migrants-were-targeted-in-raids-35-were-arrested/ar-AAEJySW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malls filling empty spaces with doctor's offices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/07/23/business/mall-of-america-health-clinic/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As malls search for innovative ways to draw in shoppers and fill empty storefronts, they are turning to unexpected partners: health clinics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi blogger visiting Israel attacked by Palestinians at Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/saudi-blogger-visiting-israel-attacked-by-palestinians-at-temple-mount/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohammed Saud, a Netanyahu fan touring the country at the Foreign Ministry's invitation, is heckled, spat on and has chairs hurled at him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3-legged bear scares Florida neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article233009297.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New implant, vaccine trial offer fresh HIV hope...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190723-new-implant-vaccine-trial-offer-fresh-hiv-hope</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New implant, vaccine trial offer fresh HIV hope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paleo 'caveman' diet linked to heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/health-med-fit-science/paleo-caveman-diet-linked-heart-disease-biomarker-study-finds/nhpqZohLPYSntwe4CdB55H/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Paleolithic diet, also known as the caveman regimen, is touted for improving gut health. But those who follow the Paleo diet may have twice the amount of a key blood biomarker closely associated with heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  'Anonymous' data not so anonymous...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/anonymous-data-might-not-be-so-anonymous-study-shows-n1033111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers’ model suggests that more than 99 percent of Americans could be correctly re-identified from any dataset using 15 demographic attributes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Asks for Aide to Appear as Witness During Hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mueller-asks-for-aide-to-appear-as-witness-during-hearings/ar-AAEKHnU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asked Justice Dept for letter limiting testimony to 'boundaries' of report...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/barr-mueller-asked-doj-to-send-him-letter-saying-testimony-must-remain-within-boundaries-of-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Bill Barr told Fox News on Tuesday that it was former Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s team who asked the Justice Department to send Mueller a letter telling him to keep his upcoming testimony to House lawmakers "within the boundaries" of the public version of his Russia probe report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC: FACEBOOK deceived about facial-recognition...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/07/23/facebook-deceived-users-about-way-it-used-phone-numbers-facial-recognition-ftc-allege-complaint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FTC will allege Facebook was not clear that advertisers could target users who submitted their numbers as part of a security feature and will contend that Facebook gave some people inadequate information about ways to opt out of some facial recognition features. It will not, however, require Facebook to admit guilt, the sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sues NY AG, House committee to block tax return disclosure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/23/trump-sues-house-ways-and-means-panel-to-block-disclosure-of-his-tax-returns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump filed a lawsuit against the House Ways and Means Committee, the New York state's attorney general and tax chief to block the disclosure of years of his tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Israeli PM apologizes for killing of Arab protesters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/afaa016de0ff4b2ba37d16113e1d233c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CENTCOM: May have downed more Iranian drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/centcom-commander-kenneth-mckenzie-suggests-us-brought-down-more-than-one-iranian-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an interview with CBS News' David Martin, CENTCOM commander Gen. Kenneth McKenzie suggested there were possibly two drones downed in the incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probe opened in France over radioactive water rumors...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/probe-opened-france-over-radioactive-water-rumours-101329786.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the panic, the prosecution: investigators in Paris have opened an enquiry to track down the source of false reports last week that drinking water in the French capital had been contaminated. In a viral message spread on the WhatsApp messaging app last week, a woman presenting herself as a nurse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker: My Testosterone Makes Me Want To Punch Trump...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/booker-my-testosterone-sometimes-makes-me-want-to-feel-like-punching-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate and Sen. Cory Booker (N.J.) on Tuesday said his testosterone sometimes makes him want to "feel like punching" President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO: Schools denied my offer after warning on lunch bills...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d08cb7de39e849e08943def345d9a4ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Prepping Troops for Laser, Electromagnetic Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/07/air-force-wants-simulated-wargames-plan-lasers-electro-magnetic-weapons/158589/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wargames are meant to teach airmen about these new weapons and help the Air Force develop new tactics and procedures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. willing to offer Maduro deal if he leaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article232964207.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six-year-old does record 4,183 push-ups...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7273895/Chechen-Schwarzenegger-Rahim-Kurayev-6-breaks-two-press-world-records-Grozny-Chechnya.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rahim Kurayev drew a large audience when he went onto Chechen state television in Grozny to attempt the world records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH OF 'TEA PARTY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/gop-repeals-entire-legacy-tea-party-one-fell-swoop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raising spending 20 percent over 2017 — and not a dime for the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE WATERS: Impeachment First, Prison Next...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/07/22/maxine-waters-impeachment-first-prison-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) on Monday evening predicted that Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s appearance before Congress on Wednesday will give Democrats “the ammunition” they need to “start impeachment immediately.” | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Robot Photographer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-22/robot-photographer-snaps-products-at-a-warehouse-in-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris chaotic path to power...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b48561749c65479fbadbcdc35808343a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straight Pride Parade In California?</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/07/22/city-of-modesto-straight-pride-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Modesto is considering awarding a permit for a straight pride march in a local park and residents have mixed reviews on the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Explanation From NASA Over Large, Low-Flying Jetliner Buzzing Over LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/23/altadena-nasa-plane-flying-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The large DC-8, painted white with a blue stripe and the NASA logo on the tail, was spotted flying over Altadena at the height of afternoon rush hour in the San Gabriel Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KING OF NEWS RATINGS; NEARLY 8 MILLION VIEWERS A NIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/186493604356/world-news-tonight-with-david-muir-wins-across</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘World News Tonight’ Out Delivers NBC by 1 Million Viewers and CBS by 2.6 Million for the Week David Muir Anchors Live for the First Time Ever From Apollo 11 Mission Control Season to Date ‘World News...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico sets murder record...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c197a3ee34834ea69f745975fa632ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man rides electric scooter on Dallas highway during rush hour...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox4news.com/news/dash-camera-captures-lime-scooter-rider-on-i-35-in-downtown-dallas-during-rush-hour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox4news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers expect traffic on I-35 during the morning commute in Dallas. But dash camera video captured by one driver showed something different – a man zipping up the interstate on an electric rental scooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Film Fest Unveils Star-Studded Slate...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/toronto-film-festival-2019-lineup-mister-rogers-joker-judy-garland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIFF's formidable lineup of directors will include Steven Soderbergh, Noah Baumbach, Taika Waititi, Rian Johnson, John Crowley ... and Bruce Springsteen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The president's silent spokeswoman...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/07/23/trump-spokeswoman-stephanie-grisham-1426697</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one of the most fiery months of the Trump presidency, the new press secretary has had very little to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QB Mark Sanchez retires from NFL for high-profile ESPN job...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/23/mark-sanchez-retires-from-nfl-for-high-profile-espn-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quarterback Mark Sanchez is putting away his helmet and heading to ABC/ESPN to be a college football analyst, The Post has learned. Sources tell The Post the former Jets quarterback’s main job will…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muir reflects on letting people tell story, keeping public's trust...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/lifestyle/article/David-Muir-reflects-on-letting-people-tell-their-14116070.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Muir, 45, is the anchor of ABC's "World News With David Muir" and co-anchor of its newsmagazine, "20/20." Muir has won the Edward R. Murrow Award for his reporting at home and abroad.  - - -  A: I was a total nerd. [Laughs.] I was the kid in the backyard who would be playing with everybody else, but then would excuse myself to go inside to watch the news every night - the local news, and then Peter Jennings.  A: Everybody knew. Which played into that whole nerd status. I even remember trying to guess on Fridays who the Person of the Week was, because oftentimes Peter would provide a clue throughout the newscast.  I started writing to local news reporters in town when I was 13; I remember racing out to the mailbox at the end of the driveway to see if someone had written me back. One of the anchors, who was considered, you know, the Walter Cronkite of my hometown, wrote back. I still have the typewritten letter with that giant newsroom font. The last line said something along the lines of, "Competition in television news is keen. There's always room for the right person. It could be you." After that, I set up a visit at that TV station, and then began interning at 14, carrying the tripods and equipment. I was so happy to be doing that. And to this day I am grateful to those photographers and reporters who let me bum around in the back seat of that cruiser.  A; I think about it every day, to be honest with you. I'm fully aware that when I go upstairs - that same stairwell that Peter [Jennings] took and Charlie [Gibson] took and Diane [Sawyer] took - and walk up to that desk, that I'm having a conversation with America in a very polarized time. And it has evolved quickly into a two-way conversation - through social media and all the tools we have to reach out to the audience and for them to let us know in an instant...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never-Googlers: Web users take ultimate step to guard data...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Never-Googlers-Web-users-take-the-ultimate-step-14116157.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - In the small South Carolina town of Newberry, Bob's Red Mill muesli cereal is hard to come by.  That presents a challenge for resident Gregory Kelly, who can't get enough of the stuff. He'd rather not truck the 40 miles or so to Columbia to stock up on it, but he's also loath to buy it from the company's website, which he says is riddled with tracking software from Google.  His privacy being paramount, Kelly grudgingly chooses to head into Columbia every so often, rather than cede his data to Google or turn over his purchase history to another online retailer. "I'm just not sure why Google needs to know what breakfast cereal I eat," the 51-year-old said.  Kelly is one of a hearty few who are taking the ultimate step to keep their files and online life safe from prying eyes: turning off Google entirely. That means eschewing some of the most popular services on the Web, including Gmail, Google search, Google Maps, the Chrome browser, Android mobile operating software and even YouTube.  Such never-Googlers are pushing friends and family to give up the search and advertising titan, while others are taking to social media to get word out. Online guides have sprouted up to help consumers untangle themselves from Google.  These intrepid Web users say they'd rather deal with daily inconveniences than give up more of their data. That means setting up permanent vacation responders on Gmail and telling friends to resend files or video links that don't require Google software. More than that, it takes a lot of discipline.  People like Kelly are trying to build barriers to Google and other tech giants largely due to increasing concerns about the massive data collection. A series of privacy scandals showing how these companies collect and use consumer data has raised alarm bells for many people about how much they've...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vin Diesel body double seriously injured in shoot for 'FAST &amp; FURIOUS 9'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7275667/Pictured-Vin-Diesels-Fast-Furious-body-double-fighting-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British stuntman Joe Watts is in hospital battling a serious head injury after plunging 30ft at the Warner Bros Studios in Hertfordshire, on the set of Fast and Furious 9 in front of Vin Diesel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STALLONE: IT STILL STINGS...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/features/sylvester-stallone-rocky-ownership-stake-1203275639/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sylvester Stallone shares an uncanny, symbiotic connection with Rocky, the underdog boxer character he created four decades ago — a kindred spirit who served as his creative muse in spawning one of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director debating third 'KILL BILL'?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/07/23/quentin-tarantino-admits-talking-third-kill-bill-movie-uma-thurman-10444282/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will The Bride be back?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBS CEO Warns of 'Dangerous' Bubbles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ubs-ceo-warns-dangerous-bubbles-094125375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- UBS Group AG’s chief executive officer is sounding the alarm on fresh monetary easing just as European policy makers appear poised to deliver another helping to stimulus-hungry markets.“I’d be very, very careful about growing further the balance sheet of central banks,’’ Sergio Ermotti</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Russian-Chinese air patrol in Asia-Pacific draws shots from SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-southkorea-russia-aircraft/first-russian-chinese-air-patrol-in-asia-pacific-draws-shots-from-south-korea-idUSKCN1UI072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia carried out what it said was its first long-range joint air patrol in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Hong Kong police face protester anger, some would rather be on other side...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-Hong-Kong-police-face-protester-anger-some-14115723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG - The 29-year-old police officer was nearing the 24th hour of his shift last month, standing with his unit between a throng of protesters and Hong Kong's most important government building, when the order came down: It was time to escalate.  Edward suited up. He donned his gas mask as officers readied tear-gas canisters.  The stinging clouds came thick and fast, along with rounds of rubber bullets. The crowd scattered. Officers rushed masked young protesters, thumping them with batons.  He did not want to follow those orders on June 12. This was not the side he wanted to be on.  Five years ago, Edward was camped out with other protesters on Hong Kong streets, calling for free elections. Those demonstrations failed to achieve their aims but invigorated a generation of young activists frustrated by China's refusal to grant the semiautonomous city full democracy.  This time, Edward - who joined the force in 2015 because of the relatively high salaries - has been an officer stationed on the front lines of almost every major protest during weeks of anti-government demonstrations in Hong Kong.  "I didn't expect I would ever be standing opposite to the action," said Edward, who wanted to be identified by only his first name because he was not authorized to speak to the media. "I understand the protesters. Really, I feel like I am one of them."  Once known as "Asia's Finest," the Hong Kong Police Force has been caught between a furious public - angered by officials' plans to allow extraditions to mainland China - and Hong Kong's pro-Beijing government.  The police have faced intense criticism of their tactics, from the use of tear gas and rubber bullets to tardiness in responding to emergency calls when an armed gang attacked people returning from a demonstration late...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENTIRE Bay Area sees homelessness surge...</title>
      <link>https://sf.curbed.com/2019/7/22/20704224/bay-area-point-in-time-homless-count-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sf.curbed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neighboring counties saw 2019 homeless levels increase more than San Francisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela blames 'electromagnetic attack' for blackout... Developing... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-lights-coming-back-life-121544879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lights were returning to life across Venezuela on Tuesday following a massive blackout that crippled communications, froze the Caracas metro and snarled rush hour traffic, officials said. Energy Minister Freddy Brito said power had been restored in the capital of Caracas and at least five of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals push back on #MeToo after backfire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/al-frankens-sexual-assault-is-what-metoo-was-created-to-address-and-now-liberals-feel-victimized-by-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats and liberals in the news media have found a sudden nuance when defining “sexual misconduct,” though the concept was conveniently a lot more clear-cut when a Supreme Court seat was on the line just 10 months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR RAGE: Passenger smashes laptop over 'boyfriend's' head on packed plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9563513/passenger-smashes-laptop-over-boyfriends-head-on-packed-plane-because-he-looked-at-other-woman/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN flew into a rage on flight and lamped her boyfriend with a laptop for “looking at other women”. The raging passenger can be seen berating her partner on board the packed plane before things…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 35 People Detained in ICE Raids...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ice-raids-just-35-people-detained-in-trump-raids-targeting-thousands-of-migrants-last-week-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The widely publicized raids appear to have been hampered by their pre-announcement by President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Spicy Diet Linked To Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mild-sauce-clear-mind-spicy-diet-linked-to-dementia-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's something to consider the next time you're thinking about ordering a spicy dish: a new long-term international study has found that a spicy diet could lead to dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brexit by Halloween?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-leader/britains-new-leader-johnson-vows-to-get-brexit-done-idUSKCN1UH2JQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson, the ebullient Brexiteer who has promised to lead Britain out of t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare moment man from 'world's most endangered tribe' filmed hunting in Amazon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/793564/Amazon-rainforest-tribesman-Awa-uncontacted-hunting-rare-footage-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Getting Harder to Fire People for Using Pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/it-s-getting-harder-to-fire-people-for-using-pot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Itâ€™s Getting Harder to Fire People for Using Pot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe gears up for record-breaking heatwave...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/europe-gears-record-breaking-heatwave-114020296.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France and western Europe were Tuesday bracing for a new record-breaking heatwave that is forcing the temporary shutdown of a French nuclear power station and will test competitors in the legendary Tour de France cycle race. Forecasters predicted new temperatures highs in a string of countries, including</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HERE COMES BORIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9563529/boris-johnson-new-uk-prime-minister-jeremy-hunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson will be Britain’s next Prime Minister after defeating Jeremy Hunt in a landslide victory to be declared the new Tory leader today. The incoming PM will have just 100 days to del…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOLLYWOOD' Frenzy in Heart of Tinseltown...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/inside-once-a-time-hollywood-premiere-quentin-tarantino-1226164</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director's ninth film premiered in the heart of Tinseltown, shutting down traffic on Hollywood Boulevard where fans and A-list stars like Chris Hemsworth and Britney Spears contributed to the frenzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea fires 360 rounds of warning shots at Russian warplane...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a7b5969087e7408baaa65a0e4f16968c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel vote will expose Dem divisions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/454232-israel-vote-will-expose-democratic-divisions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is slated to pass legislation Tuesday to oppose the global boycott movement against Israel, a vote that will put a spotlight both on Democratic divisions and Rep. Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana policemen fired after suggesting Ocasio-Cortez  needed to be shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-politics-aoc-threat/louisiana-policemen-fired-over-facebook-post-suggesting-ocasio-cortez-be-shot-idUSKCN1UH2JI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Louisiana policeman who suggested on Facebook that high-profile U.S. Represent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren warns of 'coming economic crash'...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@teamwarren/355703da148b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Elizabeth Warren</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEAL KEEPS LIGHTS ON</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b72be6c420bb478ea469da72c73065e2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
