<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Site Holy to Jews and Muslims Returns as Nexus of Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/a-site-holy-to-jews-and-muslims-returns-as-the-nexus-of-conflict/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Clashes broke out Friday for the seventh time in eight days at the holiest site in Jerusalem, foregrounding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrecy, sex and sun: Captain reveals life aboard superyachts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/news/2022/apr/22/secrecy-sex-and-sun-captain-reveals-life-aboard-superyachts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaires’ excesses are under scrutiny like never before after Russia’s invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA STRIPS DISNEY</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10744543/Florida-Gov-Ron-DeSantis-officially-STRIPS-Disney-55-year-old-special-privileges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor wrote into law the plan which scrapped the Reedy Creek Improvement District on Friday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like fingerprints at crime scene': Study finds new clues about causes of cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2022/apr/22/like-fingerprints-at-a-scene-study-finds-new-clues-about-causes-of-cancer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For first time it is possible to detect patterns in cancers’ DNA – opening up to possible personalised treatments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAWTHORN IN DRAG: Photos reveal rep wearing women's lingerie in public setting...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/22/madison-cawthorn-photos-00027286</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The embattled congressman has outraged Republican colleagues with accusations of orgies and drug use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Posts Graphic Showing Grave of CNN+, Ghost of Former Anchor Wallace...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/fox-news-posts-nuts-graphic-showing-grave-of-cnn-and-ghost-of-former-anchor-chris-wallace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News shared an Instagram showing the animated grave of CNN+ as ghosts of several of the platform's hosts, including Chris Wallace, bounced around it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army To Test Biggest Interactive Drone Swarm Ever Over Utah...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/army-to-test-its-biggest-interactive-drone-swarm-ever-over-utah</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mix of drones, most launched from aircraft, will swarm enemy positions and soften up the landing zone for a behind enemy lines air assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodyguards status symbol amid Venezuela's crime and poverty...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bodyguards-status-symbol-amid-venezuelas-015726250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a rich neighborhood east of Caracas, a bodyguard flashes his rifle as a private armored car with dark tinted windows speeds away under his intimidating watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, EU Looking at Ways to Slash Vlad's Oil Money...</title>
      <link>https://au.finance.yahoo.com/news/u-eu-looking-ways-slash-193913489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. officials and the European Union are in talks over steps the EU could take to restrict oil imports from Russia and cut the income that Moscow makes from sales, according to people familiar with the matter.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Latest: UN Chief to See Putin; Russia Aims for SouthThe Second Wave of the Russian Oil Shock Is StartingU.S. Blasts China’s Support for Russia, Vows to Help IndiaKremlin Insiders Alarmed Over Growing Toll of Putin’s War in UkraineUkraine Lates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron extends lead...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/macron-extends-poll-lead-over-le-pen-as-high-stakes-french-presidential-campaigns-end/ar-AAWuqzi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows Was Registered to Vote in 3 Different States...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/mark-meadows-was-registered-to-vote-in-3-different-states-at-the-same-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until last week, Mark Meadows and his wife were simultaneously registered to vote in North Carolina, South Carolina and Virginia, the Washington Post reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA STRIPS DISNEY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/22/politics/desantis-disney-congressional-map-anti-crt-bill/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW plunges more than 900 points; Fourth straight weekly loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/21/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks sank on Friday, putting the Dow and S&amp;P 500 on pace for consecutive weekly declines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban vows crackdown on ISIS as violence surges in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2022/04/22/world/taliban-vows-crackdown-isis-violence-surges-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A four-day blitz of terrorist bombings across Afghanistan has left the country reeling after months of relative calm, raising fears that the Taliban will be unable to maintain the peace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians clash with Israeli police at Jerusalem holy site, 57 injured...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/palestinians-clash-israeli-police-jerusalem-074312744.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (Reuters) -At least 57 Palestinians were injured in clashes with Israeli police within Al-Aqsa mosque compound in Jerusalem on Friday, medics said, as violence persisted during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan at a site also revered by Jews. Israeli police said they intervened when hundreds of people hurled rocks and fireworks and drew close to the Western Wall, where Jewish worship was underway. Reuters witnesses said police entered the compound after the morning Ramadan prayers and fired rubber-tipped bullets and stun grenades at a crowd, some of whom were throwing rocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandates return to college campuses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-new-york-education-pennsylvania-04bea7874bb2351e71525f3068758a19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final weeks of the college school year have been disrupted yet again by COVID-19 as universities bring back mask mandates, switch to online classes and scale back large gatherings in response to upticks in coronavirus infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: FRANCE DECIDES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-french-election-final-campaign-day-4fe9b1f74244f869ff18e46e611fec6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — The finalists for France’s presidency, President Emmanuel Macron and far-right leader Marine Le Pen, traded blows on the last day of campaigning Friday as they tried to convince undecided voters why their political agenda — and not their rival's — is the right choice .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas vows to escalate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/hamas-says-its-ready-to-escalate-fighting-as-jerusalem-tensions-soar/ar-AAWri9p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabled vet pleads guilty in border-wall scheme that included Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/disabled-vet-pleads-guilty-in-border-wall-scheme-that-included-bannon/ar-AAWsQ8U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Project X' for TWITTER takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-signals-with-46-5-billion-he-s-serious-about-buying-twitter/ar-AAWs13b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half world's population has headaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/half-the-worlds-population-has-headaches-women-more-than-men-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study found that women suffer from headache disorders more than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lie Puts Hypocrisy on Display...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/mccarthys-lie-puts-g-o-p-hypocrisy-on-trump-on-display/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Representative Kevin McCarthy’s denial of disparaging comments he made about President Donald J. Trump after the Capitol attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Denies 'Insurrectionist' Charge in Court...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/marjorie-taylor-greene-denies-insurrectionist-charge-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene, Republican of Georgia, on Friday repeated false claims of widespread fraud in the 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Madison's Montpelier, Fight Over Power for Slaves' Descendants...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/at-madisons-montpelier-a-fight-over-power-for-slaves-descendants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year, the foundation that runs the sprawling Virginia estate that was the home of President James Madison announced what</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN POLL SLUMP CONTINUES; SECOND LOWEST OF MODERN ERA...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/391973/biden-job-approval-stuck-low-40s.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's job approval rating averaged 41.3% during his fifth quarter, the second-lowest for an elected, post-World War II president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE DON:  WE'RE GOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/why-trump-might-give-mccarthy-a-pass-on-jan-6/ar-AAWuuMd?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of NYC teachers investigated over fake vax cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-teachers-fake-vaccine-cards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of New York City teachers face unpaid leave as they are investigated for allegedly using fake vaccine cards to stay in the classroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone-Tracking Firm Demo'd Surveillance Powers --  by Spying on CIA, NSA!</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2022/04/22/anomaly-six-phone-tracking-zignal-surveillance-cia-nsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anomaly Six, a secretive government contractor, claims to monitor the movements of billions of phones around the world and unmask spies with the press of a button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Cutting Smartphone Use By Just HOUR Each Day Improves Well-Being...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smartphone-use-well-being/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you need to throw your smartphone in the trash to live your best life?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK TOPS AMAZON SALES...</title>
      <link>https://www.amazon.com/This-Will-Not-Pass-Americas/dp/1982172487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.amazon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Said Trump Acknowledged 'Some Responsibility' for Jan. 6 Rampage...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/mccarthy-said-trump-acknowledged-some-responsibility-for-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Kevin McCarthy, the House Republican leader, told G.O.P. lawmakers in the days after the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Ethiopians line up to join Kremlin's fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/africa/hundreds-of-ethiopian-men-queue-to-join-russias-fight-in-ukraine/news-story/c5bb3140595e0c37e9c18a2b7959e3c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of Ethiopians have been seen queuing outside their local Russian embassy in Ethiopia with the hope of escaping the famished nation to provide support for the invading force in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret tapes spook the swamp...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/nyt-reporters-say-they-have-more-damaging-tapes-of-kevin-mccarthy-after-releasing-audio-of-him-planning-to-ask-trump-to-resign-over-jan-6/ar-AAWu6v3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The death of conservative elite...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/04/the-death-of-the-conservative-elite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican Party can't live on populism alone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Oligarchs Die in Mysterious Circumstances 24 Hours Apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/oligarchs-murder-suicide-1699766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As well as Western sanctions on oligarchs, Russian President Vladimir Putin also appeared to target billionaires during a rant about Westernized Russians last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU eyes deal to tame internet 'Wild West'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220422-eu-eyes-deal-to-tame-internet-wild-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union on Friday homed in on new regulation to require Big Tech to remove harmful online content, the bloc's latest move to rein in the world's online giants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don admitted bearing some responsibility for Capitol attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/22/politics/trump-january-6-responsibility-book/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the days following the January 6 insurrection, House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy told Republican lawmakers on a private conference call that then-President Donald Trump had admitted bearing some responsibility for the deadly attack, according to new audio -- a significant admission that sheds light on Trump's mindset in the immediate aftermath of the US Capitol riots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychologist: Why money can buy you happiness...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/22/wharton-psychologist-why-money-actually-can-buy-you-happiness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since 2010, prevailing research has shown that money doesn't necessarily lead to happiness. Wharton psychologist Matthew Killingsworth says that's not true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting rowdy at Coachella? Party police coming for you...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/getting-rowdy-at-coachella-weekend-the-palm-springs-party-police-are-coming-for-you/ar-AAWu9tK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli police storm Jerusalem holy site after rock-throwing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-religion-jerusalem-israel-70ec6d764384ad816c8a5adb81b770d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli police in full riot gear stormed a sensitive Jerusalem holy site sacred to Jews and Muslims on Friday after Palestinian youths hurled stones at a gate where they were stationed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeNe Leakes Sues BRAVO, Andy Cohen for Alleged Racist Environment...</title>
      <link>https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/nene-leakes-sues-bravo-andy-cohen-for-alleged-racist-environment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NeNe Leakes appeared on seasons of 'The Real Housewives of Atlanta' from 2008 until 2020 before announcing her final departure — details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hearing held in Rep. Greene eligibility challenge... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-biden-presidential-atlanta-525429753ace40f5b6e01ceab6f79549</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — U.S. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene is expected to appear at a hearing Friday in Atlanta in a challenge filed by voters who say she shouldn't be allowed to seek reelection because she helped facilitate the attack on the Capitol that disrupted certification of Joe Biden’s presidential victory .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCALS BRACE FOR TAX HIT</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/reedy-creek-improvement-district/39779429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move many say was intended to punish Disney, punishes the people of Orange County as well, according to Orange County tax collector Scott Randolph.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young People Lonelier Than Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n5aj/loneliness-epidemic-young-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;30 percent say they don’t know how to make new friends and they’ve never felt more alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeffrey Epstein, a Rare Cello and Enduring Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/22/jeffrey-epstein-a-rare-cello-and-an-enduring-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Jeffrey Epstein died in prison in 2019, he took many secrets with him. One was how a sexual predator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's ailing command...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10742521/Putin-seen-gripping-table-amid-cancer-battle-rumours-meets-slurring-defence-minister.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin's poor posture and his bloated face and neck sparked speculation about the Russian leader's health, which has reportedly been in decline since the Ukraine invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman, with legs bound, falls 8 stories out of DC building...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2022/04/woman-falls-out-of-building-in-dc-suspect-in-custody/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman is in the hospital after falling out the eighth floor of a building in Northwest D.C., and a child related to the victim and a suspect have been located, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un's Hollywood Makeover Highlights New Propaganda Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-un-s-hollywood-makeover-highlights-new-propaganda-push/ar-AAWnW5n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian General Lets Slip Secret Plan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-general-lets-slip-secret-115858854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artyom AnikeevAs Russian troops tighten their grip on the strategic port town of Mariupol, their strategy is finally becoming clear. Russian military commander Rustam Minnekaev now says the second phase of President Vladimir Putin’s “special operation” is focused on establishing a “land corridor” from the Donbas all the way to Moldova, which would cut off the rest of Ukraine from the sea.“One of the tasks of the Russian army is to establish full control over the Donbas and southern Ukraine. This</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Raid MAGA 'King of Toxic Masculinity' in Human-Trafficking Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-raid-maga-king-toxic-085056681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/Getty/Channel 5Romanian police raided the home of prominent pro-Trump online personality Andrew Tate this month as part of a human-trafficking investigation, bringing new attention to Tate’s ties to leading figures in the American MAGA movement.Before the April 11 raid, Tate was best known as a kickboxer and vocal Trump supporter in the online far right. On social media, Tate portrayed himself as a wealthy cigar-smoking playboy, prompting one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians clash with Israeli police at Jerusalem holy site, 31 injured...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/palestinians-clash-with-israeli-police-at-jerusalem-holy-site-31-injured/ar-AAWtpBE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's plot to invade Moldova...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1599493/vladimir-putin-invasion-plot-Transnistria-second-stage-donbas-war-crimea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR PUTIN'S plot to invade Moldova has been revealed as Russia outlines the "second stage" of its brutal war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of 'eco-anxiety' in kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220315-how-eco-anxiety-affects-childrens-minds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More and more children are experiencing "eco-anxiety": a chronic fear of environmental doom. But some are converting their panic into a force for good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai further tightens restrictions after weeks of strict lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/apr/22/shanghai-further-tightens-covid-restrictions-after-weeks-of-strict-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China vows to eradicate virus, neighbourhood by neighbourhood, amid frustration among residents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOT, billionaire trying to take down Republican senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/22/boozman-bequette-republican-donor-arkansas-00027089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The challenge against Sen. John Boozman has one of the biggest Republican donors on one side and Donald Trump on the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow Plays Recording After GOP Leader Denied...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/listen-maddow-plays-recording-of-kevin-mccarthy-saying-hed-recommend-trump-resign-after-he-denied-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McCarthy had every intention of asking Trump to resign following the Jan. 6 Capitol riot, despite his claim Monday that a report which stated so was "wrong."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDIO: McCarthy said he would urge Trump to resign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-2022-midterm-elections-kevin-mccarthy-rachel-maddow-2dda5a508f77bb14fe31b0fa89b08197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Republican leader Kevin McCarthy told fellow GOP lawmakers shortly after the Jan. 6, 2021, Capitol insurrection that he would urge then-President Donald Trump to resign, according to audio posted by The New York Times and aired on Rachel Maddow’s MSNBC show .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Nebraska's Surprisingly Effective Covid Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/04/22/nebraska-covid-response-pete-ricketts-00026993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska’s obsession with government efficiency gave it an advantage when the virus struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest known infection was record 505 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-61173945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK doctors who treated the patient at a London hospital say persistent infections are still rare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Sows Confusion by Talking Masks After Query on Immigration...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/biden-sows-confusion-by-talking-masks-after-query-on-immigration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden Sows Confusion by Talking Masks After a Query on Immigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CULTURE WAR FLARES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/florida-ends-disneys-special-status-193206779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's legislature scrapped Disney's self-governing status in its Orlando theme park on Thursday, in a move widely seen as retaliation in a bitter row over what has become known as the "Don't Say Gay" law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inappropriate behavior complaint about Bill Murray roils film set...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/being-mortal-bill-murray-1235007590/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Following the news that production was suspended on the Searchlight film Being Mortal, sources tell Deadline the suspension had to do with a complaint made against star Bill Murray for i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas vows to escalate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-xl/news/other/hamas-says-its-ready-to-escalate-fighting-as-jerusalem-tensions-soar/ar-AAWri9p?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron says Le Pen risks 'civil war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/macron-says-le-pen-risks-civil-war-as-he-brushes-off-attacks/ar-AAWr5bF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British pop singer attacked and robbed after NYC concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/singer-tom-grennan-attacked-outside-nyc-bar-manager-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone attacked and robbed British singer-songwriter Tom Grennan outside a bar in Manhattan early Thursday, sending him to the hospital, his manager said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACK OFF:   Philly will lift mandate reinstated 3 days ago...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/philadelphia-indoor-mask-mandate-department-of-health-covid-in-philly-policy/11778105/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of Philadelphia will no longer be requiring masks indoors but officials are strongly recommending they be worn, Action News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds, families fight INFOWARS bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/21/justice-department-sandy-hook-families-question-infowars-bankruptcy-00027079</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge is asked to postpone Friday's hearing on an effort by the right-wing provocateur Alex Jones to ward off creditors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICANS MOVE ON MICKEY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-legislature-passes-bill-repealing-disney-e2-80-99s-special-tax-status/ar-AAWspdl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama says tech companies have made democracy more vulnerable...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/obama-says-tech-companies-have-made-democracy-more-vulnerable/ar-AAWs4pN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabled vet pleads guilty in border-wall scheme that included Bannon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/disabled-vet-pleads-guilty-in-border-wall-scheme-that-included-bannon/ar-AAWsQ8U?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Project X' for TWITTER takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-signals-with-46-5-billion-he-s-serious-about-buying-twitter/ar-AAWs13b?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff arrests own daughter in meth bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article260631372.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The last person you ever want to arrest is one of your family members, especially your child," the sheriff told news outlets.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
