<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>India orders anti-trust probe of GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-google-india-antitrust-exclusive/exclusive-india-orders-anti-trust-probe-of-google-for-alleged-android-abuse-sources-idUSKCN1SG17O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India's antitrust watchdog has ordered an investigation into Alphabet Inc&amp;#...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia demands NASA answer for 'alcohol stench' on International Space Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/778046/russia-nasa-iss-international-space-station-alcohol-smell-dragon-capsule-explosion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LYFT crashes amid middling UBER market debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/10/lyft-crashes-amid-middling-uber-market-debut.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyft stock moved down 9% Friday as indications of the debut of Uber on the New York Stock Exchange were lower than the company's IPO price.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO Describes Tech Giants as Humble, Trustworthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/05/09/google-ceo-sundar-pichai-describes-the-masters-of-the-universe-as-humble-trustworthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google CEO Sundar Pichai recently published an op-ed in the New York Times in which he stated that "privacy should not be a luxury good," and describes his company as having "a profound commitment to responsibility and a healthy dose of humility."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani urges Ukraine to investigate Democrats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0d7a2c280a8a4a588fb28c06e618d171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump's personal lawyer says he is urging Ukraine to open investigations that could benefit Trump politically in the United States. Rudy Giuliani used...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Female suspect had seven syringes hidden in body cavity...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/seven-syringes-seized-275931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 9--In what may be a U.S. record, a Florida Woman had seven syringes stashed inside a body orifice when she was booked into a county jail late Tuesday evening, records show. Police were called to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoFundMe Campaign to Build Wall Is Bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/shocker-the-gofundme-campaign-to-build-the-wall-is-a-bust</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And now, the donors to the effort are demanding answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Shapiro cuts short BBC interview after tough grilling...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/watch-ben-shapiros-has-tantrum-on-the-bbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vows retaliation after America hikes tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e8a5195c21af44e5b783082366cc2f29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — President Donald Trump's latest tariff hike on Chinese goods took effect Friday and Beijing said it would retaliate, escalating a battle over China's technology ambitions and other...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE UNDER THREAT</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2019/05/10/chinese-tariff-increases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;9to5mac.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese tariff increases threatened by President Trump on Monday have started to take effect. Trump made two tweeted threats to increase tariffs on Chinese imports, one of which would have hit Appl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Obsessive, Tumultuous Lives of SPACEX Rocket Chasers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-obsessive-tumultuous-lives-of-spacex-rocket-chasers/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penis extensions don't work, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2019/may/10/penis-extensions-dont-work-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Procedures carry high risk of complications ‘and should almost never be carried out’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is that guy? Yang draws crowds, money, spot on debate stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Andrew-Yang-s-presidential-campaign-draws-crowds-13835027.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STUART, Iowa - Andrew Yang knows that most Americans have absolutely no idea who he is. Even before he makes his expected debut on the presidential debate stage next month, he has a good guess what viewers will be thinking when the camera shifts to him.  "'Who the hell is that guy?' " said Yang, 44, speaking between stops during a recent campaign swing through Iowa.  He's not wrong. A Taiwanese American entrepreneur, lawyer and philanthropist from New York who launched his long-shot bid for the presidency more than a year ago, Yang is barely a blip in most national polls, where his support ranks between 1 percent and 3 percent.  But Yang has become something of a below-the-radar phenomenon in the crowded field of candidates vying for the Democratic presidential nomination. Some candidates far better known than him have been struggling to catch fire on social media and are playing to smaller audiences; Yang has been packing in some of the largest crowds in the race - an estimated 3,000 in San Francisco; 2,000 in Los Angeles; and 2,500 in Seattle, where he paused the rally to point out a pair of bald eagles soaring overhead.  "It's a sign!" Yang declared, as supporters broke into a chant of "USA! USA! USA!"  While Democratic voters are so far largely embracing conventional politicians, the ability of an outsider like Yang to generate buzz shows how the unsettled political climate that paved the way for Donald Trump's stunning 2016 rise is reverberating in the 2020 contest. Some of the more prominent Democratic candidates have tried to answer voter unease over the economy and the state of the country by staking out positions far more liberal than those held by the party four years ago - but Yang is selling himself as a total disrupter.  He has laid out nearly 80 policy proposals on his website, including his call for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Row over German anthem erupts amid nationalism debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190510-row-over-german-anthem-erupts-amid-nationalism-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Row over German anthem erupts amid nationalism debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first bird brain surgery performed on parrot...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/10/worlds-first-bird-brain-surgery-performed-on-parrot/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These human surgeons are for the birds. When wildlife rangers discovered a strange lump on a “wild-hatched” parrot’s skull, they took action and got it the best medical attention …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Bears Locked In Vicious Battle Over Mate On Man's Front Lawn...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/09/n-j-homeowner-stumbles-on-2-bears-battling-tooth-and-claw-across-homes-front-lawn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two bears were caught on camera battling it out on the front lawn outside a family’s house in Sussex County, and one expert says it was all over getting a mate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zellweger stuns as Judy Garland in first biopic trailer...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/trailers/2019/05/10/renee-zellweger-judy-garland-movie-trailer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://youtu.be/QPgWnMXRv5o A star is reborn in the first trailer for Renée Zellweger's Judy Garland biopic. The Oscar-winning actress brings the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rideshare backseats germier than toilets...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/05/10/uber-lyft-germs-health-safety/1128117001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising awareness about the dangers of sitting in the back seat could give you pause the next time your Uber or Lyft rolls up to the curb.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Golden Spike' event marks 150th anniversary of Transcontinental Railroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-goldenspike-idUSKCN1SG0WV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of visitors, many of them train enthusiasts, are expected to crowd ont...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Tactical Rabbi' helps synagogues defend against violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-chabad-security-after-poway-20190510-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the shooting at Chabad of Poway, religious leaders have organized active-shooter drills and defense training. Some think congregants should be armed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radioactive remnants of nuke bomb tests found in world's oceans...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/nuclear-bomb-tests-oceans-radioactive-mariana-trench-crustaceans-a8907616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Baffles With 'No Rush' Tweet, Delete, Retweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-10/trump-says-no-need-to-rush-in-china-talks-after-tariffs-hit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Businesses Squeezed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-10/-i-m-not-apple-small-businesses-squeezed-by-trump-s-big-duties </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farrakhan rails against 'Satanic Jews' in wake of FACEBOOK ban...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/10/louis-farrakhan-rails-against-satanic-jews-in-wake-of-facebook-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Farrakhan spoke at a Catholic church Thursday night in the wake of his Facebook ban and denied that he hates Jewish people while ranting about “Satanic Jews.” The Nation of Islam …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average American hasn't made new friend in 5 years...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/09/why-the-average-american-hasnt-made-a-new-friend-in-5-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-five percent of adults say they find it difficult to make new friends, according to new research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indigenous peoples, 'guardians of Nature', under siege...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/indigenous-peoples-guardians-nature-under-siege-235931504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Amazon rainforests to the Arctic Circle, indigenous peoples are leveraging ancestral knowhow to protect habitats that have sustained them for hundreds and even thousands of years, according to a landmark UN assessment of biodiversity released Monday. Whether it is logging, agribusiness and cattle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER will tap user data 'treasure trove' to become profitable?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-uber-ipo-profit/the-answer-to-ubers-profit-challenge-it-may-lie-in-its-trove-of-data-idUSKCN1SF0O5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over the past two years, Uber Chief Executive Dara Khosrowshahi has used his pea...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Trans in China classified 'mentally ill'; Forced to perform surgery on selves...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7014125/Transgender-people-China-classified-mentally-ill-forced-perform-self-surgery-Study.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In China, trans people are classified as having a mental illness and gender-affirming surgeries require the consent of families, creating a major barrier in accessing safe treatment, Amnesty International said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts see Russia fingerprints...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/20afeea785634442b8300ba2fab0c002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The three new missiles North Korean leader Kim Jong Un has tested over the past week are eerily familiar to military experts: They look just like a controversial and widely copied...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians turn to sex coaches to overcome Soviet-era taboos...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russians-turn-sex-coaches-overcome-soviet-era-taboos-025813277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surrounded by erotic toys, half a dozen women of all ages sit in a central Moscow basement facing a whiteboard as a sex coach trains them in speaking openly about their sexual desires. "I finally want to know what it's like to be a satisfied woman, what sexual pleasure is," one of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate rages in Egypt as Christian women told to cover up...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/debate-rages-egypt-christian-women-told-cover-092052510.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Coptic priest's comments about women's clothing being too revealing in churches has sparked a heated debate this week among Egyptian Christians, the largest religious minority in the Middle East. Father Daoud Lamei, a well-known parish priest in an upmarket Cairo suburb with a sizeable social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns Ebola could spread elsewhere if attacks don't stop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f37cb9c50fea45b4a061c1e8d7b33a03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) — The World Health Organization warned Friday that it may not be possible to contain Ebola to the two affected provinces in eastern Congo if violent attacks on health teams...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Least feminist nation in world -- Denmark?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/may/10/and-the-least-feminist-nation-in-the-world-is-denmark </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCKETMAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles/north-koreas-kim-orders-stronger-strike-power-u-s-still-open-to-talks-idUSKCN1SG0BF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of North Korea ordered its military to boost its strike capability as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto's Long History of Failing Upward...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/05/10/beto-orourke-2020-president-campaign-profile-failing-up-226866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His band didn’t catch on, his alt-weekly flopped and he lost his highest-profile race. Inside the long, risk-free rise of Beto O’Rourke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Revolution? Mexico Still Waiting as AMLO Nears Half-Year Mark...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/10/world/americas/amlo-mexico-lopez-obrador.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can M.J. Hegar Finish Job Beto Started? Purple Heart Vet Takes Aim in TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/09/opinion/mj-hegar-texas-senate-beto.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;M.J. Hegar’s kind of like Ann Richards crossed with Barbara Bush — with a Purple Heart and a Distinguished Flying Cross.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering 'Holy Grail' therapy could repair heart attack damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7014293/Pioneering-gene-therapy-repair-deadly-heart-attack-damage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at King's College London injected pigs with a gene which restarted the growth of specialised heart cells called cardiomyocytes, the majority of which are developed before birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'No need to rush'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/10/trump-signals-he-could-stick-with-china-tariffs-no-need-to-rush.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots Thrive in Forest on Jobs Humans Find Too Boring...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-10/robots-thrive-in-the-forest-on-jobs-that-humans-find-too-boring</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's fastest bullet train' starts test runs in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Companies/World-s-fastest-bullet-train-starts-test-runs-in-Japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;asia.nikkei.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next-generation shinkansen to clock in at 360 kph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/10/us-markets-as-higher-tariffs-on-chinese-goods-kick-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares on Wall Street were poised to see losses at Friday's stateside open, as tariffs on Chinese goods were increased shortly after the stroke of midnight ET.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditation retreats BAD for mental health...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/meditation-retreats-bad-mental-health-175758729.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Going on trendy meditation retreats may be bad for participants’ mental health, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China vows to retaliate after US hikes tariffs...</title>
      <link>http://www.globaltimes.cn/content/1149320.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.globaltimes.cn&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress Demands Details on NSA Phone Surveillance Operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/policy/2019/05/lawmakers-demand-details-nsas-sweeping-phone-surveillance-operations/156844/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force leaker charged with spilling drone secrets to reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/former-air-force-intelligence-analyst-charged-leaking-obama-era-drone-n1003721</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court documents said the analyst gave classified documents to a reporter that were published on a news site federal officials have confirmed was The Intercept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border Patrol Agents Contracting Illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/border-patrol-rep-record-number-of-agents-contracting-illness-from-illegals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I believe this is probably the record, you know, Border Patrol-wide, since ever, of agents calling in sick'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gonorrhea may be transmitted by kissing...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/french-kissing-gonorrhea-infection-disease-kiss-a8906456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 hit by European Measles outbreak; Spreading at alarming rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/777832/Measles-outbreak-hits-100-000-people-in-Europe-WHO-confirms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market on edge...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/09/stock-market-on-edge-as-traders-wait-to-see-if-trump-hikes-tariffs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. equity futures were higher Thursday evening stateside as traders awaited a midnight deadline for tariffs to increase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China prepared for all outcomes on trade talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/09/china-says-it-is-prepared-to-respond-to-all-kinds-of-outcomes-on-us-trade-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing has made adequate preparations to respond to the U.S. on trade, the Chinese Ministry of Commerce said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:  Diane Keaton's Senior Citizen Comedy About as Funny as a Colonoscopy...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/05/poms-review-diane-keaton-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s always intriguing to see what Diane Keaton can do with silly material, and it doesn’t get any sillier than ‘Poms.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fake heiress gets years in prison for high-society scam...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/09/fashion-loving-fake-heiress-gets-4-12-years-prison-for-high-society-scam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She won’t be wearing designer labels for a while. Fake heiress Anna Sorokin, who scammed her way into New York society, was sentenced Thursday to four to 12 years in prison, where the fashion-obses…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: America's fastest growing cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/05/09/americas-fastest-growing-cities/39442201/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While US population growth hit an 80-year low in 2018, some cities are flourishing with growth at a rate more than triple than the average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA seizes NKorea ship...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/u-s-seeks-seize-north-korean-ship-suspected-violating-u-n1003811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 17,000-ton freighter, called the Wise Honest, was stopped in Indonesia last year after it was found to be carrying coal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK CO-FOUNDER CALLS FOR GOVT TO BREAK IT UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/money/technology/its-time-to-break-up-facebook/ar-AAB84r5?li=BBr5KbJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Surfer dies after shark chomps off leg...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-48219268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local authorities are calling for vigilance in the sea as they warn of the threat of bull sharks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  We face constitutional crisis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/442889-pelosi-i-do-agree-we-are-in-a-constitutional-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) on Thursday said she agreed with House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler's (D-N.Y.) assertion that the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams says still considering jumping in...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/443048-stacey-abrams-not-ruling-out-2020-white-house-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Georgia gubernatorial candidate Stacey Abrams (D) said Thursday that she has not ruled out entering the crowded Democratic primary field, though she said she has not made a decision yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caretaker arrested after HUNDREDS OF BUGS crawl out of child's backpack...</title>
      <link>https://www.pnj.com/story/news/local/2019/05/09/florida-woman-arrested-neglect-home-infested-roaches/1150266001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pnj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The children wore the same clothes for weeks and couldn't remember their last bath. An investigation into mom's home found cockroaches on every surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race for South Pole prime extraterrestrial real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/05/why-moons-south-pole-may-be-hottest-space-destination-blue-origins-shackleton-crater/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos and his spaceflight firm Blue Origin have announced their lunar ambitions—joining the global race for this prime extraterrestrial real estate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS BLUE MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7011507/Is-Blue-Origin-headed-moon-Jeff-Bezos-set-reveal-rocket-firms-space-vision.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On stage, Bezos took the wraps off a massive model of what will be the firm’s first lunar lander, dubbed Blue Moon. The event kicked off at 4 p.m. in Washington D.C, and was not live streamed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ALEXA' transcripts live on -- after voice records deleted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/amazon-alexa-transcripts-live-on-even-after-you-delete-voice-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can delete voice recordings so Amazon can't listen to your conversations with Alexa anymore, but text records are a different story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flare lights up sky as Air Force tests ICBM -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.vcstar.com/story/news/local/2019/05/09/unarmed-missile-launched-test-vandenberg-air-force-base/1153956001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vcstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force launched an unarmed intercontinental ballistic missile from Santa Barbara County, the second such test this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peace, love, litigation: WOODSTOCK 50 battle heads to court...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/09/arts/music/woodstock-50-court.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woodstock 50, LLC filed a petition on Wednesday requesting an injunction against its former financier, an arm of the Japanese advertising giant Dentsu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verge of A.I. arms race: Machine or humans decide who to slay?</title>
      <link>https://www.c4isrnet.com/unmanned/2019/05/09/we-are-on-the-verge-of-a-no-win-ai-arms-race-warns-ngo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c4isrnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report from nongovernmental organization Pax warns that gains from AI-enabled weapons will be nasty, brutish and short-lived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propaganda music video champions 'Social Credit System'...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-05-08/beijing-makes-music-video-promoting-the-social-credit-system/11088402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China releases a music video promoting the importance of integrity and trustworthiness ahead of the scheduled national rollout of the controversial Social Credit System next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rattles saber ahead of make-or-break trade talks...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-trade-china/trump-rattles-saber-at-china-ahead-of-make-or-break-trade-talks-idUKKCN1SF2BD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said on Thursday he was taking steps to authorise ne...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY HITS NEW HAMPSHIRE?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/hillary-hits-new-hampshire-fresh-off-speaking-tour-clinton-heads-to-first-primary-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is Hillary Clinton running a non-campaign campaign for president? The twice-failed Democrat presidential candidate isn’t interested in discussing an endorsement for 2020, and sources close to Clinton have repeatedly said she hasn’t closed the door on a rematch with President Trump. Then on Wednesday, just days after wrapping up a national speaking tour with husband …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China surveillance hell: 'All your life in the record'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-chinas-massive-surveillance-operation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Xinjiang, northwest China, the government is cracking down on the minority Muslim Uyghur population, keeping them under constant surveillance and throwing more than a million people into concentration camps. But in Istanbul, 3,000 miles away, a community of women who have escaped a life of repression are fighting a digital resistance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS BLUE MOON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-exploration-bezos/billionaire-jeff-bezos-to-unveil-plans-for-moon-presence-sources-say-idUSKCN1SF1WI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire entrepreneur Jeff Bezos, founder of rocket company Blue Origin, unve...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spy whale' rescues dropped iPhone from ocean floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.9news.com.au/world/russian-spy-whale-video-of-beluga-rescuing-dropped-iphone-from-ocean-floor/331335d6-b0aa-428a-8062-fc853d8abfb7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.9news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Building the road'...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2019/05/09/jeff-bezos-aims-blue-origin-at-the-moon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today at a packed event blocks from the White House, Jeff Bezos took the stage in front of select members of the media, executives, government officials and a gaggle of middle schoolers to reveal new details of his plan to get to the Moon by 2024.  Blue Origin is going to send humans to space [&amp;hel…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE hopes $30M Carnegie Library rehab does more than sell iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/tim-cook-hopes-apples-30-million-rehab-of-d-c-s-carnegie-library-will-do-more-than-sell-iphones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has spent two years and probably more than $30 million to open a flagship Apple Store next week in Washington D.C. by renovating the 116-year-old Carnegie Library. The question may be, why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan embassy goes dark as standoff intensifies on DC streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Venezuelan-embassy-goes-dark-as-standoff-13832785.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The sun had just dipped below the horizon Wednesday evening when the lights flicked off inside the Venezuelan embassy in Washington.  Waves of cheers rolled up and down the ordinarily quiet street in the elite Georgetown neighborhood at the center of an intensifying standoff between backers of Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaidó and left-wing activists who oppose U.S. intervention and support President Nicolás Maduro.  With no electricity, the activists who have been living inside the building adjusted to the latest challenge in their month-long occupation of the embassy. Organizers with Code Pink, a left-leaning organization known for its theatrical and provocative protests, said the utility bills had been paid in full by the building's owners: the Maduro-led Venezuelan government.  The group has been inside the embassy since April 10 at the invitation of Maduro government officials. About two weeks into Code Pink's residency, Venezuelan and Venezuelan-American protesters began to gather outside. They have not left since.  The embassy, a four-story brick building on a quiet side street near the Chesapeake and Ohio Canal, has become the site of a proxy power struggle that mirrors the international fight over the future of Venezuela.  Activists inside the building Thursday said they had no running water or electricity, although a spokesman for D.C. Water said water had not been shut off to the property. The utility Pepco declined to comment on why the electricity apparently was cut.  "Out of respect for customer privacy and public safety and in accordance with Public Service Commission regulations, Pepco does not discuss the status of individual customer accounts or service to individual properties," the company said in a statement. "This privacy protocol covers all Pepco customers including...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says John Kerry should be prosecuted for shadow diplomacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-kerry-prosecuted-iran</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday accused former Secretary of State John Kerry of breaking the law by meeting with Iranian officials last year -- and went so far as to say he should be prosecuted under the Logan Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELF-DEPORTATIONS RISING DRAMATICALLY...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/09/self-deportation-spikes-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of illegals who are choosing to voluntarily leave the country, self-deportation, has spiked since President Donald Trump entered the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE 'most ambitious' retail store set for DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190509-apples-most-ambitious-retail-store-set-us-capital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's 'most ambitious' retail store set for US capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless Man Surrounded By Porn Mags Pleasures Self In Middle Of Neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/downtown-homeless-man-exposes-self-neighbors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People living in downtown say they don’t feel comfortable in their own home. Some are even moving, all because of a homeless man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social giant auto-generates videos celebrating ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f97c24dab4f34bd0b48b36f2988952a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The animated video begins with a photo of the black flags of jihad. Seconds later, it flashes highlights of a year of social media posts: plaques of anti-Semitic verses, talk of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: I 'temper' Bolton's hawkish instincts...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/09/donald-trump-john-bolton-1314722</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;He has strong views on things but that's okay. I actually temper John, which is pretty amazing,&amp;quot; Trump said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top intel, military advisers hold 'unusual' Iran meeting at CIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/top-trump-admin-intel-military-advisers-held-meeting-cia-iran-n1003736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current and former officials said it is extremely rare for senior White House officials or Cabinet members to attend a meeting at CIA headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More tigers now in cages than in wild....</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/wild-tigers-face-extinction-this-man-pursues-those-responsible/ar-AAB8WfO?li=AAggFp4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie's Brutally Honest Mayoral Memos: 'Don't Know Who I Am'...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2019/05/bernie-sanders-brutally-honest-mayoral-memos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the mid-1980s, the Democratic presidential candidate was a messâ€”and so was his house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC reporter fired over racist royal baby chimp tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-48212693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC sacks the presenter over his "royal baby" image of a chimp in a suit holding hands with a couple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set of new HBO series goes up in flames...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/09/set-of-new-hbo-series-starring-mark-ruffalo-rosie-odonnell-destroyed-by-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive fire on Thursday destroyed the upstate New York set of a new HBO series starring Mark Ruffalo and Rosie O’Donnell. The upcoming “I Know This Much Is True,” also featurin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple films sex tape in driverless TESLA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9039159/couple-sex-tape-driverless-tesla-motorway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RECKLESS couple has filmed a raunchy sex tape while speeding down a highway in a self-driving car – and admit they “wouldn’t recommend it”. Amateur US porn star Taylor Jackson p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame melted roof leaves astronomical lead levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/medical/article/Notre-Dame-s-melted-roof-leaves-astronomical-lead-13831424.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) - Notre Dame Cathedral's melted roof has left astronomically high lead levels in the plaza outside and adjacent roads.  Paris police say lead levels from the roof were found to be between 10 and 20 grams per kilogram of ground - between 32 and 65 times the recommended limit by French health authorities of 0.3 grams per kilogram. The areas closest to the cathedral are currently closed.  The statement Thursday said the main danger is lead dust that could coat surfaces of nearby homes and businesses. To avoid lead poisoning, authorities have recommended a good cleaning with a damp cloth, and that pregnant women and children wash hands frequently.  Hundreds of tons of lead were used in Notre Dame's frame, as well as the church spire that burned and collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos erupts as AL Senate strips rape exception from abortion ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2019/05/alabama-senate-strips-rape-exception-from-abortion-ban-vote-on-bill-next-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senators could give final passage today to a bill to make abortion a felony in Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child Rapist Vows To 'Rape First Woman He Sees' After Release...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/05/08/convicted-child-rapist-vows-rape-first-woman-sees-after-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Arkansas issued a warning Monday about a level 3 sex offender who threatened to "rape the first woman he sees" after he's released from custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One by one, D-Day memories fade as war's witnesses die...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e84da6ba6781413e8cdedff30e661432</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — One more funeral, one less witness to the world's worst war. Bernard Dargols lived almost long enough to join the celebrations next month marking 75 years since the D-Day, 75...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope requires sex abuse reported to church, not police...</title>
      <link>https://www.newson6.com/story/40443733/pope-issues-new-law-requiring-all-catholic-priests-nuns-to-report-clergy-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newson6.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis has issued a new law requiring all Catholic priests and nuns around the world to report clergy sexual abuse and cover-ups by their superiors to church authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Starr Ramps Up Attacks on Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ken-starr-ramps-up-attacks-on-mueller-his-report-has-over-1000-footnotes-i-mean-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former independent counsel Ken Starr attacked the length of special counsel Robert Mueller's report, saying that "there's just too much detail."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members of Congress plot pay raise...</title>
      <link>https://wsbt.com/news/connect-to-congress-deprecated/some-house-members-consider-taking-pay-raise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsbt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of senior House lawmakers, frustrated by a decade of frozen congressional salaries, are quietly exploring whether to accept an annual pay raise that they&amp;rsquo;ve shunned since Barack Obama was first president. It&amp;rsquo;s a longshot at best, requiring comity that&amp;rsquo;s in short supply in a Capitol riven with partisanship.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
