<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Virus reaches previously Covid-free New Caledonia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210307-virus-reaches-previously-covid-free-new-caledonia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virus reaches previously Covid-free New Caledonia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE WOMEN ACCUSE CUOMO</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/06/two-more-women-accuse-gov-andrew-cuomo-of-inappropriate-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more women came forward Saturday to accuse Gov. Cuomo of sexually harassing behavior, including a former press aide who describes struggling to free herself from his repeated hugs, and a young …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Brooks Resigns From Nonprofit After More Evidence Of Conflicts Emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/times-columnist-david-brooks-told-people-to-join-nextdoor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His resignation comes amid new revelations of entanglements with Nextdoor and the Walton Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov in Isolation: How Cuomo Lost Grip on New York...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/06/a-governor-in-isolation-how-andrew-cuomo-lost-his-grip-on-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo came under fire just a few weeks ago over his handling of nursing home deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As violence surges, some question Portland axing police unit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-shootings-police-violence-coronavirus-pandemic-704eeab551b452658cf2fa91a123b483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Elmer Yarborough got a terrifying call from his sister: She wept as she told him two of his nephews may have been shot in broad daylight as they left a bar in Portland,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov in Isolation: How Cuomo Lost Grip on New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/06/nyregion/cuomo-crisis-sexual-harassment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid calls for his resignation, the governor is relying on a shrinking circle of advisers to help him navigate the biggest crises of his political life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Jack auctions first ever tweet as digital memorabilia...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210306010413-3jzpc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Buzz: Crypto Mogul Bids $2 Million for Dorsey Tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/social-media-buzz-crypto-mogul-bids-2-million-for-dorsey-tweet/ar-BB1ejvG3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- What’s buzzing on social media this morning: Jack Dorsey, Twitter’s co-founder and chief executive, is selling his first-ever tweet -- “just setting up my twttr”-- on a website called Valuables that auctions tweets. The highest bid is $2 million as of Saturday morning in New York, by Justin Sun, the Chinese crypto entrepreneur who earlier won an auction for Warren Buffett’s charity dinner. Valuables said on its website that owning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Swarm of 20,000 quakes could make Iceland's volcanoes erupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/iceland-earthquakes-volcanic-eruption-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents have been 'waking up to earthquakes' every day for more than a week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist warns public on danger of patronizing horror films...</title>
      <link>https://mb.com.ph/2021/03/05/priest-exorcist-warns-public-on-the-danger-of-patronizing-horror-films/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mb.com.ph&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exorcist priest said patronizing horror films or films that deal with magic and witchcraft is "dangerous" as this could lead to possible demonic possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Hypersonic Missile Set for Inaugural Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/39634/agm-183-hypersonic-missile-to-make-first-flight-within-30-days-according-to-air-force</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new schedule comes after an Air Force official said just recently that the first flight test of the AGM-183 would take place this past week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American porn star sparks fury in Tehran after stripping off in Iranian music video...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2459626/porn-star-alexis-texas-sparks-fury-tehran-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORN star Alexis Texas has sparked fury in Tehran after stripping off her clothes in an Iranian music video – prompting hardliners to want her banned. Iranian pop star Sasan Yafteh – wh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen urged to 'publicly apologize'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1406401/Queen-Elizabeth-II-news-Meghan-Markle-Oprah-Winfrey-US-The-View-celebrities-latest-vn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US CELEBRITIES have rallied around Meghan Markle ahead of her interview with Oprah Winfrey, with co-hosts from popular US talk show The View calling on the Queen to publicly apologise to the Duchess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meditation linked to lower cholesterol, blood pressure, blood sugar...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/life-style/health/1406451/how-to-live-longer-meditation-lower-cholesterol-blood-pressure-blood-sugar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEDITATION is "about training in awareness and getting a healthy sense of perspective", noted Headspace - an app that guides its users on how to meditate. Now a research study demonstrated the lifeskill can achieve so much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK WILD!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2455109/florida-beaches-spring-break-covid-spike-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRING breakers heading to Florida have sparked fears of yet another Covid surge. College students were spotted in crowds on the sandy beaches, as nearly 2,000 Americans yesterday died from Covid-1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports fans much healthier and happier than generally imagined, science finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Sports-fans-are-much-healthier-and-happier-than-16005624.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sluggish. Inactive. Incurious. Stereotypical sports fans are lazy louts who love their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dems who could take Cuomo's place...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/03/06/new-york-governor-potential-democratic-candidates-473916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Cuomo wounded, next year could get very interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bisexual women with straight male partners least likely to be out, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/bisexual-women-straight-male-partners-least-likely-be-out-study-n1259770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There are meaningful differences in relationships depending on the sexual and gender identity of bi women’s partners,” the report’s lead author said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rushes to accommodate border surge, with few signs of plans to contain it...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Biden-administration-rushes-to-accommodate-border-16005619.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As the Biden administration races to find shelter for a fast-growing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California bone dry. Will March bring more misery or a miracle?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-bone-dry-march-bring-002412223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's a graphic look at where California stands after a dry winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico barricades presidential palace ahead of women's march...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210306010713-daidk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year's march was punctuated by clashes between marchers and apparent Nazi sympathizers that left dozens injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope, top Iraq Shiite cleric hold historic, symbolic meeting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-islamic-state-group-ali-al-sistani-pope-francis-iraq-f95098b179f6a82157e87a7cb6cc0c3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLAINS OF UR, Iraq (AP) — Pope Francis and Iraq's top Shiite cleric delivered a powerful message of peaceful coexistence Saturday, urging Muslims in the war-weary Arab nation to embrace Iraq’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters say out with Cyprus 'Satanic' Eurovision entry...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/eurovision-song-contest-europe-cyprus-e474a5c343e5aca0516ecf0b76389d75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICOSIA, Cyprus (AP) — Dozens of Orthodox Christian faithful held up wooden crosses and sang Church hymns outside of Cyprus' state broadcaster on Saturday to demand the withdrawal of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speedy variants power virus surge sweeping Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-england-coronavirus-pandemic-france-milan-2b4e8c5092db92c38194884a4b8049e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The virus swept through a nursery school and an adjacent elementary school in the Milan suburb of Bollate with amazing speed. In a matter of just days, 45 children and 14 staff...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
