<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet ALTOS LABS, Silicon Valley's latest bet on living forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/09/04/1034364/altos-labs-silicon-valleys-jeff-bezos-milner-bet-living-forever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Funders of a deep-pocketed new "rejuvenation" startup are said to include Jeff Bezos and Yuri Milner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Thieves Steal 17 Cars From Dealership!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/03/police-search-for-17-cars-stolen-from-brooklyn-park-dealership/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local car dealership is hoping for help finding more than a dozen cars that were stolen over the course of two days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Jewish population now numbers 15.2 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/there-are-152-million-jews-in-the-world-jewish-agency-data-678733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the world’s Jews, 6.9 live in Israel, and 8.3 live in the Diaspora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female boxer dies after being knocked out in ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/boxer-jeanette-zacarias-zapata-dies-days-after-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican boxer Jeanette Zacarias Zapata has died after suffering serious injuries in a fight in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian among 3 killed from 'cocaine-laced fentanyl overdose' at LA party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9959319/Comedian-Fuquan-Johnson-three-people-dead-suspected-overdose-party-LA.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The other two victims have not been officially identified, while a fourth person who appeared to have also overdosed, believed to be comedian and model Kate Quigley, as per TMZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE 'Horse Dewormer' Hit-Piece Debunked By Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/covid-19/rolling-stone-horse-dewormer-hit-piece-debunked-after-hospital-says-no-ivermectin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's Foreign Gambles Making French Diplomats Uneasy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/macron-s-foreign-gambles-are-making-some-french-diplomats-uneasy/ar-AAO7cGR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s president has fought a quiet battle with his diplomats but was persuaded to start Afghan evacuations earlier than other Western powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why China's bitcoin miners are moving to Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-58414555</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing's crackdown on cryptocurrency sends bitcoin entrepreneurs moving to the wild wild west.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Long Island Man Became 'Forrest Gump of Jihad' -- Then Flipped...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/09/05/forrest-gump-of-jihad-book-excerpt-509587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What Bryant Neal Viñas can teach us about the lessons from Afghanistan the U.S. still hasn’t learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 anchors of safety net ending, affecting millions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-19-safety-net-ending-unemployment-evictions-bca43d873a61a9059c72fe15b88b9a9a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mary Taboniar went 15 months without a paycheck, thanks to the COVID pandemic. A housekeeper at the Hilton Hawaiian Village resort in Honolulu, the single mother of two saw her income completely vanish as the virus devastated the hospitality industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxx paramilitary group, which discussed violent insurrection, disbanded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-anti-vaxx-paramilitary-group-which-discussed-violent-insurrection-via-telegram-was-disbanded-after-a-newspaper-exposed-it/ar-AAO7ngR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British group 'Veterans 4 Freedom' comprised more than 200 former servicemen and servicewomen and planned to attack vaccine centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady says he contracted after Super Bowl parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32149146/tom-brady-says-contracted-covid-19-shortly-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady says he was diagnosed with COVID-19 right after the Tampa Bay Buccaneers' Super Bowl parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan, Harry make audacious bid for meeting with Queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3601938/meghan-harry-queen-summit-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEGHAN and Harry have made an audacious bid for a UK meeting with the Queen in the coming weeks. It comes after “olive branch” calls home following the Oprah chat row. Harry and Meghan plan to intr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kabul airport re-opens -- with no radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kabul-s-airport-re-opens-for-domestic-flights-with-no-radar-as-taliban-battle-resistance-fighters-in-last-holdout/ar-AAO7hjL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news of the domestic flights comes as efforts continue to re-open the airport for international flights, a key step to enable humanitarian aid to enter the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hunting Americans,' says California mom-to-be left behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/taliban-hunting-americans-california-afghanistan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pregnant woman named Nasria, a California native, flew to Afghanistan in June to visit family and get married. As of early September, she remained one of the estimated 100 to 200 Americans left behind in the chaotic withdrawal of U.S. forces, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scion of legal dynasty, whose wife and son were murdered, shot in head...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/04/alex-murdaugh-reportedly-shot-in-south-carolina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Murdaugh, the scion of a South Carolina legal dynasty, whose wife and younger son were shot to death in June, was shot on a rural road while on his way to Charleston, his lawyer Jim Griffin sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do we need humans for that job? Automation booms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/humans-job-automation-booms-covid-061159699.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask for a roast beef sandwich at an Arby’s drive-thru east of Los Angeles and you may be talking to Tori — an artificially intelligent voice assistant that will take your order and send it to the line cooks. “It doesn’t call sick,” says Amir Siddiqi, whose family installed the AI voice at its Arby’s franchise this year in Ontario, California. Past experience suggests that such automation waves eventually create more jobs than they destroy, but that they also disproportionately wipe out less skilled jobs that many low-income workers depend on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No major religion objects to Covid vaccines. Will religious exemptions hold?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/religious-exemptions-vaccine-mandates-could-test-sincerely-held-beliefs-n1278514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t think most of this is sincere. I think it’s just a way to get out of having to take a vaccine,” a bioethics professor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Democracy Losing Race With Disruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/democracy-is-losing-its-race-with-disruption/ar-AAO7u9X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New technologies have accumulated tremendous power over our politics, economy, and lives—no one knows what to do about it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple joins backlash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/05/satanic-temple-joins-backlash-against-texas-abortion-law/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Satanic Temple lobbied for the FDA to provide abortion pills to its Texas members, arguing it qualifies as an exemption as a faith-based group that supports the procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enzyme genetically related to snake venom found in Covid fatalities...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/science/does-this-enzyme-raise-the-chance-of-covid-related-death-678710</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers discovered an enzyme that is genetically related to a key enzyme in snake venom and was found in COVID-19 fatalities in doses 20 times the safe amount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly Week Without Power, New Orleans Facing 'Race With Clock'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nearly-a-week-without-power-new-orleans-is-facing-a-race-with-the-clock/ar-AAO6CMa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS — When Stephanie Crier emerged from her New Orleans apartment last week after hunkering down for Hurricane Ida, she was relieved to find that the storm had not flooded the city or left catastrophic destruction on par with Hurricane Katrina.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women say they met porn actor Jeremy for fun; rape came next...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-de178cd37c7e247bffcb31d5b0edeac2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Adult film actor Ron Jeremy leveraged the novelty of his celebrity to meet and often isolate women who he raped and sexually assaulted, using the same tactics for years, according to grand jury testimony from 21 women that was unsealed Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary 'TODAY' show weatherman Willard Scott dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/willard-scott-dead-t152927</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Willard Scott, who forecast the weather on TODAY for more than three decades and spent 65 years at NBC, died this week, TODAY's Al Roker has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clown Prince of Sun and Showers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/willard-scott-tvs-clown-prince-of-sun-and-showers-is-dead-at-87/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Willard Scott, the antic longtime weather forecaster on the “Today” show, whose work, by his own cheerful acknowledgment, made clear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This YOUTUBE star wants to be gov. He's best-known Dem on ballot...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/story/2021-09-03/kevin-paffrath-youtube-star-democrat-recall-candidate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Paffrath's real estate advice has attracted 1.7 million YouTube followers. The Democrat is a potential contender in the recall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Supreme Court Test On Docket...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/09/03/texas-abortion-law-scotus-roe-casey-509490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court case this week wasn’t about Roe or Casey. But that doesn’t mean we can’t learn from it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas ban may spur tele-abortions: Virtual visits, then pills...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/texas-ban-may-spur-tele-abortions-virtual-visits-then-pills/ar-AAO61AH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Days before the U.S. Supreme Court cleared the way to effectively end abortion in the state, a truck rolled through parts of west Texas bearing a billboard with a message in English and Spanish: “Missed period? There’s a pill for that.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banderas, Cruz poke fun at film biz excesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210904-banderas-cruz-poke-fun-at-film-biz-excesses-at-venice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Banderas, Cruz poke fun at film biz excesses at Venice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE COVID CASES THAN LAST LABOR DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/03/us-heads-into-labor-day-with-covid-vaccines-but-substantially-worse-outbreak-than-last-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though the outbreak is worse by most measures than 2020, the delta variant, vaccines and open schools make it hard to predict how the pandemic will unfold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  GET SET FOR MU!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-mu-variant-health-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Health Organization has dubbed Mu a "variant of interest," but the U.S. says it is not "an immediate threat" for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban Fighters Crush Women's Protest Amid Flickers of Resistance...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/04/taliban-fighters-crush-a-womens-protest-amid-flickers-of-resistance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban fighters violently suppressed a women’s protest Saturday in Kabul, while 70 miles to the north ex-Afghan army and militia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARIZONA 3,000 SICK A DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arizona-coronavirus-pandemic-a75eab49ce1b259d2095a2a022240345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Arizona on Saturday stayed on its recent pace of reporting more than 3,000 additional COVID-19 cases per day during the current surge. The state's coronavirus dashboard reported 3,424 additional cases and 38 virus-related deaths, increasing the pandemic totals to 1,027,359 cases and 18,997 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New migrant caravan sets off for USA from southern Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/new-migrant-caravan-sets-off-us-southern-mexico-2021-09-04/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A migrant caravan of around 400 people, including many children, set off from the southern Mexican city of Tapachula for the United States on Saturday, just a couple of days after security and migration officials dispersed another large group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump in Talks to Sell Rights to DC Hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/scoop-trump-nears-deal-dc-hotel-5b093f84-b9b9-426b-93be-6b13435be774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic building became a prop and symbol for both sides in the political wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent calls police after child pulled from class for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/570858-new-york-parent-calls-police-after-child-pulled-from-class-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parent in New York called the police after their child was pulled from class for not wearing a mask.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
