<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Party luminaries hit trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Party-luminaries-hit-campaign-trail-Saturday-to-13360291.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luminaries from both major political parties were set to hit the campaign trail Saturday in a late push to drive up turnout for Tuesday's midterm elections in key battlegrounds that will determine control of Congress and dozens of governorships. President Donald Trump has another pair of rallies planned, in Montana and Florida, two states with marquee Senate races. In Florida, Trump is also trying to bolster the fortunes of Republican gubernatorial hopeful Ron DeSantis, a candidate he endorsed during the GOP primary, who has been lagging in polls behind Democrat Andrew Gillum. If elected, Gillum would be the state's first black governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN worries about next 'America First' ambassador after Haley resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/un-worries-about-next-america-first-ambassador-after-haley-s/article_39070a72-673b-515b-a313-5d165c133d83.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK –– President Donald Trump’s “America First” rhetoric was never popular at the United Nations, but officials there are now worried they’re losing a critical ally as the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 52 UNCOVERED? Mysterious aircraft at secret US base 'intentionally BLURRED' by GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1040448/Area-52-UFOs-aliens-mysterious-Google-Maps-top-secret-military-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPECULATION has erupted over a mysterious aircraft spotted at a top-secret US military base, amid claims that Google Maps has "refused" to update its satellite imagery of the area for more than eight years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Pentagon rejects request for troops to act as emergency law enforcement at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/02/politics/white-house-pentagon-troops-border/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Trump administration first asked the Pentagon to send troops to the southern border, the administration wanted the troops to take on duties that Department of Defense officials viewed as law enforcement functions, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make America mindful again: Meditation app offers 'politics pack' for election anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/02/headspace-app-offers-politics-pack-for-election-anxiety.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Headspace says it has seen an uptick in the use of its guided meditation sessions in times of high public stress, including after the 2016 presidential election that pitted Donald Trump against Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabled veteran knocks MSNBC crew for blocking handicapped spots at polling site...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/414708-disabled-veteran-knocks-msnbc-crew-for-blocking-handicapped-spots-at-polling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disabled Air Force veteran this week voiced frustration with an MSNBC news crew for blocking handicapped parking spots outside of a polling site in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaigns in high gear days before elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-campaign/u-s-campaigns-in-high-gear-three-days-before-congressional-elections-idUSKCN1N80II</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. congressional candidates hammered into the homestretch of a bruising campai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embryo swapping is Wild West...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/03/embryo-swapping-is-the-wild-west/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a handful of states — including Florida, Louisiana, Oklahoma and Georgia — have passed legislation regarding embryo donation. (New York is not among them.) Georgia was the first to allow embry…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama builds in Mueller probe...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/414630-drama-builds-around-stone-in-mueller-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller continues to zero in on Roger Stone as speculation builds that the special counsel could take a major overt step in his Russia investigation following the midterm elections next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffet BERKSHIRE Bought Back Nearly $1 Billion of Own Stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/warren-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-repurchases-more-than-900-million-of-stock-1541248428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berkshire Hathaway repurchased $928 million of its stock in the third quarter, a rare move that indicates Chairman Warren Buffett sees a dearth of appealing investment options for his company’s large cash pile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech on Live Chats Tests YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hate-speech-on-live-super-chats-tests-youtube-1541205849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube’s Super Chat, which allows users to pay to have comments amplified during streaming videos, generates revenue but can contain racist comments and other hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Sex Worker Taking Hollywood by Storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-former-sex-worker-taking-hollywood-by-storm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The excellent new Netflix horror film ‘Cam’ captures the everyday fears of millions of cam girls, and was penned by ex-cam girl Isa Mazzei. Here, she opens up about her journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX culture of fear...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/805123/netflixs-culture-fear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Silicon Valley giant's workplace is reportedly ruthless. Is it worth it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida teen charged with strangling, burying mother...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-teenager-charged-strangling-burying-mother-135413575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAYTONA BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Authorities say a 15-year-old Florida boy was charged in his mother's strangulation death after her body was found buried at a nearby church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON new HQ in Virginia?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/03/amazon-reportedly-in-advanced-stages-of-naming-va-as-2nd-headquarters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon is in the advanced stages of placing its second headquarters in Northern Virginia, The Washington Post reported on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: THREE signs Biblical prophecies about end of world 'coming true'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/three-signs-biblical-prophecies-end-13526987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trio of 'signs' have all emerged in the past few months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Generation Of Warfare: Genetically-Engineered Viruses...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-02/next-generation-warfare-genetically-engineered-viruses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Saudi crown prince crushed his rivals at the RITZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/how-saudi-royal-crushed-his-rivals-shakedown-ritz-carlton-n930396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royals and others held at the luxury hotel after a Nov. 4, 2017, roundup were subjected to extortion, psychological abuse and torture, U.S. officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France, spate of homophobic attacks on record just 'the tip of the iceberg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181103-france-homophobic-attacks-record-lgbt-violence-gay-pride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An increasing number of victims of anti-LGBT violence in France have spoken out over recent weeks, as rights groups have warned of a spike in attacks and the government has confirmed a 15 percent increase since the start of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past midterms, some zero in on amending Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e84cdca5b568402398eabfcd2b6ada07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Whatever success Republicans have amassed in taking control of all three branches of U.S. government, and whatever fate awaits them as midterm elections near, some on the right are working to cement change by amending the Constitution. And to the mounting alarm of others on all parts of the spectrum, they want to bypass the usual process. They're pushing for an unprecedented Constitutional convention of the states. While opponents are afraid of what such a convention would do, supporters say it is the only way to deal with the federal government's overreach and ineptitude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for chip implant?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/are-you-ready-for-a-chip-implant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You walk into a grocery store and pick up eggs. No smartphone? No problem. You swipe your hand across a reader, and the amount is deducted from your bank account. If that sounds far-fetched, you obviously haven’t been to Sweden recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: TRUMP ACCOMPLISHMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/here-it-is-complete-list-of-president-trumps-accomplishments-in-the-two-years-since-his-historic-2016-election-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraplegic athlete 'forced' to drag himself through airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/paraplegic-athlete-justin-levene-forced-to-drag-himself-through-luton-airport-after-wheelchair-was-left-behind-on-flight/ar-BBPhf0x?li=AAaD62f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Guetta still spinning: Success is 70% hard work...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/news/dance/8483002/david-guetta-ap-interview-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grammy-winning DJ-producer and hitmaker David Guetta says success is mostly down to hard work and luck -- not talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Dead In Building Collapse At AMAZON Fulfillment Center...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/02/partial-building-collapse-at-baltimore-amazon-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to our media partners the Baltimore Sun, officials say it was a partial building collapse and a search is underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia turns up uninvited to major NATO wargames...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181103-russia-turns-uninvited-major-nato-wargames</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite crackdown, 'junk news' still flourishes on social media...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-crackdown-junk-news-flourishes-social.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite an aggressive crackdown by social media firms, so-called "junk news" is spreading at a greater rate than in 2016 on social media ahead of the US midterm elections, according to researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Breakdancing Underdog at 60...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-breakdancing-underdog-at-60-1541242800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ad executive looking for a more fun way to lose weight discovers he can’t stop dancing against competitors half his age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 76: Mueller About to Roll Out the Barrels?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/03/robert-mueller-investigation-222184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that the special prosecutor’s quiet period is nearly over, many Russia-scandal observers expect dramatic news from the long-silent investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of GOD? Claims humans will 'worship AI Messiah'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/740301/god-artificial-intelligence-ai-messiah-dan-rown-da-vinci-code</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tweets himself as star of own Iran sanctions movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-tweets-himself-star-own-iran-sanctions-movie-192208255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington (AFP) - "Game of Thrones" fans are primed for the final season, but starring Donald Trump? Well not quite, though the president had a laugh at Iran's expense Friday by posing in a GoT-style picture. Each "O" in the fictional Trump title is crossed by vertical lines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects bid to halt 'climate change' trial...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/u-top-court-rejects-trump-administration-bid-halt-224951065.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The loss for the administration means it now faces a high-profile examination of U.S. climate change policy during the trial that was due to begin on Oct. 29 in Eugene, Oregon but has since been postponed by the judge. Chief Justice John Roberts on Oct. 19 had temporarily put the case on hold while</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man touched raw shrimp after hurricane. It left him fighting for his life...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article220977730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Wake County, North Carolina teacher was infected with deadly Vibrio vulnificus bacteria from touching raw shrimp from the Atlantic coast after Hurricane Florence. He could have both legs amputated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment comes under fire; Military in partisan crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-border-mission-military-20181102-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's decision to send as many as 15,000 troops to the southern border has drawn sharp and unusual criticism from former military leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What it's like to live with poliolike condition: One little boy's journey...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-child-after-diganosis-poliolike-condition-afm-condition-20181018-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years after her son’s diagnosis, questions linger for the Northwest Indiana mom who worries anew each time her toddler complains of an ache or has the sniffles: Could this be another complication related to acute flaccid myelitis?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists may have found the key ingredient for universal flu vaccine, and it comes from llamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.biospace.com/article/a-llama-antibody-could-be-the-key-to-a-universal-flu-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.biospace.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than a week ago, Roche snagged regulatory approval for Xofluza, a single-dose oral medication, the first new flu treatment approved in 20 years. Now, new research indicates that llamas, the doe-eyed South American pack animal, may hold the key to flu vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump raises stakes with Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-46071747</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House describes it as "the toughest sanctions regime ever imposed on Iran".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I was touched by an angel': Beloved Baltimore barber survives shooting on violent Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/crime/bs-md-ci-halloween-shootings-20181031-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people — including a 13-year-old boy — were killed, and three others injured on a violent Halloween in Baltimore, police said, bringing to a close the second-most violent month of 2018, which saw more than a killing a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OVER RISE IN USE OF MELATONIN TO AID SLEEP...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/nov/02/rise-in-melatonin-use-to-help-children-sleep-leads-to-safety-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors fear hormone is being overprescribed despite little evidence of its effectiveness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Record Spending, Hollywood Dems Fearful Ahead of Midterm Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/state-of-the-midterms-cruz-feels-heat-from-beto-in-new-poll-as-blackburn-pulls-away'&gt;POLL: Cruz feels heat from Beto...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires put money behind Gillum...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/maddieberg/2018/11/02/why-out-of-state-billionaires-have-gotten-behind-this-democrat-in-florida/#6c5e717221c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the swing state’s gubernatorial race, Tom Steyer, George Soros and Michael Bloomberg are putting their money on Andrew Gillum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Followed, Punched Driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6347445/SNL-star-Alec-Baldwin-arrested-New-York-City-allegedly-punching-someone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Alec Baldwin has taken to Twitter to defend his name hours after he was released from a New York jail, claiming he never threw any punches in the parking dispute he was arrested for on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  WE'RE KEEPING THE HOUSE!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/414649-pence-declares-gop-will-retain-control-of-the-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think there's a broad range of areas that we'll be able to work with that Democrat minority in the House and the Senate," vice president tells The Hill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin Arrested After Fight Over Manhattan Parking Spot...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/11/02/alec-baldwin-released-from-police-custody-after-parking-spot-punch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grim-faced Baldwin sauntered out of the NYPD’s 6th Precinct station house in Greenwich Village around 4 p.m., not uttering a word as he hopped into a waiting car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin Arrested After Fight Over Manhattan Parking Spot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Alec-Baldwin-Arrested-Fight-New-York-499430941.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Alec Baldwin was arrested Friday after allegedly punching someone in the West Village, an NYPD spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious interstellar asteroid could be 'solar sail' sent by aliens, claim astronomers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6347379/Interstellar-asteroid-Oumuamua-giant-solar-sail-sent-civilization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers from the Harvard Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics concluded that the strange asteroid 'might be a lightsail of artificial origin.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GOP dummy' hanging from tree sparks outrage in TN...</title>
      <link>https://fox17.com/news/local/political-dummy-hanging-from-tree-sparks-outrage-in-shelbyville</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox17.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A political Halloween decoration has people in Shelbyville outraged. An unknown person hung a dummy from a tree at the corner of 130 and Snell Road. The dummy had a GOP outfit on, a white dunce hat, and a Marsha Blackburn sign hanging from it. Under that, thereâ€™s a sign reading â€œStop the Hate. â€�Billy Grimes has lived in Shelbyville for eight years. He couldnâ€™t believe his eyes when he spotted the dummy eerily swaying in the breeze as he drove across a bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bus ride from Hell: Panicked passengers jump out windows...</title>
      <link>https://www.presstelegram.com/2018/11/02/shuttle-bus-ride-for-queen-marys-dark-harbor-turns-scary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.presstelegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“All we wanted was one more night of Halloween and we got the bus ride from Hell.” one passenger said.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
