<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/author/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Sen. Tom Coburn, Washington's top wastewatcher, dead at 72...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/28/former-sen-tom-coburn-dies-washingtons-top-wastewa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Coburn, a medical doctor turned politician died Saturday morning at age 72 after a lengthy battle with cancer, according to his family, leaving one of the most substantial legacies in recent congressional history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope's special blessing: God turns everything to our good...</title>
      <link>https://www.vaticannews.va/en/pope/news/2020-03/pope-francis-urbi-et-orbi-blessing-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vaticannews.va&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis delivers an extraordinary blessing “To the City and to the World” on Friday to pray for an end to the Covid-19 coronavirus pandemic. In ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO SLAMS</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2020-03-28/trump-eyes-quarantine-of-new-york-area-to-slow-coronavirus-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses Buy Spy Software to Keep Tabs on Remote Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2020/03/27/covid-19-bosses-panic-buy-spy-software-to-keep-tabs-on-remote-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com.my&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The email came from the boss. We’re watching you, it told Axos Financial Inc employees working from home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promised drive-through testing sites haven't materialized...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Promised-drive-through-testing-sites-haven-t-15162863.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks ago, President Donald Trump promised a network of drive-through covid-19 testing sites across the country where people could be tested "very safely, quickly and conveniently." In a Rose Garden news conference, chief executives of Target, Walgreens, Walmart and CVS said they would work with the government to provide space in store parking lots.  While the four retailers have a combined 26,400 U.S. stores, this vision of a proliferation of coronavirus testing sites has yet to materialize. Walgreens and CVS have opened one site each, while Walmart last weekend opened two drive-through testing locations near Chicago. Target hasn't opened any. Rite Aid, which joined the effort later, has opened one drive-through facility in Philadelphia.  Like much of the nation's coronavirus response, the burden of organizing and operating these testing sites has fallen to state and local governments. On occasion, they've enlisted the help of private industry. But an array of logistical challenges, ranging from a shortage of testing supplies to funding, has meant only a small fraction of Americans can get diagnosed for covid-19 in a way that is routine in South Korea and elsewhere.  "We have to change how we are approaching this, or we will just hope that people will stay isolated or pay attention, said Garrett Contreras, the fire chief in the Bay Area city of Hayward, who managed to launch a testing site Monday after he personally appealed to scores of pharmaceutical companies to provide equipment. "I mean, how did some knucklehead fire chief from Hayward find a lab? It's just wrong."  A senior administration official, speaking anonymously to share internal deliberations, said the administration's initial drive-through testing ambitions had to be scaled back because of the lack of tests nationwide. Another initial challenge was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organized crime enforces Brazil lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/25/brazil-rio-gangs-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drug traffickers in Cidade de Deus and other Rio favelas order residents to stay home as fears grow over impact of virus on poorest Brazilians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where Hope Finally Made a Comeback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorker Tries to Recreate 'Italy Magic' By Singing Out Window,  Told to 'Shut The F**k Up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020/03/video-quarantined-new-yorker-tries-to-recreate-italy-magic-by-singing-out-window-but-is-told-to-shut-the-fk-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, he tried...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>