<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AI in adult industry: Porn may soon feature people who don't exist...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2020/feb/07/ai-in-the-adult-industry-porn-may-soon-feature-people-who-dont-exist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Porn has often driven technological innovation, but research into deepfakes raises questions about its potential misuses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania, once reluctant campaigner, hitting trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/07/politics/melania-trump-campaigning/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a first lady who generally begs off rallies, fundraising shindigs and campaign events, Melania Trump appears poised to be a larger campaign presence for President Donald Trump's reelection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's last chance?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/893842/elizabeth-warrens-last-chance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To win in New Hampshire, the 'capitalist to her bones' needs to remind voters of who she really is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill speaks to 10 people...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/jill-biden-speaks-from-podium-in-nh-living-room-to-10-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is taking a critical day off the campaign trail today, and is leaving the glad handing to his wife. The only problem? There aren’t that many people who want to see her, either. Fox 10 captured Biden playing to a very small crowd in the all-important state of New Hampshire today: Could be …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden goes missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/his-campaign-on-the-line-joe-biden-goes-missing-in-new-hampshire/ar-BBZJV2R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets and Stick Shifts: Chateau Marmont Valets 'Unsung Heroes' of Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/why-chateau-marmont-valets-are-unsung-heroes-hollywood-1274735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than three decades, the same four car valets have been trusted with the beloved wheels (and juiciest stories) of the hotel’s A-list guests: "I think he might have seen us make out for the first time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for Bloomberg winning...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-case-for-Michael-Bloomberg-winning-15037699.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back in 2016, a wealthy New Yorker got into a crowded presidential race and was immediately dismissed. Virtually nobody actually liked the candidate, polls showed, and there were also questions about how serious he was about the whole thing. Then that candidate won.  Could it happen again in 2020?  The results of the Iowa caucuses have fed speculation that former New York mayor Mike Bloomberg might actually have a shot at the Democratic nomination. He wasn't on the ballot, mind you, but the results - with a Democratic socialist senator and the young, former mayor of a relatively small American city finishing in the top two slots - seem to have cracked the door ajar to a wild card. Couple that with the "gut punch" suffered by the leading "establishment" candidate - Joe Biden's fourth-place finish - and it's not unreasonable to think a lane could open for Bloomberg.  It's anything but likely, but it's hardly the punchline it once was.  Let's break it down. First is what happened in Iowa and what it means. It has been abundantly clear throughout this process that the Democratic Party is terrified - terrified - of picking the wrong candidate, only to see them lose to President Donald Trump. Iowa Democrats liked Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg so much that they combined for more than half the vote, but it's not difficult to see voters confronting the reality of those two actually facing Trump and, rightly or wrongly, suddenly getting skittish.  And that goes double now that Trump's numbers are creeping up. There was a time when Democrats seemed to have the luxury of picking any number of hopefuls who would be favored against Trump, because they all led him in the polls. That's not so clearly the case anymore. Trump's approval rating has hit or tied new highs in several new polls in recent weeks - including 49 percent in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAGES ACCELERATE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-jobs-top-estimates-225-133001952.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. employers ramped up hiring in January and wage gains rebounded, providing fresh evidence of a durable jobs market that backs the Federal Reserve’s decision to stop cutting interest rates and hands President Donald Trump an early election-year boost.Payrolls increased by 225,000 after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Is Toughest Question Facing Jury...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/07/this-is-the-toughest-question-facing-harvey-weinsteins-jury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Manhattan district attorney’s office made an unusually risky decision when it brought criminal charges against Harvey Weinstein. The two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>63.4%: Labor Force Participation at Trump-Era High...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/susan-jones/634-labor-force-participation-trump-era-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump bragged about the economy Tuesday night in his State of the Union speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowback scorches Perez...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/07/iowa-caucus-blowback-tom-perez-dnc-111795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It was very frustrating to not hear from the DNC for 48 hours, except for them throwing Troy under the bus," said one state Democratic Party chair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MULVANEY ON THE CHOP?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/07/politics/white-house-staff-shake-up-donald-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a five-month impeachment saga behind them, White House aides are bracing for the prospect of another staff shake-up in the West Wing as President Donald Trump looks to enter a new chapter of his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's best?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/481938-trumps-best-week-ever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His highest approval ratings yet. A Democratic debacle in Iowa. A State of the Union address that fired up his base and infuriated his foes. And finally, an historic acquittal in the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment Acquittal Leaves Diplomats Bracing for Impact...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-impeachment-acquittal-leaves-diplomats-090005968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump mostly stifled his fury toward the impeachment witnesses who detailed, over hundreds of hours of testimony, the turmoil wrought by his handling of Ukraine policy. Now that he’s been acquitted of two impeachment charges, they’re bracing for payback.It’s not just the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders Builds California Primary Machine to Land Knockout Blow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bernie-sanders-builds-big-primary-090000599.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the Democratic presidential race speeds toward the make-or-break Super Tuesday primaries, Bernie Sanders has built an operation aimed at winning the night’s biggest prize: California.Sanders’ strong ground game, enviable advertising budget and broad support positions him above his rivals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global shortage of protective equipment...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200207115327-0muw0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/WHO (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-WHO warns of global shortage of coronavirus protective equipment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg likely in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200207052534-xmhdg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/DEBATE (PIX):After Iowa, Buttigieg likely to be in crosshairs at New Hampshire Democratic presidential debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's killing horses in Central Florida? Mystery terrifies owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/crime/2020/02/04/whos-killing-horses-in-central-florida-a-mystery-terrifies-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three killings in late 2019, and an array of alarming incidents after, rocked the equestrian community. No culprits have been caught.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All suspected patients sent to quarantine camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7977649/China-orders-Wuhan-round-suspected-coronavirus-patients-quarantine-camps.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Vice Premier called on a 'people's war' against the fast-spreading epidemic, which has killed at least 638 people and infected more than 31,520. She said the country was in 'wartime condition'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citizen Journalists Covering Outbreak Go Missing...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/two-citizen-journalists-covering-virus-go-missing-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Citizen Journalists Covering Virus Outbreak From Wuhan GoÂ Missing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA mystery: Did Iran kill 'Ayatollah Mike?'</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/2020/02/article/cia-mystery-did-the-taliban-kill-ayatollah-mike-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody is talking after Michael D’Andrea, the CIA’s top Iran Mission Center Chief, is allegedly killed in plane crash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debacle deepens division between Sanders, national party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481961-iowa-debacle-deepens-division-between-sanders-national-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. - The vote-counting debacle around the Iowa caucuses has furthered distrust and hardened anger between Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) and the national Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro Embraces Capitalism and Venezuelan Emigres Returning...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/maduro-embraces-capitalism-venezuelan-emigres-090000638.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Carlos Viloria came home to Venezuela last month.A 35-year-old lawyer, he’d had enough of 15-hour days and abusive bosses as a restaurant worker in Argentina for a year and a half, one of more than 5 million Venezuelans who’ve left over the past five years hoping to escape one of the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems prepare for NH debate as urgency rises...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fe831dcada14e355d635709d021ec985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANCHESTER, N.H. (AP) — The Democratic Party's seven strongest presidential contenders are preparing for what could be the fiercest debate stage clash of the 2020 primary season as candidates look...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Back off, before we come get you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.instagram.com/p/B8NdfPjHQft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instagram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;390.3k Likes, 25.4k Comments - @snoopdogg on Instagram: “P. S. A. Let the family mourn in peace 💝🙏🏾. #gayleking outta pocket FDHBiiiych.…”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking animal welfare violations uncovered at US government labs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shocking-animal-welfare-violations-uncovered-us-government-labs-015332625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mice baked to death after a heating system failure, or left to die from hunger and thirst when researchers forgot to put food or water in their cages for a week -- and nobody noticed. Primates kept in a room where the lights were on 24-hours-a-day for nearly five months because a facility manager was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  LOW KEY OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oscars-night-nearly-1917-leads-charge-020027401.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood's award season reaches its extravagant finale at the Oscars on Sunday, with war epic "1917" tipped to dispatch a brigade of winners to the stage at the movie industry's biggest night. Sam Mendes's "1917" launched a late assault on this year's Academy Awards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WE MAY NEVER KNOW THE REAL RESULTS!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/nbc-news-review-iowa-caucus-vote-finds-potential-errors-inconsistencies-n1132011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results as reported by the Iowa Democratic Party raise questions about the accuracy of the outcome of the first-in-the-nation vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC CALLS FOR IOWA TO RECANVASS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/buttigieg-sanders-neck-neck-iowa-nearly-all-votes-reported-n1131261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The results of Monday's Iowa caucuses were delayed after there were problems with a smartphone app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advance draft of President's budget has war on spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamandrzejewski/2020/02/06/trumps-new-war-on-wasteful-spending--an-advance-draft-of-the-presidents-budget-to-congress-fy2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purchases included:Inflatable games ($42,500), model rockets ($34,000), china tableware ($53,004), alcohol ($308,994), musical instruments ($1.7 million), workout equipment ($9.8 million) and lobster tail and crab ($4.6 million).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
'IT WAS ALL BULLSHIT'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-impeachment-acquittal-speech-watch-live-stream-today-2020-02-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president celebrated his Senate acquittal, lashing out as his opponents and airing his grievances over obstacles that have gotten in his way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Could be down to 3 white guys by end of month...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2020/02/bells-tolling-amy-liz-joe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's fundraising has fallen off, and it is unlikely major donors are going to send cash to a candidate who just ran fourth in Iowa and lose New Hampshire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA:  LOVE YOU, DAD!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/IvankaTrump/status/1225547788626296832</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Love you, Dad! 💛”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOMCBS to launch new streaming service...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/06/viacomcbs-new-streaming-service-to-include-paramount-cbs-all-access.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ViacomCBS is in the awkward position of being simultaneously early and late to the streaming wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC to vote on decriminalizing psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2020/02/election-board-allows-proposal-to-decriminalize-psychedelics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of a proposal to decriminalize the use of certain psychedelic plants are one step closer to putting the measure on the ballot in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House, Bezos escalate feud...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/481920-trump-adviser-bezos-escalate-feud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's top trade adviser and Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos on Thursday escalated their feud over allegations that Bezos has declined to sit down with the White House to discuss the online retail giant's struggles to combat online coun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corey Feldman: 'Biggest problem in Hollywood is pedophilia'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/feb/06/corey-feldman-nobody-wants-to-go-after-the-bad-guys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 80s teen star is known for odd, even sleazy behaviour. Is that why his claims about the film industry are not taken seriously?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Seniors With Active Social Lives Live Longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/seniors-who-keep-an-active-social-life-may-live-longer-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that the perks of rubbing elbows with a wide variety of people, especially in our senior years, could lead to a happier, healthier life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Bernie declares 'decisive victory'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/02/06/iowa-caucus-results-bernie-sanders-declares-decisive-victory/4680676002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We are holding a press conference that should have occurred three nights ago in Des Moines, but for the inability of the Iowa Democratic Party to count votes in a timely fashion," Sanders said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Killing U.S. Kids Isn't the One Dominating the Headlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/flu-not-coronavirus-is-the-virus-killing-us-kids-like-luca-calanni</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus, with zero American fatalities, is dominating headlines, while the flu has killed dozens of U.S. kids this season—including 11-year-old Luca, a true “Giver of Light.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Biden Blew It...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/02/how-joe-biden-blew-it/605821/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president’s Iowa dud was a long time coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army's new fabric works to destroy nerve agents...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/2020/02/05/armys-new-fabric-may-destroy-nerve-agents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Army fabric works to neutralize nerve agents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxpayers Forking Over $6,500 per Illegal Alien...</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/rob-shimshock/report-taxpayers-forking-over-6500-illegal-alien</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the media attention garnered by the border crisis typically revolves around states that border Mexico like Arizona and Texas. Yet a February report reveals the devastating economic consequences of illegal aliens on taxpayers as far north as Montana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves ahead on shrinking Utah monuments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75fe8c1076d98d41ecf9a7ddb9be53c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — The Trump administration on Thursday implemented plans to downsize two national monuments Utah, ensuring the lands previously off-limits to energy development will be open to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Theory: There Is No Swing Voter...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/02/06/rachel-bitecofer-profile-election-forecasting-new-theory-108944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Bitecofer’s radical new theory predicted the midterms spot-on. So who’s going to win 2020?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Results Riddled With Errors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/iowa-caucus-results-riddled-with-errors-and-inconsistencies/ar-BBZIMYd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock after alcohol flows from kitchen taps...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-51372583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents in the state of Kerala woke up to find an unexpected cocktail gushing out of their taps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Trump 'apoplectic' in call with Boris Johnson over HUAWEI...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/481869-trump-apoplectic-in-phone-call-with-uks-johnson-about-huawei-decision</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump reportedly had a heated conversation with British Prime Minister Boris Johnson last week after the United Kingdom allowed the Chinese tech manufacturer Huawei to have a role in the U.K.'s 5G cellphone networks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online dating goes mainstream despite doubts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/online-dating-goes-mainstream-despite-doubts-us-survey-151700084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' use of online apps and dating websites to meet potential partners is growing even if many people express concerns about participating in these services, a survey showed Thursday. The Pew Research Center report showed 30 percent of US adults, and 31 percent of internet users have used</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Might be here to stay; Return every winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/02/06/coronavirus-wuhan-china-recurring-winter-illness-flu/4665482002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like swine flu, the new coronavirus might become a regular part of a winter mix of respiratory bugs causing common colds and other illnesses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police investigate suspicious substance near Schiff's office...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/06/adam-schiff-capitol-police-investigate-suspicious-substance-111496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Intel chairman and lead impeachment manager has received several threats in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Trump 'apoplectic' in call with Boris Johnson over HUAWEI...</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/a70f9506-48f1-11ea-aee2-9ddbdc86190d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MUELLER TOP SCUM'</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/atrupar/status/1225485150143877121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Trump laments that Hillary Clinton wasn't prosecuted and calls the former leaders of the FBI "scum" https://t.co/hittsDWoJD”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  TRIBUNE execs cut in bloodbath...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/06/tribune-publishings-new-ceo-cuts-executives-in-bloodbath/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even the ax men are getting axed at Tribune Publishing. The struggling newspaper giant’s new boss has unleashed a bloodbath in the executive ranks — and casualties include a former New York Daily N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59.99% chance for reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/2020-odds-jump-for-trump-59-99-chance-for-reelection-16-7-for-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A week of strong job approval polls for President Trump has ended with the one survey that sizes up his chances for reelection, and the odds are nearly 60% that he will win a second term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Denies Spending $100M on Oscar Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/02/netflix-budget-oscar-campaigns-irishman-marriage-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody out-spends the deep-pocketed streamer when it comes to the Academy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk ready to connect brain with computer...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/359723/elon-musk-promises-awesome-neuralink-headset-that-links-brain-to-computer-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has tweeted that his brain-computer chip company Neuralink is working on an “awesome” version of the device. The kooky billionaire believes his brain interface tech will turn …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Tech Can See and ID People Through Walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2020/02/army-wants-technology-can-see-through-wallsand-identify-people-other-side/162873/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This sounds like science fiction—but for soldiers, it could soon be a reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 dogs captured after terrorizing neighborhood for months!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/3-dogs-captured-after-terrorizing-nj-neighborhood/2278692/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police officers captured three dogs that they say terrorized an Ocean County, New Jersey, neighborhood, biting at least a dozen people over the span of a few months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill to make voting mandatory introduced in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/californians-who-register-to-vote-would-be-required-to-cast-ballots-under-new-bill/ar-BBZH8db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Biblical plague' of bats forces town into lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/biblical-plague-bats-forces-town-21442650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bat-tornado was so intense that the local hospital's air ambulance was grounded as they made it impossible to fly in Ingham, Australia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'ultimate feminist' defending Harvey...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/donna-rotunno-harvey-weinstein-lawyer-profile-feminism-2020-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein's defense attorney Donna Rotunno has built a career out of defending men accused of rape. To date, she's lost only one case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man burns $1M in bonfires to avoid paying ex-wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-says-he-burned-1m-in-cash-to-avoid-paying-ex-wife-child-support</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Canadian businessman and failed mayoral candidate was thrown in jail for 30 days after telling a judge he burned 1 million Canadian dollars in cash to avoid paying his wife spousal and child support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Xi disappears... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/rumours-swirl-after-president-xi-21445247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The President hasn't been seen in public in several days and missed his regular media appearances - but Chinese social media users speculating about his whereabouts are being censored</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTE MIDLER TRUMP MELTDOWN: 'He Will Rule You Until HE DIES, YOU DIE, or BOTH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/bette-midler-takes-trumps-video-seriously-if-he-wins-again-he-will-rule-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“YOU THINK THIS IS A JOKE, DON’T YOU? IT’S NOT. HE MEANS IT,” actress Bette Midler warned Tuesday in reaction to a playful video posted by President Donald Trump after his Senate acquittal on both counts of impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana U defends 'Sex Fest' featuring BDSM demos, kink and toys...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=14332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“safe, sane, and consensual"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School District Calls Police After 6-Year-Old Girl Pretends To Shoot Teacher With Finger...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/02/04/exclusive-maggie-gaines-says-tredyffrin-easttown-school-district-called-police-after-6-year-old-daughter-with-down-syndrome-pretended-to-shoot-teacher-with-finger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Gaines says 6-year-old Margot, a student at Valley Forge Elementary School, now has a police record on file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY SETS BRUNO MARS MOVIE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/bruno-mars-disney-deal-live-action-theatrical-feature-flim-sean-bailehy-mitchell-leib-1202852299/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: After months of discussion, Disney has set a deal with Bruno Mars. The studio will develop a music-themed theatrical narrative feature that Mars will star in and produce. The plot is bei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi speculates President was drugged during State of Union...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/he-looked-sedated-pelosi-speculates-trump-was-drugged-during-sotu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi spent several minutes of her weekly press conference ripping President Trump’s State of the Union address. Without evidence, Pelosi told reporters Trump looked “a little sedated” as he prepared to deliver remarks to both houses of Congress and the American people. ﻿ “I welcomed the hand of friendship to him, welcome …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Red October' style hunt for Russian subs off East Coast failed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10904844/red-october-style-hunt-for-russian-subs-lasted-for-weeks-off-east-coast-as-navy-warns-waters-no-longer-safe-haven/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAJOR operation to track a deadly Russian sub off the East Coast has failed as the US Navy warns that US North Atlantic waters are no longer a ‘safe haven’. Navy Second Fleet command …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real data on virus leaked?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10904402/coronavirus-chinese-media-giant-lists-deaths-as-24589/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CHINESE media giant has sparked conspiracy theories after appearing to publish the coronavirus death toll as more than 24,589 – before changing it to 304. Tencent, the multinational tech co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snoop Dogg  unleashed on CBS anchor...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article240035398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impeachment over, but Trump and Roberts aren't done with each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Impeachment-is-over-but-Trump-and-Chief-Justice-15034863.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. has gotten an earful about President Donald Trump while presiding over the president's impeachment trial, and received a few words from the man himself Tuesday night at the State of the Union address.  The trial may be over, but these two are hardly done with each other.  Currently, the chief justice is either writing or reviewing the Supreme Court's decision on whether Trump acted within his power to end the program protecting young immigrant "dreamers" from deportation. A decision could come at any time before its term concludes at the end of June.  Next month, Roberts will call the court to order to decide whether Trump may shield his personal financial information from a congressional committee and New York prosecutor each investigating matters beyond the president's impeachment.  It ensures that controversies over investigations into Trump's conduct will continue into the heart of the presidential election campaign.  And on and on it will go.  Trump's expansive view of his powers has met an unprecedented legal pushback from Democrats and civil rights organizations, and the president's lawyers have not hesitated to run quickly to the conservative Supreme Court, which they see as a counterbalance to liberal federal judges.  Even as Roberts presided one day at the trial, the Supreme Court on a 5-to-4 vote granted an emergency request allowing the Trump administration to begin implementing new rules making it easier to deny immigrants residency or admission to the United States because they have used or might use public-assistance programs.  Roberts, who marked his 65th birthday attempting to "carry out ill-defined responsibilities in an unfamiliar setting," invited lawmakers to visit, saying the front row of the court is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Rips Impeachment Foes at Prayer Breakfast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7974205/Donald-Trump-Nancy-Pelosi-meet-National-Prayer-Breakfast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump slammed Nancy Pelosi and Mitt Romney for using their faith to justify their actions in the impeachment trial and inquiry during his remarks at the National Prayer Breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETTE MIDLER MELTDOWN: 'He Will Rule You Until HE DIES, YOU DIE, or BOTH'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/trump-trolls-impeachment-deprived-dems-new-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minutes after his acquittal in the Senate on both counts of impeachment on Tuesday, President Donald Trump celebrated by tweaking Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gayle King hits turbulence with Kobe Bryant rape questions...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/06/gayle-king-furious-with-cbs-for-viral-interview-about-kobe-bryant-rape-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King addressed the criticism Thursday on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
