<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BEN &amp; JERRY'S ice cream with CBD?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/ben-jerry-s-with-cbd/ar-AAKzgsN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben &amp; Jerry’s made a bold new flavor announcement in May 2019: CBD ice cream was coming ... “as soon as it’s legalized at the federal level.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Covid cases near  low...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/30/us-covid-cases-lowest-in-a-year-as-memorial-day-travel-picks-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11,976 new Covid-19 cases reported on May 29 were the lowest since March 23, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown in China...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-limits-travel-most-populous-094613554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese authorities imposed fresh travel limits, cancelled flights and tested thousands of residents in Guangdong Monday after the Indian variant of the coronavirus was reported in the country's most populous province.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday still subdued by pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531140733-3ksl5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-HOLIDAY/MEMORIALDAY (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. travelers on the road again with Memorial Day holiday still subdued by pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES FINAL CURTAIN</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531104812-din11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/NETANYAHU (TV, PIX):Israel's 'magician' Netanyahu faces final curtain after record run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS FOR FALLEN HEROES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/2988538/memorial-day-biden-lays-wreath-tomb-uknwown-soldier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden appeared to shed a tear as he laid a wreath at the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier during his first Memorial Day ceremony as president on Monday. Biden traveled to Arlington National Cemetary…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  INSTA star kills self on livestream after tying up and abusing girlfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2987224/s2k-wya-instagram-kills-himself-livestream-abusing-girlfriend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Instagram star live-streamed his final moments before killing himself after he led cops on a chase as they tried to arrest him for allegedly abusing his girlfriend. Angel Hernandez Grado, 28, wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of quakes rattles Disneyland visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article251798218.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“After a day of rides at Disneyland I thought maybe I was still feeling the Indiana Jones ride.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'First step to sanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/opinion/a-government-for-the-people-analysis-669648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naftali Bennett spoke like a uniter, someone who believes in bringing people together. The story of Israeli politics from now on, he explained, is not about “me, but about us."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu has ruled for total of 15 years...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-netanyahu-corner-change-alliance-104809180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli opposition leader Yair Lapid on Monday said many obstacles remain before a diverse coalition can be built to oust veteran Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu but voiced hope it will achieve the "greater goal".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Detectors Sweeping Country; Record Sales...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/31/the-new-detectorists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People have been metal detecting since 1881, when Alexander Graham Bell invented a device to find the bullet lodged in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Underlying Racism,' 'Human Zoo' Environment...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/adamzagoria/2021/05/30/kyrie-irving-calls-out-underlying-racism-human-zoo-environment-after-boston-fan-throws-water-bottle-gets-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Nets guard Kyrie Irving called out what he termed the “underlying racism” and “human zoo” environment in Boston after a fan threw a water bottle at his head as he was leaving the arena Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden commemorates war dead at Arlington National Cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/veterans-government-and-politics-3c14d961839b6bf0b4ecd20b5d7d2efd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Va. (AP) — President Joe Biden honored America’s war dead at Arlington National Cemetery on Memorial Day by laying a wreath at the hallowed burial ground. The president was joined on Monday by first lady Jill Biden, Vice President Kamala Harris and second gentleman Doug Emhoff in a somber ceremony at the Virginia cemetery's Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, which is dedicated to the fallen U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is sun going into hibernation?</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/is-our-sun-going-into-hibernation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each sunspot cycle has been getting less intense. Is our star falling asleep?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wine country, newspaper war brings down mayoral 'prince' accused of sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wine-country-newspaper-war-brings-120007624.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prize-winning Santa Rosa newspaper neglected accusations against Dominic Foppoli, until its former employee took the scoop to a competing paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Americans face eviction as housing protection expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/31/millions-of-americans-could-face-eviction-as-housing-protection-expires-in-june.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 11 million Americans are behind on their rent and many could face eviction when national housing protection expires in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF ROAD FOR BIBI?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-e2-80-99s-netanyahu-fights-to-block-opposition-parties-from-taking-power/ar-AAKyz30 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning to normal not simple for everyone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/31/health/us-coronavirus-monday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memorial Day weekend has brought back images of family gatherings and crowded beaches, but though things may look more normal, a clinical psychologist told CNN many people may still be dealing with emotional impacts from the Covid-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magician' Netanyahu faces final curtain after record run...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-politics-netanyahu/israels-magician-netanyahu-faces-final-curtain-after-record-run-idUSKCN2DC10M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long the familiar face of Israel, Benjamin Netanyahu has held on as prime minister for more than a decade, clinging to power through a criminal indictment and four elections in the past two years alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Junk Hits, Damages ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.iflscience.com/space/piece-space-junk-damaged-part-international-space-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iflscience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A robotic arm attached to the International Space Station (ISS) has been hit by a tiny piece of space junk, resulting in damage to its thermal blanket and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists hunt for 'Su' who could be mystery 'patient zero'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/scientists-hunt-patient-su-woman-24217556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The revelations come after British officials conceded this week that the possibility of a lab leak remains "plausible" - with mysterious "Patient Su" appearing to have been traced close to the Wuhan Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Biden, deeply personal Memorial Day weekend observance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-health-coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-memorial-day-c3886def81f78c762fd1e920148ef32a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW CASTLE, Del. (AP) — President Joe Biden marked his first Memorial Day weekend as commander in chief by honoring the nation’s sacrifices in a deeply personal manner as he paid tribute Sunday to those lost while remembering his late son Beau, a veteran who died six years ago to the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Hat Shop Selling Nazi-Style Jewish Stars Proclaiming 'Not Vaccinated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wkrn.com/news/more-hatmakers-cut-ties-with-nashville-hat-shop-after-controversial-instagram-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wkrn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Friday, the owner of hatWRKS hat shop on 8th Ave South in Nashville posted a photo to Instagram with a yellow patch resembling the Star of David along with the words “not vaccinated”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious B.I.G. executed by Nation of Islam convert arranged by Suge Knight, ex-FBI agent claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9634317/Notorious-B-G-executed-Nation-Islam-convert-hit-arranged-Suge-Knight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suge Knight (top right) allegedly paid a hitman to kill Notorious B.I.G. in LA in 1997 as revenge for Tupac Shakur's (bottom right) murder even though the intended target was Sean 'Diddy' Combs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark accused of helping USA spy on Merkel, European officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-57302806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denmark's secret service is accused of helping the US target politicians such as Germany's Angela Merkel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials worry rise in violent crime portends bloody summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/officials-worry-the-rise-in-violent-crime-portends-a-bloody-summer-e2-80-98it-e2-80-99s-trauma-on-top-of-trauma-e2-80-99/ar-AAKxyhR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the nation marks Memorial Day, the unofficial kickoff to summer, many officials are concerned violence could be especially pronounced this season as Americans emerge back into society after a year of coronavirus-related lockdowns and restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Shakeout Stirs Debate on Ether Shot at Usurping Bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-shakeout-stirs-debate-on-ether-e2-80-99s-shot-at-usurping-bitcoin/ar-AAKyqGI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The relative resilience of Ether in May’s cryptocurrency rout has put the spotlight back on the idea that the second-largest digital token could one day overtake Bitcoin by market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Moves to Three-Child Policy to Boost Falling Birthrate...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-57303592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Census results show China's population grew at its slowest pace in decades last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531094331-qp71v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/WHO-REFORMS (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-WHO, at heart of world's sluggish response to COVID, faces potential shake-up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210531003534-ol0dn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-JUSTICE/OATHKEEPERS:Four more Oath Keepers indicted in Jan. 6 federal conspiracy case: court filing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems walk, stop TX sweeping voting restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tx-state-wire-texas-government-and-politics-92d26e25c9db88a32e0fda890773b908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Texas Democrats pulled off a dramatic, last-ditch walkout in the state House of Representatives on Sunday night to block passage of one of the most restrictive voting bills in the U.S., leaving Republicans with no choice but to abandon a midnight deadline and declare the legislative session essentially over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do deficits matter anymore? Biden's first budget signals they don't...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/do-deficits-matter-anymore-biden-s-first-budget-signals-they-don-t/ar-AAKuHYg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s first budget predicts a $1.8 trillion deficit for 2022 and deficits of $1.3 trillion for years to come to fund big investments in education, infrastructure and the social safety net.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass shooting at Miami rap concert leaves 2 dead, 20 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/05/30/at-least-20-people-shot-2-killed-at-northwest-miami-dade-concert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victims were rushed to several hospitals in Miami-Dade and Broward counties after a shooting at a banquet hall, some in their personal vehicles, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS Fan Throws Bottle at Player...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/31/td-garden-fan-water-bottle-kyrie-irving-boston-celtics-brooklyn-nets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Players from both the Celtics and Nets condemned a fan who is now facing charges and a liftetime ban from TD Garden after throwing a water bottle at Nets guard Kyrie Irving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New lockdown in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/uptick-in-coronavirus-cases-prompts-chinese-city-to-lock-down-neighborhood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The southern Chinese city of Guangzhou has shut down a neighborhood and ordered residents to stay home for door-to-door coronavirus testing following an upsurge in infections that has rattled authorities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look inside all of Ellen DeGeneres' homes: Her $450M real estate portfolio!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/article/a-look-inside-all-of-ellen-degeneres-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ellen DeGeneres owns $63.3 million in homes and has sold $390 million in houses over the last 17 years, making an estimated $65 million profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Naftali Bennett...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210530163854-syuhk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Netanyahu's grip on power loosens as rival moves to unseat him</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
