<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Biden first to come close to acknowledging what conspiracy theorists assumed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/12/15/jfk-kennedy-assassination-documents-524221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the assassination files were supposed to be public in 2017. Donald Trump blocked them; Joe Biden is still holding some out. Why?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Man Wanted In Swastika-Drawing Spree Across Lower Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/12/15/swastika-vandalism-spree-lower-manhattan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows the man drawing a swastika on a pillar at City Hall on Monday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Bank robber deposited stolen loot in ATM outside branch...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/delaware-bank-robber-402618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DECEMBER 15--Moments after robbing a Wells Fargo branch in Delaware, a man deposited some of the stolen loot in an ATM outside the bank’s front door, according to police who arrested the suspect on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANCEL CHRISTMAS?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/17049449/daily-covid-cases-highest-level-ever-78k-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TODAY’S reported Covid cases are the highest daily total since the pandemic began, amid the new Omicron wave. A total of 78,610 infections were reported by the Government this afternoon, 15.5…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE JFK FILES RELEASED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4276966/jfk-assassination-documents-released-biden-keeping-more-classified/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW files regarding the assassination of President John F Kennedy have been released. While some of the files were released today, more secrets will be unveiled on the same date next year. The US P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police foil 'anti-vaxxer murder plot' against state premier...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/german-police-conduct-raids-saxony-over-anti-vaxxer-murder-plot-2021-12-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police have foiled a plot by anti-vaccination activists to murder the state premier of Saxony in eastern Germany, they said on Wednesday, as concerns grow over an increasingly violent pushback against COVID-19 vaccination plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail sales disappoint in November; Inflation tamping down spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/retail-sales-disappoint-in-november-raising-concerns-that-inflation-is-tamping-down-on-spending/ar-AARQlEW?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant may be no worse than flu, says govt adviser...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/health/medical/omicron-may-be-no-worse-than-flu-says-government-adviser/ar-AARNwve</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron may be no worse than flu, says former government adviser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly warns against gatherings...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/philadelphia-officials-urge-against-inter-household-christmas-gatherings-amid-covid-19-case-spike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Please do not get together with other households for Christmas," Philadelphia Health Commissioner Dr. Cherly Bettigole urged. The city has seen COVID-19 case counts double in recent weeks, while hospitalizations are up 50%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flamin' Hot Cheeto Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4265080/are-flamin-hot-cheetos-discontinued/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRITO-LAY’s signature snack, Flamin’ Hot Cheetos, is reportedly in a shortage. Rumors of the beloved “hot chip” being discontinued have started circulating across the intern…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OFFLINE:  NETFLIX, XBOX, HULU and more all down in mass outage as angry users report errors...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech-old/4277713/xbox-playstation-hulu-netflix-down-mass-outage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MASS outage appears to have affected some of the major apps as frustrated users claim they can’t access them. Xbox, Playstation, Hulu, Netflix and more are all experiencing issues according…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate grills on cancellations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/15/airline-ceos-face-senate-panel-over-flight-cancellations-after-taking-54-billion-in-taxpayer-aid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines are now scrambling to hire workers after pushing tens of thousands of employees to take leaves of absence or buyouts during the Covid pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J Shot Loses ALL Antibody Protection Against Omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/j-j-shot-shows-no-neutralization-against-omicron-in-lab-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp; Johnson’s vaccine produces virtually no antibody protection against the omicron variant in a laboratory experiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auschwitz-Style Banner at Polish Protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2021-12-15/shameful-auschwitz-style-banner-at-polish-covid-vaccine-protest-condemned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgery delays grow at hospitals dealing with COVID...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-technology-health-business-minnesota-10bef4d91a41dba291a4e93c9115070e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Minnesota health care systems say surgery delays are growing as coronavirus patients crowd hospitals. Doctors say hospitals have deferred procedures to free up beds, leaving some patients in prolonged pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATALITIES SPIKE IN PREGNANT WOMEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4276552/spike-pregnant-people-dying-covid-vaccine-hesitancy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEWLY released CDC data has shown a spike in pregnant people dying of Covid with 40 percent of deaths occurring in the last four months as vaccines have been refused. The CDC released new informati…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER to Penalize Users Who Claim Vaccinated People Can Spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/twitter-to-penalize-users-who-claim-vaccinated-people-can-spread-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter will begin imposing penalties up to a permanent ban on users who claim that vaccinated people can spread Covid-19, according to a change quietly added to the website's terms of service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misinformation Has Already Made Its Way to Metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/misinformation-has-already-made-its-way-to-the-metaverse/ar-AARQtwE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love him or hate him, Jake Paul in it for long haul...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/jake-paul-is-it-long-haul-2021-12-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Love him or hate him, boxing fans had better get used to Jake Paul after the YouTuber-turned-prizefighter told Reuters he had no intention of ever walking away from the sport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEHRAN TIMES reveals Iran targets in Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/tehran-times-publishes-targets-iran-will-attack-in-israel-688785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly trade-offs, by the numbers: How each state has fared...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2021/covid-by-the-numbers-how-each-state-fared-on-our-pandemic-scorecard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICO’s State Pandemic Scorecard shows how state decisions impacted lives, jobs, education and well-being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Previously classified JFK assassination documents expected to be released...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/15/politics/biden-administration-jfk-documents/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration faces a Wednesday deadline to publicly release a tranche of secret documents that some historians -- and conspiracy theorists -- hope might shed light on the 1963 assassination of President John F. Kennedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to get first female police commissioner to lead nation's largest force...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/us/keechant-sewell-nyc-first-female-police-commissioner/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City will get its first female police commissioner to lead the nation's largest police department, after Mayor-elect Eric Adams picked Nassau County Chief of Detectives Keechant Sewell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Sales Trail Forecast, Suggesting Drag From Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/u-retail-sales-climbed-less-133200920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. retail sales rose by less than forecast in November, suggesting that consumers are tempering purchases against a backdrop of the fastest inflation in decades.Most Read from BloombergZero Taxes, Golf and Beach Houses Create a Crypto Island ParadiseCan Indoor Farms Reach Skyscraper Height?China Is Building the World’s Largest National Park SystemBoris Johnson’s Furious MPs Worry That His Next Misstep Could Be FatalThe value of overall retail purchases increased 0.3%, the smalle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB reveals top searches '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4276021/pornhub-year-in-review-most-searched-hentai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORNHUB has exposed what horny Americans and Brits have been looking for in the past year – and there’s a new favourite in town. Hentai porn is now the XXX site’s most searched te…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCETON, CORNELL Move Finals Online...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/cornell-imposes-lockdown-after-omicron-is-detected-on-campus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cornell Imposes Lockdown After Omicron Is Detected on Campus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia reopens borders closed since March '20 to vaccinated non-citizens...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/585870-australia-reopens-borders-closed-since-march-2020-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia reopened its borders on Wednesday to skilled migrants and foreign students who have received a coronavirus vaccine more than a year and a half after they were closed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary 2024? Given competition, she may be Dems' best hope?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/585843-hillary-2024-given-the-competition-she-may-be-the-dems-best-hope</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary is 74 years old, which is like being bathed in the fountain of youth compared to Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges go back to drawing board -- again...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-new-york-syracuse-6686dfd1111baea6fb54791a26d232b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing rising infections and a new COVID-19 variant, colleges across the U.S. have once again been thwarted in seeking a move to normalcy and are starting to require booster shots, extend mask mandates, limit social gatherings and, in some cases, revert to online classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus case cuts short Blinken tour of Asia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-indonesia-journalists-asia-95eeb4ea633c7c8ca89bad795e7fe4bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KUALA LUMPUR, Malaysia (AP) — A positive COVID-19 test among U.S. Secretary of State Blinken’s traveling party has cut short the top diplomat’s first official tour of Southeast Asia. A member of the press corps accompanying Blinken on what was to have been a three-nation visit to Indonesia, Malaysia and Thailand tested positive for the coronavirus on Wednesday in Kuala Lumpur, forcing Blinken to abandon the program at his next and last stop in Bangkok, and return to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTACART driver saw elderly couple's thin blue line flag. So she ran ove groceries...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-instacart-driver-saw-an-elderly-couple-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98thin-blue-line-e2-80-99-flag-so-she-ran-over-their-groceries-police-say/ar-AARPCSv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One year of 'President Manchin': For Dem agenda, all roads go through W Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/one-year-of-president-manchin-for-the-democratic-agenda-all-roads-go-through-west-virginia/ar-AARPTBJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over-65s in France without booster to lose health pass benefits...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211215-french-adults-over-65-without-a-covid-booster-shot-to-lose-health-pass-benefits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France on Wednesday begins implementing a new tightening of rules in the fight against Covid-19, meaning people aged 65 and over will lose the validity of their health pass unless they have had a thi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cards starts in UK despite biggest rebellion of Johnson era...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-59662142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over-18s must now prove they are double-jabbed, or have a recent negative test, to enter certain venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kennedy built anti-vaccine juggernaut amid COVID-19...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-business-health-public-health-4997be1bcf591fe8b7f1f90d16c9321e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Robert F. Kennedy Jr. strode onto the stage at a Southern California church, radiating Kennedy confidence and surveying the standing ovation crowd with his piercing blue Bobby Kennedy eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine lawyers to focus defense on 'memory, manipulation and money'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211215105734-ph3o9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (PIX):Ghislaine Maxwell's lawyers to focus her defense on 'memory, manipulation and money'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Celebrates as Judge Orders Release of Giuffre's Settlement With Epstein...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/prince-andrews-team-celebrates-as-judge-orders-release-of-virginia-giuffres-settlement-with-epstein</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew has long argued that Virginia Giuffre’s 2009 deal with Epstein shields him from legal action by her. Now, judges say it should be made public early next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxpayers spent billions bailing out airlines. Did industry hold up end of deal?</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Taxpayers-spent-billions-bailing-out-airlines-16702961.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bailout of U.S. airlines under Presidents Donald Trump and Joe Biden was meant to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed expected to take very big step toward first rate hike...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/14/the-federal-reserve-is-expected-to-take-a-very-big-step-toward-its-first-rate-hike.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve is expected to announce a dramatic policy shift Wednesday that will clear the way for a first interest rate hike next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin, Xi Show United Front Amid Rising Tensions With USA...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/15/putin-and-xi-show-united-front-amid-rising-tensions-with-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — President Biden may have his alliance of democracies, but Russia and China still have each other. Xi Jinping</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Executes People for Watching K-Pop, Rights Group Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/15/north-korea-executes-people-for-watching-k-pop-rights-group-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL — North Korea has publicly executed at least seven people in the past decade for watching or distributing K-pop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On single street, twister killed 7 children...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tornadoes-lifestyle-europe-kentucky-bowling-green-6a7098a304b1a5ba130e28be89aa0f22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOWLING GREEN, Ky. (AP) — The little red wagon was strewn upside down on a heap of rubble — a pile of boards and bricks, a mangled blue bicycle, a baby doll. Behind it, there was little more than a hole in the ground where a house had stood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police stage raids after threats to pro-vax politician...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211215-german-police-stage-raids-after-threats-to-pro-vaccine-politician</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police and special forces on Wednesday launched an operation in the eastern city of Dresden after death threats were issued against a top politician who backs coronavirus vaccines, authorities…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultraconservative candidate Jose Antonio Kast vows to save Chile from communism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-ultra-conservative-who-vows-to-save-chile-from-communism/ar-AARKV5t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneur reflects on space journey aboard Bezos rocket:  'I'm a different person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/e2-80-98i-e2-80-99m-a-different-person-e2-80-99-miami-beach-entrepreneur-reflects-on-space-journey-aboard-bezos-e2-80-99-rocket/ar-AARNoye?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of DUAL infection?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/17035413/dual-infection-omicron-and-delta-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE is a very real risk of getting a “dual infection” from both Omicron and Delta, a top vaccine boss has warned today. Dr Paul Burton, chief medical officer for Moderna, said: “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  Variant spreading rapidly, could bring punishing wave of infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/omicron-spreading-rapidly-in-u-s-could-bring-punishing-wave-as-soon-as-january-cdc-warns/ar-AAROACj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gwyneth Paltrow-Backed Crypto Miner Tumbles in Debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/gwyneth-paltrow-backed-crypto-miner-terawulf-tumbles-in-debut/ar-AAROpE5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital media companies begin merging with their biggest rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/why-companies-like-vox-media-are-merging-with-their-biggest-rivals/ar-AAROMXM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN:  TIME FOR MUSK TO PAY TAXES!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/585830-musk-hits-back-after-warren-accuses-him-of-freeloading</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk hit back at Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) on Tuesday, saying she reminded him of an "angry mom" after the progressive senator accused the billionaire and entrepreneur of "freeloading" on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House to vote on Meadows criminal contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/house-expected-vote-mark-meadows-criminal-contempt-referral-n1285908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meadows, who was White House chief of staff at the time, has refused to answer questions about the Jan. 6 attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Sued by More Women Alleging Sex Harassment at Plant...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-labor-report/tesla-sued-by-more-women-alleging-sexual-harassment-at-plant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc.’s factory in Fremont, California, is more like a crude frat house than a facility owned by a cutting-edge company in the heart of a progressive region, six women who are current and former employees claimed in the latest barrage of lawsuits to hit Tesla over alleged sexual harassment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spiritual but not religious'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-religion-0722d2f1484d38163d75b32b6f095ddf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nathalie Charles, even in her mid-teens, felt unwelcome in her Baptist congregation, with its conservative views on immigration, gender and sexuality. So she left. “I just don’t feel like that gelled with my view of what God is and what God can be,” said Charles, an 18-year-old of Haitian descent who identifies as queer and is now a freshman at Princeton University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona hospitals stretched to limit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-arizona-c1b3db28b716c388035ac1e344243717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Phoenix-based Banner Health is at its most overwhelmed since the pandemic began, leading the company's officials to issue a warning Tuesday that its hospital system may have to eventually choose who can receive care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS:  San Francisco mayor pledges more police, safety measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-police-san-francisco-9210b1e49ad00f0001532a2d50bead81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco's mayor announced Tuesday even more initiatives aimed at curbing open drug use, brazen home break-ins and other criminal behavior that she says have made a mockery of the city's famed tolerance and compassion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge scraps lawsuit to shield tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/14/trump-tax-returns-legal-524235</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the judge stayed the impact of his ruling for 14 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK suspends mandate for employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/amtrak-suspends-vaccine-mandate-for-employees/ar-AAROult</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Prices Go Haywire on COINBOSE, Other Providers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/crypto-prices-go-haywire-on-coinbase-coinmarketcapcom/ar-AAROSi1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPs back passes in England despite huge Tory rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-59659851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 100 Tory MPs defy Boris Johnson - but the measures become law thanks to Labour support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping can make you more creative...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/mental-health/585828-sleeping-can-make-you-more-creative-new-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There is a creative sweet spot within the sleep-onset period, and hitting it requires individuals balancing falling asleep easily against falling asleep too deeply,” researchers wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She Met Guy on FACEBOOK. Then Mowed Him Down Outside...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/she-met-guy-facebook-then-222558994.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State of Wisconsin Department of JusticeA Wisconsin woman is charged with first-degree murder after allegedly killing a man she had recently met online, by stabbing him then intentionally running him over, after which she circled the block and ran down the victim again “to make sure he was dead,” according to a criminal complaint filed in Milwaukee County Circuit Court.Lydia Carmona-Cartagena, 23, appeared in court Monday on charges of first-degree intentional homicide and use of a dangerous wea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don's Fraud Inquiry's Focus: Did He Mislead His Own Accountants?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-fraud-inquiry-s-focus-did-he-mislead-his-own-accountants/ar-AAROBLM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agents investigated for allegedly soliciting prostitution on assignment overseas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/politics/fbi-soliciting-prostitution/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six FBI agents were investigated for allegedly soliciting prostitution, trafficking drugs and failing to report unofficial interactions for foreign nationals while on assignment overseas, a Justice Department watchdog says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billie Eilish began watching porn at 11: 'Destroyed my brain'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/14/billie-eilish-says-porn-has-destroyed-her-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I think it really destroyed my brain and I feel incredibly devastated that I was exposed to so much porn,” she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don's Fraud Inquiry's Focus: Did He Mislead His Own Accountants?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/14/trump-fraud-inquirys-focus-did-he-mislead-his-own-accountants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As prosecutors in Manhattan weigh whether to charge Donald J. Trump with fraud, they have zeroed in on financial documents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli mall entry to require 'Green Pass'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/covid-in-israel-shopping-malls-to-operate-under-green-pass-outline-688737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House cancels Christmas parties due to Omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10306353/Biden-administration-sends-invites-holiday-tours-sign-parties-canceled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and first lady Jill Biden have canceled White House holiday parties will instead host 'Holiday Open Houses' for visitors to view the decorations in the executive mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORNELL shuts campus after surge detected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/us/cornell-university-covid-cases/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cornell University is shutting down its Ithaca, New York, campus and moving to "alert level red" after what the school described as a "rapid spread" of Covid-19 among students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Politicians Now Settling Disputes With MMA Fighting...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/wxdnvx/brazilian-politicians-are-now-settling-disputes-with-mma-fighting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two politicians had been arguing over a waterpark project and decided to settle things by getting in the ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson Suffers Biggest Tory Revolt Over New Covid Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/boris-johnson-suffers-biggest-tory-revolt-over-covid-rules/ar-AAROsLJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA craft 'touches' sun for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-sun-cdb6e773cbe6fea2c7225bea213701c2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — A NASA spacecraft has officially “touched” the sun, plunging through the unexplored solar atmosphere known as the corona. Scientists announced the news Tuesday during a meeting of the American Geophysical Union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin millionaire who retired at 35 complains being rich 'boring'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/bitcoin-millionaire-who-retired-35-25698602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who threw his life savings into the cryptocurrency Bitcoin and became a millionaire has said that being rich is boring and that he didn't deserve to be able to retire early</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Diet' soda disappearing from store shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/14/business-food/diet-soda-zero-sugar/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you make your way through the soda aisle, you may notice a lot less of the word "diet" than you used to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OJ Simpson 'completely free'; Parole ends...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/college-football-sports-entertainment-business-arts-and-entertainment-110d82684a8599f35deb0dd8529d6acb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — O.J. Simpson is a free man. The 74-year-old former football hero and actor, acquitted California murder defendant and convicted Las Vegas armed robber was granted good behavior credits and discharged from parole effective Dec.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate moves forward on raising debt ceiling by $2.5 TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/14/democrats-raise-debt-ceiling-524204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The amount is expected to carry spending until after the 2022 midterms, preventing another standoff over the debt limit until after elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of Work: 60-Year Career...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/careersandeducation/the-future-of-work-is-a-60-year-career/ar-AAROm5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 100-year-old newspaper became go-to way to influence Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/14/joe-biden-news-journal-ad-targeting-524196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the Biden era, the pages of The News Journal have become a way to reach a new audience of one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starup Pitched Tasing Migrants from Drones...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2021/12/13/brinc-startup-taser-drones-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well-funded Brinc positions its use of robots as nonviolent, but an early promo video undercuts this message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston STARBUCKS workers seek to unionize after Buffalo vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-boston-buffalo-labor-unions-4813d76fc45dbcf4ddc8fa5b11505d8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — Starbucks workers at two locations in Boston are looking to unionize, days after a successful union vote at a Starbucks in Buffalo, New York, a first for the 50-year-old coffee retailer in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tells Israel new tanker jets, key to Iran strike, not coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/us-tells-israel-tanker-jets-key-to-iran-strike-wont-arrive-anytime-soon-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to NYT, during his visit to DC Defense Minister Gantz asked to accelerate delivery of KC-46 refueling planes but was told first aircraft unlikely to arrive before 2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea sees deadliest day after attempt to return to normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/south-korea-sees-deadliest-day-of-pandemic-after-attempt-to-return-to-normalcy/ar-AAROebT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo ordered to return $5.1M pandemic book profits to state...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/14/andrew-cuomo-ordered-to-return-pandemic-book-profits-to-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The extraordinary resolution was approved by the Joint Commission on Public Ethics Tuesday in a 12 to 1 vote.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
