<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>USA is the accidental Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/07/15/covid19-accidental-sweden-fall-could-be-catastrophic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden's light-handed restrictions produced results similar to those in countries with stricter policies because Swedes voluntarily self-isolated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible hand: Patients not told of AI systems advising their care...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/07/15/artificial-intelligence-patient-consent-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of prominent hospitals are using AI-powered tools to advise patient care. But patients often aren't informed, a STAT examination finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret order gives CIA more powers to launch cyberattacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/secret-trump-order-gives-cia-more-powers-to-launch-cyberattacks-090015219.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Central Intelligence Agency has conducted a series of covert cyber operations against Iran and other targets since winning a secret victory in 2018 when President Trump signed what amounts to a sweeping authorization for such activities, according to former U.S. officials with direct knowledge of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli doc claims to 'reverse' aging with pure oxygen treatment study...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-doctor-claims-to-reverse-aging-with-pure-oxygen-treatment-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers aged 65-plus ended up with sharper brains after sessions in a special oxygen chamber, says Shai Efrati. One volunteer: 'I entered healthy and left a tiger'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Fires Back: 'Bizarre' White House Behavior Hurts President...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/07/trump-fauci-coronavirus-pandemic-oppo/614224/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s top public-health expert tells The Atlantic that he isn’t going anywhere, despite the Trump administration’s newest attempts to undercut him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Police Use Drones To Spot Nude Beachgoers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90528260/report-minnesota-cops-use-drones-to-spot-nude-beachgoers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police used the aircraft to spot people in the nude but ultimately left amid pushback from the beachgoing crowd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maskless mob confronts French prez, wife...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/15/frances-macron-wife-confronted-by-protesters-on-bastille-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron’ and his wife Brigitte were confronted by maskless protesters during a Bastille Day stroll in a public garden, raising new concerns about their security arrangement…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela tightens measures in capital...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuela-tightens-covid-19-measures-capital-surge-153755802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro announced on Wednesday a tightening of containment measures in the capital Caracas and neighboring Miranda state to try to halt the spread of the coronavirus. According to official figures, Venezuela was one of the least affected countries in Latin America by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freed from gag order...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/books/2020/07/14/mary-trump-says-donald-trump-utterly-incapable-being-president/5439601002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump delivers a withering assessment of President Trump in first post-gag order interview to promote her book, "Too Much and Never Enough."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC AND GUARDIAN ANNOUNCE HUNDREDS OF CUTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejournal.ie/bbc-guardian-job-cuts-5150987-Jul2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejournal.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC intends to implement 520 cuts and The Guardian newspaper plans to axe 180 jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women say life is 'like scary movie' as vrius spreads in Fort Worth prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article244167007.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative alternative to TWITTER wants to be place for free speech for all; Rules still apply... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Conservative-alternative-to-Twitter-wants-to-be-15409996.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In late June, two days after Twitter put a fifth warning label on one of President Donald Trump's tweets, Sen. Ted Cruz, R-Texas, tweeted that he was joining Parler, calling it "a platform [that] gets what free speech is all about."  The social media site, which has been described as a conservative Twitter, is on a tear with people who say Twitter and Facebook are silencing conservative voices. In one week, it gained 1 million users, bringing its total to 2.8 million by early July.  Some of its most prominent users are part of the conservative establishment. Trump campaign director Brad Parscale is on Parler, as is Eric Trump, the president's son, and White House press secretary Kayleigh McEnany. Conservative commentator Dan Bongino announced in mid-June that he had taken an ownership stake in the company.  A crackdown by Twitter and, more reluctantly, Facebook, against messages from President Trump that the companies said violate their policies is fueling Parler's rise. Parler bills itself as a place for "free expression without violence and a lack of censorship," key words that many conservatives have picked up as a rallying cry to promote the app online.  Parler chief executive and co-founder John Matze said the app welcomes all voices. But the company appears to cater to a right-wing base fed up with what they view as censorship on traditional social media sites.  "We initially attracted conservative users because they felt disenfranchised by other social media platforms," Matze said in an email sent through a spokesperson.  But Parler is quickly discovering the limits of free expression. On June 30, Matze took to Parler to explain its house rules, apparently frustrated with some of Parler's new users testing the limits of its free-expression motto by posting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service braces for mail-in ballot issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Postal-Service-braces-for-mail-in-ballot-issues-15410083.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Postal workers found three tubs of uncounted absentee ballots the day after the Wisconsin primary. Some Ohioans did not receive their ballots in time for the election because of mail delays. And in Dallas, absentee ballots some voters sent to the county were returned just days before Election Day, with no explanation.  Problems caused by a spike in absentee voting during this year's primaries are serving as potential warning signs for the U.S. Postal Service, which is bracing for an expected onslaught of mail-in ballots this fall as states and cities push alternatives to in-person voting because of the pandemic.  The concern extends to local elections offices that may be unaccustomed to aspects of the mail, such as the time it takes for parcels to reach their destinations and how to design their ballots to meet postal standards.  So the Postal Service is regularly sending advice and checklists to thousands of elections officials. Local elections offices are hiring temporary workers to process absentee ballots, and some local elections boards are adding options for voters to do curbside drop-offs of their mail ballots on Election Day.  The Postal Service is also recommending that voters request their ballots at least 15 days before Election Day and mail their completed ballots at least one week before the due date.  "Voters: We all have the power to make it better in November," said Tammy Patrick, elections expert and senior adviser to the Democracy Fund, a bipartisan group. "Just because you can [wait until] the deadline, doesn't mean you should."  In a statement to The Washington Post, the Postal Service said it was working closely with state and local elections officials to head off problems in the fall.  "As we anticipate that many voters may choose to use the mail to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OKLAHOMA GOVERNOR, 47, TESTS POSITIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-oklahoma-governor-kevin-stitt-45e8c591-511c-4880-bbe7-8b6c7e66fd27.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's believed to be the first governor to test positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval at record low...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign-polls/507413-trump-approval-at-record-low-among-battleground-voters-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s approval rating hit a record low of 45 percent among likely voters in six battleground states, according to a CNBC-Change Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the life of tech CEO found in pieces...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/15/who-was-fahim-saleh-the-tech-ceo-brutally-dismembered-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tech CEO who tweeted a nighttime shot of his luxury East Houston Street apartment building — where police discovered his chopped-up body scattered in garbage bags in his seventh-floor apa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HORRORS: Corpse found wrapped in plastic bag on roof of Bronx MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/15/mans-corpse-found-wrapped-in-bag-on-roof-of-nyc-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dead man — or part of one — wrapped in a plastic bag was discovered early Wednesday on the roof of a Bronx McDonald’s, cops and sources told The Post. The body of the man, who has not yet b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami outbreak 'comparable to Wuhan'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/14/florida-nurse-warns-nursing-shortage-hit-state-covid-hospital-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other states are worried about the coronavirus straining their hospital systems. More than 8,000 people in Florida alone are now hospitalized with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened To Record Income Taxes Americans Paid Last Year?</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/what-happened-record-income-taxes-americans-paid-last-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In fiscal 2019, the federal government collected a total of 3,462,196,000,000 in various taxes, according to the Monthly Treasury Statement. But is also spent a record $4,446,584,000,000 in that same year. So, what are Americans getting for the dollars the federal government extracts from their income?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina city votes to give reparations to Black residents...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1142664/north-carolina-city-will-give-reparations-to-black-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IN A historic move, one US city has apologized for its role in slavery and voted in favor of providing reparations to its African-American community. The vote to provide reparations passed unanimou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Dogs Not To Blame For Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dogs-not-to-blame-for-covid-19-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say the research that claims dogs passed the coronavirus onto humans is ‘scientifically flawed.’ AURORA, Colo. — Rest easy, dog lovers. Our beloved canine companions aren’t responsible for the COVID-19 pandemic, new research shows. A study from earlier this year claims the SARS-CoV-2 virus made the jump to humans via dogs. Now, a new collaborative project…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Woolery's Son Tests Positive After Game Show Host Said 'Everyone is Lying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2020/07/14/chuck-woolerys-son-gets-covid-connection-tests-positive-for-virus-after-game-show-host-said-everyone-is-lying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lost in the confusion of yesterday’s Tweets, ex game show host Chuck Woolery made a startling admission. His son has tested positive for coronavirus. That’s one day after Donald Trump r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 2020 Hits, NETFLIX Rewriting Summer Blockbuster Script...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/with-2020-hits-netflix-is-rewriting-the-summer-blockbuster-script/ar-BB16L4o0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX HYPE!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/covid-vaccine-front-runner-is-months-ahead-of-her-competition/ar-BB16KxaR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hazmat Suit for Air Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/hazmat-suits-for-air-travel-are-here/ar-BB16Kln4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor of Hialeah says DeSantis refused to let him into meeting...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/state-politics/article244218502.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami outbreak 'comparable to Wuhan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/doctor-miami-becoming-epicenter-of-pandemic-comparable-to-wuhan-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida's rapidly increasing number of coronavirus cases is turning Miami into the “epicenter of the pandemic,” a top doctor warned Monday, while an epidemiologist called the region's situation “extremely grave.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE FISH WITH HUMAN TEETH...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/internet-wowed-fish-human-teeth-22360307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The triggerfish family have baffled the internet with their teeth which they us to fight sea urchins and crabs with their bite being so powerful it can puncture diving suits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ghislaine Maxwell Locked up until July 2021 trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8518795/Ghislaine-Maxwell-pleads-not-guilty-fights-5M-bail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell, 58, was denied bail on Tuesday as a judge ruled she must stay locked up until her trial in July of 2021. She is being held at the Metropolitan Detention Center in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida has 9 of 20 metro areas with worst daily outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/florida-coronavirus-cases-deaths-2ce489c7-3eb8-4675-8a42-5b2306e7023a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state announced its highest number of deaths yet yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor warns 'dangerously close' to rolling back...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/07/15/mayor-lori-lightfoot-warns-city-might-have-to-move-back-to-phase-3-if-covid-cases-continue-to-rise-we-are-on-the-precipice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we continue to see this uptick in cases, we’re going to have no choice but to go back into Phase 3," the mayor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus resurgence forces countries to reimpose restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/605b05fe86eef1d927fbc21a371d623a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROMACHONAS, Greece (AP) — Countries around the world are reimposing lockdowns and implementing new health checks at their borders in an effort to curb a resurgence of the coronavirus before it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROAD KILL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2f16dba053e6c8d29f8b742261cf51e9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOBILE, Ala. (AP) — Jeff Sessions took the stage with the same sense of conviction he had displayed in giddier times at a Mobile stadium almost five years ago, declaring once more that Donald...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Joy Reid Faces Revived Libel Claim Upon Big Appellate Decision...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/msnbc-host-joy-reid-faces-revived-libel-claim-big-appellate-decision-1303284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley could hit 130 degrees; Hottest temp ever recorded...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/death-valley-temperatures-130-record-heat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The temperature hit 129.2 degrees on June 30, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000-DEGREE fire burns for 4th day on Navy Ship in San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8524453/Explosion-threat-eases-burning-Navy-warship-San-Diego.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Efforts to control the blaze inside the 844-foot ship in San Diego continued for a fourth consecutive day Wednesday, with officials voicing optimism the inferno could finally be extinguished later today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan 'extremely concerned' by growing outbreak on U.S. bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/japan-okinawa-covid-extremely-concerned-growing-coronavirus-outbreak-on-us-military-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before the outbreak on U.S. bases, the island of Okinawa had confirmed only 148 coronavirus cases, now there are at least 284.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART to require all customers to wear masks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/507431-walmart-to-require-all-customers-to-wear-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart announced on Wednesday it will require shoppers to wear a face covering starting on July 20 in all stores and clubs across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces unprecedented opposition --  from own party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-singular-danger-president-faces-100008098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican anti-Trump groups aim to convince just enough GOP voters that it's OK to support a Democrat to oust this president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emu bites Bolsanaro during quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/emu-bird-pecks-brazils-bolsonaro-135758755.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jair Bolsonaro, the president of Brazil, has reportedly been bitten by an emu-like bird while trying to feed it during his coronavirus quarantine at the presidential palace in Brasilia. According to local outlet Metropóles, Mr Bolsonaro was “pecked” by a rhea bird while he was out on an afternoon stroll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AC makes spread worse?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/07/15/covid-air-conditioning-could-facilitate-coronavirus-airborne-spread/5429919002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say some features in a typical HVAC system, such as ventilation and filtration, isn't enough to protect you against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will lack of sex force players to break NBA bubble?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2020/jul/15/humans-need-it-will-a-lack-of-sex-force-players-to-break-the-nbas-bubble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the league resumes at the end of the month, players will be without their partners for weeks. Coping without intimacy could be tough to deal with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ENTOURAGE' Star Kevin Connolly Accused of Sexual Assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/entourage-star-kevin-connolly-accused-of-sexual-assault-i-want-it-to-be-known-that-he-is-dangerous</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Costume designer Gracie Cox alleges the actor/director attacked her at a wrap party for his directorial debut “The Gardener of Eden,” produced by his best pal Leonardo DiCaprio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret spouse she won't reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1140252/ghislaine-maxwell-secretly-married-reveal-prosecutors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell is secretly MARRIED but won’t reveal who to, say American prosecutors. Evidence however points to this secret husband possibly being tech company CEO Scott Borgerson, 43, wh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: At Least Seven Ships on Fire in Iran Port...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200715122556-a24j0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-FIRE/BUSHEHR (URGENT):Seven ships catch fire at southern port - Tasnim agency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's 'dysfunctional' upbringing created 'dangerous situation' for US, niece claims...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/president-trumps-dysfunctional-upbringing-created-dangerous-situation-america/story?id=71788912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's niece, Mary Trump, said her uncle is "utterly incapable of leading this country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUARDIAN cuts 180 jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2020/jul/15/guardian-announces-plans-to-cut-180-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revenues expected to be down by more than £25m as effects of pandemic hit media industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Found Wrapped in Plastic on Roof of MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/body-found-wrapped-in-plastic-on-roof-of-nyc-mcdonalds-police/2516810/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are investigating the death of a man who was found wrapped in a plastic bag on the roof of a McDonald’s in the Bronx early Wednesday, police say. Cops got a 911 call about an unconscious person on the roof of the fast-food restaurant on East 149th Street shortly before 6 a.m. He was pronounced dead at the scene….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump heads to Georgia, one of the new battleground states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-georgia-battleground-2020-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest CBS News Battleground Tracker poll rates Georgia as a toss-up for the presidential election; currently, Biden leads Trump by two points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hazmat Suit for Air Travel...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/biovyzr-hazmat-suits-aim-to-make-flying-safer-during-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Haute hazmats are just the thing to make flying feel safe again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX HYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2020-07-15/oxford-s-covid-19-vaccine-is-the-coronavirus-front-runner?srnd=premium</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantines or not, Americans descend on vacation spots...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200715091342-n2m0w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/NEW MEXICO (PIX):Quarantines or not, Americans descend on summer vacation spots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans bars reclose...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/241a391d6eac4eba2eef24f1aa6ad862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — It's a fresh taste of bitter medicine for New Orleans: A sharp increase in COVID-19 cases and hospitalizations is forcing bars in the good-time-loving, tourist-dependent city to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated by lockdown? Iceland offers to release screams over loudspeaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/discover/frustrated-by-lockdown-iceland-offers-to-release-your-screams-over-loudspeaker-1011253.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The idea is inspired by so-called scream therapy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: At Least Three Ships on Fire in Iran Port...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/at-least-three-ships-on-fire-in-iran-s-bushehr-port</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Least Three Ships on Fire in Iranâ€™s Bushehr Port</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With 2020 Hits, NETFLIX Rewriting Summer Blockbuster Script...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/with-2020-hits-netflix-is-rewriting-the-summer-blockbuster-script</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With 2020 Hits, Netflix Is Rewriting the Summer Blockbuster Script</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media App PARLER, GOP Darling, Isn't Catching On...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2020-07-15/social-media-app-parler-a-gop-darling-isn-t-catching-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public's disconnect from COVID-19 reality worries experts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/507334-publics-disconnect-from-covid-19-reality-worries-experts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is being ravaged by a deadly pandemic that is growing exponentially, overwhelming health care systems and costing thousands of lives, to say nothing of an economic recession that threatens to plague the nation for years to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers Warn Of 'Jaw Dropping' Crash In Fertility Rate...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/07/15/researchers-warn-of-jaw-dropping-crash-in-global-fertility-rate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ 'Fear Gauge' Flashes Warning Signs About Tech Rally...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-fear-gauge-flashes-warning-100943874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- There are more signs of possible trouble ahead for high-flying technology stocks, this time from gauges of expected volatility.One alert stems from the widest spread since 2004 between the Cboe NDX Volatility Index, a measure of implied equity swings for the Nasdaq-100, and the counterpart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepfake used to attack activist couple shows new disinformation frontier...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cyber-deepfake-activist-idUSKCN24G15E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oliver Taylor, a student at England's University of Birmingham, is a twenty-something with brown eyes, light stubble, and a slightly stiff smile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uses Rose Garden event for extended attack on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-uses-Rose-Garden-event-for-extended-attack-15408585.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump on Tuesday held a Rose Garden event under the guise of punishing China over its crackdown on Hong Kong, delivering a lengthy diatribe against Democratic rival Joe Biden in a display that resembled a campaign speech at the White House.  The president began his rambling 54-minute opening statement by announcing that he had signed congressional legislation that authorizes his administration to enact sanctions on banks that do business with Chinese officials and an executive order to revoke Hong Kong's special economic trading status. But he glossed over the specifics and said nothing about the pro-democracy protests on the island as he pivoted swiftly to his attacks on Biden, the presumptive Democratic presidential nominee.  Trump lambasted Biden's record on Beijing, casting the former vice president and longtime senator from Delaware as soft on China during its rise to become the second-largest economy in the world. He faulted Biden for initially opposing his administration's decision to shut down some flights from China over the coronavirus, and he inaccurately stated that Biden "sided with China" on its handling of the pandemic - even though Biden had sounded alarms months ago as Trump was still praising Chinese President Xi Jinping.  And he suggested that Biden has been critical of the United States while rooting for China's economic success, citing a July 4 video message during which Biden had stated that U.S. history was "no fairy tale."  "Joe Biden's entire career has been a gift to the Chinese Communist Party," Trump said.  "He said the idea that China is our competitor is really bizarre. He's really bizarre," the president said. "Nobody's ripped us off more than China the last 25-30 years - nobody close - and he says China's not a problem? He wants to take it all back now. He...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Man's Dismembered Body Found in Luxury Manhattan Condo... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/14/decapitated-dismembered-body-found-in-nyc-apartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of a decapitated, dismembered man was found inside a Lower East Side apartment on Tuesday afternoon — sorted in plastic bags right next to a power saw, sources told The Post. Police came u…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House tells 18 million unemployed workers to 'Find Something New' in ad campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/white-house-tells-18-million-unemployed-workers-to-find-something-new-in-ad-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Ivanka Trump urged out-of-work Americans to "find something new" Tuesday as part of a new jobs initiative designed to tout the benefits of skills training and career paths that do not require a college degree. But the effort...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branson Rescues VIRGIN ATLANTIC as 70th Birthday Gift to Himself...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/branson-rescues-virgin-atlantic-70th-164716570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Richard Branson has spent decades cultivating an image as a daredevil entrepreneur, glorifying risk with stunts such as sky-diving or hot-air ballooning across the ocean to promote everything from soda to space travel. Now, less than a week shy of his 70th birthday, Branson is taking one</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORTRESS NEW YORK; 22 STATES QUARANTINE WATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/we-went-through-hell-cuomo-ups-ante-on-quarantine-order-travelers-to-ny-face-2000-fine-for-failing-to-submit-form/2514296/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four more states were added to the tri-state’s quarantine-restricted list Tuesday — New Mexico, Minnesota, Wisconsin and Ohio. Delaware came off, no longer meeting the criteria to be considered a viral hotspot under New York standards. That brings the total number on the list to 22. In addition to the newcomers, the restricted states include: Alabama, Arkansas, Arizona, California, Florida,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Director Warns of Difficult Fall and Winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cdc-director-warns-this-coming-fall-winter-may-be-one-of-the-most-difficult-times-weve-experienced-in-american-public-health/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDC director Robert Redfield said in a new interview Tuesday he's concerned about the public health challenges the United States may be facing in the fall and winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronic 'tattoo' could monitor your health...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article244225222.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banks make out with $18 billion in fees for processing PPP loans...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/07/14/banks-cares-act-ppp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s money taken directly out of the $640 billion pot of funding Congress allocated to the PPP program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gray hairdo amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/14/trump-sporting-more-natural-gray-hairdo-amid-the-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a briefing in the Rose Garden on Tuesday, the president emerged from the Oval Office with his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. County Record Hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/los-angeles-county-coronavirus-record-highest-number-new-cases-hsopitalizationsever-1202985694/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The day after California Governor Gavin Newsom shut down a number of business sectors in the state, the Los Angeles County Department of Public Health confirmed record new COVID-19 cases and hospit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeking comeback, Sessions faces Tuberville in Alabama race... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/eb8d04c518fd8cb9d6d2d0eeef812ec6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTGOMERY, Ala. (AP) — President Donald Trump made a last-minute attempt to end the comeback hopes of his former attorney general, Jeff Sessions, ahead of Tuesday's Republican primary runoff,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARY:  RESIGN</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/message-president-donald-trump-niece-resign/story?id=71779486</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Trump, President Donald Trump’s niece, on Tuesday called on the president to step down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever and chills... </title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/justice-ruth-bader-ginsburg-hospitalized-infection/story?id=71784311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg was hospitalized Tuesday for a possible infection and is expected to remain for several days, according to a statement from the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Possible infection; Underwent procedure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/14/politics/ruth-bader-ginsburg-hospitalized/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg has been taken to the hospital and treated for a possible infection, according to a court spokeswoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies bail for Ghislaine Maxwell...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/14/jeffrey-epstein-case-ghislaine-maxwell-sex-crimes-bail-ruling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell was denied bail nearly a year after her friend Jeffrey Epstein killed himself while awaiting trial on child sex trafficking charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warship challenges China in South China Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/us-challenges-chinas-south-china-sea-claims-after-rejecting-them-2020-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US "will not let China claim the South China Sea as its own," a senior US State Department official said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT editor details harassment from woke colleagues in resignation letter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/14/bari-weiss-on-why-she-left-the-new-york-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saying that “Twitter has become its ultimate editor,” New York Times columnist and editor Bari Weiss resigned yesterday with a scathing letter to the paper. Weiss, one of the few centrist voices at…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In surprise move, Trump reverses course on barring many foreign students...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200714193735-c6tbu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/STUDENTS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-In surprise move, Trump administration reverses course on barring many foreign students</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate wore janitor's uniform to escape from prison...</title>
      <link>https://kttc.com/2020/07/14/report-inmate-wore-janitors-uniform-to-escape-from-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kttc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — A report from a North Carolina prison says an inmate who escaped put on a janitor’s uniform and followed another employee out the door. The News &amp; Observer of Raleigh quotes authorities who say Chad Lee Houser, who was in prison awaiting trial on murder charges, escaped from Central Prison last</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN THE FAMILY: President's Brother Fails to Block Niece...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mary-trump-free-to-dish-on-her-family-and-tell-all-book-judge-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has freed Mary Trump from a gag order that prevented her from discussing Trump family drama and promoting her bombshell book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans breaking from President's talking points...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/14/trump-allies-coronavirus-surge-360751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of the president's allies are undercutting his attempts to minimize the pandemic's dangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA PURGE: Andrew Sullivan out at NEW YORK mag...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/925465/bari-weiss-resigns-from-new-york-times-andrew-sullivan-leave-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of prominent writers announced they're leaving their prominent publications Tuesday. The resignations appear to be related to recent debates within the wider media landscape about the alleged stifling of public discourse. Bari Weiss, a former op-ed staff editor and writer for The New York Times, resigned from the newspaper today, while prominent New York writer Andrew Sullivan announced this would be his last week at the magazine. In a lengthy resignation letter addressed to Times publisher A.G. Sulzberger, Weiss said she made her decision because she became the 'subject of constant bullying by colleagues who disagree' with her 'centrist' views and that 'intellectual curiosity' has become a 'liability' at the Times. NEW: Bari Weiss has published her resignation letter to publisher A.G. Sulzberger https://t.co/FZLfuqzRMQ pic.twitter.com/OKgSYKGBCG â€” Jeremy Barr (@jeremymbarr) July 14, 2020 Sullivan, meanwhile, tweeted his news, noting that he has 'no beef' with his colleagues, but hinted he's leaving over ideological differences and will explain more fully in his final New York column slated for Friday. Tim O'Donnell I've been preparing for this eventuality, and the column will continue elsewhere. See you on Friday, when I'll detail some exciting news. â€” Andrew Sullivan (@sullydish) July 14, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. units of Chinese companies got bailout money...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/china/u-s-units-chinese-companies-got-coronavirus-bailout-money-n1233692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designed to help businesses hurt by COVID-19, PPP loans included up to $10 million for Continental Aerospace Technologies, run by a Chinese defense giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves rob Dallas testing site...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2020/07/13/thieves-take-covid-19-testing-supplies-delaying-opening-of-new-site-in-pleasant-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The opening of a new walk-up COVID-19 testing site in Pleasant Grove was delayed after testing supplies and equipment were stolen overnight. The testing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Layoffs at VOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/14/vox-media-preparing-round-of-layoffs-due-to-coronavirus-business-impact.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vox was 40% off its revenue forecast for the second quarter and plans to miss its full-year target by 25%, sources say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Museum Curator Called Racist for Collecting Art From White Men; Resigns...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/14/gary-garrels-san-francisco-museum-modern-art-racism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Irate employees of the San Francisco Museum of Modern Art said the removal of Gary Garrels was "non-negotiable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal stockpile thin...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/federal-stockpile-thin-amid-coronavirus-surge-documents-show-n1233791</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;States, hospitals and nursing homes may not be able to rely on Washington to supply personal protective equipment for medical professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Sweden Screwed Up...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2020/07/coronavirus-covid-sweden-herd-immunity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European country thought it could get away with a more lenient COVID response. It thought very, very wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demand For Robot Cooks Rising...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/07/14/robot-cooks-growing-demand-coronavirus-covid-19-blendid-chowbotics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots that can cook - from flipping burgers to baking bread - are in growing demand as virus-wary kitchens try to put some distance between workers and customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine Abortion Gets Green Light From Federal Court...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/14/telemedicine-abortion-gets-green-light-from-federal-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: "Heartbeat law" ruled unconstitutional, introducing the Atlas of Surveillance, Brave New World reimagined, and more...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
