<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'I don't do cover-ups'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-blows-up-meeting-with-dems-bashes-pelosis-cover-up-remarks-attacks-media-in-impromptu-presser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump railed against the Mueller probe yet again at an impromptu presser at the Rose Garden this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your nipples teeming with mites? Tiny creatures mate while sleep...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7060255/Your-face-teeming-mites-Tiny-eight-legged-creatures-feast-skin-oils.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mites known as Demodex folliculorum, live near hair follicles, including the invisible hair on nipples and faces. They are related to the spider family and measure a third of a millimeter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vows no more legislation while under investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/22/trump-hosts-democratic-leaders-at-white-house-infrastructure-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president abruptly walked out of a meeting Wednesday, saying he would not negotiate with Democrats while they continue to investigate him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China secretly emitting banned ozone-destroying chemical...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/scientists-discover-china-has-been-secretly-emitting-banned-ozone-depleting-gas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found that between 40 and 60 per cent of the total global CFC-11 emissions originated from eastern China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Uses High-Tech Surveillance to Subdue: 'God-eye view'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/22/world/asia/china-surveillance-xinjiang.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has turned the Xinjiang region in its far west into an incubator for automated authoritarianism that could spread across the country and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive asteroid with own moon to zoom past Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/asteroid-kw4-1999-with-its-own-moon-trailing-behind-enters-our-galaxy-this-week-passing-earth-nasa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The asteroid will be visible until May 27</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cable News Made Household Name...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/03/28/cnn-and-msnbc-made-shakedown-artist-michael-avenatti-a-household-name/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea dragons dazzle in CA...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Sea-dragon-exhibit-dazzles-visitors-at-California-13869825.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA JOLLA, California (AP) - At first glance, it looks like a branch of kelp, but then an eye moves among its leafy appendages, and ridges of tiny, translucent fins start to flutter, sending the creature gliding through the water like something from a fairy tale.  A Southern California aquarium has built what is believed to be one of the world's largest habitats for the surreal sea dragons, whose native populations off Australia are threatened by pollution, warming oceans and the illegal pet and alternative medicine trades.  The Birch Aquarium at the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego hopes the exhibit, which opened this month, will lead to the leafy sea dragon, the lesser-known cousin of the seahorse, being bred for the first time in captivity.  "It literally just looked like a piece of kelp," said Steven Kowal, 25, who was visiting San Diego from Greensboro, North Carolina, and took time to see the exhibit. "It was crazy to me that it was, like, actually living and swimming around, so that's cool. I've never seen anything like that."  That's a common reaction.  "They look like something out of this world," said Leslee Matsushige, the aquarium's associate curator, who noted the sea dragons' amazing ability to camouflage themselves. "When people see them move, you hear them say, 'What? That's alive? Wow! That's crazy.'"  Scientists like Matsushige hope the creatures' magnetic power will prompt people to read signs next to the tanks that outline ways to protect them and what can be done to make oceans healthier, such as picking up trash and stopping pollutants from going down the drain.  Few aquariums have sea dragons. There are only two types of sea dragons, the leafy and the weedy, each representing its own genus. Both are found...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Half Use Swimming Pools As Bathtub...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/05/22/survey-half-americans-use-swimming-pools-communal-bathtub</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer is almost here and that means there's a good chance you'll soon be taking a dip in the pool to cool off. But beware before you get in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK PHOTO: Woman Poses With Baby After Ripping From Murdered Mother's Womb...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/05/22/clarisa-figueroa-hospita-marlen-ochoa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS 2 has obtained a photograph of Clarisa Figueroa in Advocate Christ Medical Center with the baby she is alleged to have ripped from the womb of Marlen Ochoa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage 'trapped' bus by people armed with milkshakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9132151/nigel-farage-brexit-bus-people-milkshakes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGEL Farage reportedly refused to get off his Brexit Party bus today because people gathered around it were carrying milkshakes. It comes days after the party leader was covered in a caramel shake…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fugitive Says He'll Surrender if 15,000 People 'Like' Wanted FACEBOOK Poster...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Connecticut-Fugitive-Surrender-Facebook-Like-Wanted-Poster-510272771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Connecticut police department says a fugitive has agreed to surrender if enough people respond to an online wanted poster on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Briefed on Plan to Send MORE Troops to Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/22/politics/iran-troops-options/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pentagon officials are scheduled to brief senior members of President Donald Trump's national security team as soon as Thursday on a plan that could send thousands of additional US troops to the Middle East amid rising tensions with Iran, according to three US officials familiar with the effort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime at MCDONALD's every 36 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-22/mcdonald-s-workers-want-osha-to-investigate-pattern-of-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commons leader quits...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-48374098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrea Leadsom says she no longer believes the government's approach will deliver Brexit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli scientists brew 'ancient beer' from 5,000-year-old yeast...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-scientists-brew-groundbreaking-ancient-beer-from-3000-year-old-yeast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using pottery sherds from four Holy Land sites, interdisciplinary team isolates and revitalizes six strains of ancient yeast to create alcoholic beverages of yore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivors' photos defaced in Vienna...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3bda38f1dbd470aa7b88a8f2edce28b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Photos of Holocaust survivors exhibited on a central Vienna street have been defaced with swastikas, drawing condemnation from political and Jewish leaders. Broadcaster ORF...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coast Guard to reassert US leadership in Arctic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2ab54c78d4e41d0a56ed824ab5731b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW LONDON, Conn. (AP) — U.S. National Security Adviser John Bolton has told 240 new Coast Guard Academy graduates they will help lead the way in "reasserting American leadership in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds expected to charge Avenatti in dealings with Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/feds-expected-charge-avenatti-dealings-stormy-daniels-sources/story?id=63203832</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors are expected to charge Michael Avenatti with additional financial crimes Wednesday, sources briefed on the case told ABC News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loved to death: Is euthanizing pets to be buried with dead owners OK?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbc12.com/2019/05/16/loved-death-is-euthanizing-pets-be-buried-with-dead-owners-ok/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chesterfield woman put in her will that her beloved dog should be put down upon her death so its remains can be buried with her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada passes National Popular Vote bill in bid to upend Electoral College...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/22/nevada-senate-passes-national-popular-vote-bill-pa/?234</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nevada Senate approved Tuesday a National Popular Vote bill on a party-line vote, sending the legislation aimed at upending the Electoral College to the governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG BATTLE FOR PA...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-looks-sew-doubts-biden-keystone-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is on President Trump's mind, and his supporters' in safe GOP country in Pennsylvania. But down east, there's some ambivalence for the former VP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia to behead author, journalist and cleric on 'terrorism charges'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-to-execute-three-16181112</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the men was arrested shortly after he tweeted a prayer for reconciliation between Saudi Arabia and Qatar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLBERT Gives CBS First Late-Night Ratings Season Win In 20 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/stephen-colbert-captures-late-night-ratings-crown-2018-19-1212766 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS' 'Late Show' ekes out a demographic win over NBC's 'Tonight Show' for the first time in more than 20 years while increasing its total-viewer lead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers seek answers to gray whale deaths after 57 stranded this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/researchers-seek-answers-to-gray-whale-deaths-after-are-stranded/article_ce526116-f333-5a4c-85d4-3d7722d2b7dc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — Gray whales are dying at twice the usual rate as a brutal migration unfolds, with whales washing up on Washington state beaches, apparently starved to death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIRECTOR SNAPS AT NYT REPORTER...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/markets-festivals/quentin-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-margot-robbie-sharon-tate-1203223332/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino snapped at a female reporter from The New York Times who asked why Margot Robbie wasn’t given more to say or do in his latest film “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood.” “I reject your …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem impeachment calls swell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/abf4b46fcb07477d9871ad56df45b3ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — More Democrats are calling — and more loudly — for impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump after his latest defiance of Congress by blocking his former White House...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi blasts 'cover-up,' but urges patience...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/34f3711675e14bb6aed2e7349c4acacf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on Congress and investigations into President Donald Trump (all times local): 10:35 a.m. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, meeting with Democrats behind closed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORDER PATROL CHIEF OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/border-patrol-chief-carla-provost-to-leave-before-years-end-sources</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Border Patrol Chief Carla Provost is expected to leave her post by December, according to several high-ranking former Department of Homeland Security and union officials with first-hand knowledge of the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI: COVER-UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2019/05/pelosi-trump-is-engaged-in-a-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi to execute prominent scholars...</title>
      <link>https://www.middleeasteye.net/news/exclusive-saudi-arabia-execute-three-prominent-moderate-scholars-after-ramadan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.middleeasteye.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The treatment of Salman al-Odah, Awad al-Qarni and Ali al-Omari, all facing charges of 'terrorism', has been condemned by rights groups</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INCORRECT FIGURE'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-friends-challenge-sarah-sanders-over-drudge-border-wall-headline-less-than-2-miles-built/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"That is an incorrect figure," Sanders claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 MILES BY END OF YEAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7058091/Trump-built-2-miles-new-wall-1-57-BILLION-Congress-handed-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It appears that CBP has now constructed 1.7 miles of fencing with its fiscal year 2018 funding,' the House of Representatives general counsel wrote to a federal judge on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Quakes Worldwide Linked to Birth of Submarine Volcano?</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201905221075233082-france-submarine-volcano-earthquakes/?utm_source=https://t.co/XK29lOeKHU </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The birth of a unique submarine volcano near a French island located between Africa and Madagascar could shed light on a puzzle that has baffled scientists since last year. In 2018, seismic sensors detected strange low-frequency ripples thousands of kilometres away from the discovered developing volcano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon admits it investigates UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/22/the-pentagon-finally-admits-it-investigates-ufos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon has finally uttered the words it always avoided when discussing the possible existence of UFOs — “unidentified aerial phenomena” — and admits that it still investigates rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR BUCKLES UNDER SCHIFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/justice-department-and-house-intelligence-panel-strike-deal-for-mueller-materials/2019/05/22/f8f2380a-7c7e-11e9-8ede-f4abf521ef17_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agreement means the committee will not enforce a subpoena against the attorney general, while the Justice Department works to turn over requested materials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toilet Predicts if You'll Have Heart Failure...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/this-toilet-will-predict-if-youll-have-heart-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best way to monitor patients with heart disease might be with a simple hack of their bathroom habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trendy LA Hotel Where Workers Suffer ICE Threats, Homophobia, Literal Sh*t...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/freehand-the-trendy-los-angeles-hotel-where-workers-suffer-ice-threats-homophobia-and-literal-shit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers at L.A.’s Freehand Hotel claim they were forced to clean up poop explosions without protective gear and were subjected to sexual harassment and ICE threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Americans retiring abroad...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/840586/pros-cons-retiring-abroad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More people are spending their golden years abroad, and it's not hard to see why</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway rips 'most unfit and incompetent president' in history...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/444956-george-conway-attacks-trump-as-most-unfit-and-incompetent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frequent Trump critic George Conway “fixed” President Trump’s tweet attacking Democrats on Wednesday morning, calling Trump the “most unfit and incompetent president in American history.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top French journalist summoned by intelligence service...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-french-journalist-summoned-intelligence-003940765.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior reporter at France's Le Monde daily who broke the story of an explosive scandal concerning a security aide to President Emmanuel Macron has been summoned for questioning by the domestic intelligence service, the newspaper said Wednesday. Ariane Chemin was told by the General Directorate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RV driver leads police on wild chase; Slams into cars, dogs leap from vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/05/21/police-in-pursuit-of-stolen-rv-in-san-fernando-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wild pursuit of an RV through the San Fernando Valley saw a dog leap from a moving vehicle, multiple crashes, and ended with the female driver taken into custody Tuesday evening. The chase began in Santa Clarita when authorities tried to pull over an RV on Towsley Canyon around 7 p.m. LASD initially called the vehicle a stolen RV, but Commander Ritchie Lew with Simi Valley Police Department later said the RV is believed to have been purchased using a stolen identity at Giant RV in Downey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IQ rates dropping in developed countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/iq-rates-are-dropping-many-developed-countries-doesn-t-bode-ncna1008576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An intelligence crisis could undermine our problem-solving capacities and dim the prospects of the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign pitch: Make America Normal Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-biden-presidential-candidate-nostalgia-20190522-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's kickoff speech in Philadelphia was folksy, conciliatory, combative — and focused almost entirely on beating Trump. That's smart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: President Should Worry About Approval Rating...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2019-05-22/donald-trump-should-worry-about-his-approval-rating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex drought all-time high...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/society/sex-drought-experts-say-americans-get-frisky-less-often-now/5312139/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of U.S. adults reporting they didn't have sex for an entire year reached an all-time high in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobs ruining storm chasing...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-mobs-are-ruining-storm-chasing-13866653.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I had heard grumblings about the downsides to storm chasing for a long time - poor driving habits, traffic jams as cars converge near violent storms, and the dangers of rogue chasers and hobbyists. It had always been on my mind, but four years of venturing to the Plains had taught me it was just something I'd have to live with. I always brushed it off as an unavoidable byproduct of chasing.  But Monday was different. I witnessed firsthand the practices that will drive me away from the sport I once loved with my entire being. The past week of storm chasing has been eye-opening. In just seven days, I've encountered:  --Chase vehicles parked perpendicular to roads blocking major intersections  --Multiple chasers with red/blue police lights "pulling over" others to clear their path to the storm; in 70 mph winds and egg-sized hail and less than a mile from a tornado, this could have been deadly  --Traffic jams 200 cars deep  --Chasers parking on/in the road to take pictures, blocking traffic  --Chasers barreling down a one-lane road at 90 mph  --Chasers driving on the wrong side of the road  The dangers speak for themselves.  There's a reason why my biggest fear about storm chasing isn't weather-related; it's not the softball-sized hail, it's not hurricane-force winds, and it's not even lightning or the tornado. It's other chasers. On Monday, when a large tornado passed by Mangum, Oklahoma, the Oklahoma Highway Patrol reported just one injury, not from wind but "involving two vehicles with storm chasers."  The perils have been manifest before. Three storm chasers were killed in an accident in Texas on March 28, 2017, when a pair of Weather Channel contractors blew through a stop sign at 70 mph. In 2013, veteran storm chaser Tim Samaras fell victim to a tornado near El Reno,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first 'vertical theme park' set to open...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-7057197/Theme-park-star-Hunger-Games-Twilight.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lionsgate Entertainment World in China will offer more than 25 rides and virtual reality experiences in a futuristic-looking bean-shaped building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS posters depict Big Ben on fire, suicide bomber in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7057465/ISIS-posters-depict-Big-Ben-fire-warn-London-attacks-soon.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS-affiliated media have released three posters that incite lone wolf attacks on the west, which were posted on Twitter by the Terror Research and Analysis Consortium - a terrorism watchdog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread flu-like illness hits migrant processing facility...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/widespread-flu-like-illness-hits-main-south-texas-migrant-processing-facility-today-2019-05-22/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAllen, Texas facility temporarily stops taking in detainees; Guatemalan teen who just died was diagnosed with flu there</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum grows to create 'Do Not Track' registry...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/444919-momentum-grows-to-create-do-not-track-registry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislation to stop tech companies from tracking users online is finding new momentum as Congress seeks to crack down on big tech’s privacy practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa Dems brace for caucus turnout record...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/444863-iowa-democrats-brace-for-caucus-turnout-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES — Democrats in Iowa are preparing for what’s likely to be the most widely attended caucuses in state history next February, and they’re hoping to avoid the acrimony that followed the closely fought contest in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vax Movement Spreads To Pet Population...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/05/21/anti-vax-movement-spreads-to-pet-population/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anti-vaccination movement has spread to our pets. Some owners say they're done with shots for their dogs-- after what they claim happened to their furry friend. Is it a false fear or legitimate concern?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Americans suffer 'workout hangover'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/21/more-than-half-of-americans-have-suffered-a-workout-hangover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 55% of Americans say they have suffered a workout hangover that’s caused them to stay inside all day, with more than a quarter even admitting to skipping work the next day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey kills man, injures 10 others in nine-day rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/780582/monkey-killer-rampage-deaths-india</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking robot to deliver packages...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ford-way-finish-driverless-deliveries-040101421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ford is working on a way to resolve what self-driving researchers refer to as “the last 50-foot problem.” If an autonomous delivery vehicle arrives at your house, without any humans aboard, who’s going to carry the package, grocery bags or piping-hot pizza to your doorstep? In Ford’s case, the solution</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May faces a new coup... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/9125276/theresa-may-coup-second-referendum-backfired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERESA May faces a new coup after a gamble to force through her Brexit deal by offering Remainers a second referendum backfired spectacularly. The offer was blasted by MPs on all sides — and left …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group oral sex session was interrupted by federal raid, former NXIVM cult follower testifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-cult-commitment-ceremony-oral-sex-20190521-5wqddh22jjfghk7mrdd757espe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exotic commitment renewal ceremony with his front-line followers was nothing more than a “group (oral sex) session for alleged sex cult leader Keith Raniere that was interrupted when federal agents busted into his Mexican hideaway to arrest him, a former member testified Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day care center to close, months after toddlers found on highway...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article230647224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada lawmakers close to REPEALING tough rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/333d1b4090a24064a4e0e6c836ad0cb6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARSON CITY, Nev. (AP) — Nevada lawmakers are bucking a national trend of restrictive abortion laws by voting to repeal requirements that physicians document a pregnant woman's marital status and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Trump can't relate to average family's struggles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1279f7d8cf264cec82a782977087a0c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE MARY, Fla. (AP) — Joe Biden is responding to President Donald Trump's latest attack on his candidacy, saying Trump can't understand the difficult decisions that struggling families must...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico county rejects relocation...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/21/sierra-county-new-mexico-rejects-migrant-relocatio/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Mexico county has approved a resolution opposing the relocation of migrants within its boundaries as federal authorities grapple with the influx of people crossing the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEWS:  'HOLLYWOOD' a meandering ode to bygone era...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2019/05/once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-review-quentin-tarantino-brad-pitt-leonardo-dicaprio</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino’s latest is a meandering ode to a bygone era, featuring great performances by DiCaprio, Pitt, and Margot Robbie as Sharon Tate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Self-mummified' monk who meditated to death found encased in ancient statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9125459/1000-year-old-buddhist-statue-skeleton-monk-inside/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the mummified remains of a Buddhist monk who meditated to death, encased inside a 1,000-year-old ancient statue. Scientists scanned the Buddha and made the grisly discovery, when they saw b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison guard got pregnant after sex with inmate...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article230669224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Movie Without Harvey Weinstein to Temper Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/05/21/mixed-early-buzz-from-cannes-for-quentin-tarantinos-first-movie-without-harvey-weinstein-to-temper-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s mixed early buzz from Cannes right now for Quentin Tarantino’s “Once Upon a Time…in Hollywood.” It’s his first movie without Harvey Weinstein. I can&amp;#821…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force investigating cyber attack --  from Navy?</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2019/05/21/why-the-air-force-is-investigating-a-cyber-attack-from-the-navy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force has reportedly seized an attorney's computer and phone as part of an investigation into whether the Navy improperly spied on defense attorneys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots 'will end need for nursing homes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-new-tech-can-turn-any-home-into-a-retirement-home-2019-05-21 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your end-of-life caregiver may be a robot — why that might not be such a bad thing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS MEMO: Trump tax docs must be given to Congress unless executive privilege...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/business/article/Confidential-draft-IRS-memo-says-tax-returns-must-13868160.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A confidential Internal Revenue Service legal memo says tax returns must be given to Congress unless the president takes the rare step of asserting executive privilege, according to a copy of the memo obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'PLOTLESS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/review/once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-cannes-2019-1212805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo DiCaprio and Brad Pitt play a fading action star and his inseparable stunt double in Quentin Tarantino's freewheeling trip through 1969 Tinseltown at the time of the Manson murders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economic model is gone...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90353613/nyts-dean-baquet-most-local-newspapers-will-die-in-5-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dean Baquet has a depressing outlook for the local media landscape. Billionaire owners may be the only hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STALL:  LESS THAN 2 MILES BUILT!</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/federal-wall-funding-of-1-57-billion-yields-1-7-miles-of-fence-1.1262220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadler Subpoenas Hope Hicks...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/house-judiciary-committee-subpoenas-hope-hicks-ae88c865-08a3-460b-ae6d-349930333f9d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee also subpoenaed Don McGahn's former chief of staff, Annie Donaldson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2-hour-and-41-minute tale...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/reviews/cannes-film-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-review-quentin-tarantino-brad-pitt-leonardo-dicaprio-1203222012/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been 25 years to the day since Quentin Tarantino’s “Pulp Fiction” premiered at the Cannes Film Festival, crystalizing a cinema revolution, and we have never looked back. Yet here…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA ratings plunge 48%...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/raptors-bucks-eastern-conference-finals-ratings-011932974.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Toronto Raptors and Milwaukee Bucks haven&amp;#39;t drawn huge television numbers in the United States during the Eastern Conference Finals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARANTINO TAKES CANNES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/quentin-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-cannes-premierence-pitt-dicaprio-robbie-superb-1202620071/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking a page from Quentin Tarantino’s Instagram post this week imploring Cannes Film Festival audiences to keep the details of his competition film Once Upon a Time in Hollywood secret, Fest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover video reveals brutal treatment of Falun Gong prisoners inside Chinese labor camps...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/undercover-video-reveals-brutal-treatment-of-falun-gong-prisoners-inside-chinese-labor-camps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California family is taking their fight to the Chinese government after they say their loved one was tortured and killed inside of a Chinese labor camp nearly 20 years ago, simply for supporting the spiritual meditation practice known as Falun Gong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Warns Assad As Signs Point To Chemical Weapons Use...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2019-05-21/us-says-sees-signs-syrian-government-may-be-using-chemical-weapons</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive 'island' of plastic rubbish forms in sea off Corsica...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.fr/20190521/giant-island-of-plastic-rubbish-forms-in-sea-off-corsica</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.fr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A floating “island” of plastic rubbish several dozen kilometres long has formed off the coast of the French island of Corsica.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Commissioner: LeBron in L.A. Hurt Ratings...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/adam-silver-lebron-james-leaving-173858979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Difficult problem to tackle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tillerson Secret Meeting On Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rex-tillerson-secretly-meets-with-house-foreign-affairs-committee-to-talk-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former secretary of state talked with lawmakers about his time with the president and the frictions he had with the president’s son-in-law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticket holders snubbed: Get off red carpet or get arrested...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/quentin-tarantino-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-cannes-premiere-ticket-holders-turned-away-1202619954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Get off the red carpet or get arrested was the message sent by Cannes Film Festival ushers Tuesday night to hundreds of ticket holders who were turned away from the premiere of Quentin T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm Emanuel now contributing editor for THE ATLANTIC...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/politics/2019/5/21/18633818/rahm-emanuel-contributing-editor-the-atlantic-chicago-mayor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Chicago mayor has contributed 12 articles for the publication since October 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft IRS memo says tax returns must be given to Congress -- unless...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/economy/confidential-draft-irs-memo-says-tax-returns-must-be-given-to-congress-unless-president-invokes-executive-privilege/2019/05/21/8ed41834-7b1c-11e9-8bb7-0fc796cf2ec0_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo, written last fall by an Internal Revenue Service attorney, contradicts the Trump administration’s justification for denying the president’s tax returns to lawmakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Man wakes from boozy night out to find penis chopped off...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9123104/man-makes-boozy-night-penis-chopped-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN woke up after a boozy night to discover his penis had been hacked off – and he had no idea how it happened, it’s reported. Tan Nan had allegedly been out with friends in Hunan, so…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Dean Baquet Predicts Most Local Papers Dead In 5 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/ny-times-editor-dean-baquet-predicts-doom-for-local-newspapers-most-will-die-in-next-five-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Their economic model is gone."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mahomes believes can throw football 100 yards!</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/sports/spt-columns-blogs/for-petes-sake/article230614184.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
