<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Italy says 'arrogant' France risks becoming 'No.1 enemy' on migration...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italy-says-arrogant-france-risks-becoming-no-1-172859262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy on Saturday said "arrogant" France risked becoming its "No.1 enemy" on migration issues, a day before European leaders convene in Brussels for a hastily arranged meeting on the divisive issue. In answer to comments by French President Emmanuel Macron, who said migration flows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE SPOKESWOMAN KICKED OUT OF RESTAURANT BY TRUMP HATER!</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/23/sarah-huckabee-sanders-restaurant-thrown-out-moral-grounds-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Huckabee Sanders kicked out of a restaurant on moral grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERDOGAN ON BRINK...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/angry-erratic-erdogan-cusp-becoming-080000736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recep Tayyip Erdogan sat in stony silence as he listened to the complaints of his citizens.  During his final drive for votes ahead of Sunday’s elections, the Turkish president agreed to go on a popular radio call in show, where the host nervously played recordings of people who had phoned in with their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV BLACKOUT FOR OPPOSITION...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-23/on-eve-of-vote-only-erdogan-gets-tv-time-campaign-trail-update </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s biggest rival appealed to a massive rally in Istanbul in the campaign’s final hours. You just wouldn’t know it watching state television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushes back against border separation uproar...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5877399/President-Trump-tweets-link-images-Obama-era-family-migrant-holding-centers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An article linked by the news aggregation site contained numerous photos of children pictured in 2014 at Obama-era holding centers for unaccompanied migrants in Texas and Arizona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney making final pitch ahead of Senate primary in Utah...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/romney-making-final-pitch-ahead-senate-primary-utah-152942760--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN FORK, Utah (AP) — Mitt Romney is flashing his familiar smile at city parks and backyards in Utah's mountains and suburbs this week, making his final pitch after being forced into a Republican Senate primary Tuesday against a conservative state lawmaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numb to Outrage, Republican Voters Feel Deepening Bond to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/23/us/politics/republican-voters-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the president’s approval rating at 90 percent among Republicans, many supporters say they defend Mr. Trump even with some misgivings because they feel criticism of him is constantly overblown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Beck's Media Empire Implodes. Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/glenn-becks-media-empire-implodes-again </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative mogul’s business woes continue via another round of layoffs and the death of a sale to the billionaires backing fellow right-wing media giant Ben Shapiro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London BLOODBATH: Parents told to count their knives to fight crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/978448/Parents-count-knives-combat-knife-crime-bloodbath</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOME Office Minister Victoria Atkins has said British parents should count their knives to check their children haven’t taken any, in a bid to help combat surging knife crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penske war with neighbors over plan to turn historic church into mega mansion...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5876449/Media-mogul-war-neighbors-plan-turn-historic-local-church-mega-mansion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media mogul and heir to his father's billions, Jay Penske, is at war with his neighbors over plans to replace a historic church in the local black community with a mansion for himself to live in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Sanders kicked out of restaurant because manager didn't want to serve...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5877545/Sarah-Sanders-gets-kicked-Virginia-restaurant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaike Foley-Schultz, a server at the Red Hen in Lexington, said the White House Press Secretary lasted just two minutes in the restaurant until his boss asked her to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major New York-area traffic bottleneck about to get worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/major-york-area-traffic-bottleneck-worse-150112230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTH BERGEN, N.J. (AP) — It is the bane of tourists and truckers, theatergoers and weekday 9-to-5ers: the congested, pothole-strewn roadway that bisects the teeming towns overlooking the Hudson River before descending into the Lincoln Tunnel to New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP House Candidate Who Beat Sanford Seriously Hurt in Car Accident...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/gop-house-candidate-who-beat-sanford-seriously-hurt-in-car-accident-1529764753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolina State Rep. Katie Arrington, who defeated U.S. Rep. Mark Sanford in his re-election bid, has undergone surgery after being seriously injured in a car wreck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood reeling over 'career suicide note'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5876211/Why-Hollywoods-reeling-whats-called-Johnny-Depps-career-suicide-note.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnny Depp will surely come to regret the narcissistic impulse which led him to ask a Rolling Stone magazine journalist to come and spend a few days with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa lions threatened with extinction by villagers bent on revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/23/revenge-poisonings-using-pesticides-threaten-wipe-africas-lions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poison is supposed to be so fast-working that the locals call it &amp;ldquo;Two Step&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; because &amp;ldquo;you take two steps and drop dead&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; but the lions died slowly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Denies Plan to 'Take Down Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-cohen-denies-joining-forces-with-tom-arnold-to-take-down-trump?ref=home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s self-proclaimed fixer says he had only a “chance, public encounter” with the comedian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating robotic factory will build satellites and spaceships in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/made-in-space-created-a-robotic-factory-to-build-satellites-in-orbit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Archinaut, a system made of 3-D printers and robotic arms, could be the flying factory humans need to colonize space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING robot submarine back roaming off California coast...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-boeing-echo-voyager-20180623-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Co.'s Echo Voyager undersea drone has embarked on its second round of testing in the waters off the Southern California coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man who was fired by machine 'out for blood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/at-work/no-human-could-do-anything-the-man-who-was-sacked-by-a-machine-out-for-blood/news-story/1852bfd331a671a5ac153721bf91eb1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOT content with taking our jobs, the machines have already started firing people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space tourists could be struck down by astro-sickness, warns astronaut...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/space-tourists-could-struck-down-120000359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dream of boldly going where only a few have gone before has inspired hundreds of people to sign up with space tourism companies like Virgin Galactic. But Nasa astronaut Anna Fisher, who made history by becoming the first mother in space, has warned many are unprepared for the rigours of spaceflight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Media Firms Pay CEOs More for Less...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/big-media-firms-pay-ceos-more-for-less-1529751600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief executives in the media and telecom industries made twice as much as their peers in the S&amp;P 500 even though the group’s performance came up short.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC: Psychopath Capital of America...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/06/23/washington-dc-the-psychopath-capital-of-america-218892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study ranks each state, plus D.C., by their psychopathic tendencies. The race for first? It isn’t even close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Up Getty: Fabled Family Finds Their Showbiz Portrayals 'Demonizing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/23/style/getty-family.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fabled family finds their showbiz portrayals “demonizing,” “disgusting” and unrepresentative of their super-L.G.B.T.Q. values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LYNCH: 'You gotta be selfish. It's a terrible thing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/jun/23/david-lynch-gotta-be-selfish-twin-peaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Twin Peaks director lives for his work. He talks about his four marriages, why explaining his films is a ‘crime’, and what makes him a happy camper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Left-Wing Mob Descends on  Homeland Secretary's Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/22/protesters-descend-kirstjen-nielsens-home-no-justi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of protesters gathered outside Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen’s Virginia home Friday morning, chanting “no justice, no sleep” and blaring audio of migrant children crying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trainwreck Interview on CNN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tom-arnolds-cnn-interview-is-a-mind-boggling-trainwreck-i-am-not-f-ing-around/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX's top spokesman fired over use of racial term...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/jonathan-friedland-exits-netflix-1122675</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In lengthy internal memo, CEO Reed Hastings addressed letting go top communications executive Jonathan Friedland: "His descriptive use of the N-word on at least two occasions at work showed unacceptably low racial awareness and sensitivity."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX's top spokesman fired over use of racial term...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netflixs-top-spokesman-fired-over-racial-term-232824349.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix CEO Reed Hastings says he fired the company's top spokesman over use of the N-word. The spokesman, Jonathan Friedland, confirmed in tweets that he was leaving the company, saying he was insensitive in speaking with his team about words that offend in comedy. In a memo to employees, published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushes back against border separation uproar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08eda57806d844618ccfd657e286cf15/Trump-pushes-back-against-border-separation-uproar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump tried to cast doubt Friday on wrenching tales of migrant children separated from their families at the border, dismissing "phony stories o</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400 people use California assisted death law...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07070506167549edacffd30ad6b3f126/Nearly-400-people-used-California-assisted-death-law-in-2017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California health officials reported Friday that 374 terminally ill people took drugs to end their lives in 2017, the first full year after a law made th</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone woman digs for family lost under Guatemalan volcanic rubble...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/lone-woman-digs-family-lost-under-guatemalan-volcanic-163412270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Carlos Jasso and Sofia Menchu SAN MIGUEL LOS LOTES, Guatemala (Reuters) - Eleven days after the Fuego volcano rained down on the Guatemalan village of San Miguel Los Lotes, a backhoe ripped the roof off one of the homes buried by ash, revealing a corpse in the still-hot dust. "It's my sister</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVER 'CORRECTION'</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/white-house-accuses-democrats-media-exploiting-toddler-photo-175002249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The photograph, taken by photographer John Moore at the scene of a border detention this month, became a powerful image in the media coverage of the separation of families at the U.S.-Mexican border. Dozens of newspapers and magazines including Time and the Washington Post published the image. The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE:  Few client communications found so far in documents...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/few-client-communications-found-far-michael-cohen-documents-235132326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Brendan Pierson NEW YORK (Reuters) - A review of documents seized from U.S. President Donald Trump's longtime personal lawyer Michael Cohen has so far turned up only a handful of communications between Cohen and his clients, a federal judge said in a written order on Friday. Out of nearly 300,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Turkey opposition candidate challenges Erdogan again in giant rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkey-opposition-candidate-challenges-erdogan-again-giant-rally-194712684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have the courage, confront me," Muharrem Ince, a fiery lawmaker from the secular Republican People's Party (CHP), told hundreds of thousands of people in Ankara. "Look, that's my last proposal to you ... If you want, I can even cancel my Istanbul rally for you. The Ankara campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania does it her way...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/much-ado-melania-us-first-lady-does-her-171043126.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after moving into the White House with her young son to rejoin her husband, Melania Trump -- this most enigmatic of presidential wives -- demonstrated once more this week she is anything but the typical US first lady. As the United States grapples with a political crisis sparked by the forcible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela urged to stop spread of measles, diphtheria...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuela-urged-stop-spread-measles-diphtheria-222825380.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pan American Health Organization on Friday painted a bleak picture of Venezuela's healthcare system, calling for urgent action to stop the transmission of measles and diphtheria amid an intensifying crisis that has seen an exodus of doctors. The Americas were declared measles-free in 2016, but</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLIANO: Liberate men with satin and corsets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/liberate-men-satin-corsets-fashion-icon-galliano-180745412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Galliano set out Friday to redefine 21st-century masculinity with corsets, sensual satins and vinyl trousers to "liberate" men from their sartorial shackles. The British designer's new collection for Maison Margiela at Paris men's fashion week not only blurred the lines between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another court defeat for jailed Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/22/paul-manafort-money-laundering-charge-664793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manafort's defense team argued that the tens of millions of dollars he's accused of laundering didn't qualify as the proceeds of criminal activity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK's Relentless Drive to Track Every Detail of Users' Lives...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/creepy-patents-show-facebooks-relentless-drive-to-track-every-detail-of-users-lives/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook wants to weaponize our phones to spy on us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers accused of dealing meth out of WENDY'S...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/wendys-workers-in-meth-bust-652093</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 22--A quartet of fast-food workers sold methamphetamine from a Wendy’s in Georgia, according to police who raided the eatery and busted the employees on narcotics charges. Investigators allege</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels Heading to Border to Help the Kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/stormy-daniels-says-shes-headed-to-the-border-next-week-as-soon-as-she-figures-her-best-course-of-action/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX SHARES HIT FRESH HIGHS ON DISNEY DEAL DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/disney-willing-to-divest-more-fox-assets-for-deal-clearance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walt Disney said it was willing to divest Twenty-First Century Fox assets that generated up to $1 billion to get a regulatory nod for the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-gun protester David Hogg -- protected by armed guards?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/anti-gun-protester-david-hogg-struts-through-nyc-with-armed-guards/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Hogg is a VIP now. The 18-year-old attended the Parkland, Florida school where a student murdered 17 people in February, then made himself famous with relentless calls for gun control in the wake of the tragedy. Now he’s got a book deal, and publicists — and armed guards. Sean Di Somma snapped some pictures …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEX PREZ CANDIDATE: FLOOD THE USA!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/22/mexican-candidate-immigration-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal immigration ... what's that?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Fake News With $300 NYT T-Shirt?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/kzkjpx/the-new-york-times-invites-you-to-fight-fake-news-with-this-dollar300-t-shirt-vgtrn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Gray Lady teamed up with a Japanese streetwear company to sell you woke merch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garcetti says L.A. can resume overnight sidewalk sleeping ban...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-sidewalk-sleeping-20180622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven years ago, L.A. officials agreed to stop arresting people who bedded down for the night on streets and sidewalks. Now Mayor Eric Garcetti says the city has built enough housing to meet the terms of a legal settlement, clearing the way for the city to enforce the disputed law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Male DC journalists don't tweet with women...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/6/22/17489516/male-politics-reporters-only-tweet-other-men-nikki-usher</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals why female journalists are so much less influential on Twitter than men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TIME Stands By Cover After 'Correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/time-magazine-stands-by-cover-after-photo-correction-captures-stakes-of-this-moment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Testimonies...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/22/trump-rips-media-for-ignoring-angel-families-permanently-separated-by-illegal-immigrant-crime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday blasted what he described as a media double standard, as he honored families whose loved ones were killed by illegal immigrants and accused the press of ignoring them to focus on the plight of migrants caught crossing the border.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
