<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker Stumps in Iowa Seeking Position as Obama's Heir...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cory-booker-stumps-in-iowa-seeking-position-as-obamas-heir-11549749749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Cory Booker is betting the path to the 2020 Democratic presidential nomination runs through young people and African-Americans—the same groups that propelled Barack Obama’s campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In country music capital, political divides rock the industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/a-country-music-artist-navigates-an-art-form-altered-by-americas-poisoned-politics/2019/02/09/8b9a1d28-24cb-11e9-ad53-824486280311_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Margo Price, a best new artist Grammy contender, finds her audience in a deeply divided country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Purple Heart Triple-Amputee Undergoes Invasive TSA Groping... </title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/awful-purple-heart-triple-amputee-brian-kolfage-undergoes-invasive-tsa-groping-at-tucson-airport-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen's secret agenda as Trump's fixer...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-xer-s-secret-agenda-13604305.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK - At first, Michael Cohen appeared indifferent as he listened to the group of Republican leaders urge his boss to run for governor. It was the fall of 2013, and Donald Trump was already fixated on "the big thing," as he referred to running for president. But the Republicans knew they were getting somewhere when Trump signaled to his attorney that he wanted more talks. "So Michael," Trump would say, "you get us a date on the calendar." Soon enough, no one in the billionaire's coterie was more enthusiastic than Cohen about the prospect of a Governor Trump. Albany, Cohen believed, was a great opportunity not only for his boss but also, as it happened, for himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutal murder of 19-year-old girl shocks Jerusalem...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Brutal-murder-of-19-year-old-girl-shocks-Jerusalem-580105</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ori Ansbacher, from Tekoa in Gush Etzion, was murdered in Jerusalem on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN BANKS ON POPULISIM</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Warren-refocuses-populist-message-in-official-13604175.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAWRENCE, Mass. - Sen. Elizabeth Warren formally launched her presidential bid Saturday by reemphasizing her signature issues of fighting economic inequality and corporate wrongdoing, an effort to move beyond new questions that arose in recent days about her previous claims that she was a Native American. The outdoor rally - on the steps of a former cotton mill and the site of a historic labor strike led by women and immigrants - was intended to position Warren as the leader of a renewed crusade against what she called the "corrupt" influence of large companies and powerful politicians. "The story of Lawrence is a story about how real change happens in America," Warren told a crowd that the campaign estimated at 3,500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump divides Dems with warning of creeping socialism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/429207-trump-divides-democrats-with-warning-of-creeping-socialism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump hadn’t had much success dividing Democrats until he found a word that would provoke very different responses from different members of the party during his State of the Union address: socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress closes in on deal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d6f8067a647b4a67bb1fe628e2d8a084</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Congressional bargainers are working toward a border security deal amid indications that the White House is preparing to accept a bipartisan agreement that would give President Donald Trump a fraction of the money he's demanded for his proposed southern border wall. Participants said they expect money for physical barriers to end up well below the $5.7 billion that Trump has sought to begin construction of the wall, which has attained iconic significance for him and his conservative supporters. Underscoring the clout he's lost during a battle that's dominated the opening weeks of divided government, the amount seems sure to fall much closer to $1.6 billion, the participants said, a figure that was in a bipartisan Senate bill last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-govt protests again turn violent in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/64582c7c8c0c4d17bdde5f0a5c162796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A French yellow vest protester's hand was ripped apart Saturday during violent clashes in Paris as demonstrators tried to storm the French National Assembly in a 13th consecutive week of unrest. Police said the injured protester lost four fingers as police swooped in to stop protesters from breaching the parliament's exterior. Police could not confirm French media reports that the hand of the demonstrator, who is now being treated in the hospital, was blown up by a grenade used to disperse unruly crowds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD:  Bezos and his complexifier... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/09/opinion/sunday/jeff-bezos-national-enquirer-blackmail.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-in-a-billion chance: a heroic billionaire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Hit by Unusually Heavy Snowfall...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/photos-heavy-snow-slams-washington-and-oregon-triggering-major-travel-disruptions/70007391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio journalist shot dead in Mexico's latest media killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenews.com.pk/latest/429889-radio-journalist-shot-dead-in-mexicos-latest-media-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenews.com.pk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesus Ramos Rodriguez was killed in the town of Emiliano Zapata, an official from the local prosecutor´s office told AFP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENQUIRER pushed envelope with Bezos, but was it crime?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-bezos-national-enquirer-legal-explainers-20190208-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Enquirer has undoubtedly pushed the envelope in its dealings with Jeff Bezos, but proving a crime of extortion might prove difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 minors charged in deadly shooting of Nashville musician...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/5-minors-charged-in-fatal-shooting-of-nashville-musician-kyle-yorlets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five kids -- three girls and two boys -- range in age from 12 to 16. They were arrested at a Walmart in Nashville</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Hip-Hop Make Long-Awaited History at GRAMMYS?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/will-hip-hop-make-history-at-grammys-wins-record-song-year-1184619 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The music awards show has had a pretty dodgy past with recognizing the genre’s merits — and diverse winners in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren kicks off bid with challenge to wealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/09/politics/elizabeth-warren-campaign-kickoff-massachusetts/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren officially launched her 2020 presidential campaign Saturday at a rally in Lawrence, Massachusetts, using the backdrop of Everett Mills -- the site of a historic 1912 labor strike led by women and immigrants -- to issue a call to action against wealthy power brokers who "have been waging class warfare against hardworking people for decades."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOTTI DAUGHTER: My Father Would Be President If Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-news-john-gotti-president-victoria-gotti-20190206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Gotti supported a Rudy Giuliani presidency and could have himself been elected President in 2020 according to his daughter Victoria</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More states adopting gun-seizure laws...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3d5722abc06245b4b931933f253e3743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the year since the deadly mass shooting at a Florida high school, more and more states have passed laws making it easier to take guns away from people who may be suicidal or bent on violence against others, and courts are issuing an unprecedented number of seizure orders across the country. Supporters say these "red flag" laws are among the most promising tools to reduce the nearly 40,000 suicides and homicides by firearm each year in the U.S. Gun advocates, though, say such measures undermine their constitutional rights and can result in people being stripped of their weapons on false or vindictive accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Geyser Gushing at Record Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.travelbreakingnews.net/2019/02/yellowstones-steamboat-geyser-is-gushing-at-a-record-pace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.travelbreakingnews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sections SEARCH Skip to content Skip to site index Science Subscribe Log In Log In Today’s Paper Science | Yellowstone’s Steamboat Geyser Is Gushing at a Record Pace Supported by Trilobites It’s the talk of the national park these days, erupting a record 32 times last year and keeping up its showstopping pace this winter.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Firefighters battling inferno forced to dodge moving robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/ocado-robots-at-andover-warehouse-hampered-firefighters-gwtj0zqd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters trying to put out flames at an Ocado warehouse had to dodge robots as they battled through the smoke to find the one that started the fire. The company’s customer fulfilment centre in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York prosecutors pose greatest threat to president?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/feb/09/new-york-southern-district-donald-trump-inauguration-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separate from the Mueller inquiry, the southern district of New York’s pursuit of the inauguration committee could herald more pain for the president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siesta no more? Spanish sleeping habits under strain...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2019/feb/09/why-spanish-sleeping-habits-under-strain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spaniards eat later and stay up longer than their European neighbours because of the siesta. But now that’s under threat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange could be given asylum in Switzerland after vote in Geneva...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/758757/julian-assange-latest-asylum-switzerland-wikileaks-geneva-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Military Warns of Threat From Chinese-Run Space Station in Argentina...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/02/08/us-military-warns-of-threat-from-chinese-run-space-station-in-argentina/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense officials are worried about a remote compound Beijing says helped it land on the far side of the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chief Justice Roberts emerges as Supreme Court swing vote...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190209115114-alni0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/ROBERTS (PIX, REPEAT):RPT-Chief Justice Roberts emerges as U.S. Supreme Court's swing vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New pro football leagues may disrupt NFL, college...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2019/02/08/pro-football-new-leagues-aaf-xfl-change-nfl-college-game/2800945002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alternative pro football leagues have failed before, but investors are betting time is right for leagues like AAF and XFL to succeed in shadow of NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Ford delivers apocalyptic climate warning; 'Worldwide destruction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/uae/harrison-ford-delivers-apocalyptic-climate-change-warning-1.823568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor spoke out ahead of Dubai's World Government Summit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINDA RONSTADT: Country songs now what I call Midwest mall-crawler music...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-country/linda-ronstadt-interview-live-album-parkinsons-791219/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer, who retired in 2009, has released the new ‘Live in Hollywood,’ recorded in 1980</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD OF ILLEGALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/After-holiday-lull-Central-American-family-13602434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. border officials said Friday they saw an abrupt drop-off in illegal crossings during the holiday season, but the number of Central Americans arriving in family groups has returned to record levels since then. The lull in unauthorized crossings suggests some Central American migrants - and the smuggling organizations that deliver them to the border - may have taken a break or deferred the journey north until after the holidays. During the first week of January, when the extended Christmas season was still being celebrated in Mexico and Central America, the number of migrant family members taken into custody by U.S. agents fell to as low as 200 on some days, according to preliminary data from U.S. Customs and Border Protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Bundy's deadly charm still polarizes, 40 years later...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cd9e9b2f3e504338a280d3a39ba0e279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — She kept her eyes on the dapper, wavy haired man who smiled, winked and exuded self-confidence as the courtroom proceedings moved along. "I don't know what it is he has, but he's fascinating," the teenage spectator explained to me at the time. "He's impressive. He just has a kind of magnetism." It was that beguiling magnetism that investigators said helped make the object of her interest — Ted Bundy — one of the nation's most prolific serial killers, with at least 30 women and girls' deaths linked to him in a multiple-state spree that spanned the late 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra! Designer makes news (literally) on runway...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3bd73357d5744557bc7271a6d699c116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CHAOS! HORROR! PANIC! BABY, IT'S HOT! Designer Jeremy Scott has always liked to make news, but with his latest collection he did it literally, drawing design inspiration from New York's tabloid headlines. Chromatically speaking, Scott's runway show Friday evening at New York Fashion Week was a very disciplined collection in all black and white; Scott usually uses a riot of bright colors and large cartoon graphics in his clothes. Here, garments were emblazoned with an artist's versions of the New York Post and the Daily News — on dresses, trousers, jackets, jumpsuits and much more. Some of the most striking items: dainty, elegant chiffon party dresses printed with tabloid headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer allegations hurt 'BOHEMIAN' Oscar chances?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/16f6675df584439cb9a5714c0be798e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Director Bryan Singer hasn't been involved with the Queen biopic "Bohemian Rhapsody" for over a year, but with a fresh exposé alleging that he sexually assaulted minors and the British Academy of Film and Television Arts "suspending" his nomination, will he be the film's Oscars Achilles heel?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Doomsday Bunker 26-Feet Beneath Vegas Hits Market...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/02/08/las-vegas-bunker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A house like no other is for sale in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX shows successful? Who knows?</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/are-netflix-shows-successful-who-knows/505567322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming company refuses to release viewership figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth concentration near 'levels seen during Roaring Twenties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/wealth-concentration-near-levels-last-seen-during-the-roaring-twenties-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shift is eroding security from families in the lower and middle classes, who rely on their small stores to finance retirement and to smooth over shocks like the loss of a job. And it's consolidating power in the hands...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House hunts for schedule leaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/08/trump-executive-time-schedule-1160691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exasperated Trump is aware of the search, which is making use of the White House IT office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggressive polar bears invade Russian Arctic islands; Emergency declared...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russian-arctic-islands-sound-emergency-over-invasion-by-polar-bears-1990975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian Arctic archipelago on Saturday declared an emergency situation over an "invasion" of dozens of aggressive polar bears that have entered homes and public buildings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom in AI-generated art?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/ai-art-from-mario-klingemann-memories-of-passersby-to-sell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Art Has Been Created by AI. Will Collectors Want It?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Brazil, Cat's Away and Mice Just Aren't Playing Nice...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/in-brazil-the-cat-s-away-and-the-mice-just-aren-t-playing-nice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Brazil, the Cat's Away and the Mice Just Aren't Playing Nice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona considers declaring porn public health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/legislature/2019/02/07/arizona-legislature-considers-declaring-porn-public-health-crisis/2802281002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona ranksÂ fourth-lowest in the country forÂ offering comprehensive sex education in middle school, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could women in white sway soldiers blocking aid? </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/could-women-white-sway-venezuelan-soldiers-blocking-aid-021353085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soldiers blocking humanitarian aid from entering Venezuela look unlikely to give any ground, but Maria Acevedo thinks she knows how to make them let the shipments through. Acevedo, 26, wants to join together with fellow Venezuelan women and escort the food and medicine across the border from Colombia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto to headline counter-Trump rally at border...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/429232-orourke-to-headline-counter-trump-rally-at-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O’Rourke (D-Texas) will headline a rally on Monday in El Paso at the same time that President Trump is set to hold a rally there.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
