<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Group outraged at beating of Jewish effigy in Poland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-poland-anti-semitism/jewish-congress-condemns-revival-of-folk-tradition-in-poland-as-anti-semitic-idUSKCN1RY0L2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Jewish Congress has condemned as anti-Semitic the revival of a folk tr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka's social-media shutdown illustrates global discontent with Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/asia/sri-lanka-social-media-shutdown-part-of-global-rethink-on-silicon-valley-20190423-p51gb6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Deep concern'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-mexico-border/mexico-warns-of-deep-concern-over-armed-groups-on-u-s-border-idUSKCN1RW0N6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico said on Saturday it had "deep concern" about armed groups that ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10% of Americans don't use internet. Who are they?</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/04/22/some-americans-dont-use-the-internet-who-are-they/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internet non-adoption is linked to certain demographic variables, including age, educational attainment, household income and community type.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerges as Chief Witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/newspolitics/trump-and-allies-ramp-up-attacks-as-mcgahn-emerges-as-chief-witness-in-mueller-report/ar-BBWbROR?li=AA524b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood A-List Sets Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/mayor-pete-buttigieg-sets-la-fundraiser-hosted-by-gay-hollywood-a-list-1203864</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The co-hosts of the event include some of the highest-profile names in Hollywood including Ryan Murphy, Matt Bomer, Simon Halls, Bryan Lourd, Bruce Bozzi, Greg Berlanti, Robbie Rogers, Kevin Huvane and Billy Eichner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mexican soldiers detain American soldiers on U.S. soil...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/mexican-soldiers-detain-american-soldiers-u-s-soil-government-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are we a country or not?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York mayor targets classic skyscrapers with Green New Deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-mayor-targets-classic-skyscrapers-green-deal-195551528.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio marked Earth Day by outlining measures to make New York greener Monday, including dramatically cutting the carbon footprint of the city's signature building, the skyscraper. The New York version of the "Green New Deal" currently being pushed by freshmen Democratic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists flee...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tourists-flee-sri-lanka-travel-industry-faces-uncertainty-162144862.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists are scrambling to flee Sri Lanka and cancelling holidays after a string of deadly suicide blasts that have sparked concerns the lucrative tourism industry could be sent into a tailspin. The attacks on hotels and churches came as Sri Lanka was emerging as a leading tourist hot-spot, named the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands attend Jewish Passover blessing at Western Wall...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thousands-attend-jewish-passover-blessing-western-wall-091735679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US ambassador to Israel David Friedman, an Orthodox Jew, was among those in attendance, an AFP photographer reported. The "priestly blessing" takes place twice a year at one of Judaism's holiest sites during the week-long holidays of Passover and Sukkot, which occurs in the autumn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA HIGHEST IN 5 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/04/17/california-gas-prices-hit-average-of-4-highest-in-the-state-since-2014/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's gas prices continued to climb Wednesday, hitting the highest levels in almost five years. Motorists throughout the Golden State are paying an average of $4.01 for a gallon of regular gasoline, by far the highest in the country and well above the national average of $2.83, according to a news release from AAA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea leader Kim to visit Russia for summit with Putin...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190422214734-m9he0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-RUSSIA/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-N.Korea confirms leader Kim Jong Un to visit Russia for summit with Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NOT BREAKING ANY LAWS'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190422163842-5wcam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MILITIA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Leader of armed group at U.S. border boasted of assassination training -FBI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Criticized for 'Ambush' of Mueller After Church Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/msnbc-criticized-for-ambush-of-robert-mueller-after-easter-church-service-disgusting-and-rude/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If he were anybody but the president, would Mr. Trump be indicted, sir," MSNBC reporter Mike Viqueira asked the special counsel on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SUES HOUSE OVER FINANCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6c93faea091450889821bd031b1848e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump and his business organization sued the Democratic chairman of the House oversight committee on Monday to block a subpoena that seeks years of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military gets special powers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4cd638f46eb04906819be649163185b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLOMBO, Sri Lanka (AP) — Sri Lanka's president gave the military sweeping police powers starting Tuesday in the wake of the Easter bombings that killed nearly 300 people, while officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Homeless Dying At Record Rate; On Benches, Sidewalks...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-ln-homeless-people-death-unsheltered-substance-abuse-20190422-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths of homeless people in Los Angeles County have jumped 76% in the past five years, outpacing the growth of the homeless population, according to a Kaiser Health News analysis of county coroner data. Experts say drug and alcohol abuse are significant factors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS fanatic...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6948615/The-missed-warnings-Sri-Lankan-security-forces-told-threat-April-4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security services in Sri Lanka face backlash as its revealed Muslim groups alerted military intelligence officials to Easter Sunday bombers, National Thowheed Jamaath and its leaders, three years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says not ready to 'inundate people with policy minutia'...</title>
      <link>https://wsbt.com/news/local/a-busy-dyngus-day-for-buttigieg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsbt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The primary season is in full swing. There&amp;rsquo;s extra buzz this year in South Bend, as Mayor Pete Buttigieg has officially launched his presidential run. People were fighting for a close spot to watch Buttigieg unveil the Dyngus Day sign for his eighth and final time. It was a huge sign of support for the presidential candidate. Warren Street and Ford Street were temporarily renamed to Dyngus Day Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD cruiser runs over sunbather on Venice Beach!</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/police-cruiser-runs-over-sunbather-on-venice-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles police cruiser ran over a person sunbathing at Venice Beach.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Different book versions top spots on 'best seller' charts...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190422-mueller-report-tops-amazon-best-seller-charts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller report tops Amazon best seller charts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADLER SUBPOENAS FORMER WH COUNSEL</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/house-judiciary-chairman-subpoenas-ex-white-house-counsel-don-mcgahn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McGahn was requested to appear before the committee May 21.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Audit Makeover Tactic: Target Wealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/irs-audits-more-wealthy-taxpayers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRS Commissioner Charles Rettig said he wants to work with lawmakers to concentrate on streamlining parts of the audit process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skipping breakfast tied to higher death risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/22/health/skipping-breakfast-cardiovascular-death-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skipping breakfast was associated with a higher risk of early death and cardiovascular mortality than in people who consumed breakfast every day, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodward: Investigate FBICIA Handling of 'Garbage' Dossier...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/04/22/bob-woodward-investigate-dossier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Woodward said Sunday that the FBI and CIA's reliance on the Steele dossier &amp;quot;needs to be investigated.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican police detain hundreds of Central American migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/business/national-business/article229548639.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman wakes up from coma after almost 30 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/uae/health/emirati-woman-wakes-up-from-coma-after-almost-30-years-1.851923</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A car crash in 1991 left Munira Abdulla in a comatose state but her son never lost hope that she would wake up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA warns 'beauty and beast' aurora could wreak havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/nasa-warns-spectacular-beauty-beast-14446044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists warn that a solar flare could one day bring down the Earth's communication networks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New USA 'project sovereignty' Arctic strategy as China, Russia look north...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/New-Coast-Guard-strategy-for-Arctic-highlights-13785357.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Coast Guard's new strategy for the Arctic calls for upgrading ships, aircraft and unmanned systems there, an effort to make sure the United States is "projecting sovereignty" into an increasingly contested region, the service's top officer said.  Adm. Karl Schultz, the commandant of the Coast Guard, said in an interview that the shift is a "little bit different," although existing Arctic efforts will continue.  "Before, it was a peaceful, safe, secure Arctic collaboration," he said. "None of that goes away. We want the Arctic to be a peaceful place where we work to cross international lines here with partner nations that share interests in a transparent fashion. But I think if you're looking around at what's going on in the Arctic, I would say it's maybe trending in a slightly different direction. This will pivot with a little more focus on projecting."  The 48-page document is being released amid concerns in Washington about actions by both China and Russia in the Arctic. It comes as the Defense Department, at the direction of Congress, prepares its own new Arctic strategy that is due to be provided to lawmakers in June.  China, despite its geography, has declared itself a "near-Arctic state," has begun building icebreaker ships and has said it wants to build a "Polar Silk Road" in which goods can be delivered from China to Europe through the Arctic Ocean as ice in waterways diminish.  Russia also has increasingly focused on the Arctic, expanding its fleet of icebreakers to more than 40, reopening Cold War-era military bases above the Arctic Circle and making plans to deploy antiaircraft missiles on some of them.  The Coast Guard, as part of the Department of Homeland Security, is unlikely to have the primary role if open conflict ever broke out in the Arctic. But the service highlights in its new strategy a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ominous warning for Earth?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/22/nasa-photographs-stunning-beauty-beast-aurora-warning-humanity-9284091/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The northern lights are produced by a natural phenomenon that could one day bring civilisation to its knees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can virtual reality boost positive feelings in depressed patients?</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/04/22/using-virtual-reality-boost-positive-feelings-patients-depression/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Existing depression treatments aim to curb negative symptoms, but don’t often boost positive feelings. One researcher hopes virtual reality can change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS installing needle-disposal boxes in across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/starbucks-needle-disposal-boxes-more-locations-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starbucks has installed needle-disposal boxes in bathrooms in at least 25 markets as the chain attempts to address workers' safety concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S employee accused of pouring grease on customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/mcdonald-employee-accused-attacking-pouring-grease-customer/EJxeBubJyNSIchg94obQwK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta police said a McDonald’s employee ran away after attacking a customer with a chair and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA in race to find crashed stealth fighter...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2019/04/22/china-wont-find-lost-f-35-stealth-fighter-first-says-pentagon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not long after the F-35 went missing, pundits speculated whether Chinese or Russian assets were seeking out the secretive aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Officers Accidentally Shoot Each Other While Chasing Suspect...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/21/two-officers-suspect-shot-elk-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Elk Grove police officers are recovering from gunshot wounds they accidentally gave each other while chasing down a suspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Heiress Criticizes CEO Iger's Compensation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/disney-heiress-criticizes-ceo-robert-igers-compensation-11555959591</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abigail Disney, granddaughter company co-founder Roy O. Disney, said Robert Iger’s $65 million pay package is an example of the bulk of corporate profits going to the wrong employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULITZER PRIZE on defense after award goes to board member's wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/22/pulitzer-prize-administrator-defends-process-after/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pulitzer Prizes organization has been accused of being an exclusive club in which members give awards to each other, and the institution did nothing to dispel that notion last week by honoring the wife of a prominent board member.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Feud Explodes; Palace Mulls Exile of Harry and Meghan...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/royal-feud-explodes-into-public-view-again-as-palace-mulls-exile-of-harry-and-meghan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why on earth would Kate and William choose to post a photograph excluding Meghan to mark the Queen’s 93rd birthday? Why would Harry not meet his brother’s eye? The feud is real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio vows to ban steel, glass skyscrapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bill-de-blasio-says-green-new-deal-will-ban-inefficient-steel-and-glass-skyscrapers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s mayor touted on Monday his version of the Green New Deal that sputtered in Washington D.C., saying it will require the city to switch to entirely renewable energy within five years and would ban “incredibly inefficient” steel and glass skyscrapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer center ousts 3 scientists over Chinese data theft concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/texas-cancer-center-ousts-3-scientists-over-chinese-data-theft-n997151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cancer center in Houston has ousted three of five scientists whom federal authorities identified as being involved in Chinese efforts to steal research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOWA POLL: Biden, Sanders tied; Buttigieg close behind...</title>
      <link>http://orlando-politics.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/Iowa-April-18-2019-v2.pdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;orlando-politics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security to run dry in 2035...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/personal-finance/social-security-trust-fund-to-run-dry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a share of GDP, the annual cost of the program will increase to 5.9 percent by 2039</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMSUNG delays $2,000 folding phone after units break...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/22/samsung-galaxy-fold-launch-delayed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung's Galaxy Fold is delayed past its original April 26 launch date, the company confirmed to CNBC on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL SPIKES ANOTHER 3%</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/22/energy-prices-up-on-reported-end-to-sanctions-waiver-for-iranian-oil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices surge on reports that Washington will announce that all buyers of Iran's oil must end imports, or be subject to U.S. sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Easter Bunny Attacks Man In Brawl Outside Nightclub...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/04/22/video-florida-easter-bunny-brawl-viral-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video of an Easter bunny brawl in Orlando is going viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN EGGS AT WHITE HOUSE ROLL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6947099/Melania-rebrands-Easter-putting-Best-slogan-eggs-White-House-Easter-egg-roll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania Trump's Easter Egg Roll on Monday will feature her signature Be Best campaign throughout the festivities. The event will feature Be Best hopscotch and musical eggs with Be Best logo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6945319/Pictured-British-lawyer-mother-son-killed-Easter-Sunday-Sri-Lanka-bomb-attacks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chilling footage, which reportedly shows one of the attackers entering St Sebastian's Church in Colombo, Sri Lanka, shows a man wearing a large backpack walking into the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD Counterterror Chief: Al Qaeda Resurgent...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/04/22/john-miller-sri-lanka-terror-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking on "CBS This Morning," John Miller said "the wheels started turning in New York" from the very beginning of the attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says 'nobody disobeys' him, has no impeachment worries...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52169bbb113e4f07b04b9441618140d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump says that "nobody" disobeys his orders, a reference to the Mueller report, which paints a deeply unflattering picture of his presidency. Trump made...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to strangle Iran oil exports...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2019/04/21/no-more-waivers-united-states-will-try-force-iranian-oil-exports-zero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo will announce Monday that every country must stop importing Iranian oil or face U.S. sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge and lawyer trade accusations of blackmail and extortion over 'intimate' photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/fl-ne-scherer-blackmail-lawsuit-20190419-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach judge and prominent Broward lawyer trade allegations that read like the plot of a prime time soap opera — one that could result in ramifications for the central players: Marni Bryson and Bill Scherer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's countless monuments neglected... </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/notre-dame-fire-warning-bell-europe-listen-061805312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — It's a thin line where the patina of age on Europe's countless monuments gives way to the onset of neglect. Like with so many loved ones, all is assumed to be fine, until suddenly it's not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOVT SHUTS SOCIAL MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fc4dd89b31b342069732964f64d2a280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sri Lankan authorities flicked the off switch on most social media after Easter Sunday attacks on churches and hotels killed hundreds of people, a dramatic reaction that reflects distrust in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Venezuela, women sell hair as another way to get by...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6094f864299e4a28bcaff44d023e1b32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Valery Díaz covered her eyes and held her breath before looking in a hair salon mirror to see herself without much of the long dark hair that used to frame her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>71 cases in week...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190422144159-littn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. records 71 new measles cases in week as outbreak spreads</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of armed group stopping illegals at border to face federal charges...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190422134924-qr3i3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MILITIA (PIX):Leader of armed group stopping migrants at U.S.-Mexico border to face federal charges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrests at London 'climate change' protests top 1,000...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190422115641-yohkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate group Extinction Rebellion has staged non-violent protests in London with the aim of stopping what it calls a global climate crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. measles cases surge as officials scramble to stop near-record outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-04-22/new-york-outbreaks-drive-us-measles-count-up-to-626</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20th candidate jumps in...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/rep-seth-moulton-becomes-the-20th-democratic-candidate-for-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Seth Moulton, a Massachusetts congressman known for prioritizing veterans issues declared his bid for the White House on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DE BLASIO: We Are Going to Ban Glass, Steel Skyscrapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/nyc-mayor-de-blasio-we-are-going-to-ban-glass-and-steel-skyscrapers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACE OF SRI LANKA MASTERMIND?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/International/Who-is-Moulvi-Zahran-Hashim-mastermind-of-one-of-the-Sri-Lanka-attacks-587544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Islamist extremist imam, he was a prolific lecturer for National Tawheed Jamaath.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media coverage of violent events found to fuel cycle of stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/media-coverage-of-violent-events-is-found-to-fuel-a/article_207707b6-58de-505e-9af3-a2650e590979.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an era of round-the-clock news cycles and ever-present social media apps, violent events that occur thousands of miles away can feel as though they strike increasingly close to home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home sales fall 4.9% in slow start to spring buying season...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/home-sales-fall-4-9-in-slow-start-to-spring-buying-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of existing U.S. homes fell in March after a huge gain the previous month, held back partly by a sharp slowdown among the most expensive properties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists stunned by creature capable of CLONING self...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1117276/antarctica-david-attenborough-bbc-blue-planet-divers-stunned-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTARCTICA researchers were left stunned by an animal they discovered below the ice capable of living for eternity by cloning itself, a documentary revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SUES HOUSE OVER FINANCIALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/22/trump-sues-to-block-subpoena-from-house-democrats-seeking-information-on-his-finances.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump says in the complaint that Democrats have "declared all-out political war" against him, with subpoenas as their "weapon of choice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel stumped by 'shifty, unreliable' witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/836501/muellers-team-reportedly-stumped-by-all-shifty-unreliable-people-trumps-orbit-employ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigators followed "several meandering paths" in their two-year investigation, "propelled by discoveries of unusual interactions between Trump associates and Russians," The Washington Post reported Sunday night. Mueller uncovered a lot in his 448-page final report, but his team was left with "some unanswered mysteries, a lot of dead ends and, ultimately, a conclusion that the contacts they found did not establish a criminal conspiracy," the Post says. Mueller's team had to grapple with a legal dispute with Attorney General William Barr over whether a president can even be accused of crimes, plus President Trump and his son Donald Trump Jr. refused to be interviewed, and the witnesses they did have "were not ideal," the Post reports: A few key players, prosecutors would contend, lied in interviews. Many were loyal to the president and echoed his rhetoric that Mueller's team was acting in bad faith. Some used encrypted applications with disappearing messages that could not be reviewed. Others were overseas, unreachable to American investigators. In some cases, their statements were only loosely tethered to the facts. [The Washington Post] Ex-Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort fits in the first three categories, and the "loosely tethered" description matches conspiracy theorist Jerome Corsi, the Post reports, citing an interview with Corsi's lawyer, David Gray. Corsi had offered "tantalizing leads" about Roger Stone and WikiLeaks, but his story was never quite straight and his leads always led to dead ends, the Post reports. Trying to get actionable material out of Corsi, "it's their biggest nightmare," Gray told the Post. "The supposed best of the best were just frankly dumbfounded by the whole situation." Corsi was not charged, he added, because after six marathon interviews, "at the end of the day, they threw up their hands and said, 'We can't use any of this.'" Read more about the obstacles Mueller couldn't get over at The Washington Post. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85 detonators found at bus station...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/22/85-bomb-detonators-found-main-sri-lanka-bus-station-9284689/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery was made a day after suicide bombers attacked churches and hotels killing 290 people and wounding about 500.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: PRESIDENT APPROVAL 39%... </title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS on rebound...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/isis-is-on-the-rebound-establishing-attack-zones-and-support-zones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS’S ZONE OFFENSE: ISIS may have lost its last “zone of territorial control” in Syria last month, but its Plan B is gaining momentum across Iraq and Syria, according to an analysis by the Institute for the Study of War.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Physician Burnout Jumps Dramatically; Half Frustrated...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/doctors-overworked-robots-physician-burnout-jumps-dramatically/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Physicians may be more stressed than ever -- one recent survey found that half were thinking about hanging up their stethoscopes for good. New research continues to demonstrate the demise of doctors, with burnout levels jumping dramatically over just a three-year span.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil hits 2019 high...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-oil/oil-hits-2019-high-on-u-s-plan-to-tighten-squeeze-on-iran-idUSKCN1RY00J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil topped $74 a barrel on Monday, the highest since November, as the United Sta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key 2020 constituency: Florida Hispanic vote doubled in '18...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/article229463804.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches Have Become #1 Target...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/churches-have-become-the-1-target-for-hate-attacks-an-average-of-105-every-single-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bombings in Sri Lanka have once again put a spotlight on the rising tide of violence against Christians all over the world</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk says machine to connect human brain to computers 'coming soon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-twitter-neuralink-brain-machine-interface-computer-ai-a8880911.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Raises Stakes With Threat to Close Hormuz...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2019/04/22/iran-will-close-strait-of-hormuz-if-it-can-t-use-it-fars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will close the Strait of Hormuz, a waterway vital for global oil shipments, if the country is prevented from using it.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA gears up for fully self-driving cars amid skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/09894dee68d7496399f176a77a8bc98d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Tesla CEO Elon Musk appears poised to transform the company's electric cars into driverless vehicles in a risky bid to realize a bold vision that he has been floating for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Proposes Student-Debt Cancellation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/sen-elizabeth-warren-proposes-student-debt-cancellation-11555934400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren is proposing using taxpayer money to wipe out hundreds of billions of dollars in student-loan debt as a way to control rising college costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19th candidate jumps in...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/rep-seth-moulton-of-massachusetts-enters-2020-democratic-presidential-race-11555931157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraq War veteran, who unsuccessfully opposed Nancy Pelosi, is the 19th Democratic candidate to join the campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fastest growing cities in each state...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/04/22/the-fastest-growing-city-in-each-state/39362311/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every state has at least one city that has reported rapid population growth in recent years. Net migration and natural growth are the factors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin refuses to congratulate...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/ukraine-election-volodymr-zelensky-putin-congratulate-comedian-a8881051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurrection in faith-based films...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/a-resurrection-in-faith-based-films-breakthrough/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long out of favor in Hollywood, faith-based movies, like "Breakthrough," are back on screen, with big-name talent, larger budgets, and box-office success</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Cancer Center Ousts 3 Chinese Scientists; Plot To Steal Data, Research...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/04/20/texas-cancer-center-ousts-3-chinese-scientists-concerns-data-theft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prominent cancer center MD Anderson in Houston has ousted three of five scientists whom federal authorities identified as being involved in Chinese efforts to steal American research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka Points to Islamic Militants in Easter Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/sri-lanka-makes-arrests-in-easter-bombing-attacks-11555918580 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sri Lankan officials believe an Islamist militant group was behind the Easter morning attacks that killed at least 290 people and wounded another 500; authorities took 24 people into custody in connection with the bombings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA investigates video of parked Model S exploding...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tesla-china/tesla-investigates-video-of-parked-model-s-exploding-in-shanghai-idUSKCN1RY023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. electric vehicle (EV) maker Tesla Inc said it has sent a team to investigat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Report, Biden Entry Set to Reshape Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/mueller-report-biden-s-entry-set-to-reshape-democratic-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller Report, Bidenâ€™s Entry Set to Reshape Democratic Campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Warnings, More Americans Die From High Sodium Intake...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/despite-warnings-more-americans-die-from-high-sodium-intake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diets High in Sodium AreÂ Killing Americans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Elderly Twice as Likely to Work Now Than in 1985...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/america-s-elderly-are-twice-as-likely-to-work-now-than-in-1985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in 57 years, participation rate in the labor force of retirement-age workers has cracked the 20 percent mark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group outraged at beating of Jewish effigy in Poland...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2499a84a203e4960b9a64cc049cf5b26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — The World Jewish Congress has expressed its "disgust and outrage" following reports that an effigy made to look like a stereotypical Jew was hanged and burned in a Polish...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince memoir 'BEAUTIFUL ONES' coming out in fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0c8b1deaae3b4329905d848b284f044b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The memoir Prince was working on at the time of his death is coming out Oct. 29. Random House confirmed Monday to The Associated Press that "The Beautiful Ones" will combine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg steals Beto thunder...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/439613-buttigieg-steals-betos-thunder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Texas Congressman Beto O’Rourke has been eclipsed in recent weeks by Pete Buttigieg, the upstart Indiana mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Where is God?'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/where-god-sri-lankans-stunned-deadly-blasts-060739864.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Shantha Prasad carried children wounded in Sri Lanka's deadly attacks into a Colombo hospital, memories of the country's deadly civil war flooded back. For many Sri Lankans, Sunday's attacks against churches and high-end hotels brought back painful memories of a conflict that lasted three</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns terrorists continue to plot attacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-warns-terrorists-continue-plot-sri-lanka-attacks-090121152.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US State Department has warned of possible terrorist attacks in a revised travel advisory for Sri Lanka, after a series of deadly blasts killed nearly 300 people -- including Americans -- in the island nation on Easter Sunday. Sunday's attacks saw suicide bombers target churches during Easter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Names Fiery New Chief to Head Elite Force Targeted by USA...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iran-names-fiery-chief-head-072631769.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei appointed General Hossein Salami, 58, to replace General Mohammad Ali Jafari, according to a decree published on his website. Salami’s fiery speeches during Friday prayers and his zealous support for the Islamic Revolution are among his hallmarks. No reason was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landslide election victory thrusts Ukrainian comedian into limelight...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190421203605-osgq8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-ELECTION/ZELENSKIY-NEWSMAKER (NEWSMAKER, PIX):NEWSMAKER-Landslide election victory thrusts Ukrainian comedian into limelight</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
