<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Australia calls for another mass evacuation as monster bushfires return...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-australia-bushfires/australia-calls-for-another-mass-evacuation-as-monster-bushfires-return-idUSKBN1Z730R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian authorities urged another mass evacuation across the heavily populate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUFTHANSA flight 'turned around'...</title>
      <link>https://www.flightglobal.com/air-transport/iran-surface-to-air-missile-downed-ukraine-737-canadian-and-us-officials/136070.article</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.flightglobal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian and US officials believe Iranian military forces, possibly by mistake, shot down the Ukraine International Airlines Boeing 737-800 that crashed outside Tehran on 8 January, killing 176 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan flees to Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7870677/Prince-Harry-Meghan-Markle-left-young-Archie-Canada.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Mail has learnt that Meghan Markle has returned to North America, where her and Prince Harry's eight-month-old son, Archie, had been left with his nanny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women with transplanted uterus gives birth to 'miracle' baby...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b8c4a4da006bf965b6706dc7ac6962b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who gave birth to a boy she carried inside a transplanted womb said Thursday that the experimental procedure delivered a “miracle.” Jennifer Gobrecht and her husband, Drew Gobrecht,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7870409/Video-appears-surface-air-missile-hitting-Ukrainian-plane-moments-crashed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage was released hours after Pentagon officials said they believe the Ukrainian Airlines flight which crashed in Tehran killing 176 people Wednesday was shot down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/09/stock-market-wall-street-in-focus-amid-us-iran-tensions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks jumped to record highs on Thursday as tensions between Iran and the U.S. eased for the time being, with tech shares outperforming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby Blames #MeToo For Conviction...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2020/01/09/bill-cosby-appeal-blames-metoo-sexual-assault-conviction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cosby filed the appeal with the Pennsylvania Supreme Court, which does not have to take the case, on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANADA: Perhaps 'Unintentional'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-crash-canada/canada-pm-says-evidence-indicates-iran-shot-down-ukraine-jet-idUSKBN1Z82JZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada has intelligence from multiple sources indicating a Ukrainian airliner th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg drops annual challenges...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-facebook-zuckerberg-goals/facebook-ceo-zuckerberg-drops-annual-challenges-to-focus-on-longer-term-goals-idUSKBN1Z82IN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc's Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg said on Thursday he ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA coach under fire for calling team 'bunch of thugs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/28453087/sources-john-beilein-meets-cavaliers-players-gives-emotional-apology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cavaliers are planning to continue with John Beilein as coach after he made an emotional apology to his players and met with GM Koby Altman on Thursday, sources told ESPN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell backs measure to change rules, dismiss...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/477587-mcconnell-backs-measure-to-change-senate-rules-dismiss-impeachment-without</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) is backing a resolution to change the Senate’s rules to allow for lawmakers to dismiss articles of impeachment against President Trump before the House sends them over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic conference call...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/01/09/harry-reportedly-held-epic-post-megxit-conference-call-with-royals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen, Prince Charles, Prince William and Harry burned up the phone lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border arrests drop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6a1d7f4d132225c902e93e3a9b5cd6ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The number of people arrested or stopped entering the United States along the Mexico border fell for a seventh straight month in December. with Mexicans making up a larger than...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'AMERICAN CRIME STORY: IMPEACHMENT' Delayed Until 2020 Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/american-crime-story-impeachment-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The third season of FX's "American Crime Story" on the Impeachment of Bill Clinton will not air in September as it was originally scheduled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance video from Epstein's first 'suicide' attempt 'no longer exists'... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/surveillance-video-jeffrey-epstein-s-first-apparent-suicide-attempt-no-n1113166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials at the federal jail housing Epstein preserved video from the wrong floor due to a clerical error.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>61% of say too much economic inequality...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/09/61-percent-of-americans-say-theres-too-much-economic-inequality-in-the-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Americans agree that the unequal distribution of income and opportunity between different groups has gotten to be too much. But less than half rate it a priority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: '60 MINS' MEETS THE REAL JOAQUIN PHOENIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/60-minutes-meets-joaquin-phoenix-2019-01-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dark, complex characters may be a trademark, but Joaquin Phoenix showed 60 Minutes a different side when he met Anderson Cooper. See the full interview, Sunday on CBS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Issued No-Fly Order Hours Before...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-issued-no-fly-order-over-iran-iraq-hours-before-ukrainian-plane-downed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just hours before a Ukrainian plane was shot down Wednesday over Iran, the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration issued a no-fly order over Iran and Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAG-AFTRA Office Evacuated for Second Time in 3 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sag-aftra-la-office-evacuated-second-time-3-days-1268363</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another phone threat was called in, and police are additionally searching the New York offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Infrared Blips'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/iran-commander-vows-harsher-revenge-against-us-relief-in-tehran-today-after-trump-speech-2020-01-09/#post-update-ca108587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is set to vote Thursday on a resolution that would limit President Trump's ability to engage in hostilities against Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Considers Ban On Gas-Powered Garden Tools...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2020/01/08/california-considers-statewide-ban-on-gas-powered-garden-tools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you have any gas-powered gardening tools, you may be forced to give them up soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL offering $100,000 salary amid mounting worker shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/taco-bell-offering-24100000-salary-amid-mounting-worker-shortage/ar-BBYMNIM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  42% CHANCE ON WINNING NOMINATION...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-primary-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2020 Democratic presidential primary election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's Lee Will Vote to Remove?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-utah-mike-lee-might-123233527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- Get Jonathan Bernstein’s newsletter every morning in your inbox. Click here to subscribe.I had a Twitter discussion awhile ago in which I argued that Utah Senator Mike Lee was one of the three or four most likely Republicans to vote to convict and remove President Donald Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER tests ways to limit online abuse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/twitter-test-ways-limit-online-abuse-151540387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has announced it will test new ways to limit online abuse by offering users control over who can reply to tweets. "We want to help people feel safe participating in the conversation on Twitter by giving them more control over the conversations they start," the company tweeted. Company</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plane turned back before crashing?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-probe-finds-ukrainian-plane-turned-back-problem-064526868.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian authorities have said a Ukrainian airliner, which crashed outside Tehran with the loss of all 176 people on board, had turned back after suffering a problem, as Ukrainian experts joined the investigation Thursday. Both Canada and the United States called for a full investigation to determine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan aim to control media image...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9d3ca824003dac85311b8e884918e94e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The relationship between Britain’s royals and the media is awkward, mistrustful — and seemingly inescapable. But now Meghan and Harry want out. After years of growing tension...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Iran shot down Ukrainian jetliner!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a2dc1478299d83e233c2cb4d4cd1891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two U.S. officials said Thursday it was “highly likely” that an Iranian anti-aircraft missile downed a Ukrainian jetliner late Tuesday, killing all 176 people on board....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue mocking Trump torched in Slovenia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0bcc73fa8eac7ceef4f2f9791297e2ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LJUBLJANA, Slovenia (AP) — A wooden statue mocking U.S. President Donald Trump was burned to the ground Thursday in Slovenia, the birthplace of his wife Melania, authorities said. The nearly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg won't release women who sued him from secrecy agreements...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/bloomberg-wont-release-women-sued-secrecy-agreements/story?id=68171036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg spoke out about the controversy over the non-disclosure agreements while on the campaign trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican senator: 'Trump's stock level at all-time high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/gop-senator-trumps-stock-level-at-all-time-high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key Republican senator on Wednesday said that respect for President Trump has surged since he ordered the killing of Iran’s top military leader, and he gave credit to the White House and Pentagon for reinvigorating U.S. deterrence power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON CLAIM:  Iran shot down Ukrainian jetliner!</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/downing-street-calls-for-urgent-inquiry-pentagon-confirms-plane-in-iran-was-shot-down-by-a4330741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing Street has said it was looking into "very concerning" reports about the Tehran airliner crash following speculation that the jet was shot down by a missile.  Asked whether there were any concerns about the cause of the disaster, the spokesman said: "I'm not going to speculate on this but the reports we have seen are very concerning and we are urgently looking into them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYALS ROCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/prince-harry-queen-meghan-markle-defied-plans-senior-royals-a4330341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry defied clear instructions from the Queen not to announce that he and Meghan are to quit as “senior” royals, the Evening Standard has been told.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bots Destroying Political Discourse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2020/01/bots-are-destroying-political-discourse-we-know-it/162285/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re mouthpieces for foreign actors, domestic political groups, even the candidates themselves. And soon you won’t be able to tell they’re bots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: 92-year-old woman murdered, left bleeding on NYC street...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/92-year-old-woman-found-dead-in-queens-was-murdered-nypd/2257158/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a 92-year-old woman was found unresponsive on the streets of Queens, police initially thought she had fallen — now authorities believe she was murdered. Police say they received a 911 call about Maria Fuertes just after midnight on Monday. She was found lying along 127th Street in Richmond Hill, not far from her home. She was later pronounced dead…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegals rescued from top of 30-foot border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/illegal-immigrants-rescued-from-top-of-30-foot-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Mexicans trying to sneak into the United States had to be rescued from the top of a 30-foot tall section of the border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISSILE MYSTERY...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/explanations-for-ukrainian-air-crash-elusive-amid-political-tensions-with-iran-154827922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior official in Ukraine says the authorities in Kyiv are looking into whether a missile brought down a passenger aircraft that crashed in Iran on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Strikes Out in Attempt to Get New Judge...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-judge-rejection-jury-selection-1202825580/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge in Harvey Weinstein’s New York rape trial won’t be stepping down today from the case nor putting the brakes on it, despite a harsh January 8 request by the disgraced producer’s defense te…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Silicon Valley, some men say cosmetic procedures essential to career...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/In-Silicon-Valley-some-men-say-cosmetic-14962007.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lounging at an outdoor cafe just outside downtown San Francisco, his athletic frame filling out a slim-fit button-up, a talkative tech worker named Daniel detailed the many ways he's optimizing his existence.  Only the previous week, he says, he returned from a 10-day trip to Italy's Amalfi Coast. Before that, he boasts, he journeyed to a yoga retreat and juice cleanse in Bali, the perfect setting to unload the stress he absorbs working at a well-known tech company in Silicon Valley. After ending a five-year marriage and shedding 10 pounds of subcutaneous fat several years back - his sun-kissed body now carb- and toxin-free - Daniel has reemerged a new, seemingly younger man.  The changes have enhanced his dating life, but more importantly, he says, they've bolstered his youthful professional image, giving colleagues the impression that he's high-energy, hard-working and on-trend. There's only one problem. Most of Daniel's co-workers think he's in his late 30s, but he's actually 48 years old. As far as Silicon Valley is concerned, his birth date is the tech world's equivalent of prehistory, years before Jobs and Wozniak set up what would become Apple in Jobs's parents' garage.  So like a growing number of male tech workers, Daniel is considering a new strategy to conceal his "advanced" age for years to come: plastic surgery, including Botox, a facelift to counteract under-eye bags and the kind of midsection sculpting that could offer the impression that washboard abs ripple beneath his tailored shirts.  Daniel, who spoke on the condition that only his first name be published for fear of being outed as old, has discussed those procedures with Larry Fan, a San Francisco-based plastic surgeon. Fan estimates that about 25% of his patients now are men like Daniel, the vast majority of whom work in tech. Increasingly, he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Boasts of Stock Market In Wild Tweet: 'HOW ARE YOUR 409K'S DOING?'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-boasts-of-stock-market-in-wild-tweet-how-are-your-409ks-doing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was all over the place with his Thursday morning Twitter proclamations, but in one of his latest ones, he declared that the stock market is soaring and everyone's "409</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islamic State's Revival Back in Play...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/islamic-state-s-revival-is-back-in-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€œFrom ISISâ€™s point of view, a U.S.-Iran conflict works in its favor in a couple of different ways,â€� said Kamran Bokhari.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Strikes Out in Attempt to Get New Judge in Rape Trial...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/news/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-judge-new-york-1203461715/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein struck out in his attempt on Thursday to get a new judge assigned to his rape trial in New York. Attorneys for the movie mogul accused Justice James Burke of being prejudicial afte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Dems pressuring Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/09/senate-democrats-begin-breaking-with-nancy-pelosi-on-articles-of-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increasingly impatient Senate Democrats have started speaking out about their desire for House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) to turn over impeachment articles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mass protests in France as pension dispute grinds on...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mass-protests-france-pension-dispute-grinds-144343206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protestors poured into streets across France on Thursday in the latest mass demonstrations against a pensions overhaul that critics say would require millions of people to push back retirement. Unions are demanding the government drop its reform in their biggest show of strength in decades, with a record-breaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver 'possessed by devil' crashes into church...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7868889/Driver-possessed-devil-smashes-car-Spanish-church.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man forced his Jeep through the door of the church in Sonseca, Spain, in the early hours of yesterday morning (pictured: the vehicle parked in the aisle).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Hernandez secret gay lover opens up about relationship...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7865401/Aaron-Hernandezs-secret-gay-lover-opens-relationship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dennis SanSoucie, right, told how he first began a sexual relationship with Hernandez, left, at school. 'We didn't want anyone to know. We were just in complete denial', he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY?</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5762021/nancy-pelosi-trump-impeachment-gamble/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi has spent decades rising to the top in Congress, but the past 12 months have been arguably her most consequential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPEACHMENT TRIAL NEXT WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/477470-graham-senate-will-take-up-impeachment-trial-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) said on Wednesday that the Senate will start its impeachment proceedings next week, signaling an end to the stalemate over the articles which have sat in the House since December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary privately warned lawmakers against debating limits...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/defense-secretary-esper-privately-warned-lawmakers-debating-trumps/story?id=68164993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Mark Esper privately urged Congress not to debate limits to President Donald Trump’s power to strike Iran because he said it might hurt the troops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Bank warns of global debt crisis amid borrowing buildup...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2020/jan/08/world-bank-global-debt-crisis-borrowing-build-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Current debt wave is largest, fastest and most broad-based since 1970s, say economists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dem: Time to send articles to Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/top-house-democrat-time-send-articles-impeachment-senate-n1112831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think it is time to send the impeachment to the Senate and let Mitch McConnell be responsible for the fairness of the trial," Smith said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACO BELL Offering $100,000 Salary...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/taco-bell-offering-100-000-salary-amid-mounting-worker-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taco Bell Offering $100,000 Salary Amid Mounting Worker Shortage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Republican video mocks 'MAGA Church'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/lincoln-project-donald-trump-evangelical-voters-f6cfd864-cc1f-4b6c-b881-690151c95dd7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group of GOP strategists wants to defeat the president in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Habitual tea drinking 'linked to longer life'...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-01-09/habitual-tea-drinking-linked-to-longer-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai journalist sentenced over tweet warns of threat to media freedom...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thai-journalist-sentenced-over-tweet-warns-threat-media-114140721.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Thai journalist sentenced to two years in prison for defaming the owner of a poultry farm via a tweet said Thursday the kingdom's criminal libel laws are eviscerating media freedom. A court convicted Suchanee Cloitre in December for a tweet referencing a dispute over working conditions at a chicken</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pre-school Picasso' shakes up art world...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pre-school-picasso-shakes-german-art-world-021349416.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his striped jumper, goofy grin and dreams of becoming a professional footballer, Akar seems just like any other seven-year-old boy. Dubbed the "pre-school Picasso" by German media, Akar's paintings now sell for thousands of euros (dollars) to buyers from across the world. Akar senior</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Year for Jobs -- Also Likely Worst Since 2011...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/great-u-jobs-likely-worst-090000638.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up here to receive the Davos Diary, a special daily newsletter that will run from Jan. 20-24.It was both a great year for the U.S. jobs market, and the worst in almost a decade.The final jobs report for the year, due Friday, is forecast to show employers added 160,000 jobs in December</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French unions return to streets in make-or-break pension protest...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109114712-u3w1p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PENSIONS/PROTESTS (UPDATE 3, TV, PIX):UPDATE 3-French unions return to streets in make-or-break pension protest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin oversees hypersonic missile test...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109111839-8jhcy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/MILITARY (URGENT):Russia's Putin oversees hypersonic missile test in Crimea - TASS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will having female defense attorney help Harvey? Jury is out...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109102703-to9ts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal experts say Rotunno's gender may be an advantage when she cross-examines Weinstein's accusers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feces-smeared fakes: Scientists use rubber hands in OCD therapy...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109042732-biuje</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-OBSESSIVE/ (PIX):Faeces-smeared fakes: Scientists use rubber hands in OCD therapy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denied U.S. entry, Mexican cuts own throat on bridge over Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109030359-18daw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO-DEATH:Denied U.S. entry, Mexican cuts own throat on bridge over Rio Grande</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Puerto Ricans still without power, many sleeping outdoors after quakes...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200109005149-tln25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PUERTORICO-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Most Puerto Ricans still without power, many sleeping outdoors after quakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete 'CIA plant'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/far-left-internet-thinks-mayor-pete-buttigieg-is-a-secret-agent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Pete Is CIA” meme crystallizes a pervasive feeling about Buttigieg: that he, like the broken world we live in, was crafted by institutions that can no longer be trusted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders emerges as growing threat to Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/09/biden-sanders-concern-2020-096520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former veep is more concerned about Sanders than he lets on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN'S FURY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7866007/Harry-Meghan-step-senior-royals-financially-independent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harry and Meghan quit as senior Royals, announcing they will split their time between the UK and North America, and are understood to have done so without discussing the matter with other Royals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Quietly Removes 'Glaciers Gone by 2020' Signs...</title>
      <link>https://wattsupwiththat.com/2019/06/06/glacier-national-park-quietly-removes-its-gone-by-2020-signs-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wattsupwiththat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana Glacier National Park Mountains Cracker Lake Glaciers Appear to be Growing, not Melting in Recent Years By Roger I. Roots, J.D., Ph.D., Founder, Lysander Spooner University May 30, 2019. St…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie-Hillary echoes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/477458-bernie-hillary-echoes-seen-in-biden-sanders-primary-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Joe Biden was asked last week at an Iowa town hall if he was running a better campaign than Hillary Clinton had in 2016, it highlighted a question on the minds of some Democrats: Is Biden this cycle’s Clinton?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia bushfires flare as heatwave brings renewed misery...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-bushfires-flare-heatwave-brings-renewed-misery-035143048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bushfires flared in southern Australia on Thursday as a heatwave expected to bring renewed misery set in, and officials warned some areas are "just at the beginning" of the devastating crisis. Soldiers went door-to-door advising residents to leave the South Australian town of Parndana on Kangaroo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Won't Back Down From Allowing Lies in Political Ads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/90e5e81f501346f8779cb2f8b8880d9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Facebook has decided not to limit how political ads can be targeted to specific groups of people, as its main digital-ad rival Google did in November to fight misinformation....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia issues new evacuation alerts as monster bushfires regenerate...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108234446-pyc00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIA- BUSHFIRES/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-Australia issues new evacuation alerts as monster bushfires regenerate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian judge orders NETFLIX to stop showing gay Jesus movie...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200108230813-vil8u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-LGBT/MEDIA:Brazilian judge orders Netflix to stop showing gay Jesus movie</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
