<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Job rating sinks to 42%...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/biden-s-job-rating-sinks-42-percent-nbc-news-poll-n1282781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just nine months into his presidency, 71 percent of Americans say the country is headed in the wrong direction, the poll shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES CANCELS 1,500+ FLIGHTS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/31/business/american-airlines-cancels-flights-sunday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Airlines canceled another 634 flights on Sunday, more than 12% of its total operations for the day, the company said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun Rights Case Could Upend NYC, LA Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-supreme-court-new-york-violence-los-angeles-gun-politics-10145dcf18c16614922e5b5d73907eeb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court is preparing to hear a gun rights case that could lead to more guns on the streets of New York and Los Angeles and threaten restrictions on guns in subways, airports, bars, churches, schools and other places where people gather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabs at least 10 on Tokyo train, starts fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tokyo-commuter-train-stabbing-90912df8b86c80b9db46bc256eab5124</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A man brandishing a knife on a Tokyo commuter train on Sunday stabbed several passengers before starting a fire, police said. NHK public television said at least 10 passengers were injured, including one seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for Intelligent Life Heads Underwater...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/10/someday-we-might-really-be-able-talk-whales/620552/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are using AI to try to decode whale clicks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at CA city council member's home leaves 1 dead, 3 hurt...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Shooting-Gilroy-council-member-home-16577842.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three other people were reportedly injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban supreme leader makes first public appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211031-taliban-supreme-leader-makes-first-public-appearance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban supreme leader Haibatullah Akhundzada addressed supporters in the southern city of Kandahar, officials announced Sunday, his first public appearance since taking control of the group in 2016.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cyber heist rocks high society jeweller...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10148265/Massive-cyber-heist-rocks-high-society-jeweller-Graff.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cyber criminals have already leaked 69,000 confidential documents on to the so-called 'dark web', including files relating to Donald Trump, Oprah Winfrey, David Beckham and Sir Philip Green.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need for liver transplants due to heavy drinking soared...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/26/health/pandemic-drinking-liver-transplants-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The need for liver transplants because of heavy drinking soared during the pandemic, researchers reported Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How pandemic made America's mental health crisis worse.</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am-deep-dive-mental-health-crisis-f033a787-ab2b-457c-81d0-10402b1445f5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And how the pandemic made it worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marie Antoinette's Adultery Unmasked by Modern Science...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/marie-antoinettes-adultery-unmasked-by-modern-science/ar-AAQ9496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent study employing a technique called X-ray fluorescence spectroscopy, scientists discovered formerly redacted phrases on eight letters between Marie Antoinette and the Swedish count Axel Fersen, who was rumored to have been her lover. Further analysis revealed that the correspondence had been censored by Count Fersen himself. The altered words, which included “beloved,” “adore,” and “madly,” have now sparked something of a controversy:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF preps for war: Drill for 2,000 rockets a day, internal strife...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/home-front-command-rahel-to-carry-out-joint-war-time-drill-starting-today-683587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Front Command and RAHEL to carry out joint war-time drill starting today * In war, 2,000 rockets expected to be fired per day by Hezbollah</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives say compromise could jeopardize hopes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/579170-progressives-fear-compromise-could-jeopardize-midterm-hopes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are fretting over the pared-back framework of Democrats’ massive social policy and climate bill, warning that it won’t be enough to motivate the party’s liberal base ahead of the 2022 midterms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Florida bars professors from being expert witnesses against state...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/30/us/university-of-florida-voting-rights/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Florida told three professors hired to testify as expert witnesses in a voting rights case against the state of Florida that they cannot participate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonga find first Covid case. Now potential lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/30/asia/tonga-first-covid-case-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Pacific island nation of Tonga reported its first case of Covid-19 on Friday, spurring thousands of people to get vaccinated amid warnings of a national lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossilized charcoal shows once-temperate Antarctica was often hit by wildfires, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/fossilized-charcoal-shows-once-temperate-antarctica-was-often-hit-by-wildfires/ar-AAQ7NEz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports says “lightning strikes, fireballs, sparks and volcanic activity” were regular phenomenon in what is now an icy continent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In setback for Black Lives Matter, mayoral campaigns shift to 'law and order'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/In-a-setback-for-Black-Lives-Matter-mayoral-16577651.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayoral candidates across the country are closing out their campaigns pledging to restore...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian troop movements near Ukraine border prompt concern in USA, Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russian-troop-movements-near-ukraine-border-prompt-concern-in-us-europe/ar-AAQ8CdO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Renewed buildup of Russian personnel, materiel comes as Moscow hardens rhetoric on Ukraine, severs formal ties with NATO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia race, Biden's stalled agenda, low polls have Dems fearing 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Virginia-race-Biden-s-stalled-agenda-and-low-16577645.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic concerns about President Joe Biden's flagging approval ratings, slow-moving...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While coal makes comeback, reduced supplies stoke fears over electrical grids...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/business/businessnews/s-2588379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — Coal, a pariah fuel for climate activists, has made a quiet comeback this year in the post-lockdown economic resurgence. Coal stockpiles at power plants are getting so low that the regional electric grid operator, PJM Interconnection, has taken steps to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK faces difficult road despite rebrand...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/579218-facebook-faces-difficult-road-despite-rebrand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s rebrand as Meta has done little so far to assuage its critics or turn down the political heat focused on the Silicon Valley giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26K NYC workers remain unvaccinated after Friday deadline...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/579257-26k-nyc-workers-remain-unvaccinated-after-friday-deadline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-six percent of municipal employees in New York City were still unvaccinated following a Friday deadline that mandated workers get the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo attorney says sheriff leaked grand jury secrets in sex crime probe...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211030210628-55vxv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK/CUOMO:Cuomo attorney says sheriff leaked grand jury secrets in sex crime probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court embarks on most dramatic reckoning for abortion rights in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-embarks-on-most-dramatic-reckoning-for-abortion-rights-in-decades/ar-AAQ8aUQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a one-month span, court will take up cases from Texas and Mississippi that could alter constitutional right to abortion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/10/30/alec-baldwin-speaks-first-time-on-camera-halyna-hutchins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baldwin breaks his silence in person while laying low in Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin speaks out about fatal shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/30/alec-baldwin-breaks-silence-on-fatal-shooting-of-halyna-hutchins-on-rust-set/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A haggard looking Alec Baldwin broke his silence Saturday, declaring his friendship with Halyna Hutchins — the cinematographer he accidentally shot and killed on the set of his film “Ru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Gas Used As Weapon?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/russia-close-using-natural-gas-weapon-europes-gas-crunch-biden-energy-adviser-2021-10-25/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Joe Biden's global energy security adviser said on Monday that Russian President Vladimir Putin is getting close to using natural gas as a political tool if Russia is holding back fuel exports to Europe as it suffers an energy crunch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Pipeline Changes Direction, and Energy Politics Come to Fore...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/30/a-russian-pipeline-changes-direction-and-energy-politics-come-to-the-fore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — Natural gas, already in short supply in Europe this fall, began moving away from Germany on Saturday and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 83% Have Witnessed Paranormal Activity In Homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/moved-because-house-haunted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;83 percent of respondents say they have witnessed some paranormal activity inside their own home.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
