<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Pandemic turned us into barbarians...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/culture/sports/1001080/the-pandemic-turned-us-into-barbarians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATIONAL ENQUIRER Hit with Fine from FEC over Buying and Killing Story from Mistress...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/06/01/national-enquirer-hit-with-187k-fine-from-federal-election-commission-over-buying-and-killing-story-from-trump-mistress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember when the National Enquirer was doing Donald Trump’s dirty work? Well, they’ve just been fined $187,000 by the Federal Election Commission for buying and killing a tell all by f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts ferry operator hit by ransomware attack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/local/mass-steamship-authority-delayed-due-to-cyber-attack/2477951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ransomware attack on the Steamship Authority of Massachusetts hampered operations Wednesday morning. The largest ferry service to the islands of Martha’s Vineyard and Nantucket, the Steamship Authority issued a statement warning that traveling customers may be delayed as a result. A “team of IT professionals” is working to assess the impact of the cyber attack, according to the Authority. No further information…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China threatens USA with 'intense nuclear showdown'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15140218/china-threatens-us-intense-nuclear-showdown-atomic-program/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has threatened the United States with an “intense nuclear showdown” as it ramps up its atomic program. The Chinese Communist Party’s mouthpiece newspaper launched a blisteri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glenn Greenwald 'New Master of Right-Wing Media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/is-glenn-greenwald-the-new-master-of-right-wing-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leftist scribe has become “a practitioner of manufactured controversy” for outlets like Fox News, say his stunned former colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3-year-old piano prodigy to perform at Carnegie Hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/piano-prodigy-practices-for-carnegie-hall-performance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brigitte Xie's piano talent has earned her a spot on stage at Carnegie Hall this fall. She will likely be the youngest person on stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proof of aliens would lead to new religions and massive military spending...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/proof-aliens-lead-new-religions-24235493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former US president says many people’s religious beliefs will change if it’s ever proved alien life does exist – and there’ll be calls for huge amounts to be spent on arming ourselves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside CITIZEN: The public safety app pushing surveillance boundaries...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/E241fA5UcAAGMLd?format=jpg&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino Vows One Last Film!</title>
      <link>https://moviemaker.com/quentin-tarantino-most-directors-have-horrible-last-movies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino has long promised that his tenth movie will be his last, and he said in a podcast released Tuesday that he hopes to avoid the common director curse of going out with a “horrible” film. In an interview on Tuesday’s episode of the Pure Cinema Podcast with Elric Kane and Brian Saur, the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Stand your ground' defense rejected in iguana killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/stand-your-ground-defense-rejected-in-iguana-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge has rejected the “stand your ground” defense of a Florida man who said he beat an iguana to death only after it attacked him, biting him on the arm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod shark detections surging as researchers tag more: 118 great whites!</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2021/05/31/cape-cod-shark-detections-rising-as-researchers-tag-more-118-great-whites-detected-last-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of great white sharks detected along the Cape has ballooned over the last few years as researchers continue to tag more of the apex predators each summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HISTORIC 5TH ELECTION?!</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/israel-change-government-deadline-oust-netanyahu-cf0fd3c2-9b4d-448d-b165-8fae8afc55aa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel hasn't had a new prime minister since 2009.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Saving Routing Algorithm Makes Drivers Walk Into Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5db95k/amazons-cost-saving-routing-algorithm-makes-drivers-walk-into-traffic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s fucking horrendous, honestly. [You're crossing] multiple lanes, busy traffic."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half in relationships say current partner WORST in bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-say-current-partner-worst-ever-in-bed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds one in two Americans in a relationship admit that their current partner is the worst sex they’ve ever had.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA Steamship Authority Hit by Ransomware Attack; Ferries Delayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.necn.com/news/local/mass-steamship-authority-delayed-due-to-cyber-attack/2477951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.necn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ransomware attack on the Steamship Authority of Massachusetts hampered operations Wednesday morning. The largest ferry service to the islands of Martha’s Vineyard and Nantucket, the Steamship Authority issued a statement warning that traveling customers may be delayed as a result. A “team of IT professionals” is working to assess the impact of the cyber attack, according to the Authority. No further information…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failed Drug Test Confirmed for Kentucky Derby Winner Medina Spirit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/02/failed-drug-test-confirmed-for-kentucky-derby-winner-medina-spirit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kentucky Derby winner Medina Spirit’s post-race positive drug test was confirmed by a second sample requested by trainer Bob</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin critic Navalny loses bid to end sleep deprivation 'torture'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210602130208-ej6ih</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny loses bid to end sleep deprivation 'torture'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANSOM PAID?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210602130008-2axr7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CYBER-JBS/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-JBS beef plant workers scheduled to return to work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaped elephants leave 300 mile trail of destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/02/herd-of-escaped-elephants-leave-500km-trail-of-destruction-in-south-west-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wild herd has wrecked barns and eaten fields of crops after absconding from nature reserve in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will APPLE Be Next Tech Giant to Buy Studio?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/apple-buy-film-studio-amazon-mgm-1234961585/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid a wave of M&amp;A fever, will Amazon’s $8.45 billion takeover of MGM prompt its Silicon Valley rival Apple to refresh its shopping list to include a Hollywood studio? The iPhone maker already …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new 'hot spots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9643303/Experts-reveal-global-hot-spots-new-coronaviruses-emerge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conditions are 'ripe' for the zoonotic diseases like Covid to jump from bats to humans, particularly in China, due to changes in land use by humans, researchers reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators Eye Giuliani Security Firm as Probe Ramps Up...</title>
      <link>https://money.yahoo.com/federal-investigators-eye-rudy-giuliani-085423966.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyAs the feds expand their probe into Rudy Giuliani, investigators have homed in on Giuliani Security &amp; Safety, a consulting firm that has done business with various governments and organizations around the world, according to two people briefed on the matter and another source familiar with the situation.In recent months, the investigators have asked questions about and examined documents related to Giuliani Security &amp; Safety (GSS). Their interest comes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Teen Girl Fights Off Bear To Save Dogs!</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/01/push-an-apex-predator-man-teenage-girl-fights-off-bear-rescue-dogs-bradbury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Memorial Day will be hard to forget for one teenager who fought off a bear to protect her dogs in Bradbury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boaters allegedly harassed another group over gay pride flags. Then their boat burst into flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/moses-lake-boaters-allegedly-harassed-another-group-over-gay-pride-flags-then-their-boat-burst-into-flames/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Grant County Sheriff's Office confirmed the incident took place on Sunday on Moses Lake, adding that the agency was working to interview the people involved before releasing more information. Police did not identify anyone onboard the two boats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker wielding newfound Senate power...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/02/cory-booker-senate-491519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey Democrat says another White House run isn't on his mind, as his friend and former colleague Vice President Kamala Harris "by all measure is on deck."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic getting worse, even when seems like getting better?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-pandemic-is-getting-worse-even-when-it-seems-like-its-getting-better/ar-AAKCdt1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic may feel over for many Americans, but it’s heating up in other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video indicates how McCarthy, Luntz mixed friendship and business...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/video-indicates-how-mccarthy-and-luntz-mixed-friendship-and-business/ar-AAKCylA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House GOP leader appears to have participated in pollster's focus group while staying in his apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid origins mystery continues to spark speculation and tension...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210602-covid-origins-mystery-continues-to-spark-speculation-and-tension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid origins mystery continues to spark speculation and tension</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Boom Cooling?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/02/housing-boom-may-be-cooling-as-weekly-mortgage-demand-drops-again.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High prices and low supply are finally taking some of the heat out of the housing market, and mortgage demand is following suit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist has sex during interview for segment on swingers club...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/01/danish-journalist-has-sex-during-interview-for-segment-on-swingers-club/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louise Fischer, 26, can be heard moaning during the on-the-record intercourse, part of a two-minute segment that aired on Radio 4 in Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14-Year-Old Shot, 12-Year-Old Arrested After Opening Fire On Deputies...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/06/02/gone-wrong-sheriff-14-year-old-girl-12-year-old-boy-shot-deputies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sheriff's deputies in Volusia County were forced to fire on a 14-year-old girl and a 12-year-old boy after they reportedly opened fire on them from a home they broke into.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'GIRL FROM IPANEMA:' Re-imagining classic for today's Rio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/latin-america-entertainment-music-health-coronavirus-pandemic-bb45163a74e7d47c23a38f09a4cbe1e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Chauffeured in a classic Porsche, the Brazilian beauty steps out into 1960s Rio de Janeiro. The pastel pastiche is easy on the eyes, and so is the pin-up girl tracing twirls as a guitar strums the city’s hymn: “The Girl from Ipanema."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim woman on flight told she 'would bring whole plane down,' group says...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/muslim-woman-on-flight-told-she-would-bring-the-whole-plane-down-advocacy-group-says/article_061b15ee-5f26-56ac-9508-7205b4715659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas — A Muslim woman from Dallas-Fort Worth is the focus of a religious discrimination complaint filed against Southwest Airlines on Tuesday after she said a flight attendant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He killed iguana and got arrested. Now claiming 'stand your ground' defense...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/killed-iguana-got-arrested-now-224300133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iguana started it. Or so says a man who claims he feared for his life and had every right to bash the creature to death under Florida’s stand your ground law. PJ Nilaja Patterson, 43, is accused of animal cruelty over killing an iguana. But the 6-foot-3, 165-pound man argues that he was in fear for his life — and that the 3-foot green iguana was the first to resort to violence during their ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaster feared as chemical cargo ship sinks off Sri Lanka...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210602055442-h7jpo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SRI LANKA-SHIP/ (PIX, TV):Disaster feared as chemical cargo ship sinks off Sri Lanka</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details Emerge On 'Highly Modified Drone' That Outran Police Over Tucson...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/40756/new-details-emerge-on-the-highly-modified-drone-that-outran-police-helicopters-over-tucson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drone was first detected near an energy storage facility across from Davis-Monthan AFB before evading two pursuing law enforcement helicopters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Finds Link Between PFIZER Shot, Myocarditis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israel-sees-probable-link-between-pfizer-vaccine-small-number-myocarditis-cases-2021-06-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Health Ministry said on Tuesday it had found the small number of heart inflammation cases observed mainly in young men who received Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine in Israel were likely linked to their vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Rivals Face Midnight Deadline to Oust... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-rivals-face-midnight-deadline-to-oust-israeli-premier/ar-AAKCH8C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rivals of Benjamin Netanyahu are up against a midnight Wednesday deadline to lock down a new government that would unseat Israel’s longest-serving prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN under ethics scrutiny following Cuomo revelations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/556413-cnn-under-ethics-scrutiny-following-cuomo-revelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN is coming under internal and external criticism over its approach to conflicts of interest for journalists after host Chris Cuomo escaped disciplinary action despite advising his brother New York Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Targets Tax Break That Helped Trump Build Fortune...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-targets-tax-break-helped-090000749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden is pushing to close a tax break that helped his predecessor amass a fortune.The Democrat has proposed narrowing a tax code provision that allows real estate investors to avoid capital gains taxes when they sell property, as long as they use the gains to buy more. Former President Donald Trump’s most valuable investment, which traces back to his $95 million purchase of a west-side Manhattan development site, has benefited from the rule.In 2005, when Trump’s part</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of $113 Million Deli...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/02/the-mystery-of-the-113-million-deli/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. In a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spared for Months, Vietnam Faces Wave of Infections...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/02/spared-for-months-vietnam-faces-a-wave-of-new-infections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 20 years, the husband and wife were stalwarts of their evangelical community: pastors who founded a small</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Many Workers, Change in Mask Policy Is Nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/02/for-many-workers-change-in-mask-policy-is-a-nightmare/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kroger supermarket in Yorktown, Va., is in a county where mask wearing can be casual at best. Yet for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports first human case of H10N3 bird flu... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/15131742/first-human-case-h10n3-bird-flu-confirmed-china-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has confirmed the world’s first human case of the H10N3 bird flu. A 41-year-old man, from the eastern city of Zhenjiang, developed a fever and other symptoms and was hospitalised on Apr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers have 1 week to opt out of mass wireless sharing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/jun/01/amazon-us-customers-given-one-week-to-opt-out-of-mass-wireless-sharing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics raise transparency fears over plan to turn all smart home devices into ‘mesh network’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers unite in disdain for Bibi...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/snubbed-fired-and-vilified-opposition-lawmakers-unite-in-disdain-for-netanyahu/ar-AAKCoSX </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA STILL THRIVES...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-surreal-submerged-conspiratorial-trump-centered-political-universe-still-thrives/ar-AAKBjCz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various non-Trumps are leveraging the energy of his falsehoods and his base for their own ends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Office Supply Hits Another Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/manhattan-office-supply-hits-another-record-even-as-nyc-opens-up/ar-AAKBi7Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manhattan’s supply of office space has reached a fresh record even as leasing picks up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashes in with book...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9640605/Fauci-cashes-COVID-Doctor-release-book-TRUTH-appear-Disney-backed-documentary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infectious disease expert, 80, will publish a tome titled 'Expect the Unexpected: Ten Lessons on Truth, Service, and the Way Forward'. It will be released on November 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTACART Wants to Replace Gig Shoppers With Robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/instacart-looks-to-use-robots-over-people-to-do-grocery-shopping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instacart Wants to Replace Army of Gig Shoppers With Robots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon report clears use of drones made by Chinese...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/556370-pentagon-report-clears-use-of-drones-made-by-top-chinese-manufacturer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two drone models made by China’s largest manufacturer have been cleared for use by a Pentagon audit, according to a report summary obtained by The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK reports no new deaths!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210601143331-tpr2n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-CASUALTIES (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-UK reports no new COVID-19 deaths for first time since March 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charges after Capitol insurrection roil far-right groups...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/only-on-ap-michael-pence-donald-trump-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-1e0560dbd5572944e3435e225f8be616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indictments. Infighting. Incarceration. Former President Donald Trump’s lies about a stolen 2020 election united right-wing supporters, conspiracy theorists and militants on Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAT HACK SHAKES GLOBE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/jbs-sa-lifestyle-health-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-bf82114d3f54e5be2241bd5f9a0b2639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — The world’s largest meat processing company is getting back online after production around the world was disrupted by a cyberattack just weeks after a similar incident shut down a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will New York's Vaccine Passport Catch On?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/will-the-excelsior-pass-new-yorks-vaccine-passport-catch-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Upper East Side in Manhattan, a well-heeled crowd flashed it to get into a socially distanced dance performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas ready to roll dice on normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/01/us/las-vegas-reopening/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a giant clock counted down to 12:01 Tuesday morning, crowds cheered the complete reopening of downtown Las Vegas for the first time in more than a year, with live music and no mask or social distancing required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Elvis' stolen from Birthplace sign in Tupelo...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtva.com/content/news/Elvis-Birthplace-sign-vandalized-574538501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtva.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the past few days, someone stole the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA launches slavery reparations task force...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/1/california-launches-slavery-reparations-task-force/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark California committee to study reparations for African Americans is meeting for the first time, launching a two-year process to address the harms of slavery and systemic racism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. hotel up for sale -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trump-s-company-puts-dc-hotel-lease-up-for-sale-again/ar-AAKBCzF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump's company previously tried selling the lease to its luxury Washington hotel before covid struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disgruntled' firefighter kills co-worker,  sets property alight and kills himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9641547/Active-shooter-reported-Santa-Clarita-Police-respond-calls-one-dead-stand-off.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are responding to calls of an active shooter in Santa Clarita, California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing beings on mix-and-match booster shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/01/booster-shot-us-begins-study-testing-mix-and-match-covid-vaccine-doses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial will include about 150 adults who have been fully vaccinated with the Johnson &amp; Johnson, Moderna or Pfizer Covid vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to suspend oil leases in Alaska Arctic refuge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/alaska-arctic-wildlife-refuge-oil-gas-drilling-biden-b9f20088957d42e99b791ff94169198f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration on Tuesday suspended oil and gas leases in Alaska’s Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, reversing a drilling program approved by the Trump administration and reviving a political fight over a remote region that is home to polar bears and other wildlife — and a rich reserve of oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agent charged with attempted murder of man onboard Metro...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/montgomery-county/2021/06/fbi-agent-accused-of-shooting-metro-passenger-turns-self-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An FBI agent accused of shooting a Metro passenger last December has turned himself in after facing charges of second-degree murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Body Found In Burning Home Possibly Linked To SoCal Fire Station Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/06/01/shooting-reported-at-agua-dulce-fire-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities were on scene of a house fire in Acton which may be linked to a shooting at an L.A. County Fire Department station in Agua Dulce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  'SPONGEBOB', 'TRANSFORMERS' Cost U.S. Taxpayers $4 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/01/spongebob-and-transformers-cost-u-s-taxpayers-4-billion-study-says-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dismissed by critics and devoured by fans, “Transformers: Age of Extinction” was the top box office film in 2014, bringing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavioral health check-ups to become routine for soldiers...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/06/01/behavioral-health-check-ups-could-soon-be-as-routine-for-soldiers-as-teeth-cleanings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One soldier suggested mandatory behavioral health checkups for troops that would occur every six months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mossad head hints at continued assassinations, attacks on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/new-mossad-head-barnea-hints-at-continued-assassinations-attacks-on-iran-669807</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel would not be passive simply because the majority of the world was willing to look the other way on Iran’s nuclear program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-year-old dies after being hit by electric scooter; DUI arrest made...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/elderly-man-dies-after-being-struck-by-electric-scooter-in-venice-dui-arrest-made-lapd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have arrested a man on suspicion of DUI in connection with a crash involving an electric scooter in Venice that resulted in the death of a 91-year-old man, police said Tuesday. The victim wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite vaccines, nursing homes struggle with outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-nursing-homes-coronavirus-pandemic-health-4575fbefb2cf87e96c82043ef94e5ff3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeannie Wells had hoped that regular visits would resume at her elderly mother’s New York nursing home once all the residents were fully vaccinated against COVID-19. Around Easter, her wish finally came true, and she was able to hold the 93-year-old’s hand more than a year after bringing her mother to the facility for rehabilitation for a fractured hip and knee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel on Edge as Politicians Wrangle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-on-edge-as-politicians-wrangle-over-coalition-to-oust-netanyahu/ar-AAKzE0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — Israel’s political class was locked in frenzied horse trading on Monday, as opposition politicians struggled to strike a coalition deal to oust Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, who in turn was waging a last-ditch effort to cling to power. The bartering put a spotlight on the fragmentation of the Israeli political system, in which the short-term fate of the Israeli state — nearly paralyzed after four elections in two years,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rapper DaBaby allegedly involved in Miami shooting...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/06/01/rapper-dababy-allegedly-involved-in-miami-beach-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chart titan is allegedly being quizzed by Miami Beach Police Department after he and his entourage were involved in the shooting late on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's only mountain parrot 'moved to higher altitudes to avoid humans'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/06/01/worlds-only-mountain-parrot-moved-to-higher-altitudes-to-avoid-humans-14688980/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mischievous keas' alpine habitat is threatened by climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State to gather diplomats' health details in response to Havana syndrome...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/01/state-diplomat-health-havana-syndrome-491485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department has faced criticism for not taking the injuries seriously enough.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
