<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>L.A.'s most extravagant mansion sells for less than half list price...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/l-most-extravagant-mansion-sells-003823146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of construction, a foreclosure and a bankruptcy, the Bel-Air mega-mansion known as The One has sold at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mail carrier allegedly beat turkey to death. Was it self-defense?</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/a-california-mail-carrier-allegedly-beat-a-turkey-to-death-was-it-self-defense/article_e0ac3ca7-1dff-5695-875d-43a7604e03b2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — California wildlife authorities and the U.S. Postal Service are investigating reports that a mail carrier beat a wild turkey to death in Sacramento County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe awakens to Russian threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetelegraph.com/news/article/Europe-awakens-to-the-Russian-threat-16976696.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetelegraph.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Russian money, energy and military strength held Europe in thrall. But as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Glass Of Wine WIth Dinner Slashes Diabetes Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/wine-with-dinner-diabetes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Tulane University report that drinking wine with dinner could actually help stave off diabetes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rheumatoid arthritis drug could be lifesaver for severely ill COVID patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-rheumatoid-arthritis-drug-reduces-death-coronavirus-severe-illness-20220304-sa3fyxptfnef7oj6bpsgrkueem-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anti-inflammatory drug normally used for rheumatoid arthritis could turn out to be a lifesaver for people hospitalized with COVID, a large clinical trial indicates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills store admits to using safe deposit boxes to launder drug money...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/beverly-hills-store-pleads-guilty-to-laundering-drug-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The store's owners admitted to recruiting drug traffickers as customers and subsequently running their money through the business, a.k.a. "cleaning" the currency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>275 grave stones vandalized at TX cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/about-275-grave-stones-vandalized-at-texas-cemetery/article_105cb9cf-739e-5312-bf2b-cf7f21f14fd1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 275 grave stones at the century-old Waxahachie City Cemetery — just south of Dallas — were vandalized earlier this week, including the gravesite of one of the city’s first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham blowback after calling for Putin assassination...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Lindsey-Graham-hit-with-bipartisan-blowback-after-16976764.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., was sharply criticized by fellow lawmakers on both sides of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The agent and the comic: Putin, Zelensky in fight for Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-the-agent-and-the-comic-putin-zelensky-in-fight-for-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One is a former comic actor who became president in 2019 as a political novice. The other a one-time KGB agent now in power for over two decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians pack trains into Finland...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220304-russians-pack-trains-into-finland-as-sanctions-bite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's one of the few remaining routes from Russia to the EU: trains to Finland are packed with Russians fearful that now is their last chance to escape the impact of Western sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do You Hide 500-Foot Yacht?</title>
      <link>https://techilive.in/where-do-you-hide-a-500-foot-yacht-asking-for-an-oligarch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techilive.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s one thing to stuff cash under your mattress or move millions into an offshore bank account. Hiding a mega-yacht from multiple governments and a global mob of private citizens is a bit more tricky. To intensify sanctions on Russia and further throttle the finances of the Kremlin’s uber-wealthy allies, the Biden administration this week […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee getting closer to ex-president...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2022/03/03/jan-6-committee-work-shifts-into-new-gear-getting-closer-to-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jan. 6 select committee has stated it has a “good-faith belief” that former President Donald Trump may have committed criminal acts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: $807 million in oligarch yachts seized...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4817890/vladimir-putins-cronies-have-superyachts-seized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN billionaire Alisher Usmanov was slapped on Britain’s sanctions list last night as Vladimir Putin’s cronies had their beloved superyachts seized. Usmanov, who has been bankrolling Everton FC…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage met by revulsion -- first Jan. 6 trial shows family, nation torn by The Don...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Rage-met-by-revulsion-first-Jan-6-trial-shows-16976509.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A father's runaway political rage and his son's revulsion at lawlessness enthralled a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peer pressure ending mask usage in schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Peer-pressure-is-ending-mask-usage-in-schools-16976598.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chelsea Ellingson hopes that her children keep masks in their backpacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS rushes to hire 10,000 workers but giant backlog to persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/IRS-rushes-to-hire-10-000-workers-but-giant-16976309.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Internal Revenue Service plans to hire 10,000 employees in a push to cut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine flagship sunk to avoid capture by Russian troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.pravda.com.ua/eng/news/2022/03/4/7328077/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravda.com.ua&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Hetman Sahaidachny flagship of the Ukrainian Navy has been sunk to prevent the Russian occupying forces from using it, including for sabotage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New evidence shows Trump was told many times there was no voter fraud -- but kept saying it anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/New-evidence-shows-Trump-was-told-many-times-16975783.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A data expert for former President Donald Trump's campaign told him bluntly not long...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EUROPE AT RISK'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10575179/Russian-troops-fire-Ukrainian-civilians-protecting-Europes-largest-nuclear-plant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson led a chorus of condemnation this morning over Russia's attack on the Zaporizhzhia nuclear plant in southern Ukraine overnight, which sparked a fire the burned for several hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOX OFFICE: 'BATMAN' SET FOR $100+ MILLION OPENING...</title>
      <link>https://www.boxofficemojo.com/article/ed3748725764/?ref_=bo_ne_nl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Humans Will Live In Metaverse Soon', Claims Zuckerberg. What About Reality?</title>
      <link>https://in.mashable.com/tech/28254/humans-will-live-in-metaverse-soon-claims-mark-zuckerberg-what-about-reality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta intends to spend the next five to ten years creating an immersive virtual environment that includes fragrance, touch, and sound to allow users to lose themselves in virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE JUNK SET TO SMASH MOON...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/spacex-science-business-china-moon-7044a26d9b4b43dc44e961c250186f26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — The moon is about to get walloped by 3 tons of space junk, a punch that will carve out a crater that could fit several semitractor-trailers. The leftover rocket will smash into the far side of the moon at 5,800 mph (9,300 kph) on Friday, away from telescopes’ prying eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS IT WILL BLOW</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/russian-forces-conduct-attack-at-massive-nuclear-power-plant-in-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire has broken out at a major Ukrainian nuclear power plant under attack from Russian forces near Kyiv, according to Ukrainian officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mine warfare on Kyiv's eastern front...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220303-mine-warfare-on-kyiv-s-eastern-front</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian army battalion commander is not sure who laid the mines scattered across fields on Kyiv's eastern front that his men hit while seeking intelligence on Russian forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP RUSSIAN GENERAL KILLED</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10573429/Top-Russian-general-killed-Ukrainian-sniper-Kyiv-claims-9-000-Putins-troops-died.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major General Andrey Sukhovetsky, who was the deputy commander of the 41st Combined Arms Army of Russia's Central Military District, was killed yesterday as Ukraine's defences held firm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich kids of Russia rebel: Oligarchs' children slam Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10573267/The-rebellion-rich-kids-Russia-against-war-Ukraine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children of rich Russian oligarchs and the country's elite are urging peace in the Ukraine and Vladimir Putin to stop the bloodshed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Davidson joining Bezos on BLUE ORIGIN space flight...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/03/03/pete-davidson-flying-to-space-with-jeff-bezos-sources-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two will reportedly fly out of this world later this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine Navy's Flagship Appears To Have Been Scuttled...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/44563/the-ukrainian-navys-flagship-appears-to-have-been-scuttled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pride of the Ukrainian Navy's fleet, the frigate Hetman Sahaidachny, is now partially sunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow's Looming Economic Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-e2-80-99s-looming-economic-collapse/ar-AAUvozL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIN:   Americans warned to budget for $5-A-GALLON gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10573631/Americans-warned-budget-5-gallon-gas-prices-average-rises-3-61-1-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans can expect to see gas prices to rise to $5 a gallon in the coming weeks, as the cost of oil continues to rise in the days following Russia's invasion of Ukraine, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians Announce US-Iran Deal as Tanks Roll Across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/russians-announce-us-iran-deal-as-tanks-roll-across-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A senior Russian official announced on Thursday that a new nuclear deal with Iran will be announced within 24 to 48 hours, signaling the Biden administration’s continued reliance on and cooperation with Moscow even as it wages a full-scale war in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX internet could be 'giant target' for users...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-03-22/h_71da5789e3224ffd9140f964858b028f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has ramped up assaults on key Ukrainian cities, as President Zelensky pleads for more international assistance and a second round of talks between Ukraine and Russia are set to take place. Follow here for live news updates from on the ground in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT America ceases productions, lays off staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/03/media/rt-america-layoffs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The production company behind the American version of the Russian state-funded network RT laid off most of its staff on Thursday, according to a memo obtained by CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts: Central U.S. needs to be ready for next earthquake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-environment-and-nature-st-louis-missouri-earthquakes-3470a1e0f92800f50a188296495b3a59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS (AP) — Experts have warned for decades that a large swath of the central U.S. is at high risk for a devastating earthquake. They know that overcoming complacency is among their biggest hurdles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron declares re-election bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/mar/03/emmanuel-macron-expected-to-announce-he-is-standing-for-re-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President will stand again in April and vows to ‘explain our project with clarity and commitment’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going According to Plan'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-03-22/h_e27835f2bd93d456654860007dfae0b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel Bunkers, Iodine Pills, Canned Food: Fear of Nuke Apocalypse Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dgqpd/iodine-pills-nuclear-apocalypse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prepper community has grown quickly through the strife of the last few years, and Russia’s invasion of Ukraine has only accelerated that trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joy Behar Falls On 'VIEW' Set...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/after-joy-behar-falls-on-the-view-set-her-co-hosts-empathize-we-hate-these-chairs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the panelists walked out onto the set, viewers can see the audience standing and applauding when suddenly the footage shows Behar falling onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspends all protocols...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-nfl-business-sports-health-62d42bf438a0dc394cfae434e6540dbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has suspended all aspects of its COVID-19 protocols, citing recent trends showing that the spread of the coronavirus is declining. In an agreement with the players' association, the league sent a memo to the 32 teams Thursday in which it mentioned “encouraging trends regarding the prevalence and severity of COVID-19, the evolving guidance from the CDC, changes to state law and the counsel of our respective experts” as reasons for the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT bans all links to Russia state-sponsored RT, SPUTNIK...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2022/3/3/22960223/reddit-ukraine-russia-ban-links-entire-site</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most concrete deplatforming moves yet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Official Goes Full Culture War: West Trying to 'Cancel' Us...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/russian-official-goes-full-culture-war-west-is-trying-to-cancel-us-as-they-now-say-in-tolerant-liberal-fascist-circles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Spy Chief Sergei Naryshkin claimed his country is a victim of cancel culture as he blasted the condemnation for Russia invading Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top NFL QB prospect logs historically small hand measurement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/2022-nfl-scouting-combine-pittsburgh-qb-kenny-pickett-logs-historically-small-hand-measurement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential first-round pick logged 8.5-inch hand measurements at the combine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crucial energy hub besieged...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-united-nations-general-assembly-volodymyr-zelenskyy-kyiv-moscow-a3092d8e476949ed7c55607a645a9154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian forces battled for control of a crucial energy-producing city in Ukraine's south on Thursday and gained ground in their bid to cut off the country from the sea, as Ukrainian leaders called on citizens to rise up and wage guerrilla war against the invaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BARR:  'I Told Him All This Stuff Was Bullsh*t'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nightly-news/video/former-ag-barr-on-the-moment-trump-accepted-his-resignation-134509637544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with Lester Holt, former Attorney General Bill Barr describes the moment former President Trump accepted his resignation after Barr refused to say there were irregularities during the 2020 election. Watch much more tonight on NBC Nightly News at 6:30 pm ET / 5:30 pm CT (check local listings).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Lightfoot Bragged 'I Have Biggest D*ck in Chicago'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-mayor-lori-lightfoot-blocked-columbus-statue-deal-berated-lawyers-with-obscene-remarks-lawsuit-claims/ar-AAUzbDZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individuality will dissolve into mindless conformity...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/03/the-metaverse-will-steal-your-identity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Individuality will dissolve into mindless conformity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children committing carjackings for social media fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/carjackings-in-cities-like-nyc-jump-over-200-often-with-kids-behind-the-wheel-officials-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTURBING CRIME TREND: Carjackings have soared by 286% in New York City from 2019 to 2021. Many suspects are kids.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN SATELLITES HACKED</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4812686/russia-space-hack-satellites-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has warned that hacking its satellites is an act of war after the country’s space agency was reportedly hit by a cyberattack. Yesterday hacker group Anonymous claimed it had shutdown R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN:  I'M TAKING IT ALL!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putin-says-violence-will-26378723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian President made his comments to Emmanuel Macron, his French counterpart, during a phone call on Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud sex complaints rise in NYC!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/loud-sex-noises-leave-new-yorkers-complaining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people have called 311 in the past year to complain about people having loud sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fights to capture Europe's biggest nuclear power plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russian-army-fighting-take-26379529</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a breaking news story and is constantly being updated as our reporters work to source the latest information, reaction, pictures and video - refresh for the latest news</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How they  took over London...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/03/why-we-need-a-new-domesday-book/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's time for London to take back control</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition tech could turn America into Russia...</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/creeping-authoritarianism-facial-recognition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same facial recognition technology that China and Russia use to keep their people in line has come to America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR WEEK 2</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/no-letup-russian-strikes-putin-123659300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Russian forces fired missiles at Kyiv and bombarded cities across Ukraine, as President Vladimir Putin pushed on with his invasion in disregard of a United Nations vote to immediately halt the fighting.Most Read from BloombergRussia’s Rating Cut to Junk; Talks on Tap: Ukraine UpdateChina Holds Talks With Ukraine, Further Edging Away From RussiaBillionaire Usmanov’s Superyacht Said to Be SeizedRussian Oligarchs’ Yachts Head for Maldives as Sanctions LeviedResignation Sets In as Rus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Inside the Palace With MBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2022/04/mohammed-bin-salman-saudi-arabia-palace-interview/622822/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asked about the murder of Jamal Khashoggi, Mohammed bin Salman said, “If that’s the way we did things, Khashoggi would not even be among the top 1,000 people on the list.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU 'picking up signs Putin may bring in martial law'...</title>
      <link>https://www.gbnews.uk/news/eu-picking-up-signs-russia-may-bring-in-martial-law/239086</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gbnews.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are increasing fears on what Vladimir Putin might resort to as Russia becomes more isolated under an avalanche of Western sanctions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian oligarchs' yachts seized in Europe, others harboring in Maldives...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-maldives/russian-oligarchs-yachts-seized-in-europe-others-harbouring-in-maldives-idUSKCN2L01MJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France and Germany have seized two superyachts owned by Russian oligarchs, according to French authorities and Forbes magazine, taking concrete steps to hit Russia's super-rich under sweeping sanctions imposed on Moscow over its invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Could happen tomorrow': Experts know disaster upon disaster looms for West Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/could-happen-tomorrow-experts-know-230027986.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West Coast could at any moment face disasters that could kill thousands of people and forever change the lives of millions more, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9,000 SOLDIERS KILLED?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17832248/russian-army-ukraine-putin-coffins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA is facing staggering losses in Ukraine – with Kyiv claiming 9,000 of Vladimir Putin’s soldiers have been killed already in the invasion. Shocking photos are continuing to emerge …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'begins sea scanning' surrounding Taiwan amid growing fears of invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/china-begins-sea-scanning-surrounding-26374209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A think tank has alleged that China is using survey ships to stake claims in the South China Sea, and there are fears this could be linked to a potential invasion of Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: OTC Pain Relievers Weaken Immune System...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pain-relievers-weaken-immune-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pain relief medications like acetaminophen, ibuprofen, aspirin show a tendency to "reduce desirable immune responses when taken for vaccination."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to replace iPhones with contact lenses?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/apple-replace-iphone-magic-metaverse-26367019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The end of smartphones might not be that far away as Apple are reportedly trying to move computers into our eyeballs for a truly hands-free experience - just like something out of Black Mirror</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflammatory Markers Indicate Dementia Decades Before Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/03/02/inflammatory-markers-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests that inflammatory markers, part of the body’s defense strategy against the disease, are noticeable ten to twenty years in advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODESA BRACES</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/odesa-in-russia-s-sights-amid-faster-progress-in-ukraine-s-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russiaâ€™s invasion is gaining pace in the countryâ€™s open and hard-to-defend coastal plains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrines, memorials with powerful symbolic value at risk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-kyiv-europe-caves-0373c67a7c70f8585859c5c6ae4c6766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyiv, bracing for a potentially catastrophic Russian attack, is the spiritual heart of Ukraine. Among the sites at risk in the Ukrainian capital are the nation's most sacred Orthodox shrines, dating back nearly 1,000 years to the dawn of Christianity in the region.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
