<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UK Health Minister quits after steamy affair with aide exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15403797/matt-hancock-resigns-affair-aide-explosive-pics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATT Hancock has tonight resigned after humiliating footage of his clinch with a senior aide in his office was published by The Sun. The health secretary quit amid mounting pressure from colleagues…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I've Given Everything I Have'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/quentin-tarantino-bill-maher-confirms-retirement-plans-1235005950/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quentin Tarantino knows that once you’ve reached the top, the only option is to go down. While promoting his “Once Upon a Time in Hollywood” novel on “Real Time With Bill Ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National security risks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/560382-the-national-security-risks-of-the-us-drought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While these impacts on military infrastructure are concerning, they are concrete and measurable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR HORROR...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3162139/albuquerque-balloon-crash-four-dead-hit-power-line/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT least four people have been declared dead following a disastrous hot air balloon crash in Albuquerque. The Albuquerque Police Department announced the death count as they responded to the disast…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth about Biggie, Tupac killings could finally come out in new doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3161536/notorious-big-tupac-killings-truth-new-doc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BOMBSHELL new documentary could finally reveal the truth behind the slayings of rappers Tupac Shakur and The Notorious BIG. Tupac was gunned down on the Las Vegas strip in September 1996 while hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR MOON: DAWN OF LUNAR WARFARE...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/military-space-force-moon-warfare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"As commerce extends to the moon and beyond, it is vital we understand and solve those unique challenges so that we can provide space domain awareness and security."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rattlesnakes everywhere: Consequences of drought...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rattlesnakes-everywhere-odd-consequences-california-100001090.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snakes, bears and other animals seeking refuge from the drying landscape are increasingly finding their way into urban environments Wildlife vets have reported big changes in the numbers of abandoned babies or injured animals brought into their centers and sightings – especially of bears. Photograph: Noah Berger/EPA Len Ramirez stalked through the dried landscape, scanning the ground ahead searching for movement. Called out to an estate in Napa Valley, the owner of Ramirez Rattlesnake Removal co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 die in hot air balloon crash in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nm-state-wire-new-mexico-7b14c680f47209bc6ebf84e81d190596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — Four people died and one person was in critical condition after a hot air balloon they were riding in hit power lines in New Mexico's largest city, police said Saturday. The crash happened around 7 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key witness in Assange case admits to lies in indictment...</title>
      <link>https://stundin.is/grein/13627/key-witness-in-assange-case-admits-to-lies-in-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stundin.is&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major witness in the United States’ Department of Justice case against Julian Assange has admitted to fabricating key accusations in the indictment against the Wikileaks founder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRE HAMPERS RESCUE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/miami-building-collapses-4e872d03fc3210b49c60e6a275f2e860</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. (AP) — A “very deep fire” hampered rescue efforts Saturday at the collapsed oceanfront condominium tower near Miami where authorities are racing to recover any survivors beneath a mountain of rubble, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de France chaos after massive crash caused by fan!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3162163/tour-de-france-chaos-as-massive-crash-caused-by-a-fan-wipes-out-half-of-the-peloton/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE TOUR DE FRANCE was thrown into chaos after a fan caused a massive crash that wiped out half of the peloton. Just minutes after Christian Prudhomme had set the 108th edition of the annual bike r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J agrees to stop selling opioids nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/26/jj-agrees-to-stop-selling-opioids-in-230-million-settlement-with-new-york.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp; Johnson has agreed to halt sales of opioids nationwide in a $230 million settlement with New York state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight and Flight: TSA to Resume Self-Defense Classes for Airline Crews...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/26/fight-and-flight-t-s-a-to-resume-self-defense-classes-for-airline-crews/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration will once again offer self-defense classes to flight attendants and pilots as the airline industry deals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel shootout leaves 18 dead in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/drug-gang-shootout-leaves-18-dead-in-mexico-government-2472795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shootout among suspected rival drug cartel gunmen left 18 people dead Friday in Mexico, a government official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands climb Indonesian volcano for ritual sacrifice...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210626-thousands-climb-indonesian-volcano-for-ritual-sacrifice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands climb Indonesian volcano for ritual sacrifice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One in Five Young Adults Neither Working Nor Studying...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/one-in-five-young-adults-is-neither-working-nor-studying-in-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in Five Young Adults Is Neither Working Nor Studying in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pornification of NETFLIX Continues...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/pornification-netflix-continues-sex-life-031503518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NETFLIXThis is a preview of our pop culture newsletter The Daily Beast’s Obsessed, written by senior entertainment reporter Kevin Fallon. To receive the full newsletter in your inbox each week, sign up for it here.This week:We’ve all been so shitty to Britney Spears.Netflix is back with more porn!Everything that pissed me off this week.Christine Baranski delivers the song of the summer.The only pride message that matters.Time to Watch Porn on Netflix AgainThere was a time last summer, pretty muc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooling centers open...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210625183950-276l4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WEATHER/HEATWAVE (PIX):Cooling centers open in U.S. Pacific Northwest ahead of 'life-threatening heat'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online 'flicker test' makes hallucinate in minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3157006/optical-illusion-hallucination-test-ganzflicker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN OPTICAL illusion test is said to reveal whether your mental images are more vivid than others. It’s called the “Ganzflicker” and it’s an intense red and black flicke…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haters Everywhere in Stock Market After Big First Half...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/haters-everywhere-stock-market-p-201403623.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- People were already worried about equities six months ago. Now, after the S&amp;P 500 Index defied everything from nosebleed valuations to inflation to post one of the best first halves ever, they’re downright paranoid.Wall Street strategists, never ones to restrain their enthusiasm when it’s warranted, warn that the gains have played out. Short sellers are circling, with wagers against the largest equity exchange-traded fund rising to the highest level this year. Star investors like</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jumps from moving plane at LAX...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ca-state-wire-los-angeles-business-7f6471d6c57065c6ebd2d1b77a430743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A passenger was taken to the hospital Friday night after jumping out of a moving plane at Los Angeles International Airport, authorities said. United Express flight 5365, operated by SkyWest, was pulling away from a gate shortly after 7 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man survives 300 days with virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-believed-to-have-longest-coronavirus-infection-had-virus-for-300-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man in England is believed to have had COVID-19 for about 300 days, the longest recorded so far, according to medical papers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare Earthquake Shakes Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/06/25/maryland-earthquake-reported-near-woodlawn-tremors-felt-for-miles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 2.6 magnitude earthquake was reported in Maryland Friday afternoon, according to the USGS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETURN OF THE MAGA RALLY...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article252339798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump’s megaphone, once the loudest in politics, will be put to the test in the coming weeks as he prepares to hold his first rallies since leaving office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes limits claims from some wrongly labeled as terrorists by credit agencies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/supreme-court-limits-claims-wrongly-160521629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court's decision overturns judgment against TransUnion. In a departure for Clarence Thomas, he joins the court's liberal justices in dissent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom, legislative leaders agree to extend California eviction protections, pay 100% of back rent...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-legislative-leaders-agree-extend-170014945.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protections for tenants who pay at least 25% of their rent expire Wednesday, but the Legislature will likely OK an extension as early as Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive head in Chinese well forces scientists to rethink evolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/25/massive-human-head-in-chinese-well-forces-scientists-to-rethink-evolution</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Dragon man’ skull reveals new branch of family tree more closely related to modern humans than Neanderthals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns Europe 'on thin ice' as concerns about covid variant grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/covid-19-updates-merkel-warns-europe-is-on-thin-ice-as-concerns-about-delta-variant-grow/ar-AALq7zr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top European health agency predicted that the delta variant would be responsible for 90 percent of infections in much of Europe by the end of summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 DEAD, 159  MISSING</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/miami-beach/article252353208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grim task of recovering the bodies of victims at the site of the collapse of the Champlain Towers South condo in Surfside began overnight and continued into a somber Friday in an unfolding tragedy that is feared to be the worst building failure in Florida history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH CONTINUES FOR SURVIVORS</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Rescue-crews-scour-unstable-rubble-in-search-of-16275470.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURFSIDE, Fla. - The search for survivors in the ruins of a collapsed, 12-story...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala visits southern border, assailed by right and left...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Harris-visits-southern-border-assailed-by-right-16275435.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Texas - Vice President Kamala Harris on Friday made her first visit to America's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says country's fate in its own hands...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/As-the-last-American-forces-prepare-to-leave-16275150.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Joe Biden pledged Friday that the United States will remain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN customer arrested for salsa and battery...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/man-charged-salsa-and-battery-713205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 25--In an unprovoked attack, a 7-Eleven customer was injured when a fellow patron threw a glass jar of Tostitos salsa at him with such force that the container broke on the victim’s back, Florid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Success Driven by Hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquiremore.com/p/social-media-success-is-driven-by</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquiremore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expressing animosity towards outgroups drives engagement, new research finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest Tax Increase in San Fran History Now Funding $60,000 Tents for Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/06/25/critics-warned-the-largest-tax-increase-in-san-francisco-history-would-be-ill-spent-its-now-funding-60000-tents-for-the-homeless/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco politicians are raising eyebrows at the high costs of an emergency program that provides secure camping sites to the city's homeless.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
