<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Boris says 'Not too late' to save Brexit in resignation speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6807864/boris-johnson-set-to-make-devastating-resignation-speech-ripping-up-theresa-mays-brexit-plans-to-shreds-in-front-of-mps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson claimed it is “not too late to save Brexit” as he attacked Theresa May’s “miserable” Chequers plan in a devastating resignation speech this afternoon. He blasted the Prime Minis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to tell if you're talking to a bot...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/611655/how-to-tell-if-youre-talking-to-a-bot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five best ways to detect fake social-media accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookmaker increases chances of impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/odds-donald-trump-impeached-shot-criticised-us-intelligence-agencies-115658849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump seemed to accept Vladimir Putin’s insistence that Moscow's hands were clean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSTED:  Gun store confronts Sacha Baron Cohen after he comes to business in disguise...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/exclusive-riverside-gun-store-confronts-sacha-baron-cohen-after-he-comes-to-business-in-disguise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Riverside gun store owner has harsh words for Sacha Baron Cohen after he says he caught the actor showing up to his business in disguise and under false pretense, and it was all caught on surveillance video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Men with bat leap from Range Rover in brazen NYC sidewalk attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Bat-Attack-New-York-City-488482841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops are looking for two suspects in connection with a brazen bat attack on a Bronx sidewalk last month that was captured on disturbing surveillance video.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RASMUSSEN SLIPS TO 44%... </title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jul18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU SLAPS GOOG WITH $5B FINE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/10/eu-hits-alphabet-google-with-android-antitrust-fine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Union just hit Google with a record antitrust fine for abusing the dominance of its Android mobile operating system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodman Wants to Bring Kanye to Meet Kim...</title>
      <link>https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/dennis-rodman-wants-to-bring-kanye-west-with-him-to-north-korea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dennis Rodman revealed his plans to invite Kanye West with him to North Korea and opened up about his friendship with Kim Jong Un exclusively to Us Weekly — details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 8 Reasons Hollywood Is Stressed Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/8-reasons-hollywood-is-stressed-right-now-1127869/item/8-reasons-hollywood-stresses-murdoch-is-selling-something-be-wrong-1127871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe Rupert put Fox on the auction block because its stock was stagnant for the past three years. Or maybe he doesn't have faith in sons Lachlan or James and saw what happened to Sumner Redstone's company without a solid succession plan. Or maybe — just maybe — the savvy 87-year-old sees a Hollywood apocalypse on the horizon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA STAR TAKES SHOT AT NEW GAME...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/features/stephen-curry-hollywood-producing-unanimous-media-1202875412/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are fleeting moments when even the sport that made Stephen Curry famous is far from the front of his mind. Take one late June morning in a Mediterranean mansion in Walnut Creek, Calif., he ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US pastor denied release in latest trial hearing in Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/trial-us-pastor-resumes-turkey-56658155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Turkish court on Wednesday again denied a request for the release from custody of an American pastor based in Turkey who is on trial on charges of aiding terror groups and engaging espionage. Andrew Craig Brunson, a 50-year-old evangelical pastor from Black Mountain, North Carolina, was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby Boomers Get 'More Selective' About Friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/baby-boomers-get-more-selective-about-friends-1531918772</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today’s 55-to-64-year-olds are less socially engaged than people the same age 20 years ago. Researchers want to know why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men promised anonymous sex. They wound up on porn site instead...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/homestead/article213869259.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents arrested a Homestead man they say ran a website that featured videos of blindfolded men duped into sex acts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND SLAMS BRENNAN: 'MOST BIASED, BIGOTED DIRECTOR OF CIA' EVER...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-rand-paul-slams-john-brennan-most-biased-bigoted-director-ci</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘John Brennan started out his adulthood by voting for the communist party presidential candidate’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON says Prime Day was biggest shopping event EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/17/amazon-announces-2018-prime-day-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi suffers face spasm saying 'intelligence', calls colleague by wrong name...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/nancy-pelosi-suffers-face-spasm-saying-intelligence-calls-colleague-by-wrong-name/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Intelligence” triggers Nancy Pelosi. When the House Minority Leader attempted to say the word today, she suffered a face spasm — just one of several during today’s press conference with Intelligence Committee Democrats. ﻿ While introducing her colleagues, Pelosi said, “I’m very honored to stand, uh, before members of the House Intelligence Committee,” suffering a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ CALLS FOR OCCUPATION OF AIRPORTS, ICE OFFICES...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/socialist-ocasio-cortez-calls-for-occupation-of-airports-ice-offices/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We have to mobilize,’ she says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow warns USA 'hunting for more spies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/717253/russia-spy-washington-maria-butina-gun-activist-vladimir-putin-donald-trump-meddling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary's Orban set for controversial visit to Israel...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180718-hungarys-orban-set-controversial-visit-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android Antitrust Decision Shakes Mobile Industry, GOOGLE Business Model...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/eu-decision-shakes-mobile-industry-google-business-model-1531913525</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the first Android phone went on sale a decade ago, Google made a bet: Its free operating system would hook smartphone makers. Now that business model may need an upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KUDLOW: Economic growth could top 4% for 'quarter or two'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/18/trump-advisor-kudlow-says-economic-growth-could-top-4percent-for-a-quarter-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chief economic advisor to President Trump spoke at CNBC's Delivering Alpha conference in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warship carrying $130 BILLION worth of GOLD found off SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/990585/Dmitrii-Donskoi-Russian-warship-South-Korea-gold</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A RUSSIAN warship called Dmitrii Donskoi carrying gold worth £100 billion has been discovered off the coast of South Korea and is believed to have sunk in a naval battle 113 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of leading AI researchers sign pledge against killer robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/18/thousands-of-scientists-pledge-not-to-help-build-killer-ai-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Co-founder of Google DeepMind and CEO of SpaceX amongst the 2,400 signatories of pledge to block lethal autonomous weapons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials want to retire by 61, but most have nothing saved...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/17/ideal-retirement-age-for-millennials.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s just not the reality for most people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earlier dinner may lower risk of cancers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/17/health/eat-earlier-lower-cancer-risk-study/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People who eat dinner before 9 p.m. or at least two hours before going to sleep have a 20% lower risk of breast and prostate cancer, researchers found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Calls Cops After Hard Foul In Pickup Basketball Game...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/07/17/virginia-man-called-cops-after-hard-foul-in-pickup-basketball-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A friendly game of basketball at a local gym took a turn for the worse when one of the participants called the police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion film blocked from filming at iconic NYC spots...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/07/17/nick-loebs-anti-abortion-film-blocked-from-filming-at-iconic-nyc-spots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When reached for comment, Loeb told us the project received special permission from St. Patrick’s to shoot inside, and had permits to film on the street outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBUS unveils pioneering solar-powered drone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/airbus-unveils-pioneering-solar-powered-drone-113827524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European air giant Airbus on Wednesday unveiled a solar-powered drone called Zephyr that will fly at a high altitude and fulfil the same functions as a satellite. The project was presented at Britain's Farnborough airshow, where Airbus revealed that the Zephyr S took off on July 11 for its maiden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom or bust as homers, strikeouts dominate diamond...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxsports.com/mlb/story/boom-or-bust-as-homers-strikeouts-dominate-diamond-071818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) Boom or bust. This is what baseball has become - and that has owners worried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey urges voters to support Dems in fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/18/trump-ex-fbi-chief-james-comey-urges-voters-to-support-democrats.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI director and long-time Republican supporter James Comey is urging American voters to support Democrats in the upcoming midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists develop 'world first' melanoma blood test...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2018-07-australia-scientists-world-melanoma-blood.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian researchers said Wednesday they have developed a blood test for melanoma in its early stages, calling it a "world first" breakthrough that could save many lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens increasingly prefer family time to sex?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/teenage-sex-family-time-teen-pregnancy-online-relationships-social-media-a8452006.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Survey finds 16 to 18-year-olds also drinking less and focusing more on education</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: CONSERVATIVES BELIEVE THEIR LIVES MORE MEANINGFUL THAN LIBERALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/conservatives-liberals-meaningful-lives-politics-psychology-usc-study-a8452446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previous research suggests those with right-leaning political beliefs boast greater life satisfaction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How animals lie, cheat, kidnap, go to war to get their wicked way...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/science/how-animals-lie-cheat-kidnap-12936060</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new TV programme shows that animals' mating strategies are ingenious - and can also be devious and violent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk apologizes for calling Thai cave rescue diver 'pedo guy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/18/elon-musk-apologizes-thai-cave-rescue-diver/794873002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk lashed out after Vern Unsworth called a submarine he sent to assist in the rescue "a PR stunt."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Maria Butina gained access to elite conservative circles...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/she-was-like-a-novelty-how-alleged-russian-agent-maria-butina-gained-access-to-elite-conservative-circles/2018/07/17/1bb62bbc-89d2-11e8-a345-a1bf7847b375_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By August 2016, the FBI was monitoring the young political-science student as part of an effort to track what she was doing in the United States, according to officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 40% OF PEOPLE HAVE FIRST MEMORIES THAT ARE MADE UP...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/world/40-of-people-have-first-memories-that-are-made-up-study-finds-855965.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many first memories are fictional patchworks of early experience, photos and information from family conversations, claim researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Volcano: 100-FOOT fissure sparks park closure...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/990251/yellowstone-volcano-latest-yellowstone-super-volcano-grand-teton-national-park-fissure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 100-foot fissure has opened up in the Grand Teton National Park – not far from the potentially catastrophic Yellowstone volcano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shame of 'cannibal' pigs farm...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/717141/cannibal-pig-farm-UK-supplies-tesco-animal-rights-footage </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Pimple Popper now has own reality show... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5191c1cd09184e0daeed05c176e6bd01 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The online video star named Dr. Pimple Popper, who films herself squeezing pus from acne, is a different kind of voyeur when she's off the clock.        Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems want interpreter to testify before Congress...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/17/jeanne-shaheen-joe-kennedy-want-trump-interpreter-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two Congressional Democrats want President Trump’s interpreter to testify about his meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin. So curious are Democrats to learn what was said in Monday’s private meeting between Mr. Trump and Mr. Putin — there were no other officials in the room; only each man’s translator — that Sen. Jeanne Shaheen and Rep. Joe Kennedy III have each made the unusual request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Liquidates US Treasury Holdings...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-07-17/russia-liquidates-its-us-treasury-holdings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Trespassed in NATO Airspace on Way to Summit... </title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/estonia-says-putin-s-plane-trespassed/17704746/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW — Even before his plane touched down in Finland for a summit meeting with President Donald Trump, President Vladimir Putin of Russia, who was widely seen as coming out ahead at the meeting, had notched a victory in the air, Estonian authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOO RICH?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/07/jeff-bezoss-massive-wealth-becoming-a-problem </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage builds over MGM decision to sue victims of Vegas massacre...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2018/07/17/mgm-resorts-sues-victims-las-vegas-massacre-denies-liability/791511002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit filed by MGM Resorts International, owner of the Las Vegas hotel from which Stephen Paddock fatally shot 58 people and wounded hundreds more, is drawing outrage from survivors of the deadliest mass shooting in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DR. BUMBUM:  Celeb cosmetic surgeon vanishes after patient dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6804558/plastic-surgeon-dr-bumbum-disappear-woman-dead-brazilian-bum-lift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CELEBRITY plastic surgeon Dr BumBum has reportedly gone on the run in Brazil after a woman died hours after receiving injections to enlarge her bottom. HSBC bank manager Lilian Calixto, 46, travell…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Gallery Under Fire For ISIS-Style Trump 'Beheading'...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/fck-trump-art-gallery-under-fire-for-isis-style-trump-beheading/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest depiction of 'tolerant' left's violent fantasies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man confesses to using 675 people for sacrifice... </title>
      <link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/Man-confesses-to-using-675-people-for-sacrifice-reveals-secrets-of-fake-pastors-669559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ghanaweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YEN.com.gh has sighted a video of a young man telling a horrible...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bookmaker increases chances of impeachment...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/397431-bookmaker-increases-odds-of-trump-being-impeached-after-trump-putin-summit </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chances that President Trump will be impeached are rising, according to one Irish bookmaker, one day after Trump refused to denounce Russian meddling in the 2016 election following a meeting with Russian President Vladimir</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would It or Wouldn't It Be? </title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/17/trump-s-helsinki-would-wouldn-t-doesn-t-go-far-enough</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump's Helsinki Walk-Back Doesn't Go Far Enough</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT: 'NO TIME LIMIT' TO DENUCLEARIZE NKOREA...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-now-says-no-time-limit-denuclearize-nkorea-221458102.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Tuesday there is no hurry to denuclearize North Korea under his accord with Kim Jong Un -- a shift in tone from when the US leader said the process would start very soon. "Discussions are ongoing and they're going very, very well," Trump told reporters. Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago could soon test universal basic income program...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/07/16/chicago-universal-basic-income-ubi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With automation threatening jobs and polarizing workers, Alderman Ameya Pawar is promoting a pilot program to give $500 a month to 1,000 Chicago families.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN THE DOG HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf62711854b6482c88a611391db05a7d/Trump-backs-down-under-fire,-'clarifies'-on-Russia-meddling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Blistered by bipartisan condemnation of his embrace of a longtime U.S. enemy, President Donald Trump strained Tuesday to "clarify" his public undermining of Amer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge lifts controversial order requiring the LATIMES to alter article...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/judge-lifts-controversial-order-requiring-the-la-times-to-alter-article-about-ex-glendale-cop/ar-AAAd3mv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Asks Manafort Judge to Immunize 5 Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-17/mueller-asks-manafort-judge-to-give-immunity-to-five-witnesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Counsel Robert Mueller asked a judge to give immunity to five people who may testify at the bank-fraud trial starting next week against Paul Manafort, President Donald Trump’s former campaign chairman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPRAH GIVES BIG TO OBAMA FOUNDATION...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/obamacenter/ct-met-obama-donations-second-quarter-20180716-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donations are expected to pay for building the Obama Presidential Center in Jackson Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tumult of Europe trip smashes precedent...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tumult-trumps-europe-trip-smashes-presidential-precedent-232553388--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Plenty of U.S. presidents have created commotion in their travels abroad, but none as much as President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming Subscribers Overtake Pay-TV in UK...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/steaming-subscribers-outnumber-pay-tv-uk-ofcom-1202876000/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The level to which Netflix and Amazon are redefining the TV picture has hit home in the U.K. as new data from media regulator Ofcom show subscriptions to streaming services outnumbering those to tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot security guard patrols San Fran gas station...</title>
      <link>http://www.ktvu.com/news/robot-security-guard-patrols-san-francisco-gas-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktvu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robots are popping up at corporations, campuses, shopping malls&amp;nbsp;and airports.&amp;nbsp; But at a gas station?&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As prices slashed, Bezos sees jump in wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/amazon-slashes-prices-bezos-sees-jump-wealth-145152181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Amazon marked its "Prime Day" with price cuts across a range of products, founder and chief executive Jeff Bezos saw his net worth hit new peaks, increasing his lead over fellow billionaires. The surge in the share price for Amazon -- in which Bezos holds a stake of some 16 percent -- has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reforms loom -- but not capitalism: Cuba president...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/reforms-loom-not-capitalism-cuba-president-225236880.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban President Miguel Diaz-Canel on Tuesday said that while reforms loom in the Communist country, they would not be an embrace of capitalism. Cuba is set to adopt constitutional reforms that will recognize private property and the market economy, to update its legal system. "In Cuba, there is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Police Catch Suspected Serial Killer in TX...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Suspected-serial-killer-the-perfect-tenant-his-13082845.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa Williams said their last encounter was sometime last week. She spotted Rodriguez as he was leaving the complex with two hampers. She said he told her he was going to wash his clothes, and she lovingly warned him not to get into trouble. "Don't worry, Mama-T," she recalled Rodriguez saying. "I'm never gonna leave you."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Embassy in Jerusalem to cost  nearly 100X Trump estimate...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/us-embassy-jerusalem-cost-21-million-100-times/story?id=56645279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department awarded Maryland-based company Desbuild Limak D&amp;K a contract for $21.2 million to revamp security for the new U.S. embassy in Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens glued to phones risk  ADHD symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/teens-glued-phones-risk-modest-rise-adhd-symptoms-181947315.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could teenagers suffer symptoms of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder after engaging in excessive smartphone use? A new study out Tuesday says digital overload could be linked to a "modest" but significant rise in new ADHD behaviors, offering a warning to parents about the potential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE WILL UNHINGED:  Sad, embarrassing wreck of a man...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/this-sad-embarrassing-wreck-of-a-man/2018/07/17/d06de8ea-89e8-11e8-a345-a1bf7847b375_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Which Republicans will stand behind a president who puts Russia first?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's Next Govt Weighs Legalizing Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexicos-next-government-weigh-legalizing-drugs-232549475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President-elect Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has given his future interior minister "carte blanche" to explore the possibility of legalizing drugs in a bid to curb violent crime, she said Tuesday. Olga Sanchez Cordero, a former Supreme Court judge tapped to lead the interior ministry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON 'Dwarf-Tossing' Patent Draws Little People Ire...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/17/amazon-gets-flak-from-little-people-over-dwarf-tossing-patent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Group representing people with dwarfism says references to dwarf-tossing may lead to mockery of people with the condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: 'Climate Change' May Kill Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90203647/study-climate-change-could-kill-your-internet-in-15-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 4,000 miles of the conduit that carries the internet to much of the United States could be exposed to seawater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AD WRITER BEHIND BOYCOTT CAMPAIGN TARGETING CONSERVATIVES EXPOSED...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/16/sleeping-giants-founder-rivitz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet the California progressive behind Sleeping Giants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US trials 'Ironman' exoskeletons...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/990341/us-army-exoskeleton-ironman-russia-china-world-war-3-lockheed-martin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FUTURE wars could be fought by battalions of soldiers clad in ’Ironman-like’ exoskeletons as experts in the United States begin testing the technology to combat emerging threats posed by countries like Russia and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy as candidate touts endorsement from Jesus Christ...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2018/07/sandra_little_brown_claims_she.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brown campaign distributed flyers in the district saying she's "supported by Jesus Christ and his followers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem states sue Trump admin over tax overhaul: 'Unfairly' targets highly taxed...</title>
      <link>http://www.wsaz.com/content/news/4-blue-states-sue-Washington-over-GOP-tax-overhaul-488396511.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsaz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York, New Jersey, Connecticut and Maryland are suing the federal government over the Republican-led tax overhaul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk's latest outburst raises doubts on leadership...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/elon-musks-latest-outburst-raises-doubts-leadership-011517976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has had a series of angry social media dust-ups with Wall Street analysts, journalists, employees and others. Musk, the South African-born innovator and billionaire behind Tesla and SpaceX, found himself in hot water after insulting Vern Unsworth, a British diver who worked on the Thai soccer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuel evolution from secretive powerhouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/goldman-sachs-is-secretive-and-hide-bound-its-new-chief-wants-to-change-that-1531837427</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David M. Solomon, who was tapped to succeed Lloyd Blankfein as CEO, faces a big task in the postcrisis era as he seeks to make the firm more entrepreneurial and open. “Everything’s on the table,” the new boss has told top executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  73% of Dems Want Fresh Face In 2020...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/general_politics/july_2018/73_of_democrats_want_a_fresh_face_as_2020_nominee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bel-Air Mansions Duel to Become America's Most Expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/bel-air-homes-duel-to-become-americas-most-expensive-1531840517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A celebrity plastic surgeon is asking $180 million for his Los Angeles megamansion—$8 million less than a neighboring property</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE LIGHTS GO OUT...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/17/trump-white-house-lights-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'That must be the intelligence agencies'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Chair: FBI, DOJ Obstructing in Hope of Dem Takeover...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/national-security/intel-chair-fbi-doj-obstructing-trump-probe-hope-dem-takeover-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Devin Nunes accused the FBI and DOJ of stonewalling a sprawling investigation into claims the Trump campaign colluded with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS FLOODS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/billclarkphotos/status/1019309267847925761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Cannon tunnel now closed due to flooding”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers clash with tech over anti-conservative bias...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/397474-republicans-slam-tech-companies-over-anti-conservative-bias-democrats-slam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers clashed Tuesday at a contentious hearing over claims that social media platforms and tech companies are biased against conservative viewpoints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnet detects tumor cells...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/science/article/Stanford-scientists-wire-magnet-cancer-tumor-cells-13082346.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stanford scientists say they've developed a magnetized wire that can grab tumor cells from the bloodstream with "the same force that holds family photos to your refrigerator."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman Impaled By Beach Umbrella On Jersey Shore...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/07/17/woman-impaled-by-beach-umbrella-on-jersey-shore/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say a London woman was impaled by a beach umbrella on the New Jersey shore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Developing Mind-Control Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/07/pentagon-wants-bring-mind-controlled-tech-troops/149776/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Defense Department’s research arm is working on a project that connects human operators’ brains to the systems they’re controlling—and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for contacting ex-girlfriend 200 times per day...</title>
      <link>http://www.gainesville.com/news/20180717/stalking-charge-200-contacts-day-threats-to-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gainesville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Taylor Debaun, 25, was arrested Monday on a warrant for aggravated stalking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendants getting #MeToo movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article214956635.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A union survey of flight attendants found that nearly 70 percent have been sexually harassed on the job. Now, the Association of Flight Attendants-CWA, which also represents South Florida flight attendants, is working to develop new policies for handling misconduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors want to question US intel agents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/russian-prosecutors-question-us-intel-agents-56640996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian prosecutors are pushing to question U.S. intelligence agents and a former ambassador to Moscow in their investigation of an influential foe of Vladimir Putin. The general prosecutor's office made the announcement Tuesday in the wake of Putin's summit Monday with U.S. President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$300 SNAKE Massage...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/07/16/snake-massage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cultures revere the serpents while others simply keep them as pets. Now, you can even get a snake massage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daycare worker who hanged toddler gets probation...</title>
      <link>https://www.kare11.com/article/news/day-care-provider-who-hanged-toddler-sentenced-to-probation/89-574401488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kare11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nataliia Karia received 10 years probation on Monday for hanging a toddler in her daycare and running over two men with her minivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Gets Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/book-rising-democratic-star-kamala-harris-coming-2019-170908704--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sen. Kamala Harris, a rising star in the Democratic Party who is sometimes cited as a possible presidential contender in 2020, has a book deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian 'BATWOMAN' TV Series in Works...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/batwoman-tv-series-works-at-cw-1127574?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greg Berlanti and Caroline Dries are developing the drama ahead of the lesbian character's debut in the network's DC crossover event in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Blair calls for second vote to fix Brexit 'mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tony-blair-calls-second-vote-fix-brexit-mess-144915246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London (AFP) - "It's a total and complete mess": Former prime minister Tony Blair does not hold back when asked in an interview with AFP what he makes of the British government's approach to Brexit. Blair, who held the office for 10 years, said he sympathises with Prime Minister Theresa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines heaviest drinkers military...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/07/16/survey-military-binge-drinking-drops-but-this-service-stood-out-in-a-bad-way/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binge drinking, vaping.... these are just a few of the problems brewing in the military, according to a just-released study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Announces Series About 12-Year-Old Boy Reincarnated as Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/netflix-mark-millar-tv-series-films-millarworld-american-jesus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix announced Tuesday its first slate of films and series based on the stories of "Kick-Ass" and "Kingsman" comic book creator Mark Millar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP UNDER PRESSURE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/back-washington-trump-under-pressure-reverse-course-russia-150202135.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump found himself isolated and under pressure to reverse course Tuesday after publicly challenging the US intelligence conclusion that Russia meddled in the 2016 election during his face-to-face with Vladimir Putin. At his inaugural summit with the Russian president in Finland, Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAKE NEWS GOING CRAZY'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/17/politics/white-house-mood-donald-trump-vladimir-putin-news-conference/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was upbeat immediately after his news conference with Vladimir Putin in Finland, but by the time he returned stateside on Monday evening, his mood had soured considerably amid sustained fury at his extraordinary embrace of the Russian leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lashes out at Palin...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/16/showtime-defends-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime has issued a statement slamming critics of Sacha Baron Cohen as spreading fake— um, "widespread misinformation." In an unusual…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED:  Economy growing 'considerably stronger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/17/powell-backs-more-rate-hikes-as-economy-growing-considerably-stronger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy is running at a fast enough pace to justify continued interest rate increases, Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam withdraws license of news site, issues fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vietnam-withdraws-licence-news-issues-fine-072801197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Vietnamese news website has been suspended and fined about $10,000 after it was accused of publishing false information, as the communist government quashes any perceived criticism. The Ministry of Information and Communication said in an announcement Monday that the state-owned Tuoi Tre Online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strikes in Europe on AMAZON Prime Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/strikes-europe-amazons-prime-day-001110901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers in Spain, Germany and Poland plan to walk off the job on Tuesday as online retailing giant Amazon carries out its major summer sales event called Prime Day. The walkout at the Amazon packing and distribution centre in San Fernando de Henares, near Madrid, kicked off on Monday and was scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelly out as Chief of Staff?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/more-predictions-that-trump-white-house-chief-john-kelly-is-leaving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’ve heard them for months, the rumors that overworked White House Chief of Staff John Kelly is going to step aside, maybe to be replaced by budget boss Mick Mulvaney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZILE:  WHY IS HE ACTING LIKE PUPPET?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2018/07/16/donald-trump-stop-being-putins-puppet-protect-voting-democracy-column/786765002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump fears that if he acknowledges what the Russians did, he'll be an illegitimate president. By acting like Putin's puppet, he already seems like one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazis in their 90s: Germany intensifies hunt for war criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/17/germany-nazi-killers-einsatzgruppen/768938002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German prosecutors are intensifying their hunt for aging Nazi war criminals still at large by expanding investigations into death squads known as the "Einsatzgruppen," which were responsible for more than 1 million murders. Three suspected members have come under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Mary statue appears to 'weep' olive oil tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/17/virgin-mary-statue-crying-olive-oil/791124002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic Diocese of Las Cruces is investigating a Virgin Mary statue that appears to be weeping in a Las Cruces, New Mexico, church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Arising From Bill Maher's Use of N-Word Moves Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.tvweek.com/tvbizwire/2018/07/lawsuit-arising-from-bill-mahers-use-of-the-n-word-moves-forward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tvweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Film Critics Outnumber Women 2 to 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/study-female-film-critics-outnumbered-hurts-female-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Male critics outnumber female critics by 2 to 1, study conducted by San Diego State University's Center for the Study of Women in TV and Film says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILD'S PLAY:  FACEBOOK TURNS BLIND EYE TO UNDERAGE USERS; EXTREME CONTENT REMAINS ON PLATFORM...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6795979/facebook-underage-users-report-dispatches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK ignores underage users and knowingly allows extreme material to remain its site, according to a new Channel 4 investigation. An undercover probe by the broadcaster’s Dispatches programme w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMO babies given go-ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/17/genetically-modified-babies-given-go-ahead-by-uk-ethics-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nuffield Council on Bioethics says changing the DNA of a human embryo could be ‘morally permissable’ if it is in the child’s best interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad marriage can seriously damage health...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/jul/16/a-bad-marriage-is-as-unhealthy-as-smoking-or-drinking-say-scientists </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychologists monitored 373 couples over 16 years and found that couples who continuously disagree have poorer health</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGM sues victims from Vegas mass shooting, denying any liability...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/homicides/lawsuits-claim-mgm-has-no-liability-to-las-vegas-shooting-victims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MGM Resorts International has filed federal lawsuits against more than 1,000 Las Vegas mass shooting victims in an effort to avoid liability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Bet Big on Liberal Democracy. Now Fears He Is Losing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/17/magazine/george-soros-democrat-open-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His enemies paint him as all-powerful, but the billionaire philanthropist believes that his political legacy has never been in greater jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Montage:  Cable News Sees Apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2018/07/16/video-montage-cable-news-sees-apocalypse-trumpputin-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within mere hours of President Trump’s press conference with Vladimir Putin concluding, cable news had worked themselves into a frenzy that suggested the sky itself must be falling. While criticism of Trump’s foreign policy decisions – especially those pertaining to Russia – has been bipatisan, the sheer meoldrama of the liberal media’s comments suggested they had lost sight of what they were even covering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD PRESS MOCKS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/donald-trump-branded-traitor-putin-12932473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem heads to Cuba on campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article214940325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. David Richardson is paying a two-day visit to Cuba this week as he runs for the Democratic nomination to replace U.S. Rep. Ileana Ros-Lehtinen in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW: Worst Case Scenario...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/rachel-maddow-its-time-for-americans-to-face-worst-case-scenario-on-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC:  'Pearl Harbor!' and 'Kristallnacht!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/msnbc-contributor-trumps-performance-will-live-in-infamy-as-much-as-pearl-harbor-or-kristallnacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new AIRBUS plane for 'FAT fliers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716994/Airbus-A220-plane-Air-Baltic-Swiss-Bombardier-C-Series-Farnborough-Airshow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia celebrates: 'West has failed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716992/russia-news-vladimir-putin-donald-trump-helsinki-celebrate-cold-war-media-moscow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to Make More Drugs Easily Available, Cutting Role Docs Play...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/17/u-s-to-make-more-drugs-easily-available-cutting-role-docs-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. to Make More Drugs Easily Available, Cutting Role Docs Play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Ushers in New Era as Solomon Takes Reins From Blankfein...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/17/goldman-says-solomon-will-succeed-blankfein-as-ceo-in-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Solomon finally has a start date for his reign atop Goldman Sachs Group Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Voting Machine Vendor Admits It Installed Remote-Access Software...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/mb4ezy/top-voting-machine-vendor-admits-it-installed-remote-access-software-on-systems-sold-to-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote-access software and modems on election equipment 'is the worst decision for security short of leaving ballot boxes on a Moscow street corner.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find quadrillion tons of diamonds in ground...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/16/scientists-just-found-150000000000000000000000000-diamonds-ground-7722550/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shhh, no one tell the Hatton Garden gang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza's Latest Weapon? Arson Bird...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gaza-latest-weapon-arson-bird-122609768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians in the Gaza Strip have used kites, balloons and flaming condoms to try to start wildfires across the border in Israel -- and now a bird, according to Israeli authorities. A falcon, outfitted with a harness tied to a steel wire with flammable material at the end, was found hanging in a tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking fine could put GOOGLE business model at stake...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2018/07/16/google-antitrust-fine-this-week-will-break-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European regulators are expected to hit Google with a multibillion fine on Tuesday or Wednesday, an announcement that’s being closely watched not because of the anticipated size of the penalt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump returns from summit in HEL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf62711854b6482c88a611391db05a7d/Trump-returns-from-summit-with-Putin-to-forceful-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — In an extraordinary embrace of a longtime U.S. enemy, President Donald Trump openly questioned his own intelligence agencies' firm finding that Russia meddled in t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama delivers Mandela address on 'values' in rebuke to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9c415f558c874ddba99ef23f2cd040f5/Obama-delivers-Mandela-address-on-values-in-rebuke-to-Trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Without ever mentioning President Donald Trump by name, former U.S. President Barack Obama on Tuesday took aim at "strongman politics" in his highest-profile s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Police Warn of 'Possible Serial Killer'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/serial-killer-wanted-connection-murder-spree-police/story?id=56632731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parolee who cut off his ankle monitor is now suspected in connection to a series of murders in the Houston area has been arrested, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Worst ever cable-news hatred of president...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/07/trump-calls-off-cold-war-ii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beginning his joint press conference with Vladimir Putin, President Trump declared that U.S. relations with Russia have “never been worse.” He then added pointedly, that just changed “about four hours ago.” It certainly did. With his remarks in Helsinki and at the NATO summit in Brussels, Trump has signaled a historic shift in U.S. foreign […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daughter accused in fatal beating of 85-year-old mom who left her out of will...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/fort-lauderdale/fl-sb-lauderdale-fatal-mom-beating-20180716-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fort Lauderdale woman is accused of killing her 85-year-old mother after an ongoing fight about the older woman's will, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Scores 327,000 Viewers...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/07/17/sacha-baron-cohens-scathing-satire-who-is-america-scores-just-327000-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime didn’t do much to promote Sacha Baron Cohen’s new show “Who is America?” And it shows. Just 327,000 people watched it on Sunday night. The only real publicity the s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Bit Off, Swallowed Chunk Of Victim's Nose...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/texas-nose-bite-attack-249370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 16--A Texas woman is facing an assault charge after allegedly biting off and swallowing a large chunk of the nose of a female victim, according to investigators. Jessica Collins, 41, was arreste</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHWARZENEGGER: Looked like 'little wet noodle'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/news/397328-schwarzenegger-trump-looked-like-a-little-wet-noodle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former California Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger (R) tore into President Trump on Monday, saying he acted like a “fan boy” of Russian President Vladimir President in their "embarrassing" press conference earlier in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power demand breaking records during heat wave...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180717130806-925xz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-POWER/DEMAND:Texas power demand breaking records during heat wave -ERCOT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER DRIVER JOINS  'RESISTANCE'; DUMPS TRUMP SUPPORTERS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/16/exclusive-young-republicans-dumped-at-a-random-gas-station-by-anti-trump-uber-driver-speak-out/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He drove off and said 'welcome to the resistance'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
