<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fed Quietly Masking Efforts to Calm Market?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-may-quietly-masking-extent-171616740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wall Street sleuths are wondering whether the Federal Reserve is quietly doing more to calm the U.S. repo market than just the headline-grabbing liquidity injections that have captivated observers for months.The New York Fed runs something called the foreign reverse repo pool, a place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian mag raises issue of 'unconditional loyalty'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191224023342-ynppd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RELIGION (PIX):Christianity Today again slams Trump, raises issue of 'unconditional loyalty'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothers charged with obstructing GirlsDoPorn investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/courts/story/2019-12-23/brothers-charged-with-obstructing-girlsdoporn-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators suspect duo removed computers from home of Michael Pratt before he fled the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passionate but dwindling crowds mark the decline of Tijuana bullfights...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2019-12-23/passionate-fans-but-dwindling-crowds-at-tijuana-bullfights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tijuana once hosted bullfights in a 22,000-seat arena. But with fewer crowds, the aficionados now watch from a 3,000-seat plaza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABERNATHY:  In age of Trump, it's OK to be [deeply] conflicted... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/opinion/article/In-the-age-of-Trump-it-s-OK-to-be-deeply-14928014.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HILLSBORO, Ohio - Considering recent reports chronicling the decline of Christianity in the United States, the level of outrage expressed over President Donald Trump's offhand comment that the late congressman John Dingell, D-Mich., might be "looking up," presumably from hell, is somewhat surprising. Suddenly, at least for a day or two, everybody got religion.  To be fair, Trump first suggested that Dingell was "looking down" from heaven. But the president couldn't resist his little joke, and the resulting anguish it caused Rep. Debbie Dingell, the congressman's widow, was entirely understandable. Trump should apologize.  He won't, of course. Not that Trump's lack of contrition will cost him any support. The president's devotees long ago accepted his callousness as a character flaw that is offset by his frontal assault on a corrupt and complacent Washington swamp. The local Republican Party county chair told me last week she had just returned from Dayton, where the printer claims to be working around the clock to keep up with the demand for Trump fliers, pamphlets and memorabilia. There is no abatement in enthusiasm, he told her.  The blowback from the pundit class over Trump's musings on the fate of someone's eternal soul would be more meaningful if the same empathy was accorded the president when it is predicted that he will burn in hell. Such insinuations are regularly made, and similar hopes expressed in emails I receive. There are even fine art prints of "Trump's Arrival in Hell" available online ($30 unframed), but widespread disgust over such an affront to our president has yet to be observed.  Despite the Bible's observation that the path to heaven is narrow and few will travel it, while the road to hell is wide and much more populated, it is still improper in polite society to suggest that anyone will end up in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They came to the US on raft from Cuba, then built 'vast empire of fraud,' feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article238654813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEEN:  GOODBYE, 2019!</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1220676/queens-speech-christmas-message-queen-news-2019-brexit-royal-family-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Queen has spoken publicly for the first time about the Royal Family’s “bumpy” year. In her Christmas Day message, she admits 2019 has not been a vintage year for them – or the UK. The monarch, who has repeatedly tried to heal divisions within the royals and the nation, describes “how small steps taken in faith and in hope can overcome long-held differences to bring harmony and understanding”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA TALKS UP WARREN BEHIND CLOSED DOORS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/475576-obama-talks-up-warren-behind-closed-doors-to-wealthy-donors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren has spent her presidential campaign railing against the donor class, making it known she doesn't want their help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversies under Prince Mohammed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-controversies-under-prince-mohammed-130921138.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has been engulfed by a series of controversies since Mohammed bin Salman was named crown prince and heir to the throne in June 2017. The brutal murder of critic Jamal Khashoggi and the increased repression of dissidents have overshadowed the prince's efforts to modernise the economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising popularity of Chinese medicine threatens wildlife populations, say conservation groups...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rising-popularity-chinese-medicine-threatens-173018089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The growing popularity of traditional Chinese medicine is ravaging global populations of donkeys, tigers and other many other animals, conservation groups say.  Poachers target various species for their organs and treatments are offered for a variety of ailments, from arthritis to erectile dysfunction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government proposes release of Fukushima water to sea or air...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e60f93b7f7de2ff7b5b015fb5167dd9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan's economy and industry ministry proposed on Monday the gradual release or evaporation of massive amounts of treated but still radioactive water being stored at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feeling of doom envelops Coach Garrett...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d69c8a113ff966376647eef871135b51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though the Dallas Cowboys still have a path to the playoffs, there's a feeling of inevitability in one of the most disappointing seasons for Jerry Jones in 30 years as owner and general...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS ON A HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/23/us-futures-point-to-cautiously-higher-open.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks climbed higher on Monday, hitting new records, as the year-end rally continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell NOT closing door on trial witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e8550f1b1469b642d221c457d281df0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Monday that he was not ruling out calling witnesses in President Donald Trump's impeachment trial — but indicated he was in no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tests internet -- to work if cut off from worldwide web...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191223181421-ew39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/INTERNET:Russia checks its internet can work if cut off from worldwide web</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Excess Belly Fat Worsens Ability To Think...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-your-belly-affects-your-brain-as-we-age-excess-body-fat-worsens-fluid-intelligence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that extra belly fat may hurt one's ability to think and react to new situations on the fly, referred to as "fluid intelligence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans leaving the House at record pace. Why?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/republicans-are-leaving-the-house-at-a-record-pace-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far this year, 22 Republicans in the U.S. House have announced that they will not run for reelection next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON exec killed by van delivering company's packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/kenbensinger/amazons-race-to-build-a-fast-delivery-network-the-huma</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more US sniffer dogs to Egypt, Jordan after deaths...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-more-us-sniffer-dogs-egypt-jordan-deaths-210300202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has temporarily stopped sending bomb detecting sniffer dogs to Jordan and Egypt after several of the animals died due to what US officials say was lack of care. "Any death of a canine in the field is an extremely sad event and we will take every measure possible to prevent this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'God always chose people that had flaws'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/evangelicals-stand-with-trump-god-always-chose-people-that-had-flaws/ar-BBYh0li</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke bomb simulation shows how blast would destroy 6 US cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/how-nuclear-attack-would-destroy-us-cities-2019-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City would have the most fatalities from a nuclear blast. San Francisco would have the least.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDUP: FEDEX Driver Caught Tossing Packages Into Ditch...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/12/21/fedex-driver-ditches-packages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FedEx employee in Mercer County was caught throwing packages into a ditch after indicating he had delivered them to their destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military warns: DNA kits pose 'personal, operational risks'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-warns-military-members-dna-kits-pose-personal-and-operational-risks-173304318.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is advising members of the military not to use consumer DNA kits, saying the information collected by private companies could pose a security risk, according to a memo co-signed by the Defense Department’s top intelligence official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang ran 'sextortion' scam from prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article238655293.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign plagued by groups raising million$ in his name...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/23/trump-campaign-compete-against-groups-money-089454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside entities are raising huge money in Trump's name, despite disavowals from the campaign, and spending little of it on 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House counsel suggests Trump could be impeached again...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/23/doj-impeachment-vote-undercut-house-mcgahn-testimony-089604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comment came in a filing with federal court that argues Democrats still need testimony from former White House counsel Don McGahn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting goose invasion with guns, knives and forks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/stories-50816678</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of geese on Orkney is now so huge that permission has been granted to shoot and eat them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Her Head Cold, Insurer Coughed Up $25,865...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/medical-bill-of-the-month-head-cold-throat-swab-dna-tests-insurer-coughed-up-25k/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York City woman, worried that her sore throat might be strep, got swabbed at her doctor’s office. The sample was sent to an out-of-network lab for sophisticated DNA tests ― with a price tag s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Criminal probe underway in Vegas fire that killed 6...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/criminal-probe-underway-las-vegas-fire-killed-source/story?id=67899654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Saturday morning fire was believed to be Vegas' worst fatal fire in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular UAE chat app a govt spy tool...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02291ff7e07d173153b1af3c9ead67bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A chat app that quickly became popular in the United Arab Emirates for communicating with friends and family is actually a spying tool used by the government to track its users,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY:  'I know how not to commit crimes'...</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com/intelligencer/2019/12/a-conversation-with-rudy-giuliani-over-bloody-marys.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If they’re investigating me, they’re a**holes,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers See 2020 as Year More Start to Get Paid for News...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/publishers-see-2020-as-the-year-more-start-to-get-paid-for-news-1.1366284</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, news outlets promoted their work on various online platforms, hoping to bring readers and advertisers back to their own websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad angry over son's haircut shoots barber...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article238644368.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye's $300 Per Ticket 'Opera' at Lincoln Center Barely Hour Long... </title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/12/23/exclusive-kanyes-300-per-ticket-opera-at-lincoln-center-was-one-hour-long-audience-split-the-minute-it-ended</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West’s “opera” at David Geffen Hall, aka Avery Fisher Hall at Lincoln Center was supposed to start at 8pm last night. “Mary,” named for the virgin mother, began …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brought Eastern Zen to Masses...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-people-ram-dass/ram-dass-psychedelic-drug-pioneer-dies-at-home-aged-88-idUSKBN1YR0KY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ram Dass, who in the 1960s joined Timothy Leary in promoting psychedelic drugs a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind mystic predicts Russian meteorite and war for 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/blind-mystic-baba-vangas-predictions-21151259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bulgarian mystic Baba Vanga is still causing eyebrows to raise more than two decades after her death at 85 with a string of gloomy predictions for the year ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Costner Endorses Mayor Pete at Iowa Rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-costner-endorses-pete-buttigieg-at-iowa-rally-1264728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two-time Academy Award winner introduced the Democratic presidential candidate during a rally on Sunday, where he praised Buttigieg for being a "man of his moment."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC RANKED RUDEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/survey-new-york-ranked-as-americas-rudest-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a survey by Business Insider, New York city is the rudest city in the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg using  secretive tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/23/mike-bloomberg-campaign-uses-tech-firm-he-founded-earlier-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg quietly created a technology company called Hawkfish that is helping his 2020 campaign for president. The firm boasts former executives from Facebook and Foursquare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  MAN USES EYE DROPS TO STOP WIFE'S HEART...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article238654658.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON BLASTS TRUMP BLUFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/bolton-john-trump-north-korea-missiles-94088bf9-4d2d-4d10-bfd9-80db7bc36a50.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolton warned in an interview that the administration may need to admit publicly that its policy failed badly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AOC Says USA 'Not an Advanced Society', it's 'Fascism'...</title>
      <link>https://therightscoop.com/watch-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-tells-crowd-at-bernie-rally-america-is-not-an-advanced-society-but-fascism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;therightscoop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez was on the stump this weekend for Bernie Sanders. And at a rally in California that also featured Cornel West, AOC talked a little bit about America. And not in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA TALKS UP WARREN BEHIND CLOSED DOORS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/475576-obama-talks-up-warren-behind-closed-doors-to-wealthy-donors </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren has spent her presidential campaign railing against the donor class, making it known she doesn't want their help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Influencer Known For Showcasing His Extreme Wealth Under Microscope By Feds...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/12/23/cbs3-exclusive-local-omi-in-a-hellcat-youtube-celebrity-instagram-influencer-says-hes-under-the-microscope-of-federal-authorities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Omar Carrasquillo claims agents seized nearly all of his assets in a raid last month while investigating his business dealings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPSTEIN 'ADMITTED TO ME' HE WAS A SPY...</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@dylanhoward/epstein-admitted-to-me-he-was-a-spy-ex-business-partner-of-sex-criminal-claims-prince-andrew-is-c1152667bb86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medium.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Hoffenberg was arrested by FBI agents in Arkansas in 1996, after regulators accused him of defrauding investors. The former…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelical tussling escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6e6fa63541f19afbcf49efeabd2a2fc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the political clamor caused by a top Christian magazine’s call to remove President Donald Trump from office continues to reverberate, more than 100 conservative evangelicals closed ranks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING CEO out as company struggles with crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a1bca4555d49900036dc94c6bd46722d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing CEO Dennis Muilenburg resigned Monday with no end in sight to the crisis that has engulfed the manufacturer and its Max 737 jetliner. The company's board said a change in leadership...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM DASS DEAD AT 88...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a69b5c29572667db80296a00633390f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAUI, Hawaii (AP) — Baba Ram Dass, the 1960s counterculture spiritual leader who experimented with LSD and traveled to India to find enlightenment, returning to share it with Americans, has died....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary shares Hanukkah message -- with photo from White House...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/2020-vision-hillary-shares-hanukkah-message-with-photo-from-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton still has the White House on her mind. The former first lady and failed 2016 presidential candidate tweeted out a Hanukkah message to her followers on Sunday, and included a photo from a White House ceremony when she was an occupant there. https://twitter.com/hillaryclinton/status/1208770310348181504?s=11 “Sending warm wishes to everyone celebrating Hanukkah!” she wrote, along …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell NOT closing door on impeachment trial witnesses...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7821993/Mitch-McConnell-says-ruled-calling-witnesses-Donald-Trumps-impeachment-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressional Democrats had suggested the GOP was have a quick trial with little or no new evidence. McConnell says he wants witnesses chosen in mid-trial like they were in Bill Clinton's impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600 gallons of oil spill in waters off Galapagos Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/12/23/americas/galapagos-spill-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency teams in the Galapagos Islands are working to contain a 600-gallon oil spill after a cargo vessel overturned while being loaded with containers early Sunday, local officials said on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals crucify CHRISTIANITY TODAY over scathing Trump editorial...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/23/evangelicals-crucify-christianity-today-editor-for-calling-for-trumps-ouster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 200 evangelical leaders called out the president of Christianity Today for publishing a blistering editorial urging President Trump’s ouster, saying they are “Bible-believing Chr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai court to rule on case linking opposition to Illuminati...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b4aba7ab43b84c64d12224022c5125c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Thailand's Constitutional Court says it will rule on a sedition complaint that claims a popular opposition political party is linked to the Illuminati, which conspiracy theorists...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals stand with Trump: 'God always chose people that had flaws'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-23/evangelicals-split-over-trump-impeachment-god-always-chose-people-that-had-flaws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent editorial spotlighted fissures among the faithful. In some cases, it offered an occasion to solidify support for the 45th president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots 'indistinguishable from humans in five years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-sophisticated-theyre-given-21131992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll founder Matt McMullen told Daily Star Online at a panel talk in London that dolls powered by artificial intelligence will become as sophisticated as some animals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle sees darkest day in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/weather/the-infernal-darkness-friday-was-darkest-day-recorded-in-seattle-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday might have been the Northern Hemisphere's shortest day of the year. But in Seattle, Friday proved to be its darkest day in (recent) history. Technically, it was the darkest day ever recorded by three devices that the University of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China orders Christians to rewrite Bible...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/china-orders-christians-rewrite-bible-21152113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese Communists want all religious texts to fall in with the party line, or they will be rewritten</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING CEO out as company struggles with crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/23/boeing-stock-halted-pending-news-company-battles-fallout-737-max-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeing Chairman David Calhoun will step in as CEO in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby Publicist Blasts 'Hollywood Slave' Eddie Murphy For 'SNL' Jokes...</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/tv-shows/2019/12/23/bill-cosbys-publicist-issues-statement-in-regards-to-eddie-murph/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eddie Murphy pulled no punches when he stepped on stage for last nights rollicking Saturday Night [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice faces new exceptional flooding...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/18e4e4835a20f4c99d3646c31e005756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — The Italian lagoon city of Venice is facing the prospect of more intense floods at a time when it's still counting the cost of the exceptional high tide that hit it in November....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 more horses found shot to death in Kentucky...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdrb.com/news/reward-grows-more-horses-found-shot-to-death-in-eastern/article_7b3eedca-2572-11ea-871a-3f501c855486.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdrb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dumas Rescue has said that the dead horses were scattered over a large area and it appears they were hunted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban claim responsibility for killing U.S. service member...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-afghanistan-taliban/taliban-claim-responsibility-for-killing-u-s-force-member-spokesman-idUSKBN1YR0EN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban on Monday claimed responsibility for killing a U.S. service member d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia cuts loose with bevy of models and rave...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dc15cf96028ee7ba01f0688244f7ec38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DIRIYAH, Saudi Arabia (AP) — Supermodels and social media mavens, their makeup artists and hair stylists in tow, posed at a concert in leather pants, chunky sweaters and trendy black combat boots....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival camps cater to new fear: America's political unrest...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191223102815-rp1cx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO-SURVIVALCAMPS/ (FEATURE, PIX, TV):FEATURE-Survival camps cater to new fear: America's political unrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. COMMANDOS PRACTICE RAID...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191223062231-joob1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTHKOREA-USA/MILITARY (TV):S.Korea, U.S. commandos practice raiding enemy facility as N.Korea tensions rise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS rebuilding 'like Al-Qaeda on steroids'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10608058/isis-al-qaeda-steroids-iraq-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS is rapidly rebuilding in Iraq after being transformed into “Al-Qaeda on steroids”, warn regional terror experts. The worrying news comes amid fears thousands of jihadis returning f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones nearly speechless after COWBOYS loss...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/jerry-jones-nearly-speechless-after-cowboys-loss-050344095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Jones rarely shies away from a microphone. But after the Cowboys&amp;#39; 17-9 loss to Philadelphia, Jones had nothing much to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi sentences 5 to death for Khashoggi killing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/55954f982c56744b4b0f6e4b2d8ff2be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIYADH, Saudi Arabia (AP) — Saudi Arabia sentenced five people to death on Monday for the killing of Washington Post columnist and royal family critic Jamal Khashoggi, who was murdered in the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
