<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scandal could weigh on president's white evangelical fanbase...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/aug/28/jerry-falwell-jr-fall-grace-influence-trump-voters-liberty-university</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex scandal surrounding ex-head of Liberty University could weigh on president’s white evangelical fanbase in run-up to election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What was it like to ride out Cat 4 hurricane? Survivors tell their stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/what-was-it-like-to-ride-out-the-storm-survivors-of-hurricane-laura-tell-their-stories/803204</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO TV RATINGS BUMP? DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2020/08/28/tv-ratings-republican-convention-night-4-president-trump-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the latest TV ratings, the 2020 Republican National Convention’s grand finale did not appear to enjoy any major Trump bump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifeguard Catches Shark With Bare Hands On Beach!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/08/27/shark-sighting-long-island-jones-beach-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of onlookers formed around 10:15 AM last Friday at Robert Moses Field Two as a dorsal fin poked out of the water followed by a long pointed tail and of course, a set of shark teeth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming Middle East Arms Race Sparks Fear of Regional War...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/looming-middle-east-arms-race-sparks-fear-of-unprecedented-regional-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impending expiration of an international weapons ban on Iran threatens to flood the Middle East with high-tech Russian and Chinese military equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC DAYBREAK CHART... </title>
      <link>https://election.usc.edu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;election.usc.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sperm Quality Lower In Men Who Use Smartphones, Tablets At Night...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sperm-quality-worse-smartphones-tablets-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research just released by the American Academy of Sleep Medicine notes a correlation between nighttime digital media use and poor sperm quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JK Rowling returns award over trans comments criticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200828-jk-rowling-returns-award-over-trans-comments-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JK Rowling returns award over trans comments criticism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer-Spending Rebound Cools, Hinting at More Risk Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-consumer-spending-rebound-cools-130322665.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The rebound in U.S. consumer spending slowed in July amid a surge in virus cases, and now faces another roadblock after the government cut unemployment benefits.Household outlays rose 1.9% from the prior month following an upwardly revised 6.2% rise in the prior month, a Commerce Department</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to cope in anxious age: Hitchcock, Munch, Poe...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/How-to-cope-in-an-anxious-age-Try-Hitchcock-15521450.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French film director François Truffaut, who conducted a famous series of interviews with Alfred Hitchcock in 1962, said afterward that he had found Hitchcock to be a "fearful" and "deeply vulnerable" man, but that this was precisely what made him an "artist of anxiety." Hitchcock's biographer Peter Ackroyd concisely summed up the theme of most of his films: "Ordinary people, living in a familiar setting, are suddenly plunged into a 'chaos world' where no one is safe."  This can hardly be improved upon as a description of our own world since March. It may not be clear what to call the Hitchcock movie we seem to have been plunged into - "Housebound" instead of "Spellbound"? Perhaps "The Man Who Knew Too Little?"  Yet the feeling of being immersed in one of Hitchcock's movies can also induce a desire to watch them, or to consume anything comparably tense and dark and riveting. Friends of mine, from rural Wisconsin to the south of France, from Texas to Tel Aviv, have written to say that during the long coronavirus siege they have been devoting themselves to film noirs and classic Hitchcock and Clouzot thrillers, or to Poe and Kafka and Raymond Chandler stories.  In a small New England town, I've been doing the same. A tenet of homeopathic medicine is that "like cures like." I'm not sure that's true, but perhaps it can at least alleviate it (as, admittedly, can pure, carefree escapism, like the screwball comedies about mostly rich people during the Depression). The art of anxiety may deflect real-life anxiety and simultaneously put it into better focus. Anxiety involves a sharpening of the senses, a heightened awareness. In any kind of treacherous landscape, it helps us keep our balance and see what is hidden.  Like the news, Hitchcock's movies and Franz Kafka's stories are often about innocent people falsely accused of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashierless Stores Popping Up At Gas Stations, Stadiums, Even DUNKIN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/cashierless-stores-are-popping-up-at-gas-stations-stadiums-and-even-dunkin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concept popularized by Amazon Go may be getting a lot bigger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University says it caught outbreak before started. Its secret weapon: poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/The-University-of-Arizona-says-it-caught-a-dorm-s-15521359.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As 5,000 students prepared for move-in day at the University of Arizona this week, the school warned they will periodically be tested for Covid-19. One test, though, doesn't involve a nose swab. The university is regularly screening the sewage from each dorm, searching for traces of the virus.  On Thursday, officials said the technique worked - and possibly prevented a sizable outbreak on campus. When a wastewater sample from one dorm came back positive this week, the school quickly tested all 311 people who live and work there and found two asymptomatic students who tested positive. They were quickly quarantined.  "With this early detection, we jumped on it right away, tested those youngsters, and got them the appropriate isolation where they needed to be," said Richard Carmona, a former U.S. Surgeon General who is directing the school's reentry task force, in a news conference.  Researchers around the world have been studying whether wastewater testing can effectively catch cases early to prevent Covid-19 clusters. There are programs in Singapore, China, Spain, Canada, and New Zealand, while in the U.S., more than 170 wastewater facilities across 37 states are being tested. Earlier this month, officials in the U.K. announced testing at 44 water treatment facilities. The Netherlands has been collecting samples at 300 sewage treatment plants.  With colleges battling large outbreaks around the country, the University of Arizona -- which is trying a mix of online and in-person courses -- elected to test sewage from all 20 residence halls. Other schools are doing the same, including the University of California, San Diego and Syracuse University.  On Tuesday, that screening process found signs of the virus in the wastewater from a dorm called Likins Hall. Although all students living in the dorm had to pass antigen tests...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'F*ck You Up,' 'Kill You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/clips/2020/08/28/rand-paul-threats-from-dc-mob-were-f-you-up-kill-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Friday on Fox News Channel's "Fox &amp; Friends," Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) relived his experience from a night early having been confronted by a mob of protesters near the White House after the conclusion of the Republican National Committee. | Clips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 350 faith leaders endorse Biden, citing 'need of moral leadership'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/514110-more-than-350-faith-leaders-endorse-biden-citing-need-of-moral-leadership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coalition of more than 350 faith leaders endorsed Joe Biden for president late Thursday, citing a "need of moral leadership" and "hope for a better future."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk set to reveal device that connects brain to computer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-implant-v2-demo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk tweeted that his “V2” update will blow our minds. But how close is he to putting computer chips in them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flying Car' Gets off Ground -- With Person Aboard...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2020-08-28/japans-flying-car-gets-off-ground-with-a-person-aboard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands arrested for 'virus-related crimes' in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200828-thousands-arrested-for-virus-related-crimes-in-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands arrested for 'virus-related crimes' in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer creates 'AI Jesus' which goes on to make apocalyptic prophecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/engineer-creates-ai-jesus-writes-22592469</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was designed by engineer George Davila Durendal and told to write about just three topics, The Plague, Roman emperor Ceasar and The End of Days. The artificial intelligence has so far produced 60,000 words</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece starts more training exercises amid Turkey tension...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/greece-starts-more-training-exercises-100435625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greece and the United Arab Emirates have begun joint air force training exercises in the eastern Mediterranean, in the latest build-up of military forces in the region where Greece and Turkey are at odds over seabed mineral rights. The training flights started Friday, a day after the UAE completed the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron emerges as potent political force ahead of election...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828091114-oioqo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/JAMES (PIX):NBA star LeBron James emerges as potent political force ahead of November U.S. election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam ends 'experiment' with mandatory masks...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828085743-j55aj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AMSTERDAM-MASKS (URGENT):Amsterdam ends "experiment" with mandatory face masks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets Brace for Election Drama Like Never Before...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/volatility-markets-brace-election-drama-100000689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Traders across major asset classes are sending the same message: Prepare for what could be the most-contentious U.S. presidential elections in decades.One measure of hedging in the stock market is higher than at any point in the past three presidential elections. In the interest-rates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian navy conducts major maneuvers near Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f6c6dceba65e893aeeee9dfa814ef8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The Russian navy conducted major war games near Alaska involving dozens of ships and aircraft, the military said Friday, the biggest such drills in the area since Soviet times....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Flagship Carrier EL AL Set for Unprecedented UAE Flight...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/israels-flagship-carrier-el-al-set-for-unprecedented-uae-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Office Is Adrift. Divinity Consultants Are Here to Save It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/28/the-office-is-adrift-divinity-consultants-are-here-to-save-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the beginning there was Covid-19, and the tribe of the white collars rent their garments, for their workdays were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best and Worst Moments...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/28/republican-convention-best-and-worst-moments-from-trumps-big-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Opinion’s commentary for the last night of the Republican National Convention. In this special feature, Times Opinion writers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan officials decry robocall that dissuades mail voting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f754971cb5cc10942bd383ca69b3dc3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Michigan's attorney general and secretary of state on Thursday were investigating what they called a racist robocall that falsely warns residents in majority-Black Detroit...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands expected at March on Washington commemorations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e99f9bfcca9cb388054486fa41192194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Capping a week of protests and outrage over the police shooting of a Black man in Wisconsin, civil rights advocates will highlight the scourge of police and vigilante violence...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel warns coronavirus situation to get more difficult over winter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20200828/merkel-virus-fight-will-be-more-difficult-in-autumn-winter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But New Study Suggests Polls Missing Shy Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/new-study-suggests-polls-are-missing-shy-trump-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Study Suggests Polls Are Missing Shy Trump Voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American warship sails near disputed islands...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-warship-sails-near-disputed-090856776.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American warship sailed near the disputed Paracel Islands in the South China Sea, the US Navy has said, challenging Beijing&amp;#39;s claims on the resource-rich waterway and prompting a warning from the Chinese military.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bullet' plane to revolutionize travel...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/celera-500l-plane/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally, the mysterious bullet-shaped Celera 500L has been officially revealed. The super-efficicient six-person plane might hit skies by 2025 and could revolutionize private travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggressive BLM protesters heckle guests leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8672681/BLM-protesters-gather-outside-White-House-Trumps-RNC-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kentucky senator Rand Paul and his wife were attacked by a mob of protesters as they left the White House Thursday/</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul Harassed..</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/08/28/rand-paul-attacked-outside-white-protesters-trumps-speech-rnc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Kentucky Sen. Rand Paul was harassed after leaving the White House where President Trump delivered his speech for the Republican National Convention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORTS:  Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe to resign over health issues... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23a3685932db83a826360280e5e5435f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan's longest-serving prime minister, Shinzo Abe, intends to leave office because of declining health, according to his political party. In a country once known for its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Pans: 'Surprisingly Flat'... 'Lack of Fireworks'... 'Far Too Long'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/fox-news-chris-wallace-pans-trump-speech-as-surprisingly-flat-it-was-far-too-long/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Chris Wallace said Thursday night that while President Donald Trump's RNC convention speech had some effective lines, it was "surprisingly flat."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70-minute marathon!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/donald-trump-republican-convention-review-final-night-joe-biden-covd19-china-1203025652/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump delivered a Republican Convention acceptance speech that was a 70-minute marathon of attack lines against Democrats, superlative trumpeting of his own accomplishments and dir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=56BzAQFB9T0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald J. Trump's Full Remarks at the 2020 Republican National Convention. #RNC2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowded party on South Lawn mostly devoid of virus precautions...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-celebrates-at-crowded-party-mostly-devoid-15520959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump celebrated his renomination Thursday with a crowded party at the White House that offered a jarring contrast with a nation that is still widely shut down over fears of the coronavirus pandemic whose spread remains uncontrolled.  More than 1,500 supporters poured onto the South Lawn for his formal acceptance speech to cap the Republican National Convention, and most were not wearing masks, even though they were seated closely together in white folding chairs.  The overwhelming majority of guests were not administered rapid coronavirus tests, Trump campaign and RNC officials said, despite their relative proximity to the president and other White House officials. A White House official said it would have been logistically unfeasible to test such a large number of people.  Two attendees said in interviews that they were not offered tests and were not even put through a more basic screening, such as being questioned whether they had any symptoms, such as coughs, or taking their temperature. They spoke on the condition of anonymity to talk frankly.  The spectacle offered Trump a reasonable facsimile of the traditionally raucous nominating convention that was canceled this year because of the pandemic. A large stage was set up just beyond the White House portico, lined with dozens of American flags - a dramatic backdrop that allowed the president to wield the visual power of his office at a campaign event despite federal regulations that seek to limit such activities.  But the program also projected the image to millions watching on television that a president whose public approval ratings have fallen over widespread disapproval of his handling of the pandemic has returned to business as usual, even if most Americans have not.  Medical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP SPELLS HIS NAME OUT IN FIREWORKS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/acyn/status/1299190225806139392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECTACLE:  RNC TAKES OVER WHITE HOUSE!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-raises-specter-chaos-nation-172857061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump warned Thursday that his election opponent Joe Biden wants to destroy &amp;quot;American greatness&amp;quot; in a speech accepting the Republican nomination for a second term against a backdrop of explosive racial tensions and the deadly coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  What virus? Fear motivates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74c29d2096afc272e7260b84654b8307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump refused to allow the coronavirus to deny him the crowd he craved for the Republican National Convention. He ordered up a scene never before seen at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zxhZS1BR22E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump's Full Remarks at the 2020 Republican National Convention. #RNC2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-LIBERTY student claims Falwell wife climbed into bed and performed oral sex on him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8672437/Ex-Liberty-University-student-claims-Becki-Falwell-performed-oral-sex-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Liberty University student who played in a band with Becki Falwell's  son Trey claims she performed oral sex on him in 2008 when he was 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY:  UNREST WILL SPREAD IF BIDEN ELECTED...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/rudy-giuliani-rnc-speech-151780bd-6c7d-4947-892a-4b08ecf68778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He accused Biden of being a "Trojan horse" for "pro-criminal, anti-police, socialist policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA:  Dad called out DC's hypocrisy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/514089-ivanka-trump-champions-father-in-fiery-convention-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump, the president's eldest daughter and senior adviser, delivered a fiery speech on Thursday in support of her father's reelection bid, simultaneously highlighting many of the issues she has championed during his first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECTACLE:  RNC TAKES OVER WHITE HOUSE!</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828013352-h19bp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 7-Trump, Republicans attack Biden amid coronavirus crisis, street protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nXQJX1GL6aE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RNC 2020: Former NYC Mayor Rudy Giuliani Full Speech at Republican National Convention Join this channel to get access to perks: https://www.youtube.com/chan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-x-GC37SGkE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell spoke on the final night of the Republican National Convention on Aug. 27, 2020. The party planned a mix of virtual an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger dragged off flight after text saying he's positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1378201/coronavirus-ryanair-flight-dragged-off-seat-stansted-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the dramatic moment a passenger was dragged off a Ryanair flight by hazmat-clad officials after receiving a text telling him he had tested positive for coronavirus moments before departure.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows activists in Kenosha arrested by officers who jumped out of unmarked vehicles... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Video-shows-activists-in-Kenosha-arrested-by-15520782.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Seattle-based nonprofit that serves food to protesters said Thursday that several of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former top Trump officials betting he'll lose... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/27/former-trump-officials-lose-403926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And unprecedented number of administration veterans have turned against the president — and even many of those who still back him think he's doomed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA adds hundreds to 'no fly list' for mask violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/delta-bans-nearly-250-people-from-flying-on-its-planes-for-refusing-to-wear-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an internal memo released Thursday, Delta Air Lines has placed more than 240 people on a “no fly list” for failing to comply with its mandatory mask policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes embrace the protest movement by stepping off the field and speaking up...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Athletes-embrace-the-protest-movement-by-stepping-15520765.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Until this week, 2020 was the year sports seemed to matter least. Now, it may become the year sports matter most. Not for games that were played but for those that weren't - and that continue to be scrubbed as players across all major leagues show solidarity with social justice protesters in Wisconsin.  The NBA postponed its three playoff games Wednesday and did the same Thursday, though it intends to resume its postseason at some point. The NHL postponed its playoff games scheduled for Thursday and Friday. MLB went team by team - perhaps reflecting the divisions, and difficulty, in reaching consensus. But with three games postponed Wednesday and seven more postponed Thursday, more than half of the sport's 30 teams joined in the national sports protest.  Washington Nationals Manager Dave Martinez was emotional Wednesday after his team's game, saying: "Proud of the NBA and all the people who stand for justice. You know the way I feel about all this stuff. It's horrible. We need change. We're people."  By Thursday afternoon, the Philadelphia Phillies and Nationals, both unanimously, decided to postpone their game. "This is a humanitarian issue. It's time to speak up," Martinez said. "Tomorrow is Jackie Robinson Day. Jackie will be playing tomorrow."  The Phillies' Rhys Hoskins spoke for his team, noting that the New York Mets' Dominic Smith had broken down in sobs the previous night discussing the pervasive fear among Black people that they or their families could suffer from police brutality. "He's a strong Black man," said Hoskins, who is White. "If that didn't hit you differently, well, it should hit you differently. . . . We've had team conversations this year, and things have come up that I never knew about. As a White person, we need to listen."  Of the bonding through difficult conversations this year in MLB, where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAVOC IN LOUISIANA...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2020-08-27-hurricane-laura-louisiana-texas-damage-impacts-power-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Laura turned deadly as it moved inland, leaving behind damaged buildings, flooded streets and widespread power outages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL:  DEMS WANT TO REGULATE HAMBURGERS...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/934312/mcconnell-inexplicably-claims-that-democrats-want-tell-americans-how-many-hamburgers-eat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) asked Americans to 'support Republican Senate candidates across the country and re-elect my friend, President Donald Trump' during the Republican National Convention on Thursday night â€” including making an ominous (and false) threat that Democrats are prepared to take away your hamburgers if you don't. McConnell has been a bit of a reluctant ally â€” and even occasional foe â€” of the president's, even initially announcing he had no plans to talk at the convention before walking the statement back. But speaking from the verdant fields of Kentucky, McConnell stressed the importance of the election for conservative voters. Democrats 'want to tell you when you can go to work, when your kid can go to school,' McConnell claimed. 'They want to tax your job out of existence, and then send you a government check for unemployment.' He added that Democrats 'want to tell you what kind of car you can drive, what sources of information are credible, and even how many hamburgers you can eat.' 'They want to tell you what kind of car you can drive, what sources of information are credible, and even how many hamburgers you can eat' â€” Rep. Mitch McConnell thinks he knows what Democrats are all about #RNC2020 pic.twitter.com/8FVJvi032X â€” NowThis (@nowthisnews) August 28, 2020 While it's not true that Democrats are seeking to regulate hamburgers, CNN's Daniel Dale noted that the claim 'may, or may not, be an exaggerated reference to Sen. Kamala Harris's musings about dietary guidelines, which are not mandates.' Either way, McConnell's intention was clear: 'With two more liberal senators, we cannot undo the damage [Democrats have] done,' he said. Jeva Lange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters gather in Lafayette Square...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/514078-protesters-gather-in-lafayette-square-ahead-of-trump-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters descended on Lafayette Square outside of the White House Thursday ahead of President Trump’s speech formally accepting the GOP’s 2020 nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to attack Biden as nation confronts chaos...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200828002919-stndt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 6-Trump to attack Biden as U.S. confronts coronavirus, anti-racism protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen in Wisconsin shootings charged with six criminal counts ...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200827221113-nfin0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-RACE/USA-RITTENHOUSE (URGENT):Teenager in Wisconsin shootings charged with six criminal counts -complaint</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVENTION FINALE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/94ba5c99bf08a38a6c7f5152e5fab49c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing a fraught national moment, President Donald Trump was accepting his party's renomination from a massive White House South Lawn stage Thursday night, breaking with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  Brutal campaign shaping up over pandemic, race and economy... </title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Brutal-campaign-shaping-up-over-pandemic-race-15520645.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just over 10 weeks until Election Day, the campaign for president turns from a pair of scripted conventions to the trench warfare of mobilizing voters and the unpredictability of September and October, with the campaign playing out against a backdrop unlike anything seen in modern times.  In a month, the first of three presidential debates will be held, scheduled for Sept. 29 in Cleveland. Some strategists see that evening as a pivotal and potentially decisive confrontation, particularly if President Donald Trump has a bad night and Joe Biden looks strong. Still, the 2016 campaign moved late and, ultimately, decisively in Trump's direction. Democrats worry about a repeat of that playbook and warn now against complacency.  By the time of the first debate, early voting will have begun in a few states, and the pace will accelerate in October. Controversy over voting by mail is yet another backdrop of the argument between Trump, who claims without evidence that mail ballots are vulnerable to fraud, and Biden, who has charged that Republicans are trying to frustrate voters and suppress Democratic turnout.  A deadly pandemic, an economy struggling to rebound, with millions out of work, and continued racial unrest and calls for racial justice sparked by shootings of unarmed Black men continue to shape Campaign 2020. The trio of crises will be the overriding issues as voters decide whether to give Trump a second term or turn the country over to Biden.  For Trump, the challenge in the weeks ahead will be to undo impressions of nearly four years of chaotic leadership, to demonstrate the kind of discipline and focus that has too often been missing. For Biden, the challenge will be to hold steady while not appearing too passive, to persuade people he has the vision, the policies and the energy to move the country to a more...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Melania refused to move to White House until Obamas' toilet had been ripped out...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1379443/melania-trump-refused-white-house-move-obama-toilet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELANIA Trump refused to move into the White House until a new toilet was installed in the Obamas’ former bedroom, according to a new book.  Picky Melania thought the livin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk set to reveal device that connects brain to computer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1371466/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-chip-reveal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk is set to reveal a ‘working Neuralink device’ this Friday. The highly anticipated but controversial brain chip aims to help us compete with artificial intelligence and help th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  There shouldn't be any debates!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/513944-pelosi-says-there-shouldnt-be-presidential-debates-in-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) said Thursday she doesn’t think there should be any presidential debates ahead of the November election, arguing Democratic presidential nominee Joe Biden shouldn't "legitimize"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz NOT invited...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/27/ted-cruz-wasnt-invited-to-speak-at-2020-rnc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz delivered one of the most talked-about speeches at the 2016 Republican National Convention. This time around, he tells the New York Times, he wasn’t invited. “They didn&amp;#8…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG NIGHT, HIGH STAKES:  Trump Makes His Case For More... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-rnc-acceptance-speech-aims-213226293.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump hopes to galvanize support for his flagging reelection bid when he accepts the Republican nomination. He first must convince voters he can fix the health, economic and social crises that he failed to fix in his first term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality TV Moments Draw Ethics Complaints...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/donald-trump-republican-convention-white-house-ethics-complaints-hatch-act-1203025264/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Donald Trump prepares to give a norm-shattering acceptance speech on the South Lawn of the White House on Thursday, government watchdogs claim that some of the reality TV-like moments from the R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic largely ignored...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c8804d7597c4f10e9ca5bb040564026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It was a scene from a bygone era: Vice President Mike Pence shaking hands with and fist-bumping audience members who had rushed forward, standing shoulder to shoulder, to greet...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala steps into attack dog role...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/27/harris-attacks-trumps-incompetence-coronavirus-response-in-acceptance-speech-prebuttal-403770</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic vice presidential nominee accused the president of deadly incompetence and “a reckless disregard for the well-being of the American people.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue planet: Study proposes new origin theory for Earth's water...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200827-blue-planet-study-proposes-new-origin-theory-for-earth-s-water</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue planet: Study proposes new origin theory for Earth's water</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 arrested after 'suspicious vehicles with out-of-state plates' stopped on 4th night of protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox6now.com/news/9-arrested-after-suspicious-vehicles-with-out-of-state-plates-stopped-on-4th-night-of-protests-in-kenosha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox6now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said this began with a citizen tip that the vehicles planned to meet in a remote lot near State Highway 50 and Green Bay Road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB game postponed... </title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/sports/washington-nationals-philadelphia-phillies-postpone-tonights-game-in-wake-of-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Nationals game against the Philadelphia Phillies Thursday evening was postponed in the wake of boycotts protesting police violence across the spectrum of professional sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATINGS DECLINE SHARPLY FROM DNC...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/republican-convention-night-3-down-sharply-overall-from-dnc-but-fox-news-continues-ratings-dominance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' coverage on the Republican National Conventions's third night netted them another win in the TV ratings, though it's a downturn from the overall audience networks saw during t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House creating 'very large' dossier on WASHPOST journalist, others...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/27/media/white-house-dossier-journalists/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House said in a story published Thursday that it was compiling a "very large" dossier on a Pulitzer Prize-winning Washington Post reporter and others who it said are a "disgrace to journalism and the American people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could put quick end to $300 weekly jobless aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hurricane-laura-trump-300-unemployment-aid-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storm damage could sap a quarter of the emergency fund President Trump tapped to pay unemployment benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN: Dynasty may be dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/27/the-kennedy-dynasty-may-be-well-and-truly-ove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This may be the last Kennedy. Finally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study reveals evidence of airplane spread...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/27/cdc-study-reveals-how-coronavirus-can-spread-in-airplanes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 has been shown to spread on airplanes even among asymptomatic travelers, according to a new study from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The study, which was published in the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos capture damaging winds as iconic buildings torn apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbrz.com/news/videos-capture-damaging-winds-as-iconic-lake-charles-buildings-are-torn-apart-overnight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbrz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Laura has made it inland and is causing heavy damage throughout Louisiana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/multimedia/photos/collection_d810bc6a-e857-11ea-9d6b-8396220fee64.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With sustained winds of 150 mph, Hurricane Laura's eye made landfall near Cameron, Louisiana, at about 1 a.m. Thursday, August 27, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Coast Guard shoots at shark for trying to join swim call party...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2020/08/27/watch-the-coast-guard-shoot-at-a-shark-for-trying-to-join-its-swim-call-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately for the shark, the Coast Guard is known to enforce a strict “We prefer to keep our limbs” policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTACART 'tips' for workers went into company's pockets, prosecutors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/instacart-tips-for-workers-went-into-companys-pockets-dc-prosecutors-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A grocery delivery service that rose to prominence during the coronavirus pandemic allegedly pocketed fees that customers thought were tips for their delivery drivers, according to a lawsuit launched by D.C. prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea releases photos of Kim to debunk coma claims...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/north-korean-news-agency-releases-photos-of-kim-jong-un-to-debunk-claims-hes-in-a-coma/wcm/c1201ff6-e43f-4de1-87ba-23e5ef5abc92/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Trump sees Wisconsin unrest as 'political benefit'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b32115afb47a93d223d85bec3cc9d12c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden and Kamala Harris stepped up their criticism of President Donald Trump on Thursday, saying he’s rooting for violence amid unrest in Wisconsin and blasting him for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot by Secret Service outside White House was holding comb...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/man-shot-by-secret-service-officer-outside-white-house-apparently-was-holding-a-comb-documents-show/2020/08/27/61cdf110-e872-11ea-97e0-94d2e46e759b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man had announced that he was armed, officials had said earlier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen boys tortured, raped, buried alive in Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8671143/Two-teenage-boys-tortured-raped-buried-alive-Sweden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The boys were set upon allegedly by a 21-year-old and an 18-year-old at around 11pm on Saturday evening in Solna, Sweden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America ranks dead last in handling of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/27/world/global-coronavirus-attitudes-pew-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans rank dead last -- by a long way -- among citizens of more than a dozen countries who were asked whether their nation is more united now than it was before the coronavirus pandemic, according to a survey released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC walks back controversial testing guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2020/08/27/coronavirus-updates-california-cdc-testing-unemployment/5640833002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus complicates Laura evacuations. California, Nevada boost testing. Fauci says he missed CDC testing change meeting. Latest COVID-19 news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BOMBED'</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/sen-john-kennedy-on-hurricane-laura</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Laura ravaged Louisianna, leaving it looking like it was "bombed," Sen. John Kennedy, R-La., said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA caves; Players decide to resume playoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/29752941/nba-players-decide-resume-playoffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA players have decided to resume the playoffs, a source tells ESPN's Adrian Wojnarowski.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bartering experiencing unprecedented rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20200821-the-rise-of-bartering-in-a-changed-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid economic uncertainty – and a desire to connect as we distance – bartering is experiencing an unprecedented rise. Could it stick around?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We have spent last four years reversing damage Biden inflicted over last 47 years'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/27/exclusive-trump-set-to-skewer-biden-in-convention-address-403574</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have spent the last four years reversing the damage Joe Biden inflicted over the last 47 years," the president will say, according to excerpts provided to POLITICO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch masterwork stolen for third time...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/no-laughing-matter-as-dutch-masterwork-stolen-for-third-time-01598539805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thieves have stolen the painting \</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL teams halt practices over police shooting... </title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nfl-teams-halt-practices-over-152042241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple NFL teams cancelled scheduled practice sessions on Thursday in the wake of protests against the police shooting of Jacob Blake in Wisconsin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus hits isolated Indian island tribe... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-hits-isolated-indian-island-081604137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten members of India&amp;#39;s dwindling Great Andamanese tribe have tested positive for coronavirus, officials said Thursday, fuelling concerns about the safety of the group and other indigenous people in the remote archipelago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libya warns armed 'thugs' who broke up protests... </title>
      <link>https://guardian.ng/news/libya-warns-armed-thugs-who-broke-up-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;guardian.ng&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Libya's government in Tripoli on Thursday warned it would use force against militia gunmen who broke up peaceful protests by firing at crowds the day before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Wealthy Club Stockpiles Cash as Economy Fears Grow...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ultra-rich-club-stockpiles-cash-141234659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A group of multimillionaire investors in the U.S. are hoarding cash at unprecedented levels.Tiger 21, a club of more than 800 investors, reported Thursday that its members have raised their cash holdings to 19% of their total assets on concerns over the economic consequences of the covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens to withhold drug exports...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/play-dirty-chinese-official-threatens-us-medical-supplies-over-huawei-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China may restrict American access to medical supplies in retaliation for intensifying U.S. regulations on Huawei, according to a prominent economist and Chinese Communist Party adviser.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron leads calls to end season...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1378329/barack-obama-proud-nba-player-boycott-lebron-james/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BARACK Obama issued his support for the NBA player boycott as LeBron James reportedly led calls to end the season in protest. The NBA delayed three playoff games in the wake of the police shooting …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dramatic Spike In Children Abusing Their Parents During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/report-children-abusing-parents-during-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parents add being confined at home is creating a "cabin fever effect" and, for some, this "pressure cooker" environment is leading to violent outbursts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She is brilliant. She is terrifying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/opinion/article/Farewell-to-Kellyanne-Conway-the-ultimate-Woman-15518830.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kellyanne Conway had a two-word weapon that she deployed with shrewd skill during her almost-four-year stint at the White House, and it left her targets defenseless.  Excuse me, she would say, needling a news anchor to permit her to barge into the conversation and take it in a more alternative-factsy direction.  Excuse me, she would say to fellow guests who tried, unsuccessfully, to join in with their own opinions. It was a filibuster of false manners, a prim reminder that she would not be yielding the floor.  "What if his spittle - excuse me - what if (Joe) Biden's spittle had gone beyond the teleprompters and everybody there was at risk?" she demanded, absurdly, at a news conference earlier this summer, turning attention away from President Donald Trump's own coronavirus failures. In a 2018 interview with Chris Cuomo regarding payments to porn star Stormy Daniels, she once excused herself a half-dozen times, all the while steamrolling a narrative that her boss was the real victim in the whole mess.  For Conway, "Excuse me" really meant "Excuse you." It was a shaming. It implied that the the other party was in the wrong for not permitting her bulldozing, browbeating and bloviating. It relied, successfully, on the assumption that nobody wanted to be seen interrupting a tiny blonde woman on live television. And so it excused her.  She is brilliant. She is terrifying.  She is also gone, theoretically. Earlier this week Conway announced she would be resigning from her role as senior adviser to the president. Her Wednesday speech at the Republican National Convention was a farewell of sorts, the last time we can expect to see her behaving as an official mouthpiece for Trump before she retreats to her new "less drama, more mama" lifestyle.  It was the hundredth anniversary of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25% OF STATE WITHOUT POWER</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/hurricane-laura-hours-away-from-landfall-in-louisiana/799307</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG probes perplexing Trump Tower Chicago loan deal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-attorney-general-probes-perplexing-102000704.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s attorney general is trying to answer one of the most perplexing questions surrounding the troubled financing of the Trump International Hotel and Tower in Chicago: whether President Donald Trump failed to pay taxes on a $100 million loan deal related to the project. According to a court filing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best and Worst Moments...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/27/republican-convention-best-and-worst-moments-from-mike-pence-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Opinion’s commentary for Night 3 of the Republican National Convention. In this special feature, Times Opinion writers rank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Peaceful Night In Kenosha After Deadly Shooting; No Sign Of 'Armed Citizens' Group...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/08/27/live-updates-peaceful-night-of-protests-in-kenosha-in-wake-of-fatal-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wednesday night’s protests were much calmer than those that filled the streets in Kenosha earlier this week. As of early Thursday, there were no groups patrolling with long guns as there were during previous nights of protests of Jacob Blake’s shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MORNING AFTER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45ba32bafe5da34b5691544ecb3e5492</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKE CHARLES, La. (AP) — Hurricane Laura pounded the Gulf Coast with ferocious wind and torrential rain Thursday and unleashed a wall of seawater that could push 40 miles inland as the Category 4...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Laura still a hurricane 170 miles after landfall!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3268e532e5e2094bcd368885c43769bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Latest on Hurricane Laura: President Donald Trump will get a briefing about Hurricane Laura Thursday at the Federal Emergency Management Agency. Trump will get an afternoon...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
