<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Most aggressive ransomware group suddenly offline...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/13/multiple-revil-ransomware-sites-are-down-on-the-darkweb-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dark web sites linked to the REvil ransomware gang were not operating Tuesday. The gang, aka Sodinokibi, took credit for the July 2 international attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does the dawn of demisexuals tell us?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/commentisfree/2021/jul/13/what-does-the-dawn-of-demisexuals-tell-us-how-sex-drenched-society-has-become</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pop culture has become more and more sexualised, as sex is sold to us willy-nilly. But young people are turning away from it in droves, writes the Guardian columnist Arwa Mahdawi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wellness Resorts Eye Long Covid Treatments as New Moneymaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/wellness-resorts-eye-long-covid-treatments-as-new-moneymaker/ar-AAM5Lfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From colonic cleanses to brain modulation to nutrient-rich IV drips, spas are coming up with all sorts of (costly) ways to treat symptoms of long Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POOP POLICE:  Tel Aviv dog owners must now register DNA with municipality...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/dog-owners-in-tel-aviv-must-now-register-their-dogs-dna-with-municipality-673693</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The municipality calculated that an estimated 500 kilos of dog feces are not picked up from the street every month, and hope that this new law will work to decrease the amount.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-year-old 'Freedom to Zion' coins found in Binyamin...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/2000-year-old-freedom-to-zion-coins-found-in-binyamin-region-673677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coins, dated to around the Second Temple and Bar Kochba revolt periods, document the Jewish revolt against the Romans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excerpt from 'FINAL YEAR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/I-Alone-Can-Fix-It-book-excerpt-Inside-Trump-s-16311355.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOTE: This is an excerpt from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO edges out NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hbo-beats-back-netflix-to-lead-emmy-nominations-thanks-to-hbo-max</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay cable network rolled up its count with streaming service to come out ahead by a single nod with 130</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACLU gets involved in Britney battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/britney-spears-aclu-conservatorship-amicus-brief</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ACLU on Tuesday filed an amicus brief in support of Britney Spears as the pop star seeks to choose her own attorney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubs for Kidman, Corden, Myers, Fallon... MORE</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/13/emmy-nominations-shock-snubs-for-nicole-kidman-and-the-undoing-genius-aretha</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Emmys will be held on September 19th on CBS, hosted by one of their stars, Cedric the Entertainer. The presenters for the Emmy noms were father and daughter Emmy winners Ron Cephas and Jasmine …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Hospital puts new kidney in wrong patient...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wrong-patient-gets-kidney-at-ohio-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Ohio hospital has acknowledged that a patient received a new kidney meant for someone else.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMMYS:  Rodriguez First Trans Woman Nominated in Lead Acting...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2021/07/13/mj-rodriguez-emmy-nomination-pose-history-lead-actress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The category is… one for the record books. Pose star Mj Rodriguez received an Emmy nomination on Tuesday for Lead Actress in a Drama Series</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulder, CO Named Best Place to Live in USA...</title>
      <link>https://realestate.usnews.com/real-estate/articles/what-makes-boulder-the-best-place-to-live-in-the-us-in-2021-22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realestate.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado metro area's relative job stability and high marks for quality of life make it No. 1 for the second year in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://realestate.usnews.com/real-estate/articles/us-news-ranks-the-best-places-to-live-in-the-us-in-2021-2022 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realestate.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Best Places to Live rankings help consumers weigh key factors in deciding where they should live next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE: Man Burned With Unknown Liquid In Random Attack In Midtown Manhattan...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/13/midtown-unprovoked-liquid-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surveillance video shows a 57-year-old man walking on the sidewalk, when a shirtless man runs up behind him and throws an unknown liquid on his back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant: $200 french fries!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/entertainment/the-scene/serendipity3-sets-guinness-world-record-for-worlds-most-expensive-french-fries/3152081/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are a foodie with quite a bit of change to spare, an iconic restaurant may have just the thing for you to celebrate #NationalFrenchFryDay. Serendipity3, the iconic Upper East Side restaurant, set a Guinness World Records title for making the “Most Expensive French Fries” — just in time to celebrate National French Fry Day Tuesday! Serendipity3’s Creative Director…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don unloads on 'Disgraced' Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-kavanaugh-supreme-court-michael-wolff-fd429590-57ab-4a7f-a648-9a3fd50d25f3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There were so many others I could have appointed, and everyone wanted me to."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gun covered in LEGOS to look like toy sets off furor...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2021/07/13/lego-gun-glock-controversy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Culper Precision’s custom design for a Glock handgun arrived at a time when gun violence is soaring and little is being done to keep lethal weapons out of the hands of children, who are often killed in accidental shootings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENDER: President said whoever 'leaked' bunker stay should be 'executed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/13/politics/trump-white-house-bunker-leak-executed-treason-book-claims/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Then-President Donald Trump told a number of his advisers in 2020 that whoever leaked information about his stay in the White House bunker in May of that year had committed treason and should be executed for sharing details about the episode with members of the press, according to excerpts of a new book, obtained by CNN, from Wall Street Journal reporter Michael Bender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health official says boosters risk MORE SERIOUS side effects...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210713132522-as8qh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CDC (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-U.S. health official says COVID-19 boosters could risk more serious side effects</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bachelorette finalists apologizes for 'homophobic tweets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3270899/bachelorette-finalist-justin-glaze-apologizes-racist-homophobic-tweets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Bachelorette finalist Justin Glaze apologized for his past “racist and homophobic tweets” and also admitted ‘I just wanted to fit in.” During the Bachelor Happy Hour pod…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Avg Person Hides 2 Embarrassing Secrets From EVERYONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/keep-two-secrets-from-everyone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in five are most likely to keep a secret from their mothers and 16 percent don't even dare tell their best friends about their secrets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley had planet's hottest 24 hours on record...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/death-valley-had-planets-hottest-24-hours-on-record-sunday-amid-punishing-heat-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overnight low of 107.7 and a daytime high of 128.6 combined to produce the highest dailiy average temperature ever observed on Earth: 118.1. The probable world record came amid a punishing heat wave across much of the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaffe in Tokyo: IOC chief  calls Japanese people 'Chinese'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/other/olympic-size-gaffe-in-tokyo-ioc-chief-bach-calls-japanese-people-e2-80-9cchinese-e2-80-9d/ar-AAM6AkL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The IOC President is not a popular figure in Japan. Inadvertently calling the Japanese people "Chinese" hasn't helped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornel West says in resignation letter HARVARD in 'decline and decay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cornel-west-says-in-resignation-letter-over-tenure-dispute-that-harvard-is-in-decline-and-decay/ar-AAM6A29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West, considered one of the most prominent Black philosophers and progressive activists in the country, tweeted, “Let us bear witness against this spiritual rot!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Woman watches sharks eat friends 'one by one' after boat crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3272980/shark-week-attack-survivor-ate-friends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEBORAH Scaling-Kiley watched in terror as killer sharks pulled her crewmate Mark Adams beneath the surface and the sea turned red with blood. The 24-year-old had been on a routine sailing trip fro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon 'wobble' could cause mass flooding across Earth?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3272422/moon-causes-flooding-wobble-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NASA study has revealed how a ‘wobble’ in the Moon’s orbit could cause devastating flooding in the 2030s. Research led by the US space agency predicts cities along the country&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal threats 'more serious than ever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jul/13/trump-organization-tax-crimes-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in New York, Georgia and Washington have active inquiries that could yield further, serious charges against the ex-president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackie Chan praises Communist Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/people-culture/china-personalities/article/3140926/martial-arts-star-jackie-chan-wants-join</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor mocked for saying he wants to join the Communist Party, to mainlanders he is immoral because he once had an affair, while his fans outside China accuse him of being pro-Beijing for commercial reasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret algorithm transforming DNA evidence. This defendant could be first to scrutinize it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/a-secret-algorithm-is-transforming-dna-evidence-this-defendant-could-be-the-first-to-scrutinize-it/ar-AAM6pHj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors have used software to help convict thousands but have never revealed its source code. A Virginia defendant has won the right to examine it for errors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrants in Miami talk of boating to island to back movement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-cuba-miami-boating-eae2b37e75e40861e1754cde45d41d65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The United States Coast Guard in Miami is monitoring any activity aimed at increasing “unsafe and illegal” crossings between Florida and Cuba in response to rare street protests on the island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Aging Clock' Predicts Disease, Frailty, Death Years Before Symptoms Develop...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/aging-clock-predicts-disease-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The artificial intelligence tool identifies at-risk individuals early, when drugs and lifestyle changes are more likely to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This feels like 1999'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/13/startup-funding-vc-dotcom-bubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venture capitalists are writing bigger checks than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPEYES Stockpiles Chicken Meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsmax.com/finance/streettalk/popeyes-chicken-nugget-stockpile/2021/07/13/id/1028388/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popeyes, the fast-food chain that drew attention for its popular fried-chicken sandwich in 2019, is stockpiling poultry as it prepares to launch a new nugget product at a time of industrywide chicken shortages. The business, owned by Restaurant Brands International Inc., has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Attaches Nerve Syndrome to J&amp;J Jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-will-attach-warning-of-rare-nerve-syndrome-to-johnson-johnson-vaccine/ar-AAM3XQo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration warned on Monday that Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson’s coronavirus vaccine can lead to an increased risk of a rare neurological condition known as Guillain–Barré syndrome, another setback for a vaccine that has largely been sidelined in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The siege and chase...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/13/americas/haiti-president-assassins-gun-battle-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plot to kill Haiti's President allegedly spanned multiple countries and involved highly experienced former military officers and months of planning, according to local officials. Yet the primary suspects in the case appear to have been unprepared for their fierce pursuit by Haitian security forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Fined $593 Million in French Warning to Pay for News...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-fined-593-million-french-071156094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Google was fined 500 million euros ($593 million) in France after the search giant failed to follow an order to thrash out a fair deal with publishers to use their news content on its platform.The Alphabet Inc. unit ignored a 2020 decision to negotiate in good faith for displaying snippets of articles on its Google News service, the Autorité de la concurrence said Tuesday. The fine is the second-biggest antitrust penalty in France for a single company.France isn’t alone in trying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Warns 'Surprising Amount Of Death' From Increasing Covid Cases...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/07/12/surprising-amount-of-deaths-will-soon-occur-in-these-us-regions-from-increased-covid-19-cases-expert-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Delta variant rapidly spreads, US hotspots have seen climbing cases -- and an expert warns a "surprising amount" of Covid-19 deaths could soon follow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban surge sends thousands fleeing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-lifestyle-afghanistan-race-and-ethnicity-1ed5303beb691ccef61402c3f07918ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAMP ISTIQLAL, Afghanistan (AP) — Sakina, who is 11, maybe 12, walked with her family for 10 days after the Taliban seized her village in northern Afghanistan and burned down the local school. They are now among around 50 families living in a makeshift camp on a rocky patch of land on the edge of the northern city of Mazar-e-Sharif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem donor trial centers on alleged injection fetish...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-trials-4179ed1dc65cfacd248d90d5bd5ca0ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The men Ed Buck lured to his apartment for “party and play” found themselves in a situation of life and death, prosecutors said. Two men enticed by the promise of drugs for sex died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunized but banned: EU says not all shots equal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-lifestyle-health-travel-f678a53270470d9b35ce6259e48548bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — After Dr. Ifeanyi Nsofor and his wife received two doses of AstraZeneca's coronavirus vaccine in Nigeria, they assumed they would be free to travel this summer to a European destination of their choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weisselberg Flip? Indicted CFO Stripped Of Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-organization-removes-indicted-top-finance-officer-allen-weisselberg-from-leadership-roles-at-dozens-of-subsidiaries/ar-AAM4cMd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The changes were made last week, after a grand jury in Manhattan indicted Weisselberg on 15 felony counts, including grand larceny and tax fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just Say We Won': Revelations from Trump Election Night Tell-All...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/just-say-we-won-7-most-bonkers-revelations-from-trump-election-night-tell-all-i-alone-can-fix-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post has published an excerpt from a new book that reveals many behind-the-scenes details from Trump and the White House on election day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia suburb of DC extends streak as 'Fittest City'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/562549-virginia-suburb-of-dc-extends-streak-as-americas-fittest-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arlington, Va., is the fittest U.S. city for a fourth consecutive year as the Washington, D.C., suburb topped the 2021 list put out by the American College of Sports Medicine and the Anthem Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How About Concierge for Spiritual Life?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/13/how-about-a-concierge-for-your-spiritual-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jardine apartments in Los Angeles have all the trappings of luxury living in 2021: touch-less elevators, a rooftop gym and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says 'drove away' American warship in South Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-says-drove-away-us-warship-schina-sea-2021-07-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's military said it "drove away" a U.S. warship that illegally entered Chinese waters near the Paracel Islands on Monday, the anniversary of an international court ruling that held Beijing had no claim over the South China Sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX gov vows to arrest Dems who fled state to block voting bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/greg-abbott-fleeing-texas-democrats-will-arrested-return-state-1609070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican said he would call "special session after special session after special session" until the next election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wellness Resorts Eye Treatments as New Moneymaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/long-covid-treatments-crop-up-at-luxury-wellness-resorts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wellness Resorts Eye Long Covid Treatments as New Moneymaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires in 10 states...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-fires-environment-and-nature-wildfires-92bec84b0705a4b16312fb52d6e8b5c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Wildfires that torched homes and forced thousands to evacuate burned across 10 parched Western states on Tuesday, and the largest, in Oregon, threatened California's power supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene editing 'blocks transmission'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210713-gene-editing-blocks-virus-transmission-in-human-cells</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gene editing 'blocks virus transmission' in human cells</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weisselberg removed from officer positions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/12/politics/weisselberg-trump-organization-removed-officer-subsidiaries/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Organization has removed Allen Weisselberg, its chief financial officer, from officer positions at several of its subsidiaries, including Mar-a-Lago, after he and former President Donald Trump's namesake business were indicted for allegedly running a 15-year tax fraud scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California faces power shortage as electric lines threatened...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-faces-power-shortage-fires-165813981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's energy operator issued a third Flex Alert in four days, attributing it to 'extraordinary conditions' due to record-breaking heat and fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maui median home price: $1.1M...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prices-f2921e8917a2dcc329801472ea4b2f34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAILUKU, Hawaii (AP) — The highest median price for a single-family home in Hawaii last month was in Maui County at more than $1.1 million. While Kauai has been seeing the highest median statewide price in recent months, Maui County went higher in June because of a large volume of luxury home sales and low inventory, The Maui News reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns against 'outside interference'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tellerreport.com/news/2021-07-12-russian-foreign-ministry-considers-outside-interference-in-cuba-s-affairs-unacceptable.rJ28WsF6_.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tellerreport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow is closely following the development of the situation in Cuba and considers it unacceptable for outside interference, said Russian Foreign Ministry spokeswoman Maria Zakharova.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compounding woes fuel discontent...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/how-cuba-e2-80-99s-compounding-woes-have-fueled-discontent/ar-AAM4bT2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 has exacerbated Cuba's economic problem, and social media has opened new channels for dissent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAX REQUIRED FOR BARS, RESTURANTS, PLANES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9780733/Covid-France-Three-days-opening-nightclubs-President-Macron-announce-new-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron announced tonight here would be 'compulsory vaccinations' for those working with 'fragile people,' such as the elderly and the disabled, in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast music banned in South Korean gyms...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9780715/Fast-music-banned-gyms-treadmills-limited-4mph-new-South-Korean-Covid-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Korea has added a requirement that gyms do not play music with higher than 120 beats per minute (bpm) during group exercises such as aerobics and spinning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREEDOM PUSH FOILED:  Police patrol Havana in large numbers after rare protests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/cuba-protests-3772cca0298adac7ce8947ff3aac48c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA (AP) — Large contingents of Cuban police patrolled the capital of Havana on Monday following rare protests around the island nation against food shortages and high prices amid the coronavirus crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radio host Larry Elder enters California recall election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-entertainment-health-government-and-politics-arts-and-entertainment-e15a9503875b1fc406e582eb6e5f82c9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Conservative radio talk show host Larry Elder entered California’s Sept. 14 recall election on Monday, bringing a well-known voice on the political right to a muddled Republican field trying to oust first-term Democratic Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mel Gibson Salutes Donald at UFC...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3270334/mel-gibson-salutes-donald-trump-ufc-264-hollywood-maga/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOLLYWOOD actor Mel Gibson saluted former President Donald Trump when they crossed paths at Saturday’s MMA fight. The moment unfolded as Trump walked by and waved to the crowd at UFC 264, fla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed-up BURGER KING staff write 'we all QUIT' on restaurant sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3270219/burger-king-employees-quit-sign-nebraska/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SIGN at a Burger King reading “we all quit” has gone viral after fed-up employees walked out with a very public goodbye. Former employees said they were unhappy with upper management …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. commander in Afghanistan steps down, marking symbolic end to 20 year war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/top-us-commander-in-afghanistan-to-step-down-monday-marking-a-symbolic-end-to-20-years-of-war/ar-AAM2TZn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden said last week that the military withdrawal he ordered will be complete Aug. 31, but virtually all other troops, contractors and equipment already have exited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds suspected mastermind of Haiti presidential assassination plot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mystery-surrounds-suspected-mastermind-of-haiti-presidential-assassination-plot/ar-AAM36z1?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Haitian man arrested under suspicion of playing a leading role in the killing of Jovenel Moïse appears to have presented himself as a potential leader of the impoverished Caribbean nation for as long as a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Miami condo building being evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/another-miami-condo-building-is-being-evacuated-as-inspections-continue/ar-AALYXkT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apparent structural problems at a Miami Beach condo building are the latest findings to emerge from city-wide building inspections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO raunchy 'F-BOY ISLAND' dating show pushes new limits...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-videos/fboy-island-trailer-1234980747/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because, of course you want to see what something called FBoy Island looks like. Below is the first trailer for the upcoming HBO Max dating series, where three single women try to find love among 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans push to ban 'discrimination' against unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/republicans-coronavirus-vaccines-discrimination-law-states-533503fb-fa83-43d0-bd51-2d614483d241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislation around the country would protect the civil rights of people who refuse to be vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Rapper Shot Dead While Streaming on INSTAGRAM Live...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2021/07/11/indian-red-boy-fatally-shot-instagram-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Indian Red Boy was shot and killed in Hawthorne, California, as he streamed the video on Instagram Live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Former U.S. drug agency informant arrested in Haiti assassination...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/american-arrested-haitian-presidents-killing-had-us-law-enforcement-ties-source-2021-07-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the Haitian-American men arrested on suspicion of taking part in the assassination of Haiti's president last week had been an informant to the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration, a DEA official said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Bill Gates was 'total a**hole' at Sun Valley...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/12/bill-gates-was-a-total-a-hole-at-sun-valley-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates managed an appearance last week at Allen &amp; Co.’s “summer camp for billionaires” in Sun Valley, Idaho — but he wasn’t exactly a barrel of fun.  After flyi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial bias reports threaten med school accreditation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/education-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-school-accreditation-d4da4e36d3f410f4f6f7faee5ec9bf60</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Associated Press (AP) — Allegations of racial discrimination in the Tulane University School of Medicine's Graduate Medical Education program have prompted an accrediting organization to put the school on probation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNET CUTOFF...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-technology-cuba-ca1ae7975e04481e8cbd56d62a7fb30e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cubans facing the country’s worst economic crisis in decades took to the streets over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT:  Pesticide caused kids' brain damage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-science-health-environment-and-nature-lawsuits-e032c7516dcf1404ad3f0b75e09bf743</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — Lawsuits filed Monday in California seek potential class-action damages from Dow Chemical and its successor company over a widely used bug killer linked to brain damage in children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS' Semi-Secret Internet Surveillance Apparatus...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/12/the-usps-semi-secret-internet-surveillance-apparatus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency best known for delivering mail has a side hustle in online snooping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do People Want Their Pre-Pandemic Freedom Back?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/12/do-people-want-their-pre-pandemic-freedom-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polling finds wide support for draconian lockdowns and permanent restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Ever Orthodox Jew Drafted In MLB History...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/07/12/jacob-steinmetz-first-orthodox-jewish-player-drafted-mlb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Long Island native made history on Monday when he was drafted by the Arizona Diamondbacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News cameraman dies after attack by far-right mob protesting LGBTQ march...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/12/news-cameraman-dies-after-attack-by-far-right-mob-protesting-lgbtq-march/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexander Lashkarav, 37, who worked for the independent station TV Pirveli, was found dead in his bed early Sunday after his violent beatdown in the former Soviet Republic’s capital city of T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosby planning comeback...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/bill-cosby-now-a-free-man-wants-to-do-a-standup-act-again-in-u-s-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela security forces 'threaten' Guaido...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/venezuelan-security-forces-attempt-detain-guaido-wife-rosales-says-2021-07-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido said on Monday that security forces had "threatened" him with arrest at his apartment building, and an opposition spokesman said a close Guaido ally had been arrested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Dems flee state to stop elections bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/12/texas-elections-bill-499288</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic state legislators are trying to prevent Republicans from passing a bill that tightens ballot access during a special session that began last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt spy boss claims USA agreed to jail American activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/12/egypt-spy-boss-jail-american-498983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICO obtained a copy of the alleged agreement, which surfaced as the Biden administration weighs reducing military aid to Cairo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN SUPPORTS LOCAL VAX ORDERS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jen-psaki-announces-biden-will-support-local-vaccine-mandates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day after Dr. Anthony Fauci called for vaccine mandates on the local level, the White House is stating that it will support municipalities who choose to enact them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACRON MANDATES 'HEALTH PASS'</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/more/news/emmanuel-macron-covid-health-pass-mandatory-1235017731/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France president Emmanuel Macron has announced new health rules to contain the spread of the Delta variant of COVID-19. The country is currently hosting the Cannes Film Festival with several thousa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER, health officials at odds over booster...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/07/12/covid-vaccine-variant-masks-delta-pfizer-booster/7932182002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. averaged about 19,455 new cases per day over the last seven days, a 47.5% increase from the previous week. Latest COVID-19 news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edwin Edwards dead at 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/article_6c91c6a0-2bf2-11e9-b57a-0f28036ae840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He dominated state politics for 25 years with bayou charm, razor-sharp mind, quick wit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA expected to announce new J&amp;J warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-expected-to-announce-new-warning-on-johnson-johnson-vaccine-related-to-rare-autoimmune-disorder/ar-AAM3XFX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 100 preliminary reports of Guillain-Barré have been detected after 12.8 million doses of Johnson &amp; Johnson vaccine were administered, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
