<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii-Based F-22s Scrambled On FAA Request But Nobody Will Say Why...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41089/hawaii-based-f-22s-scrambled-on-faas-request-but-nobody-will-say-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alert mission was described as an "irregular patrol" with no indication of what prompted it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Dems press leaders for reparations vote this month...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/558412-black-democrats-press-leaders-for-reparations-vote-this-month</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black Democrats are pressing hard on party leaders to stage a reparations vote this month, citing the 100th anniversary of the Tulsa Race Massacre as impetus for Congress to launch a study into the delicate question of whether the count</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Bubbliest Housing Markets Flash '08 Style Warnings...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/world-most-bubbly-housing-markets-010023819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Real estate prices around the world are flashing the kind of bubble warnings that haven’t been seen since the run up to the 2008 financial crisis, according to Bloomberg Economics.New Zealand, Canada and Sweden rank as the world’s frothiest housing markets, based on the key indicators used in the Bloomberg Economics dashboard. The U.K. and the U.S. are also near the top of the risk rankings.“A cocktail of ingredients is sending house prices to unprecedented levels worldwide,” econ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distorted, Bizarre Food Smells Haunt Survivors...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/15/distorted-bizarre-food-smells-haunt-covid-survivors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marcel Kuttab first sensed something was awry while brushing her teeth a year ago, several months after recovering from Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu plots comeback  -- even before new government is sworn in!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/netanyahu-plots-comeback-even-before-new-government-sworn-in/ar-AAL16C3?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu, unseated after a bruising, two-year battle to hold on to his job, is already plotting a comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Says He Will Block Biden From Filling Vacancy?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/mcconnell-says-he-will-block-biden-from-filling-a-supreme-court-vacancy-if-hes-majority-leader/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While his take will likely surprise no one, it's hard to fathom that Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY) just came right out and said it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House starts video series on crumbling infrastructure in Mitch's home state...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/news/politics-government/article252110598.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House Monday launched a series of videos to highlight crumbling infrastructure in Eastern Kentucky as part of a media push to drum up support for President Joe Biden’s proposed infrastructure bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice official resigning amid uproar over Dems' subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/justice-official-demers-resigning-secretly-seized-records-e9fd00c31fc53f827a8921f551b4008e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department will tighten its rules around obtaining records from members of Congress, Attorney General Merrick Garland said Monday, amid revelations the department under former President Donald Trump had secretly seized records from Democrats and members of the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN GENEVA</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/biden-putin-agree-relations-abysmal-120029451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden and Putin agree the nations' relationship is at a low point before their summit. Trump sends the ex-KGB chief 'warmest regards.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis' much-touted Florida EVerify immigration law snares no one...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desantis-e2-80-99-much-touted-florida-everify-immigration-law-snares-no-one/ar-AAL1ZzB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TALLAHASSEE, Fla. – Private employers in Florida have been required to use E-Verify, a federal system for checking the legal status of a potential hire, since the start of the year. But there have been no complaints made to the state agency in charge of enforcing the law in the five and a half months it’s been in effect. A Department of Economic Opportunity spokeswoman told the Orlando ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power grid strained again; Residents asked to reduce use...</title>
      <link>https://www.kxan.com/news/texas/ercot-conservation-alert-texans-asked-to-reduce-electric-use-on-monday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kxan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday afternoon data from ERCOT indicates forecasted demand may exceed capacity during peak heat hours in the afternoon, although the council has not yet listed this as the reason for the alert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mall owner with more than 100 properties files for bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/14/business/washington-prime-group-mall-bankruptcy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Prime Group, a major mall owner of more than 100 locations across the United States, filed for bankruptcy, citing pandemic-related shutdowns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To return to normal, we must learn to trust one another again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/return-post-covid-normal-must-120015717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is set for a full reopening on June 15, but experts say a full recovery is dependent on trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  CNN anchor Christiane Amanpour reveals cancer diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/14/media/christiane-amanpour-ovarian-cancer/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN's chief international anchor Christiane Amanpour told viewers Monday that she has been diagnosed with ovarian cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tudor Jones says bet heavily on every inflation trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/14/paul-tudor-jones-says-bet-heavily-on-every-inflation-trade-if-fed-keeps-ignoring-higher-prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund manager Paul Tudor Jones told CNBC he would "probably buy commodities, buy crypto, buy gold" if the Fed shrugs off inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With no lifeguards, many pools closed, restrict hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pandemic-summer-travel-vacations-pools-concerts-ab753bea-a076-49b4-9fd3-cc2c13898454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rush back to normalcy is hitting some speed bumps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAT MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_heat.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Lead To 'Alzheimer's-Like Condition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-alzheimers-dementia-cleveland-clinic-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the Cleveland Clinic say there is an overlap between COVID-19 and brain changes often seen in Alzheimer's patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could cause 'environmental nightmare'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/video-shows-flames-engulfing-chemical-plant-northern-illinois-n1270729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evacuations were ordered near the plant, owned by Chemtool Inc., which produces greases, lubricants, metal working fluids and cleaners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive chemical fire in Illinois prompts evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/14/us/illinois-industrial-fire/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents were ordered to evacuate their homes after a chemical fire broke out Monday morning at the Chemtool Inc. plant in Rockton, Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defector slams 'woke' US schools: Even NKorea not this nuts...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/14/north-korean-defector-slams-woke-us-schools/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Korean defector who attended Columbia said even the regime she grew up in “was not this nuts” after she got a taste of “woke” indoctrination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA suspends import of canines from 113 countries...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210614175001-25uec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-DOGS:U.S. CDC to suspend import of dogs from more than 100 countries over rabies concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad likens Russian crackdown to arresting Capitol rioters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-joe-biden-europe-technology-hacking-b54f2e541877827674a8314782c993cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin, who is to meet President Joe Biden at a summit Wednesday, has suggested that the hundreds of people arrested for rioting at the U.S. Capitol are being subjected to “persecution for political opinions.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600,000 DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-covid-19-deaths-cross-painful-600000-milestone-country-reopens-2021-06-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has now lost over 600,000 mothers, fathers, children, siblings and friends to COVID-19, a painful reminder that death, sickness and grief continue even as the country begins to return to something resembling pre-pandemic normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Health Benefits of Coffee...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/14/the-health-benefits-of-coffee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans sure love their coffee. Even last spring when the pandemic shut down New York, nearly every neighborhood shop that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient in medical crisis steals ambulance to drive himself to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-ambulance-stolen-20210614-xmvjmfzdhngspg4ntyelzge3ba-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 38-year-old man experiencing a medical crisis tried to drive himself to a hospital in a Baltimore City Fire Department ambulance from Cherry Hill early Monday, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugs suspected in case of Fort Bragg soldiers found dead in barracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/2021/06/14/drugs-suspected-in-case-of-two-fort-bragg-soldiers-found-dead-in-barracks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“At this point in the investigation we do have credible information that the soldiers were involved with illicit drugs,” a CID official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Adams firm leader in NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/14/eric-adams-leads-nyc-mayoral-race-poll-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Borough President Eric Adams is in the lead in the crowded Democratic primary for mayor, with a seven-point edge over former Sanitation Commissioner Kathryn Garcia, according to a new poll…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Des Moines water use reduction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/des-moines-water-use-business-environment-and-nature-551c111b61372c48123d6e0ce93bb604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Officials at the public water system for the city of Des Moines on Monday asked customers to begin using water wisely and cut lawn irrigation by 25% as water usage reached new highs and drought conditions slowed the flow of rivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI warns: QAnon 'digital soldiers' may become violent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/14/politics/fbi-qanon-threat-assessment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI has warned lawmakers that online QAnon conspiracy theorists may carry out more acts of violence as they move from serving as "digital soldiers" to taking action in the real world following the January 6 US Capitol attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Training AI to Read Lips...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvzvdw/tech-companies-are-training-ai-to-read-your-lips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First came facial recognition. Now, an early form of lip-reading AI is being deployed in hospitals, power plants, public transportation, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ wants its reporters to pay to use their own reporting in books...</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2021/06/bad-blood-the-wall-street-journal-apparently-wants-its-reporters-to-pay-to-use-their-own-reporting-in-books/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And to get permission before even talking to a book agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears reach fever pitch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/14/americans-inflation-fears-reach-a-new-high-after-consumer-prices-jump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid fears of rising rents and home prices, Americans expect the inflation rate will be up to 4% one year from now and at 3.6% three years from now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gangs That Steal Puppies...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/pkbk5g/the-gangs-that-steal-your-puppies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch VICE's new documentary about the huge surge in dog-related crime over the last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monica Lewinsky Inks Producing Deal With 20th TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/monica-lewinsky-inks-producing-deal-with-20th-tv-exclusive-1234967358/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Lewinsky has found her own Alt Ending. 20th Television has signed the Vanity Fair contributing editor and her aptly named production company to a first look producing deal. The news comes as…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson postpones 'freedom day' as cases climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/14/uks-boris-johnson-to-extend-covid-19-restrictions-in-england-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson on Monday announced a delay to the next phase of England's reopening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NSA contractor Reality Winner released from prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/reality-winner-former-nsa-contractor-released-from-prison-2021-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bureau of Prisons records showed that Reality Winner was being housed at a residential-reentry facility in San Antonio, Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOENIX 119&amp;#8457;?</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/us/phoenix/85003/daily-weather-forecast/346935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Know what's coming with AccuWeather's extended daily forecasts for Phoenix, AZ. Up to 90 days of daily highs, lows, and precipitation chances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America giddy with post-pandemic normalcy: Baseball, church, proms, weddings, vacations...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/14/america-giddy-post-pandemic-normalcy-baseball-chur/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuxedo rentals at Men’s Wearhouse are nearing 2019 levels after almost no event business in February, Sam’s Club is selling more party supplies, and librarians in South Carolina are “practically giddy” after lifting mask rules this month and seeing patrons bring children to storytime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Don't be mad at the mirror if you're ugly'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/us-news/3078985/putin-deflects-biden-criticism-slams-us-free-speech-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has deflected criticism from President Joe Biden ahead of their summit this week, insisting: “Don’t be mad at the mirror if you are ugly.” The Russian leader’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fort Bragg soldiers found dead in barracks... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3079540/fort-bragg-army-soldiers-dead-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO soldiers were found dead in their barracks on Friday – and military officials believe they were “involved with illicit drugs.” Spc. Joshua Diamond, 35, and Pfc. Matthew Disney, 20, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most common Covid symptoms have changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3077187/two-most-common-covid-symptoms-changed-delta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE TWO main symptoms of Covid have changed, research shows. For over a year, people have been alert to a new cough, loss of smell and taste and a high temperature. 🔵 Read our coronavirus live blog…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Americans Clueless About Landmarks; 1 In 5 Think Niagara Falls Is In Iceland...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/americans-dont-know-national-landmarks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 35 percent correctly said that Shawnee National Forest is in Illinois, but 18 percent incorrectly thought the landmark is in Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarms of quakes continue to hammer California lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article252101173.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The largest registered 3.2-magnitude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Woman stabbed to death in Atlantic City casino...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-wanted-in-deadly-stabbing-at-atlantic-city-casino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man is wanted in the deadly stabbing of his girlfriend at Atlantic City's Hard Rock Hotel &amp; Casino.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Displays largest naval exercise in Pacific since Cold War...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-displays-largest-naval-exercise-24310008</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian Navy ships were seen hunting an "enemy" submarine in the war games drill, which took place just days before President Vladimir Putin will meet Joe Biden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker shortage spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chamber-commerce-jobs-unemployment-suzanne-clark-0afc58b2-0ad5-41bc-ad94-4f7fa5d45dd1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Look, this is the biggest economic challenge of our time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC TICKER TAPE PARADE FOR HEALTH HEROS</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wcbs880/news/local/nyc-ticker-tape-parade-to-honor-essential-workers-in-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio is following through on a promise he made last year to celebrate the city’s health care heroes and essential workers with a ticker tape parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-proclaimed king of New York in exile: Unwelcome mat remains out for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-donald-trump-six-years-escalator-20210613-dlo4u37b5zh2da7mfy3tmq7pey-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queens-born Trump, the one-time gossip column habitué and tabloid headline maker, remains widely reviled across the city where he was overwhelmingly spurned by his old neighbors last November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rght to be forgotten': Should teens' social posts disappear as they age?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/e2-80-98the-right-to-be-forgotten-e2-80-99-should-teens-e2-80-99-social-media-posts-disappear-as-they-age/ar-AAL1KyA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We don’t want children to say offensive things online,” said Stacey Steinberg, legal skills professor at the University of Florida. “But we also need to figure out what to do once that happens.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien contact could 'end life on Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15265888/alien-contact-end-life-on-earth-scientist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALIEN contact could ultimately “end life on Earth” and we shouldn’t seek to communicate with them as it risks “endangering mankind”, according to experts. Their fears …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem exploring one-time 'patriot tax' on wealth...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/558263-exclusive-democrat-exploring-patriot-tax-on-multimillionaires-wealth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Great 'reckoning' in Southern Baptist Convention about to take place...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/A-great-reckoning-in-the-Southern-Baptist-16246027.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. - More than 16,000 Southern Baptists are gathered here this week for a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World's Priciest Painting Ended Up in Hands of Notorious Killer...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-priciest-painting-ended-hands-080815408.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony Pictures ClassicsWhen treasure-hunting art collectors Alexander Parish and Robert Simon purchased a Salvator Mundi painting from a New Orleans auction house in 2005, they had no idea they were making the veritable find of the century: an apparent work by none other than Leonardo da Vinci. Considering that such a discovery hadn’t happened in almost 100 years, they knew they’d hit the jackpot—provided, of course, they could verify its authenticity. That turned out to be a controversial quest,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson set to postpone 'freedom day' as cases climb...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/covid-19-easing-of-lockdown-restrictions-in-england-to-be-delayed-by-four-weeks-govt-source-12332022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concerns over the Delta variant means remaining restrictions are expected to stay in place until the middle of July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 In 10 Experienced Health 'Self-Awakening' During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/millennials-young-adults-self-awakening-during-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy percent of young adults said that the top lesson they learned in 2020 was to not sweat the small stuff and to just go with the flow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temp checks, 'touchless' mustard: Maddening persistence of 'hygiene theater'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Temp-checks-digital-menus-and-touchless-16245903.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At an ice cream shop in Rockville, Md., gloved servers scoop the frozen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jailed American's parents want President to stand up for son...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/14/politics/biden-putin-summit-trevor-reed-plea/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The parents of Trevor Reed, a former US Marine imprisoned in Russia, are pleading with Presidents Joe Biden and Vladimir Putin to work out a deal at their summit on Wednesday to send him home to Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with 39 wives, head of 'world's largest family', dies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210614103003-oae5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIA-FAMILY/ (PIX):Man with 39 wives, head of 'world's largest family', dies in India</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summit stirs memories of Reagan-Gorbachev meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210614-geneva-summit-stirs-memories-of-1985-reagan-gorbachev-meet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Geneva summit stirs memories of 1985 Reagan-Gorbachev meet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Putting Last Remaining House on Market...</title>
      <link>https://ph.news.yahoo.com/elon-musk-says-hes-putting-last-remaining-house-on-the-market-110455428.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ph.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk tweeted that he’s decided to sell his last remaining house a week after a report said he and others billionaires paid little or no income taxes for several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take condoms home: Social distancing and sex in Olympic village...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210614001346-b0ege</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tokyo Olympic organisers plan to give away about 150,000 condoms to raise awareness of HIV/AIDS, not to use at the games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turned Over Info on White House Counsel...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/06/13/1006076590/trump-justice-department-subpoenaed-apple-for-info-on-former-white-house-counsel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The secret DOJ subpoena sought account information for Don McGahn as well as his wife. It is unclear what the department was investigating or whether prosecutors obtained any account information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In World's Worst Vax Line, Wait Lasts Hours and Gets You Nothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-world-e2-80-99s-worst-vaccine-line-the-wait-lasts-hours-and-gets-you-nothing/ar-AAL1dLA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elderly Venezuelans wake up in the middle of the night and rush into downtown Caracas to get in line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Dre, Jimmy Iovine to launch 'coolest high school in America'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dr-dre-jimmy-iovine-to-launch-what-could-be-the-coolest-high-school-in-america/ar-AAL1wsi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new magnet high school will be based at Audubon Middle School. The campus in Leimert Park has experienced a sharp enrollment decline, as have nearby high schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials deny knowledge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-justice-department-officials-sessions-barr-and-rosenstein-all-deny-knowledge-of-secret-subpoenas-targeting-democratic-lawmakers/ar-AAKZHH1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two attorney generals and a deputy attorney general said they did not know the phone records of Democratic lawmakers critical of Trump being seized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida city accidentally sells its water tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/florida-city-accidentally-sells-its-water-tower/article_3c5f2062-7009-5c31-8ba3-289152baa504.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKSVILLE, Fla. — The scenic city of Brooksville may not have a Brooklyn Bridge to sell. But recently — and accidentally — the city sold its water tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ watchdog will probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/11/schiff-calls-for-probe-into-trump-doj-seizing-house-democrats-data-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps. Schiff and Eric Swalwell, whose records were both reportedly seized by Trump's Justice Department, had called on the DOJ inspector general to investigate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Take on Christchurch Massacre Provokes Anger in New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/14/hollywood-take-on-christchurch-massacre-provokes-anger-in-new-zealand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCKLAND, New Zealand — A planned Hollywood film about the Christchurch mosque massacre has drawn a sharp backlash in New</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Battle Against Virus Wanes, Mayors Confront New Challenge: Crime...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/14/as-battle-against-virus-wanes-mayors-confront-a-new-challenge-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — Mayors of American cities have yearned for the moment they could usher in a return to normalcy, casting</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
