<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>State of emergency declared in Hawaii, forecasters warn of 'catastrophic' flooding...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/12/06/hawaii-blizzard-warning-canceled-flooding-looms/8889082002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A powerful storm system is pounding Hawaii with heavy rain, and forecasters warn about the chance for "dangerous" and "catastrophic" flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower details 'dysfunctional' Afghan evacuation that ignored pleas of thousands...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/british-whistleblower-details-chaotic-and-dysfunctional-afghanistan-evacuation-that-ignored-the-pleas-of-thousands/ar-AARyX2F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron Raises Vax Questions Year After First PFIZER Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/omicron-raises-vaccine-questions-a-year-after-first-pfizer-shot/ar-AARyCLw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On web and streets, Covid protests get nasty...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211207-on-the-web-and-on-the-streets-covid-protests-get-nasty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A call is out on Telegram for people opposing Covid restrictions to share private addresses of German "local MPs, politicians and other personalities" who they believe are "seeking to destroy" them t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general warns of emerging youth mental health crisis in rare public advisory...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/surgeon-general-warns-emerging-youth-120015429.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The advisory is to call attention to a "youth mental health crisis" and recommend resources to call on and actions to take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man kills family, then self, over fake vax pass...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211207133354-6f3ta</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-CRIME/ (TV, PIX):Man killed family, then self, over faked vaccine pass -German prosecutor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus kills more than all combat deaths in every American war -- combined...</title>
      <link>https://mattlabash.substack.com/p/masked-avenger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mattlabash.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How I learned to stop worrying and love/hate the face diaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom Helped Son Behead Pregnant Sister Before He Posed for Selfie, Police Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/man-in-maharashtra-honor-killing-beheads-pregnant-sister-with-a-sickle-while-mother-holds-her-down</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 19-year-old victim was reportedly attacked for marrying without her family’s consent. Her mother and brother are said to have proudly put her head on display afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Lemon accused of unethical behavior after warning cops didn't believe his account...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10282383/Jussie-Smollett-reveals-CNN-host-Don-Lemon-warned-text-cops-didnt-believe-account.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN host Don Lemon neglected to discuss his alleged meddling in the aftermath of Jussie Smollett's hate crime debacle while reporting on the disgraced star's highly publicized trial Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as trans swimmer finishes race 38 seconds ahead of nearest rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10282301/Transgender-UPenn-swimmer-Lia-Thomas-smashes-records-weekend-meets-14-SECONDS-ahead-rival.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lia Thomas, 22, smashed two U.S. swimming records at an Akron, Ohio contest. Thomas won the 1,650 freestyle in a record time of 15:59.71 beating her closest rival Anna Sofia Kalandaze by 38 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Fewer Republicans trust doctor's advice...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/357821/republicans-less-trusting-doctor-advice-past.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer Republicans today than in 2010 say they are confident in the accuracy of their doctor's advice. Democrats' trust has steadily grown since 2002.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: VIOLENT CRIME SHAKES LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/brutal-brazen-crimes-shake-la-leaving-city-at-a-crossroads/ar-AARsCHd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lizard people, deadly orgies, JFK: How QANON hijacked Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-12-07/how-qanon-has-hijacked-hollywood-movies-for-conspiracy-theories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of Q's story lines, including evil lizard aliens and a cabal of pedophiles, are pulled from films and television shows. Screenwriters are not happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks Drugs, Aging In Wide-Ranging Interview...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/elon-musk-talks-brain-chips-021423848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elon Musk, the CEO of Tesla Inc. and SpaceX, said that President Joe Biden’s “Build Back Better” bill, which includes federal funding for electric vehicle charging stations, should be canned because it would add to the country’s deficit. Most Read from BloombergThe World’s Relentless Demand for Chips Turns Deadly in MalaysiaSand and Soldiers Mix as Troops Move In to Protect Cancun TouristsEven in the Metaverse, Not All Identities Are Created EqualAutomating the War on Noise Pollut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of era: Merkel bows out after 16 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-migration-germany-7469fae14c71f1605eaf291f161be86d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Angela Merkel was assured of a place in the history books as soon as she became Germany's first female chancellor on Nov. 22, 2005. Over the next 16 years, she was credited with raising Germany's profile and influence, working to hold a fractious European Union together, managing a string of crises and being a role model for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN CEO latest airline chief to exit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-texas-scott-kirby-doug-parker-robert-isom-bda78ab3a2a4138d0e668bf8993b32d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DALLAS (AP) — American Airlines CEO Doug Parker will retire in March and be replaced by its current president, Robert Isom, as the airline seeks to rebuild after massive losses caused by the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$92,000 flying car reaches 63MPH...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/new-flying-car-goes-63-mph-20-minutes-costs-92000-2021-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you've always dreamed of flying to work, that dream may soon be a reality. Jetson One aims to make flying possible for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK: BRAIN CHIPS IN HUMANS 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/elon-musk-neuralink-hopes-to-start-human-testing-2022-2021-12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk said Monday that the first humans to get Neuralink chips would be people with severe spinal cord injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Face Is Your Boarding Pass...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/07/your-face-is-or-will-be-your-boarding-pass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If it’s been a year or more since you traveled, particularly internationally, you may notice something different at airports in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Drivers Can Now Play Video Games Even With Car Moving...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/07/tesla-drivers-can-now-play-video-games-even-with-car-moving/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not long after buying a Tesla Model 3 this summer, Vince Patton saw a YouTube clip highlighting a feature that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Followers? For Book Sales, 'It's Unreliable'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/07/millions-of-followers-for-book-sales-its-unreliable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A book by Billie Eilish seemed like a great bet. One of the most famous pop stars in the world,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Sheriff Who Wants to Put Andrew Cuomo Behind Bars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/07/meet-the-sheriff-who-wants-to-put-andrew-cuomo-behind-bars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A decade ago, in the midst of what would become a successful campaign to become county sheriff, a potentially devastating</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advocates push nationwide movement for land return to Blacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Advocates-push-nationwide-movement-for-land-16679138.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANHATTAN BEACH, Calif. - A Black family's successful fight to reclaim a picturesque...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Ghislaine trial, fight over huge cache of photos of naked women...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/at-ghislaine-maxwell-trial-a-fight-over-huge-cache-of-photos-of-naked-or-semi/article_db5c5877-8804-5e17-a680-e3dad1729d30.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — FBI agents found a cache of thick black binders — all labeled with names — that contain hundreds of naked or semi-naked photographs on CDs that Epstein</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires' share of global wealth soars during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/billionaires-share-global-wealth-soars-093440535.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The share of global wealth of the world's richest people soared at a record pace during the Covid pandemic, a report on inequality showed Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WARNS PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-sports-business-jen-psaki-vladimir-putin-3c17d207917eb90adeac03d5ccb31268</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is ready to warn Vladimir Putin during a video call Tuesday that Russia will face economy-jarring sanctions if it invades neighboring Ukraine as the U.S. president seeks a diplomatic solution to deal with the tens of thousands of Russian troops massed near the Ukraine border .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Biden calls Putin, threat of Russian invasion of Ukraine mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/as-biden-calls-putin-threat-of-russian-invasion-of-ukraine-mounts/ar-AARxMb9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China threatens USA over boycott of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/07/china/china-response-us-olympic-boycott-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has threatened the Biden administration with retaliation over its decision to impose a diplomatic boycott of the 2022 Winter Olympics in Beijing, warning the move could harm bilateral relations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock to Crypto Daredevils Joins List of Scary Market Omens...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/shock-crypto-daredevils-joins-list-160000897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A brutal bout of selling that wiped billions of dollars from profitless growth companies, IPO stocks and SPACs has now caught up with Bitcoin, further stressing risk tolerances and brokerage balances among small-time traders.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female FoundersAutomating the War on Noise Pollution‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsEven in the Metaverse, Not All Identities Are Created EqualMeet the New Climate Refugee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Ex-anchor to sue over contract...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/06/chris-cuomo-prepping-to-sue-cnn-over-his-reported-6m-a-year-contract/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Cuomo has hired lawyers and is preparing to file suit against CNN if it doesn’t honor the remainder of the four-year contract he signed last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC First-In-Nation Jab Mandate For PRIVATE Companies...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/12/06/nyc-vaccine-mandate-private-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City previously imposed vaccine mandates for city workers, but this would be the first in the nation for private employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nunes Quits Congress to Take Over Trump Media Company...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/devin-nunes-will-quit-the-house-to-take-over-trumps-media-company/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Representative Devin Nunes, a California Republican who emerged as one of former President Donald J. Trump’s most loyal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian Woman: Police Came To My Door And Took Me To Quarantine Camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/12/04/australian_woman_police_came_to_my_door_and_took_me_to_covid_quarantine_camp_told_me_you_have_no_choice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNHERD: Hayley Hodgson, 26, moved to Darwin from Melbourne to escape the never-ending lockdowns -- only to find herself locked up in a Covid Internment Camp without even having the virus. She's just returned from a 14-day detention at Howard Springs, the 2000-capacity Covid camp outside Darwin to which regional Covid cases are transported by the authorities. In an exclusive interview with Freddie Sayers, she recounted her experiences. Hodgson tells the story of uniformed police officers coming to her residence and taking her away: HAYLEY HODGSON: The police officers blocked my driveway, I walked out and I said, "What's going on, are you guys testing me for COVID? What's happening?"  They said, "No, you're getting taken away, and you have no choice. You're going to Howard Springs. You either come with us now, and we'll put you in the back of the divvy van. Or you can have the choice to get a 'COVID cab.'" So of course I chose the COVID cab. Because they said, "Well, if we're to take you, we're going to hand you a $5,000 fine." So of course, I didn't want that to happen. So I just said, "Look, I don't consent to this. I don't understand why I can't just self-isolate at home, like a lot of other people are doing." And they just said, "We've just been told from higher up where to take you. And that is all there is." Full interview:  (via UnHerd)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Does he believe his own BS?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/donald-trump/1007666/the-nagging-mystery-of-trumps-bs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do Trumpy Republicans believe their own bulls--t? Or is it all performance? Or can they even tell the difference anymore?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dole's final column: 'Too many of us have sacrificed too much'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sen-bob-doles-final-column-215240459.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Written weeks before his death, the former senator reflects on his Kansas roots, his sacrifices, bipartisan achievements and rancor in politics today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Lemon accuser says network is 'predator protecting machine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/don-lemon-accuser-predator-protecting-machine-some-accountability-cuomo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dustin Hice who accused CNN host Don Lemon of a sexually charged assault said the liberal network is "a predator protecting machine" but he’s happy to see accountability with the dismissal of Chris Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury rules in favor of Craig Wright, who claimed to invent bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/06/miami-jury-rules-in-favor-of-craig-wright-bitcoin-claimed-inventor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian computer scientist Craig Wright, who claims to be Satoshi Nakamoto, prevails in Miami court case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'VERITAS' hires first lobbyist after FBI raids...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/project-veritas-fbi-raids-lobbyist-paoletta-67f1d793-a790-4ee2-b7e6-238f6bfdf505.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Project Veritas has retained former senior Trump administration official Mark Paoletta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to head Trump social media platform...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/06/nunes-to-retire-after-midterms-plans-to-head-trump-social-media-platform/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Devin Nunes, a key ally of former President Donald Trump, will not run for re-election in 2022, a source with knowledge of his plans confirmed to The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  12 UFOs 'flying in formation'; Pilot exclaims 'weird s**t'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4216774/video-12-ufos-flying-formation-pilot-south-china-sea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A VIDEO shot from an airliner cockpit has emerged showing what appears to be a fleet of 12 UFOs flying in formation. The pilot who shot the footage can be heard reacting in astonishment to the eeri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zemmour put in headlock by protester at rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Far-right-French-presidential-candidate-put-in-16678328.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right provocateur Éric Zemmour was placed in a headlock by a protester at his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamikaze drones: New weapon brings power, peril to U.S. military...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/military/kamikaze-drones-new-weapon-brings-power-peril-u-s-military-n1285415</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some experts believe the spread of low-cost, light-weight "killer" drones will change ground warfare as profoundly as the machine gun did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lula, Brazil's popular ex-president, battles for political comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20211206-lula-brazil-s-popular-ex-president-battles-for-2022-political-comeback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva, Brazil’s president from 2002 to 2010, embarked upon a triumphant European tour worthy of a head of state in November. Cleared of corruption charges by Brazil's Supreme Cour…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron provides another excuse for govt meddling...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/584464-the-omicron-variant-is-another-excuse-for-government-meddling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time to demand the freedom for people, and the businesses that serve them, to determine for themselves which health precautions they would like to take and which hassles they’d rather avoid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy be damned, Chappelle to open NETFLIX comedy festival...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/controversy-damned-dave-chappelle-open-195127920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dave Chappelle is among the 130 comedians tapped for the Netflix Is a Joke comedy festival, which will take place in venues across L.A. next spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quits SIRIUSXM...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/06/chris-cuomo-quits-siriusxm-show-following-sexual-misconduct-claim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fired CNN host Chris Cuomo announced Monday that he has quit his SiriusXM radio show in the wake of a sexual misconduct allegation involving a past gig at ABC. Cuomo, in a tweet posted after f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator Says Dems 'Have Votes' for 2nd Amendment Crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/senator-says-dems-have-the-votes-for-new-gun-laws-its-just-the-number-of-votes-needed-is-more-than-they-have/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Chris Murphy sat down with CNN’s Jake Tapper on Sunday to talk about gun control, and said that Democrats would have the votes for passing legislation if it weren’t for the fact that they don’t. In light of the horrific school shooting at Oxford High School in Michigan, Tapper spoke to Murphy about what […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist behind vaccine says next pandemic may be worse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-europe-pandemics-f99f44ae772d92a888b00ed6413843d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — One of the scientists behind the Oxford-AstraZeneca COVID-19 vaccine is warning that the next pandemic may be more contagious and more lethal unless more money is devoted to research and preparations to fight emerging viral threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to close nightclubs, mask students...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20211206-france-to-close-nightclubs-extend-use-of-face-masks-in-schools-amid-covid-19-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nightclubs in France will be ordered to close for four weeks starting this weekend to counter surging Covid-19 cases that have seen hospitals announce emergency protocols as beds fill up, Prime Minis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi warns of 'social unrest' if fossil fuels ditched...</title>
      <link>https://www.ft.com/content/89231064-08d6-49d3-a13e-df8446abfc80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland Approves Assisted 'Suicide Capsule'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/switzerland-approves-assisted-suicide-capsule-140255771.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exit International Switzerland has just legalized a new way to die by assisted suicide. The country’s medical review board has just given authorization for use of the Sarco Suicide Pod, which is a 3-D-printed portable coffin-like capsule with windows that can be transported to a tranquil place for a person’s final moments of life. Conventional assisted-suicide methods have generally involved a chemical substance. Inventor Philip Nitschke of Exit International told the website SwissInfo.ch that h</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTORS TAKING ON HUGE RISKS...</title>
      <link>https://news.google.com/articles/CBMiP2h0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmZ0LmNvbS9jb250ZW50LzMyZTAwMGNmLWM5NWEtNDk0MC04OTg1LWY2N2NhNjE3MGFlONIBP2h0dHBzOi8vYW1wLmZ0LmNvbS9jb250ZW50LzMyZTAwMGNmLWM5NWEtNDk0MC04OTg1LWY2N2NhNjE3MGFlOA?hl=en-US&amp;gl=US&amp;ceid=US%3Aen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Derby Winner Medina Spirit Dies During Workout...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/06/medina-spirit-kentucky-derby-winner-failed-drug-test-dies-workout-santa-anita-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medina Spirit reportedly died suddenly while on the track. The 3-year-old throughbred won the Kentucky Derby in May, came in second in the Breeders’ Cup Classic and third in the Preakness Stakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIAGRA cuts risk of Alzheimer's by 69%...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4216281/viagra-cuts-risk-alzheimers-prescribed-beat-dementia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAKING Viagra slashes Alzheimer’s risk by two-thirds, research suggests. Scientists claim the love drug may help boost brain health and cut levels of toxic proteins that trigger dementia. Experts a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media venture under scrutiny by market regulators...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-elections-media-social-media-donald-trump-ba09954162b8309419134d7e2488a52e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Regulators are looking into the deal that would bring Donald Trump's new social media company to the stock market, one that has attracted both legions of fans of the former president and people looking to make a quick profit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tapper to get Prime Time?</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/jake-tapper-to-replace-chris-cuomo-primetime-cnn-andrew-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell Radar Jake had been pushing for the job behind the scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk accused of manipulating search results to bury whistleblower story...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/economy/musk-accused-of-manipulating-search-results-to-bury-whistleblower-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla founder Elon Musk faces accusations that he used Twitter to obfuscate news that the Securities and Exchange Commission is investigating his company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE ANTI-LOCKDOWN RIOTS SWEEP EUROPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4210241/anti-lockdown-marches-europe-covid-christmas-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-LOCKDOWN riots erupted today in Belgium as protests sweep across Europe over fears Christmas could be cancelled due to Covid. Six people were hospitalised including two police officers while 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second accuser testifies...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211206154013-8n4cy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-GHISLAINE MAXWELL/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Maxwell accuser testifies she had sexual contact with Epstein at 17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Enters Bear Market Following Report of SEC Probe...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-track-enter-bear-market-154538370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc.’s selloff intensified Monday following a report that regulators opened an investigation into the electric-vehicle company, briefly pushing the stock to its biggest four-day decline since March.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female FoundersAutomating the War on Noise PollutionEven in the Metaverse, Not All Identities Are Created Equal‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsMeet the New Climate Refugee in Town: CoyotesThe s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Chaos In The Loop Leads To Shooting, Beatings; 21 Arrested...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/12/05/loop-chaos-arrests-flash-mob-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens flooded the streets near Millennium Park in a similar sight to last summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer at therapy farm dies after rammed by sheep...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-massachusetts-animals-sheep-d62de90ca2125e8ae22e68803994c205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOLTON, Mass. (AP) — A 73-year-old volunteer at a Massachusetts animal therapy farm died over the weekend after she was repeatedly rammed by a sheep, police said. Kim Taylor, of Wellesley, was caring for livestock in a pen alone at about 9 a.m.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
