<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Media Mogul Key Suspect in Venezuela Corruption Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article217285655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Swiss banker who admitted guilt is helping Miami, Florida prosecutors build a criminal case against Raúl Gorrín, owner of the Globovisión network in Caracas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  FERRARI Sells for Record $48.4 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/2018/08/26/rare-ferrari-250-gto-sells-for-record-48-4-million-at-auction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A red 1962 Ferrari 250 GTO sold for $48.4 million on Saturday in California, the most ever paid for a classic car at auction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Anchor Busted for Two Fake 'Scoops' in Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/nolte-cnns-jim-sciutto-busted-for-two-fake-news-scoops-in-one-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief national security correspondent Jim Sciutto has had two big scoops debunked as very fake news in the space of just one week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot-Made Burgers Wow Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2018/08/24/640511068/fad-or-the-future-robot-made-burgers-wow-the-crowds-in-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more culinary robots find their way into commercial food prep, one restaurant in San Francisco called Creator is hoping to strike a balance between high tech and the human touch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels vows to testify before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/stormy-daniels-vows-testify-donald-13139717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The porn star who pulled out of Celebrity Big Brother at the 11th hour reveals what happened on THAT night she met the future US President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALL PREVIEW:  TWITTER Boss Dorsey to Testify Before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/twitter-chief-jack-dorsey-to-testify-before-congress-in-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter chief executive Jack Dorsey will testify before the House Energy and Commerce Committee regarding his company’s censorship practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone Predicts Mueller Will Indict Don Jr...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2018/08/24/roger-stone-donald-trump-jr-mueller-indict-process-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long-time Republican operative Roger Stone predicts special counsel Robert Mueller will soon indict Donald Trump Jr. on a process crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tavis Smiley Stumbling in Lawsuit Over PBS Firing...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/tavis-smiley-stumbling-pbs-lawsuit-1137134</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ousted anchor can't force PBS to hand over internal documents dating back decades and two of his claims have been dismissed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawless London: Fearful residents building barricades around homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/725636/notting-hill-carnival-london-acid-attack-barricades-homes-shops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reactions to passing...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/what-theyre-saying-reactions-to-mccains-passing-a2ed4475-e760-4b3a-9b76-704a507b4d0d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former rivals are remembering him as a patriot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HAPPYTIME' KILLED AT BOXOFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/08/melissa-mccarthy-happytime-murders-crazy-rich-asians-meg-weekend-box-office-1202451694/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;4TH UPDATE, Saturday AM Writethru following Friday 11:46PM: Warner Bros.’ Crazy Rich Asians is flat out doing amazing this weekend with an unprecedented $25M, which is an unbelievable -6% dip…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titan of American politics...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/john-mccain-unbridled-titan-american-politics-004555441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Sidney McCain III had but one employer throughout his iconic and tempestuous career: the United States of America. McCain was a direct descendant, he claimed, of a captain in George Washington's army during the Revolutionary War. McCain ejected, and parachuted into a small lake in the center</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Cameos Caused Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2005/07/31369/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz. Sen. John McCain, R-Ariz., is defending his cameo appearance in “Wedding Crashers,” the sexy comedy the Drudge Report called a “boob raunch fest.” “In Washington, I work with boobs every day,” joked McCain during an appearance on NBC’s “Tonight Show with Jay Leno.” McCain was responding to Leno, who noted Matt […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  Amid betrayals, Trump's barrier breaks down... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Amid-betrayals-Trump-s-barrier-breaks-down-13182773.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's wall of secrecy - the work of a lifetime - is starting to crack. His longtime lawyer, Michael Cohen, pleaded guilty last week to breaking campaign-finance laws, and said he'd arranged hush money payments to two women at Trump's direction. Both a tabloid executive - who had served Trump by snuffing out damaging tales before they went public - and Trump's chief financial officer gave testimony in the case. All three had been part of the small circle of family, longtime aides and trusted associates who have long played crucial roles in Trump's strategy to shield the details of his personal life and business dealings from prying outsiders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama beat McCain by two-to-one electoral college margin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/john-mccain-senate-maverick-arizona-dead-at-81-brain-cancer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, his Senate office said he died at 4:28 p.m. on August 25, surrounded by his wife Cindy and his family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Last of the American heroes'...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/792175/john-mccain-last-american-heroes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The indomitable Arizona senator is dead at 81. We may never see his like again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashed with media...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2007/12/mccain-responds-to-drudge-007499</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John McCain denies that he did legislative favors for a lobbyist, says campaign didn't try to spike story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane's Rains Topple Records, Inundate Parts of Big Island ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Lanes-Rains-Topple-Records-Inundate-Parts-Big-Island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rainfall amounts topped 40</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-45276831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a historic visit to Ireland, Pope Francis reportedly condemns abuse in the Church as "filth".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>35-year political career...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a8ae4ebb24f4fc5b60381e81fae1249/War-hero-and-presidential-candidate-John-McCain-has-died</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sen. John McCain, who faced down his captors in a Vietnam prisoner of war camp with jut-jawed defiance and later turned his rebellious streak into a 35-year poli</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie praises Dem move to limit role of superdelegates...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/403601-sanders-praises-decision-to-limit-role-of-superdelegates-after-2016-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) praised a move by the Democratic National Committee (DNC) on Saturday to limit the role of superdelegates in choosing the party's presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarred but Happy Warrior... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/25/opinion/john-mccain.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He could be frustratingly inconsistent, but he also bucked orthodoxy time and again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiercely independent... </title>
      <link>https://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Politics/2018/0825/Remembering-John-McCain-the-quintessential-patriot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.csmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Monitor reporters share their interactions with and observations on the Arizona senator and his lifetime of service – including his wry humor, famous temper, and bipartisan striving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senator No One Could Ignore...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/view/2018/08/26/john-mccain-the-senator-no-one-could-ignore</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senator No One Could Ignore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
MCCAIN DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/sen-john-mccain-independent-voice-gop-establishment-dies-81-n790971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His family announced that McCain died Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton question shadows Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Clinton-impeachment-question-shadows-Congress-in-13182287.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At the outset of the 1998 impeachment hearings, Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., asked a memorable question that could resonate for some lawmakers today: "Is this Watergate or Peyton Place?" "Peyton Place" was a steamy soap opera from the 1960s, based on a 1950s novel of the same name. The final judgment, based on the outcome of that impeachment process, was that President Bill Clinton's affair with Monica Lewinsky was much more a soap opera than something close to the Watergate scandal that drove President Richard Nixon from the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French vegan fest off menu amid fears of butchers' revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-vegan-fest-off-menu-162822178.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French town of Calais has been no stranger to public disorder in recent years, with recurrent battles between police and migrants or striking ferry workers making headlines across the world. But now the port town is facing a bizarre new threat, according to its council: an alliance of hunters and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNC protesters clash at rally for Confederate statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/counties/orange-county/article217286120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters gathered on the UNC-Chapel Hill campus Saturday morning, five days after the Silent Sam Confederate monument was toppled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.ie/irish-news/pope-francis-in-ireland/pope-francis-speech-was-disgraceful-and-contained-extraordinary-deflection-victims-claim-37251012.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clerical abuse survivor Colm O’Gorman has described the speech by Pope Francis at Dublin Castle as an “incredible missed opportunity”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo and Two Suicides...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/big-hollywood/2018/08/25/anthony-bourdain-jill-messick-metoo-two-suicides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the launch of #MeToo, two people connected to the movement have committed suicide - Anthony Bourdain and Jill Messick.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court strikes down measures on firing federal workers...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/403593-court-strikes-down-trump-orders-on-firing-federal-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Saturday struck down several key provisions in President Trump's executive orders that he signed earlier this year that would have made it easier to fire federal workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Warns Staged 'Chemical Provocation' Coming In Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-25/us-says-assad-will-use-chemical-weapons-idlib-russia-warns-staged-provocation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May approach Harvey's US rainfall record...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/hawaii-may-face-direct-hit-serious-damage-from-hurricane-lane-to-end-this-week/70005829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires and Catastrophic Flooding: Lane's Wrath Continues in Hawaii ...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2018-08-23-hurricane-lane-forecast-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest forecast for this dangerous, rare Hawaii tropical threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Body parts in trash bags on street...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/body-parts-found-trash-bags-side-bronx-street/story?id=57395983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Parks Department worker in New York City happened upon a grisly scene on a sidewalk outside Crotona Park on Friday when he found two black plastic bags with human body parts inside. The two trash bags were discovered Friday afternoon by the parks employee, who initially thought they might contain...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former pastor claims sex abuse against televangelist...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/25/former-pastor-claims-sex-abuse-against-televangelist.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawsuit filed by a former associate pastor at an Ohio megachurch claims televangelist Ernest Angley sexually abused and harassed him over a 10-year period starting in 2004.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-Mexico trade deal could be imminent...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-says-u-mexico-trade-deal-could-imminent-134539518.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump tweeted on Saturday that the United States could reach a "big Trade Agreement" with Mexico imminently. "Our relationship with Mexico is getting closer by the hour. Some really good people within both the new and old government, and all working closely together</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPE UNDER FIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-francis-departs-1st-papal-trip-ireland-071909848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBLIN (AP) — The Latest on Pope Francis' trip to Ireland (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: UNC braces for rally over Confederate statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/25/us/unc-silent-sam-confederate-statue/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citing a volatile mood on its campus, the University of North Carolina is urging people not to participate in a "possible rally" on Saturday in Chapel Hill over the toppling this week of a Confederate monument.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolves helping war vets deal with PTSD...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/24/wolves-are-helping-war-vets-deal-with-ptsd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being thrown to the wolves could be the best therapy session ever for the war vets featured on “Wolves and Warriors.” The Animal Planet series, premiering Saturday (Sept. 1), pairs veterans — many …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence silent...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/24/politics/mike-pence-silent-cohen-manafort/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence is keeping quiet during yet another raucous news week for the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Fed Raises GDP Forecast to 4.6%...</title>
      <link>https://www.streetinsider.com/Fed/Atlanta+Fed+Raises+GDP+Forecast+to+4.6%25/14546182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.streetinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GDPNow model estimate for real GDP growth (seasonally adjusted annual rate) in the third quarter of 2018 is 4.6 percent on August 24, up from 4.3 percent on August 16. After yesterdays releases on new-home sales and costs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates release demands amid 19-day prison strike across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/25/the-resistance-now-prison-strikes-demands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prisoners continue to protest while students target Smith &amp; Wesson in 50-mile gun control march and a survey reveals majority of Americans support Medicare for all</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's Bullard warns of recession risk in raising rates...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-fed-bullard/feds-bullard-warns-of-recession-risk-in-raising-rates-idUSKCN1LA00B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank President James Bullard on Friday raised new alarm bells over the U.S. central bank's plan to keep raising interest rates, warning that even one more rate hike could set the stage for recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As surfers taste the perfect wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-storm-lane-surfing/hurricane-treats-hawaii-surfers-to-a-taste-of-the-perfect-wave-idUSKCN1LA00N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Rozier could not sleep on Thursday night, not because wind and rain from Hurricane Lane was lashing his Hawaii home, but because he was anxious to surf the huge waves rolling into one of his favorite beaches on the Big Island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's Tourism Boom Lifting All Boats, Including Tiny Montenegro...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/europes-tourism-boom-is-lifting-all-boats-including-tiny-montenegro-1535194800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many tourists are descending on Europe this summer and a growing number are looking beyond the continent’s famous destinations to places like Montenegro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of Burning Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/725605/burning-man-festival-worlds-wildest-orgy-pictures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loyalty Tested as Closest Confidants Become Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/25/loyalty-tested-as-trump-s-closest-confidants-become-witnesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revelations that two of Donald Trump’s closest longtime allies have struck cooperation deals shows that federal prosecutors are chipping away at one of the president’s most cherished values: loyalty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: UNC board member calls for Confederate statue to be reinstalled on campus after protesters tear down...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/403573-unc-board-member-calls-for-confederate-statue-to-be-reinstalled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A board member at the University of North Carolina is calling for a Confederate statue to be promptly reinstalled on the Chapel Hill campus after it was toppled by protesters earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Returns to a Country Transformed and a Church in Tatters...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/25/world/europe/pope-francis-ireland.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholics are waiting to see whether the pope will use Ireland as a symbolic stage to announce measures to combat a crisis that threatens the future of his church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS RECORD HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/24/us-stocks-china-trade-talks-end-powell-to-speak-at-jackson-hole.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq Composite reached all-time highs on Friday as Netflix shares rose. The broader market also climbed after the top Federal Reserve official characterized the U.S. economy as "strong."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors inch closer to Trump...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/403546-trump-org-cfos-immunity-deal-is-new-problem-for-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors are edging closer and closer to President Trump’s business empire, a fact underlined by the news Friday of an immunity deal reportedly given to the Trump Organization’s longtime chief financial officer.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
