<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Terrorist Organizations Increasingly Recruiting Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/terrorist-organizations-targeting-women-radicalization/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study that claims to be the first of its kind shows that there are clear differences between male and female terrorists and potential recruits. Perhaps most alarming, however, is the finding that terrorist organizations seem to be targeting female recruits more than ever before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to name Muslim Brotherhood terrorist group...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-muslimbrotherhood/u-s-working-to-designate-muslim-brotherhood-a-terrorist-group-white-house-idUSKCN1S6159</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is working to designate the Muslim Brotherhood a foreig...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abroad, the sting of Trump's tweets dulls...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/Abroad-the-sting-of-Trump-s-tweets-dulls-13806268.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Donald Trump tweeted Wednesday that Britain's intelligence service had helped the Obama administration spy on his 2016 campaign, the British metaphorically yawned and issued verbatim their response to the same Trump charge more than two years earlier.  "Nonsense. . . . Utterly ridiculous and should be ignored," said a spokesman for Government Communications Headquarters, the British equivalent of the U.S. National Security Agency.  The same day, when Trump tweeted for the umpteenth time that Mexico "is not doing nearly enough" to apprehend drug smugglers and migrants, and threatened to send "ARMED SOLDIERS" to the border, Mexican President Andrés Manuel López Obrador figuratively shrugged.  Mexico would, of course, look into any U.S. concerns, López Obrador said at a Mexico City news conference. But "the most important thing is to tell [Trump] that we are not going to fight with the government of the United States. . . . We are not going to be tripped up by any provocation."  Friendly countries that have been the target of Trump's tweets have learned he is not always bluffing. Aluminum and steel tariffs really were imposed on allies, and the Pentagon is sending more troops to assist in Border Patrol operations.  But few now take Trump's Twitter fulminations at immediate face value. "He has shown us that what's black at 9 a.m. can be gray at 3 p.m. and white at 7 p.m.," said a Mexican diplomat of the president's revolving pronouncements.  Most have learned that responding in kind only makes matters worse. "If you don't pick a fight with him, you take away from Trump the possibility of further enraging himself and everybody else," said the diplomat, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to avoid fueling any fires.  Gérard Araud, France's U.S. ambassador until earlier this month, said he told his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabbi wounded in synagogue attack becomes global messenger of faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-rabbi-goldstein-interview-20190429-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rabbi Yisroel Goldstein takes solace in knowing that the Chabad-Lubavitch message of fighting darkness with light is reaching millions across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Percentage of Dems who see border 'crisis' jumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Poll-Percentage-of-Democrats-who-see-border-13806243.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - More than a third of Americans say that illegal immigration at the U.S.-Mexico border is at a "crisis," up 11 percentage points since January as Democrats have grown sharply more concerned about the issue, according to a Washington Post-ABC News poll.  At the same time, Americans assign a similar level of blame to congressional Democrats and President Donald Trump for the situation, the survey finds, signaling that both political parties face challenges on immigration heading into the 2020 presidential election cycle.  The Trump administration is struggling to handle a surge of migrant families arriving at the southern border with Mexico, where the number of apprehensions by Customs and Border Protection topped 100,000 in March, the largest monthly total in a dozen years, according to federal data. Although Trump responded by installing new leadership at the Department of Homeland Security three weeks ago, the number of migrants was on pace to reach a similar level in April, authorities said.  The poll, conducted by cellular and landline telephone between April 22 and 25, finds that 35 percent of Americans believe the situation is a crisis, up from 24 percent in January. While that figure included a modest increase among Republicans and independents, the percentage of Democrats who agree jumped from 7 percent to 24 percent, nearly a quarter of the p arty.  A still-larger 45 percent plurality of the public overall says illegal immigration across the southern border is a serious problem but not a crisis, while 18 percent say it is not a serious problem.  The shifting views have altered the political calculus for Democrats, including the 20 candidates already in the race for the party's presidential nomination, who have sought to challenge Trump's hard-line rhetoric on immigration. Having once accused the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: LEADS BERNIE BY 24 POINTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/30/politics/cnn-poll-2020-biden-announcement-bounce/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden's announcement of a bid for the Democratic presidential nomination earned him an 11-point polling bounce, leaving him head and shoulders above the rest of the Democratic candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK DIVES... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/30/alphabet-stock-slammed-as-analysts-cite-lack-of-revenue-growth-and-transparency.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street analysts cited slowing revenue growth and a lack of transparency for Alphabet's earnings report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's emperor prays for peace in first abdication in 200 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-japan-emperor/japans-emperor-prays-for-peace-in-first-abdication-in-200-years-idUSKCN1S5245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese Emperor Akihito, in his final remarks as his three-decade reign drew to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Memories Ruining Real Ones?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/30/learning/are-digital-memories-ruining-our-real-ones.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you find it difficult to separate your memory of real experiences from the videos and photographs you’ve seen of them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL: Record 26 Ebola deaths in DRCongo in single day...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190430-record-26-ebola-deaths-drcongo-single-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record 26 Ebola deaths in DRCongo in a single day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires Flee Homelands as Tensions Rise, Taxes Bite...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-30/millionaires-flee-their-homelands-as-tensions-rise-taxes-bite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detained activist Leopoldo Lopez freed...</title>
      <link>https://en.mercopress.com/2019/04/30/venezuela-juan-guaido-and-leopoldo-lopez-appear-together-with-military-forces-in-caracas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;en.mercopress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president in charge of Venezuela, Juan Guaidó, announced from the military air base of La Carlota that since Tuesday, April 30, Operation Libertad began to “cease the usurpation” of Nicolás Maduro's regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi urges youth to 'love' Communist Party...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/xi-urges-youth-love-communist-party-062326582.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Xi Jinping urged China's youth on Tuesday to be loyal to the Communist Party as he sought to whip up patriotic sentiment in a nationalist speech marking the centennial of a student protest. Xi delivered his hour-long plea at the Great Hall of the People to commemorate the May Fourth Movement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Jewish hate consuming Europe and America, says French Nazi hunter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anti-jewish-hate-consuming-europe-america-says-french-054733521.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's most famous Nazi hunter Serge Klarsfeld on Monday slammed the resurgence of "anti-Jewish hate," days after a teenage gunman's deadly attack on a synagogue in California. "There is no safe place on earth right now for Jews," the 83-year-old told AFP in an interview</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG TAKES ON PRESIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/incoming-new-york-attorney-general-plans-wide-ranging-investigations-trump-n946706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just-elected Letitia James, who takes office next month, tells NBC she will probe real estate deals, Trump Tower meeting, emoluments, Trump Foundation and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where did outbreak start? Officials looking abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/california/la-me-ln-measles-outbreak-la-20190429-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States may be staring down what will likely be its worst year for measles in decades, but the situation in other countries is significantly worse. Measles cases worldwide increased 300% in the first three months of 2019 compared with the previous year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi says obstructing justice 'on daily basis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/pelosi-trump-obstructing-justice-on-daily-basis-amid-standoff-over-barr-testimony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi told reporters Monday night that President Trump "has demonstrated on a daily basis his obstruction of justice".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK handing over loan documents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/deutsche-bank-handing-over-trump-loan-documents-source-204456712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank has begun to provide documents on financing for some of President Donald Trump's projects to New York State authorities, a source familiar with the matter told AFP on Wednesday. In mid-March, New York Attorney General Letitia James subpoenaed the German bank, demanding records related</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if asteroid was about to hit Earth? Scientists ponder question...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/asteroid-hit-earth-scientists-ponder-021925824.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's a hypothetical: a telescope detects an asteroid between 100 and 300 meters in diameter racing through our solar system at 14 kilometers per second, 57 million kilometers from Earth. It's this potentially catastrophic scenario that 300 astronomers, scientists, engineers and emergency experts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Over Subpoenas...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/house-democrats-trump-gear-up-for-battle-over-subpoenas-11556579190</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With President Trump vowing to “fight all the subpoenas,” the Democratic-led House of Representatives is gearing up for a protracted legal battle over its power to enforce demands for documents and testimony from the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Shows First Cracks in Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/google-parent-posts-rare-misses-as-revenue-comes-up-short-11556569259</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google’s once-untouchable online-advertising operation took a body blow, hurt by mounting competition and struggles within its increasingly high-profile YouTube unit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relatives of Saudi prisoners agonize over whether to speak out...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/the-agonizing-decision-faced-by-prisoners-relatives-in-saudi-arabia-whether-to-speak-out/2019/04/29/0bb8faa4-5d4a-11e9-98d4-844088d135f2_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When private appeals to the royal family fail, exasperated family members risk retaliation to go public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White nationalists target bookstores in protests nationwide... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/White-nationalists-target-bookstores-and-a-13805381.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a group of self-avowed white nationalists interrupted an author chat Saturday at Washington bookstore Politics and Prose with a megaphone and chants of "This land is our land," workers were surprised but not unprepared.  The bookstore began training employees earlier this year to respond to flash protests, co-owner Bradley Graham said. The decision came after previous author events, including a talk last month by former Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano, drew the ire and attention of left-wing activists and agitators.  Politics and Prose isn't alone.  Bookstores, libraries and book fairs have become frequent targets of white nationalist groups, which in recent years have interrupted author talks, children's reading hours and, in one instance, threatened to burn down a bookstore in Berkeley, California.  "One of the issues is we can't always anticipate what author or event might draw protesters or a demonstration," Graham said. "Clearly, when the political climate heats up, there would seem to be more kindling that could be lit. But whether this will translate to more disturbances at author talks, I certainly hope not, but who knows."  Patrick Casey, co-founder of the white-nationalist group American Identity Movement, strode into the bookstore Saturday, holding a megaphone branded with the organization's insignia and led a chant of "AIM" on his way out the door.  The group, which formed last month and is based in the Washington area, is considered by several organizations that track hate groups to be a rebranded version of Identity Evropa, an organization that has sought to recruit college students and young conservatives to join its ranks through posters and online propaganda, according to the Anti-Defamation League.  Leaders of the American Identity...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS leader in new video for first time in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-video-al-furqan-latest-a8891716.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Win First Round in Roy Moore Lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/showtime-sacha-baron-cohen-win-first-round-roy-moore-lawsuit-1205585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Alabama judge objects to the insinuation he's a sex offender, but Showtime is throwing up a roadblock to the lawsuit in the form of a consent agreement signed as a condition for appearing on "Who is America."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAELI ENVOY UNLOADS: PAPER IS JEWISH HATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.algemeiner.com/2019/04/29/new-york-times-is-cesspool-israeli-ambassador-to-us-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.algemeiner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE:  DISNEY should use 'AVENGERS' profits to pay workers middle class wage..</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/441237-sanders-suggests-disney-should-use-avengers-profits-to-pay-all-of-its-workers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) on Monday called on Disney to use profits from its "Avengers: Endgame" record-breaking opening weekend to pay all employees "a middle class wage."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  TRUMP ABUSED OFFICE!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbfeb1c7646e489295269cdd5505eacb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PITTSBURGH (AP) — Joe Biden accused President Donald Trump of abusing the powers of his office and ignoring everyone but his political base Monday in his first public rally as presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in measles cases leads to extraordinary measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/17623ad3d23a4f5e8e3dda3b3559dae9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Quarantines in California. Fines in New York City. Orders for some people to avoid public places in Rockland County, New York. As an outbreak of measles surges across the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABCNEWS DIANE SAWYER DOCUMENTS IMPACT OF SCREEN TIME...</title>
      <link>https://abcnewspr.tumblr.com/post/184535134461/abc-news-announces-diane-sawyer-television-event</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnewspr.tumblr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Two-Hour Special Report Features Solutions for Families   ‘ScreenTime: Diane Sawyer Reporting’ Airs Friday, May 3 (8:00 - 10:00 p.m. ET) on ABC Today, American adults spend the equivalent of 49...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army veteran arrested for plotting LA mass attack...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190430012405-w8t6e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-PLOT/ (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-U.S. Army veteran charged with plotting to bomb white nationalist rally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competition hurts revenue...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190429235832-tchqc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALPHABET-RESULTS/ (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-Google parent's shares dive as YouTube changes, competition hurt revenue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Asylum Seeker Restrictions: Accelerated Adjudication, Application Charge...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-orders-new-restrictions-on-asylum-seekers-at-southern-border-11556583894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House ordered new restrictions on asylum-seeking Central American families at the southern border Monday, including charging them to file their claims and barring them from working in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon approves 320 troops for illegal immigrant babysitting duty...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/29/pentagon-approves-320-troops-illegal-immigrant-bab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting Defense Secretary Patrick Shanahan has approved a Homeland Security request to assign 320 “personnel” to babysit illegal immigrants, driving them, feeding them and checking on their welfare, the Pentagon announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, once vaccine skeptic, changes his tune amid measles outbreaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/04/26/trump-vaccinations-measles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They have to get the shots. The vaccinations are so important," President Trump told reporters as he left the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 spa clients diagnosed with HIV after getting 'vampire facials'...</title>
      <link>https://www.koat.com/article/new-mexico-department-of-health-finds-2-cases-of-hiv-related-to-vampire-facial-at-vip-spa-in-albuquerque/27309348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.koat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Mexico Department of Health is urging customers of a now closed Albuquerque spa to take advantage of free HIV testing after two cases of the virus were found among former clients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLURS HIS WAY THROUGH FIRST SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-old-man-joe-biden-slurs-his-way-through-first-speech-preside</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The country wasn’t built by Wall St. bankers, CEOs, and hudge ... heh’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAST: Effort to Slime Buttigieg with Bogus Sex Assault Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/far-right-smear-merchants-jacob-wohl-and-jack-burkman-try-to-slime-pete-buttigieg-with-bogus-sex-assault-claim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor was briefly accused of assaulting a young man. A GOP source says right-wing operatives Jacob Wohl and Jack Burkman approached him to make similarly untrue accusations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveillance, fear, doorbells: AMAZON hiring 'crime news' editors...</title>
      <link>https://www.niemanlab.org/2019/04/a-doorbell-company-owned-by-amazon-wants-to-start-producing-crime-news-and-itll-definitely-end-well/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.niemanlab.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because what good is a panopticon if you can't generate some clicks?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon sending troops to border; Direct contact with migrants...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-immigration-mexico-pentagon/pentagon-approves-320-more-personnel-to-mexico-border-idUKKCN1S528G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military said on Monday it would send about 320 Defense Department pers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Titans Fight to Defang Landmark Privacy Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/california-privacy-law-tech-lobby-bills-weaken/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Privacy advocates worry that a slate of proposed changes to the California Consumer Privacy Act may impede the law's effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poor sense of smell linked to higher early death risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.earth.com/news/poor-sense-smell-risk-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.earth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study has found that older adults who have a poor sense of smell have a nearly 50 percent increased risk of dying within ten years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER SKETCH DRAWS REBUKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/04/29/new-york-times-prints-another-anti-israel-cartoon-amid-antisemitism-scandal-rocking-newspaper/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYT printed a second anti-Israel cartoon in its Saturday international edition, in wake of having run an antisemitic cartoon Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED covers seat cameras following passenger privacy outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/united-airlines-covers-up-infotainment-seat-camera-following-passenger-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The airline insists that the cameras have not been in active use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROD ROSENSTEIN RESIGNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/deputy-attorney-general-rod-rosenstein-submits-resignation-letter-11556572633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rod Rosenstein submitted his resignation letter to President Trump, ending a tumultuous two years in which he tried to steady a rocky Justice Department and its relationship with the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUTH OVER LIES'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/truth-over-lies-biden-takes-aim-trump-kickoff-campaign-rally-n999806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president stumped in Pittsburgh and ignored the other Democrats running for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freddy the parrot makes it back to zoo after being stolen, shot, bitten by snake...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/29/parrot-freddy-krueger-survives-kidnapping-shot-snake-bite-brazil-zoo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bird, Freddy Krueger, found his way back to Brazil zoo after thieves abducted him – the latest survival in his tumultuous life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN OPEN: FOR THE WORKERS</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/politics-nation/2019/04/29/Joe-Biden-president-2020-democrat-union-endorsement-pittsburgh/stories/201904290121</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Age, addresses, income exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/cloud-database-removed-after-exposing-details-on-80-million-us-households/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: The cache included information on addresses, income levels and marital status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy snowmelt linked to series of CA earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/04/29/melting-snow-may-have-caused-earthquakes-in-california-research-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research unveiled recently links a series of California earthquakes to heavy snowmelt during a wet winter. Scientists involved in the work said they believe that water from the runoff flowed down to the groundwater, causing seismic movement. The research offers new geological insights into one of the most seismically active areas of California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHN SINGLETON DEAD AT 51...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/john-singleton-dead-boyz-n-the-hood-hustle-and-flow-poetic-justice-1202599684/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Singleton, the groundbreaking film director, screenwriter and producer, died Monday in Los Angeles after suffering a stroke on April 17. He was 51. A family spokesperson said Singleton passed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity Thief 'Goldmine' Puts 65% of US Households At Risk...</title>
      <link>http://fortune.com/2019/04/29/security-gap-personal-information-breach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This open database is a goldmine for identity thieves and other attackers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY KING SUFFERS HEART ATTACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/04/29/larry-king-heart-attack-cardiac-arrest-angioplasty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry King suffers heart attack and goes into cardiac arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Martyrdom, bro:' Army vet wanted revenge for NZ mosque attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/california-man-busted-domestic-terror-plot-wanted-kill-lapd-officers-n999696</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Steven Domingo boasted about amassing an arsenal of weapons, but he struggled to pinpoint a target or develop a plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex US-NKorea envoy says Trump approved $2M fee to free Warmbier...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/29/politics/joseph-yun-warmbier-north-korea/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph Yun, the former State Department Special Representative for North Korea, confirmed Monday that he signed an agreement to pay North Korea $2 million for the release of American student Otto Warmbier in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE LIVE, 3:30 PM ET... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z6N1WdJgnLo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden is picking Pennsylvania for his first campaign speech of the presidential race. That signals his hopes of owning what may be the toughest battlegro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mormon valedictorian comes out in graduation speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/I-am-proud-to-be-a-gay-son-of-God-Mormon-13803233.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints considers same-sex marriage to be a "serious transgression" - and, until this spring, treated Mormons involved in these unions as apostates, subject to church disciplinary hearings that could result in their excommunication.  So a commencement ceremony on Friday at Brigham Young University, the flagship academic institution of the Mormon Church, was an unlikely occasion for this pronouncement: "I stand before my family, friends and graduating class today to say that I am proud to be a gay son of God."  The affirmation came from Matthew Easton, 24, who was being celebrated as the valedictorian in the political science department - and the graduating senior chosen to deliver remarks at the ceremony for the College of Family, Home, and Social Sciences.  Held up as a model for his classmates, he spoke plainly about the part of him that his church finds less commendable. Before an audience of about 10,000 - which included family members to whom he had not disclosed his sexuality - Easton asserted his value and his role in divine intent.  "I am not broken," he declared. "I am loved and important to the plan of our great creator. Each of us are."  Among the audience members to whom the announcement came as a surprise was one of Easton's sisters, who was recording a video of his speech. The camera slipped as she let out a whoop, part of a chorus of cheers that echoed through the Marriott Center. In the middle of the immense sports arena stood Easton, at a lectern bearing his university's initials. He smiled and paused, waiting for the applause to die down.  "Four years ago, it would have been impossible for me to imagine that I would come out to my entire college," he continued. "It is a phenomenal feeling. And it is a victory for me...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CLASHES WITH BIDEN OVER UNIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/29/trump-slams-dues-sucking-firefighters-union-leaders-as-he-attacks-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Monday unleashed a series of tweets criticizing leaders of major labor unions and former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>75% of Americans against plan to let every prisoner vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/majority-oppose-bernie-sanders-inmate-prisoner-voting-plan-insider-poll-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 35% of voters support enfranchising current prisoners in some capacity, but most of these people are not willing to go as far as Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Terror Plot in SoCal Disrupted... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/04/29/authorities-disrupt-alleged-terror-plot-in-southern-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged domestic terror plot aimed at “multiple targets” in Southern California was disrupted by federal and local law enforcement agencies, sources told The Times on Monday. A single suspect has been arrested on domestic terror charges, according to two law enforcement officials who spoke to The Times on condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to discuss the case with the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXCONN Tore Up Small Town to Build Big Factory -- Then Retreated...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foxconn-tore-up-a-small-town-to-build-a-big-factorythen-retreated-11556557652</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iPhone maker got fat incentives to build a $10 billion LCD plant that largely hasn’t materialized on land where Mount Pleasant, Wis., razed homes and crops. “We’re talking about things that are just imaginary.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has WOODSTOCK 50 been canceled? Organizers argue over status...</title>
      <link>https://www.poughkeepsiejournal.com/story/news/local/2019/04/29/woodstock-50-cancellation-argument/3616705002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poughkeepsiejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Woodstock 50 has been scheduled to be held at Watkins Glen in August.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man guilty of marrying 4 women...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/man-accused-marrying-4-women-pleads-guilty-n999581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Middleton, 43, married a Georgia woman in 2006, an Alabama woman in 2011, a New Hampshire woman in 2013 and a woman in Kentucky in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Brood Of Cicadas Expected To Swarm PA...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/04/29/massive-brood-of-cicadas-expected-in-may/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready, a massive swarm is coming in just weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPORTS ILLUSTRATED Features Muslim in Burkini for First Time...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/04/29/minnesota-model-halima-aden-makes-history-as-the-1st-to-wear-a-hijab-in-sports-illustrated-swimsuit-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Minnesota woman is breaking boundaries in the modeling world, becoming the first model to wear a hijab and burkini for Sports Illustrated Swimsuit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools install metal detectors as stabbing epidemic grips Britain...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8963689/schools-install-knife-arches-crime-south-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCHOOLS will be forced to install knife arches as a horrific epidemic of bloody crimes grips the capital. Met Police officers will also have the power to stop and search on the streets — without pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto vows to spend $5 TRILLION on climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6972109/Beto-ORourke-unveils-climate-plan-Yosemite-backdrop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Beto O'Rourke has announced his first major policy initiative, a $5 trillion plan to combat climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPREADS TO 700 CASES, 22 STATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/measles-outbreak-united-states-vaccinations-5a1b0092-a644-4923-a94c-37e7efb93fb6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are urging parents to immunize their children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New NAFTA Faces Mounting Resistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trumps-new-nafta-faces-mounting-resistance-in-democratic-house-11556493604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s push to revamp North America’s trade rules is hitting a roadblock in Washington as Democrats and labor groups demand changes, dimming its chances of passage before next year’s presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECRUITING MORE EXECUTIONERS</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8957769/saudi-arabia-beheadings-execution-jobs/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE ruthless Saudi government is beheading so many people it needs to recruit a deadly new squad of sword-wielding executioners. The news comes after it slaughtered 37 people in one bloody day last…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE SPREAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/29/us-measles-cases-climb-to-704-as-the-disease-spreads-among-unvaccinated-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three-quarters this year's 704 measles cases in the U.S. occurred in unvaccinated people, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Shares Soar...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-29/disney-poised-for-record-high-as-endgame-dominates-box-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ban on banana-eating artwork draws ridicule in Poland...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/ban-banana-eating-artwork-draws-ridicule-poland-62697089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video artwork featuring a banana was banned as being harmful to the young.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48%:  TRUMP OBAMA SHARE SAME APPROVAL AT THIS TIME IN PRESIDENCY, SAYS POLL...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_apr29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>200,000 'never-before-seen' viruses discovered lurking in ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8961505/almost-200000-never-before-seen-viruses-are-discovered-lurking-in-the-ocean/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRUSES that have never been seen before have been discovered hidden deep in the ocean. Almost 200,000 of the infectious pathogens were found during a global marine life expedition, which took over…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboards tracking shoppers with cameras; Target ads based on mood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8960640/creepy-billboards-track-with-cameras/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SURVEILLANCE cameras in shopping centre billboards are being used to spy on you so you can be targeted with the ‘correct’ advertisements. The giant screens contain technology that can w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm going to kill you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-san-diego-synagogue-shooting-hero-20190428-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar Stewart, a 51-year-old Army veteran, was at Chabad of Poway on Saturday when the sound of shots rang out. Something, he thinks it might have been the "hand of God," propelled him to the lobby, where he confronted the shooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Topple All-Time Record?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/box-office-can-avengers-endgame-topple-avatars-28b-record-1205456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marvel and Disney's superhero pic opened to an epic, record-shattering $1.2 billion globally, but the road to the highest-grossing film ever is steep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA scientist claims time travel possible because 'speed of light changing'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/775350/Time-travel-proof-NASA-insider-possible-speed-of-light-changing-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS NEW HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/29/stock-market-earnings-data-and-us-china-trade-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded along the flatline on Monday as investors braced for a busy week including a flurry of corporate earnings reports, economic data and an announcement from the Federal Reserve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible rise of Dubai as world's air travel hub...</title>
      <link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/incredible-rise-dubai-worlds-air-121500920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.style.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty years ago Dubai was little more than a village. Pearling and fishing propped up the economy and around 25,000 called it home. To put that into perspective, more people attend Sunderland’s football matches on a typical Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBAT VET WHO STOPPED SYNAGOGUE SHOOTER...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/04/28/combat-vet-stopped-san-diego-synagogue-shooter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar Stewart stopped the gunman inside the Chabad of Poway synagogue in San Diego on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day in the Life of Facialist to the Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-day-in-the-life-of-dr-barbara-sturm-facialist-to-the-stars-11556541795</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s treated Gwyneth Paltrow, Angela Bassett and at least one Hadid. How Dr. Barbara Sturm, 47, has grown her skincare business 300 percent over the last two years—entirely on word of mouth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer spending posts biggest gain since '09...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy/u-s-consumer-spending-posts-biggest-gain-since-2009-idUSKCN1S516T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer spending increased by the most in more than 9-1/2 years in March, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Want Him on Everything': Meet Woman Behind Mayor Pete Media Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/29/lis-smith-buttigieg-2020-president-campaign-manager-226756</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How hard-charging New York operative Lis Smith helped&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;turn an obscure Indiana mayor into a national name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global military spending at new post-Cold War high...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190429105059-m8xz0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORLD-DEFENCE/SPENDING (PIX):Global military spending at new post-Cold War high, fueled by US, China - think-tank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen's Last Days of Freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2019/05/06/michael-cohens-last-days-of-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These days, the President’s former lawyer, and the fall guy in his web of misconduct, looks like a victim as well as a perpetrator.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Populist economic frustration threatens Trump's strongest reelection issue...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Populist-economic-frustration-threatens-Trump-s-13803043.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's strongest case for reelection remains the country's healthy economy, but the potency of that issue for him is complicated by a widespread belief that the economy mainly benefits people already in power, a Washington Post-ABC News poll finds.  The result previews a fresh wave of populism that could reshape yet another presidential campaign with about 18 months to go before voters decide whether to return Trump to the White House.  This sentiment runs the deepest among Democratic and independent registered voters, but also exists among a significant slice of Republicans. About 8 in 10 Democrats and more than 6 in 10 independents say the country's economic system gives an advantage to those already in power, while nearly a third of Republicans share that view.  The survey finds broad dissatisfaction with the country's economic and political systems. Overall, 60 percent of all voters say the country's economic system mainly benefits those in power, while 72 percent say the same for the nation's political structures.  The polling results in many ways echo the populist fervor that swept Trump to an unlikely victory over more than a dozen Republican challengers in the 2016 presidential primary campaign and an improbable win over Democrat Hillary Clinton that November.  But the findings show that, ahead of 2020, the sentiment is also animating Democrats.  The message of economic populism is carried most prominently in the Democratic presidential field by Sen. Bernie Sanders of Vermont, who since his unsuccessful 2016 campaign has pushed the party leftward on a range of issues, and Sen. Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts, who has proposed ideas such as a massive student loan forgiveness program and free tuition at public colleges paid for by taxing the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beluga whale with Russian harness raises alarm in Norway...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8515d3a6ea4a48dda70583a616beca05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — A beluga whale found with a tight harness that appeared to be Russian made has raised the alarm of Norwegian officials and prompted speculation that the animal may have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope urges hairdressers to cut gossip...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-urges-hairdressers-cut-gossip-114746780.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Monday welcomed hairdressers, hairstylists and beauticians to the Vatican but warned them not to indulge in gossip while feathering locks or painting fingernails. Snip split ends and wax limbs while "avoiding giving in to the temptation of chatter that easily creeps into your work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cute or creepy: Why humans love some species, loathe others...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cute-creepy-why-humans-love-species-loathe-others-100326235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese giant salamander, the largest amphibian in the world, is not cute. Weighing as much as an adult human, it has slimy brown skin, a giant mouth curled to a gormless grin, and puny, mistrustful eyes. It is also one of the world's most endangered species.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
