<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Captain told passengers NOT to don life jackets?</title>
      <link>https://fox59.com/2018/07/20/several-members-of-indiana-family-among-those-killed-in-branson-duck-boat-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox59.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRANSON, Missouri – Several members of an Indiana family were on a duck boat that capsized in Branson, Missouri, Thursday night, killing 17 people.  The Missouri governor's office confirmed to FOX59 that eleven members of the family, including several children, were aboard the boat and nine of them passed away in the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind closed doors, Guantanamo secret court talks about CIA, torture and rights...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article214381804.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A McClatchy review of declassified transcripts of Guantánamo’s national security hearings found that, after the public and death-penalty defendants are sent away, what goes on at the war court often involves the CIA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overturning Roe v. Wade would send issue back to states. Then it gets complicated...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/article214820175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly five decades after the U.S. Supreme Court legalized abortion, a bitter fight looms over President Donald Trump’s nominee for a new Justice and the potential for Roe v. Wade to be overturned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago named 'rat capital' of nation...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/07/20/study-chicago-rat-capital-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study names Chicago the rat capital of the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power use to keep hitting records during heat wave...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/texas-power-keep-hitting-records-during-heat-wave-153305056--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - Homes and businesses in Texas used record amounts of power for a second straight day on Thursday and are expected to use even more in coming days as consumers crank up air conditioners to escape a brutal heat wave, according to the operator of much of the state's power grid. To keep</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW DANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-taped-conversation-with-trump-about-buying-rights-to-playmates-story-1532112954</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen taped a conversation with Donald Trump about buying the rights to a former Playboy Playmate’s story that she had an affair with Mr. Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA prepares to fly probe into Sun's scorching atmosphere...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/nasa-prepares-fly-probe-suns-scorching-atmosphere-212341778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Joey Roulette CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla (Reuters) - NASA is preparing to send a probe closer to the Sun than any other spacecraft has ventured, enduring wicked heat while zooming through the solar corona to study this outermost part of the stellar atmosphere that gives rise to the solar wind. The Parker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Major Israeli raids on Gaza amid talk of war...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/israeli-fire-kills-three-palestinians-during-border-protests-170654046.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Nidal al-Mughrabi and Ori Lewis GAZA/JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Palestinian gunmen killed an Israeli soldier along the Gaza border on Friday, said the Israeli military, which launched dozens of strikes into Gaza that killed four Palestinians, including three Hamas fighters. The soldier was the first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria rejects registering Jews for kosher meat...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/austria-rejects-registering-jews-kosher-meat-155301942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria rejected Friday registering Jews who want to purchase kosher meat after a far-right politician proposed introducing stricter controls on ritual slaughtering to reduce the practice citing animal rights. Gottfried Waldhaeusl, a cabinet minister of Lower Austria and member of the Freedom Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGM banks on never-used anti-terrorism law in suing Vegas victims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8e051bfa0a34631928d5b618ff826b3/MGM-banks-on-never-used-anti-terrorism-law-in-suing-victims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — The unprecedented move from MGM Resorts International to sue hundreds of victims of last year's mass shooting in Las Vegas using an obscure U.S. law never tested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION:  The White House week of walk-backs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73a29bf8b8b14af5ba9f61eecae36e73/Let's-be-clear:-The-White-House-week-of-walk-backs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — This was the week when "would" turned into "wouldn't" and "no" meant "yes," as President Donald Trump and his top aides tried to walk back several of his comment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revelations of US cardinal sex abuse will force pope's hand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a29b8bafa7dd47148577ee5e4a06060f/Revelations-of-US-cardinal-sex-abuse-will-force-pope's-hand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Revelations that one of the most respected U.S. cardinals allegedly sexually abused both boys and adult seminarians have raised questions about who in the Cath</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie, Ocasio-Cortez rally Dems in Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/adb409ee49cf43e38dcda8172f078542/Sanders,-Ocasio-Cortez-rally-Democrats-in-deep-red-Kansas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kansas (AP) — Two luminaries in the democratic socialist movement — one its national leader, the other its new star — descended on solidly Republican Kansas on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh lengthy paper trail becomes flashpoint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f4db142a7114bd6a0bec765f2a86ea2/Kavanaugh's-lengthy-paper-trail-becomes-flashpoint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Judge Brett Kavanaugh has a long record of judicial and executive branch service to recommend him as President Donald Trump's nominee to the Supreme Court. And t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN TAPED TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3faf47db59054b3c9c8dd414b943c9ea/Trump-was-taped-talking-of-paying-for-Playboy-model's-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump's former personal lawyer secretly recorded Trump discussing a potential payment for a former Playboy model's account of having an affair wit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne: ABC Fired Me Because I Voted Trump...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/roseanne-barr-fired-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIAN ROBOTS IN SPACE</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/07/russia-may-put-androids-orbit-next-year-state-media-says/149927/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mission would be the latest for FEDOR, created for rescue work — and more recently given the ability to shoot guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Charge Private Eye With Spying on Richard Simmons...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/prosecutors-charge-private-eye-spying-richard-simmons-1128873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The criminal complaint follows an amended lawsuit where Simmons alleges Scott Brian Mathews was hired by In Touch Weekly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Next Big Star? Artificial Intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/artificial-intelligence-hollywood-next-star-arvin-patel-commentary-1202427191/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Editors’ Note: Industry veteran Arvin Patel is Chief Intellectual Property Officer at TiVo and former chief IPO officer at Technicolor, with previous stints at Rovi and IBM. At TiVo, he overs…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael killed self after FOUR failed attempts...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/6830783/george-michael-killed-himself-fifth-suicide-attempt-lover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAGIC George Michael committed suicide, his lover claims — and it was his fifth attempt. Fadi Fawaz said the singer, 53, died on Christmas Eve, his late mum’s birthday, and not Christmas Day as wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers complain of bedbugs on flights out of Newark...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/passengers-complain-of-bedbugs-on-flights-out-of-newark</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers on flights from Newark Liberty International Airport to India are complaining about bed bug infested seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne: ABC Fired Me Because I Voted Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/roseanne-barr-abc-fired-me-because-i-voted-for-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEXT: Americans to legally download 3-D printed guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/19/us/3d-printed-gun-settlement-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun-rights activists have reached a settlement with the government that will allow them to post 3-D printable gun plans online starting August 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks and gators go tooth-to-tooth along the FL coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.naplesnews.com/story/news/environment/2018/07/20/sharks-gators-florida-coast/806636002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.naplesnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's space portal is where sharks and alligators sometimes meet and chomp it out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized 'deep fakes' alarm US military; Troop blackmail fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2018/07/19/ever-heard-of-deep-fake-technology-the-phony-audio-and-video-tech-could-be-used-to-blackmail-us-troops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ability to distort the truth is expected to reach new heights with the development of so-called “deep fake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: ULTIMATE SURVEILLANCE TOOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/kalevleetaru/2018/07/20/facebook-as-the-ultimate-government-surveillance-tool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s international reach, massive centralized data warehouse and algorithms that can divine the most sensitive and intimate elements of our lives are likely to increasingly become a go-to one-stop shop for the world’s intelligence agencies to spy, influence and destroy dissent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Chance The Rapper Goes After Rahm Emanuel...</title>
      <link>http://abc7chicago.com/entertainment/chance-the-rapper-buys-chicagoist-calls-out-mayor-in-new-song/3787186/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chance the Rapper dropped four new songs Wednesday night, including one that announced his purchase of the Chicagoist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Gunn Fired From 'GUARDIANS OF GALAXY' For Old Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-drops-james-gunn-guardians-galaxy-franchise-offensive-tweets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tweets joked about rape and pedophilia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANHATTAN MADAM SUBPOENAED BY MUELLER...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/20/manhattan-madam-kristin-davis-subpoenaed-robert-mueller-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kristin Davis, the Manhattan Madam who went to prison, is being subpoenaed in the Robert Mueller investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7,000 service members to march military parade...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/estimated-5000-7000-service-members-march-trumps-military/story?id=56715855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between 5,000 to 7,000 service members could march in President Donald Trump's military parade, according to a U.S. defense official familiar with parade planning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Gunn Fired From 'GUARDIANS OF GALAXY' For Old Tweets...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/james-gunn-fired-from-guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol-3-1202879817/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Gunn has been fired as the director of “Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 3” after a series of offensive tweets were unearthed that made light of such controversial topics as pedopheli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Home Inventory Piling Up...</title>
      <link>http://www.crainsnewyork.com/article/20180720/REAL_ESTATE/180729989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just luxury-home listings that are piling up in New York City. Even units for less than $1 million — within reach of far more people than a Billionaires' Row penthouse — are hurting for buyers. In Manhattan, the inventory of sub-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dr. Bumbum' arrested after patient dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/20/dr-bumbum-arrested-brazil-after-patient-dies/805209002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denis Furtado was performing a procedure to enlarge a patient's buttocks at his Rio de Janeiro home Saturday when the patient fell ill. He's accused of dropping her at the hospital and going on the run for five days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbine-obsessed Brit schoolboys planned attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6825821/columbine-obsessed-british-schoolboys-plan-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THESE are the first pictures of two teens who plotted to slaughter classmates in a Columbine-style gun and bomb massacre on a Yorkshire school. Thomas Wyllie and Alex Bolland were just 14 when they…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant cancels church discount after atheist outrage...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/2018/07/20/ohio-restaurant-cancels-sunday-church-discount-after-outrage-from-secular-organization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watson, who opened the restaurant the first week of June, said the response was positive — at first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California gains just 800 jobs in June...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-california-jobs-20180720-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California gained a meager 800 net jobs in June, while the unemployment rate held steady at a record low of 4.2%, according to data released Friday by the state’s Employment Development Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Israeli raids on Gaza amid talk of war...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/idf-strikes-deep-into-gaza-as-troops-come-under-fire-amid-talk-of-4th-gaza-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu arrives at defense headquarters amid fresh airstrikes on Gaza targets following sniper fire at IDF soldiers; 3 Hamas fighters dead; Minister: 'The gloves are coming off'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Beluga' Takes Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/multimedia/Airbus-Beluga-XL-Whale-Takes-Flight-for-the-First-Time-488640021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Airbus Beluga XL made its first flight. Check out photos of the super-transporter's adorable 'whale face' paint job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass gathering of golden retrievers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-highlands-islands-44898115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dogs and their owners gathered at the Highlands estate where the breed was first founded 150 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Scores more sick from MCDONALD'S salads...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/food/2018/07/20/mcdonalds-tainted-salads-sickened-people-cyclospora-parasite-fecal-matter/806682002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of people sickened by tainted McDonald's salads has jumped to 163 in 10 states, and three of the victims have been hospitalized. The fast-food chain said it has removed the lettuce blend from Fresh Express’ Streamwood, Illinois, facility and replaced it with a new supply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIONS GATE legal drama...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-lions-gate-a-drama-in-the-legal-department-1532104228</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2017, Lions Gate’s general counsel exited the company where he had worked for 17 years. A filing noted that he resigned “for health and personal reasons.” Left unmentioned was a legal drama involving a former subordinate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans pick Charlotte for 2020 convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/politics-government/rnc-2020/article215204290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Committee has voted Charlotte North Carolina as the winner of the host city bid for the 2020 RNC during their Austin TX meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges ask for share of future salary in lieu of loans...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d25f4aeb92e449de9613c80c14ad4657/Colleges-ask-for-a-share-of-future-salary-in-lieu-of-loans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTPELIER, Vt. (AP) — As more students balk at the debt loads they face after graduation, some colleges are offering an alternative: We'll pay your tuition if you offer us a perc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran reporter loses job in plagiarism probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/veteran-newspaper-reporter-loses-job-plagiarism-probe-161348823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RALEIGH, N.C. (AP) — A veteran North Carolina newspaper reporter lost her job after editors found she used material from other publications in her stories without credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Ecuador to hand over Assange 'in coming weeks or days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/433783-wikileaks-assange-ecuador-uk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecuador is ready to hand over the WikiLeaks founder to the UK in “coming weeks or even days,” RT editor-in-chief Margarita Simonyan said citing her own sources, as prospects of his eviction from the embassy are back in the media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Michael Cohen Secretly Taped Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/donald-trump-1/2018/07/20/michael-cohen-secretly-taped-donald-trump-discussing-payment-playboy-model-stormy-daniels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- President Donald Trump's longtime lawyer, Michael Cohen, secretly recorded a conversation with Trump two months before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Recorded calls 'to use as leverage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/donald-trump-michael-cohen-raid-recordings-seized-robert-mueller-special-counsel-russia-a8302401.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Now we are wondering, who did he tape? Did he store those someplace where they were actually seized?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Michael Cohen Secretly Taped Trump Discussing Payment to Playboy Model...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/20/us/politics/michael-cohen-trump-tape.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The F.B.I. seized the recording in a raid. Its existence recording highlights the potential legal and political danger that Mr. Cohen represents to the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Severely Beaten, Nearly Paralyzed In Mosh Pit At  Concert...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/07/18/keybank-pavilion-vans-warped-tour-mosh-pit-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOAT HORROR IN MO; 13 DEAD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5973021/Mass-casualty-incident-Missouri-tourist-boat-capsizes.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people have been killed and several hospitalized after a 'Ride the Ducks' boat capsized on a lake in Missouri, with 31 people on board on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA baby born in CHIK-FIL-A bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article215223135.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert and Falon Griffin delivered their baby girl in a bathroom stall at a Chik-Fil-A location in far north San Antonio, Texas. The franchise owner says he will give their daughter free chicken nuggets for life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman With PTSD Says Experimental Ecstasy Treatment Has Restored Her Life...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/07/19/ecstasy-ptsd-therapy-marcela-otalora-g-mdma-psychotherapy-boulder-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in Boulder are trying to determine if an illegal club drug could be a viable treatment for Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raid on daycare uncovers marijuana-laced candy, cookies...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/more-than-100-pounds-of-marijuana-other-drugs-seized-from-fayetteville-daycare-facility-/17709337/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were arrested after candy and cookies containing marijuana were found at a Fayetteville daycare facility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne To Launch Talk Show...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/20/roseanne-barr-talk-show-world-politics-bitch-was-white/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roseanne Barr is working on her own talk show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage of sole survivor of Amazon tribe emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/19/footage-sole-survivor-amazon-tribe-emerges-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Man believed to be in his 50s seen swinging an axe to fell a tree in Brazilian forest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spitting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jeanine-pirro-says-whoopi-goldberg-exploded-at-her-after-view-appearance-get-the-f-out-of-this-building/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Doctors Stop Listening To Patients -- After 11 Seconds!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/doctors-give-patients-11-seconds-describe-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds doctors gives a patient an average of just 11 seconds to describe their issue before cutting them off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA STRESS! Whoopi and Judge Jeanine explosive argument at 'VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/07/19/whoopi-goldberg-and-jeanine-pirro-get-into-explosive-argument-at-the-view/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an intense on-the-air exchange, things got more heated behind-the-scenes, sources exclusively tell Page Six.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Attacks Wealthy For Big Houses Before Returning To His $8 Million Mansion!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/19/obama-house-rich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mansion is Obama's second home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  CVS pharmacist denies transgender her hormones...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/scottsdale/2018/07/20/hilde-hall-arizona-transgender-woman-speaks-out-after-being-denied-hormone-prescription/805381002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hilde Hall said the CVS pharmacist refused to give her the prescription back to fill elsewhere and left her feeling "mortified."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Green Haired Leftist Assaults Teen For Wearing MAGA Hat...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/green-haired-non-binary-leftist-assaults-teen-trump-supporter-for-wearing-maga-hat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weirdo spits on hat before screaming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divers hunt for 4...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/60b99441d63a48428b5dd79bbc37c75a/Divers-hunt-for-4-after-Missouri-duck-boat-sinks,-killing-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRANSON, Mo. (AP) — Divers are searching Friday for four people still missing after a duck boat packed with tourists capsized in high winds on a southwest Missouri lake, killing a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 44%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jul20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash Brews as Bird Scooters Take Over LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/backlash-brews-as-bird-scooters-take-la-1127535 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eco-friendly transport with a billion-dollar valuation has millennials commuting with them to studio lots and talent agencies, even as users mow down pedestrians and clutter sidewalks ("Some guy almost clipped my stroller with my 6-month-old in it").</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Tumbles As Trump Blasts China, EU 'Currency Manipulation', Fed 'Tightening'...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-07-20/dollar-tumbles-below-trump-dump-lows-stocks-fade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roseanne Barr on Valerie Jarrett tweet: 'I thought the b*tch was white'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/07/20/roseanne-on-valerie-jarrett-tweet-i-thought-the-b-h-was-white/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial comedian claims that her tweets were actually “about the Iran deal.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houses torn to shreds...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5972703/Tornado-hits-factory-Iowa-injuries-reported.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hardest hit appeared to be Marshalltown, a city of 27,000 people about 50 miles northeast of Des Moines, where brick walls collapsed in the streets, and roofs were blown off buildings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle's bohemian culture struggles to survive as tech takes over...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jul/20/seattle-bohemian-counterculture-tech-industry-amazon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A solstice festival highlights the city’s history of embracing the weird as Amazon fuels a changing landscape</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fake, misleading social media posts exploding globally...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article215188910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s social media blitz to influence the 2016 U.S. election was part of a global “phenomenon” in which governments and political parties used Internet platforms to spread junk news and disinformation, an Oxford University study has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand seeks control over movies about cave ordeal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a04b55b9cc4d4a62be8ec8a25301a958</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Thailand's military government wants to control how movies portray the ordeal of the young soccer players and their heroic rescue from a flooded cave that drew worl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father of Parkland survivors shot to death in robbery...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcmiami.com/news/local/Father-Of-Two-Parkland-School-Shooting-Survivors-Killed-After-North-Lauderdale-Robbery--488636961.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcmiami.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The father of two Parkland school shooting survivors was fatally shot at his own convenient store during a robbery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTON MARTIN flying car could hit 200 mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/aston-martin-reveals-flying-car-that-could-hit-200-mph</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The British sports car maker introduced the Volante Vision Concept at the Farnborough Airshow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem rift feared as Cortez hits campaign trail with Bernie...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/19/as-upstart-ocasio-cortez-hits-campaign-trail-with-bernie-sanders-high-profile-spurs-fears-dem-rift.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is hitting the national campaign trail this week with Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders to stump for other left-wing candidates, even as the upstart 28-year-old democratic socialist's rising profile continues to rankle top Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage captures final moments...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/20/shocking-footage-captures-tragic-duck-boats-final-moments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last moments before a tourist duck boat tragically flipped over on a Missouri lake Thursday, killing 11, were captured on a video shot from a larger nearby cruise vessel, where onlookers witnes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Camp Counselor Is a Therapist...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-new-camp-counselor-is-a-therapist-1532084400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer sleep-away camps are bringing in social workers to talk with teenage campers about their anxiety and struggles to relax, make friends and give up electronic devices and social-media apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Ideal Caffeine Fix? Algorithm Can Tell...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/whats-your-ideal-caffeine-fix-an-algorithm-can-tell-you-1532084522 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Army researchers developed an algorithm to determine the ideal amount of caffeine a soldier should consume, and when, to remain alert—and it’s less than you might expect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pack Up and Get Out': Nicaraguan Unrest Shakes U.S. Expat Community...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pack-up-and-get-out-nicaraguan-unrest-shakes-u-s-expat-community-1532084519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Americans flocked to Nicaragua in recent years, attracted by a tropical climate, low costs and crime and seeming stability. Now, a violent uprising is upsetting their plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation from phones can affect memory?</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/magazines/panache/hang-up-radiation-from-mobile-phones-can-affect-your-memory/articleshow/65066435.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Potential risks to the brain can be minimised by using headphones or the loudspeaker while on a call.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hairy issue: Sailors tell Navy, 'We want beards'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hairy-issue-sailors-tell-us-navy-want-beards-040554841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Now that women in the Navy can wear ponytails, men want beards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to string undersea cable from France to Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/google-string-undersea-cable-france-virginia-062520733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIRGINIA BEACH, Va. (AP) — Google says it will string a trans-Atlantic cable from France to Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark Week Triggers Marketing Feeding Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/20/shark-week-triggers-a-marketing-feeding-frenzy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shark Week Triggers a Marketing Feeding Frenzy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin furor sparks new questions on chief of staff future...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/the-memo/397990-the-memo-putin-furor-sparks-new-questions-on-kellys-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of White House chief of staff John Kelly is the subject of growing speculation, amid the firestorm over President Trump’s recent behavior toward Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAN B: Where Super-Rich Go to Buy Second Passport...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2018-buying-citizenship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s only 10 countries that will sell you citizenship. Here’s what it costs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror in Ozarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/state/missouri/article215212175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mass casualty incident is being reported on Table Rock Lake in Branson when a duck boat capsized and submerged. There have been multiple fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:  'MAMMA MIA! 2' Is Sub-Mental Musical...</title>
      <link>http://observer.com/2018/07/mamma-mia-here-we-go-again-is-plotless-artless-junk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meryl Streep appears for about 20 seconds, making her the luckiest member of the cast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke missile with 'unlimited range'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putin-tests-nuclear-powered-12949968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Russian Ministry of Defence the apocalyptic weapon can reach any desired target on the planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Catastrophic damage'...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2018/07/19/central-iowa-tornado-weather-storms-vermeer-pella-marshalltown-marshall-courthouse-bondurant-damage/804565002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian pol wants to make Jews register to buy kosher meat...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/19/austrian-pol-wants-to-make-jews-register-to-buy-kosher-meat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Austrian far-right politician has said he wants to register Jews, in a chilling echo of Adolf Hitler and Nazi Germany. The disturbing plan was unveiled by Gottfried Waldhausl, the minister in ch…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
