<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Violated Defense Department policy?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/28/navy-reviews-trump-make-aircrews-great-again-patch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy says it is reviewing whether service members violated Defense Department policy or regulations by wearing a uniform patch with the words “Make Aircrews Great Again” during President Donald Trump’s visit to their ship in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Congressman Talking Impeachment to Run Against Trump?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnns-gloria-borger-floats-possibility-gop-rep-amash-could-primary-trump-i-think-he-might-be-running-for-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief political analyst Gloria Borger identified one possible reason for Congressman Justin Amash's relentless talk of impeaching President Donald Trump, theorizing that the Michigan Republican "might be running for president."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorcyclist rushes to save injured Bald Eagle on highway...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/pets-animals/good-samaritan-saves-injured-bald-eagle-/5318822/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dandon Miller is an American hero of sorts after running to save a bald eagle injured on the busy Route 30 bypass on Saturday of Memorial Day Weekend in Downingtown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortages plague Cuba as woes sharpen...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-cuba-economy/shortages-plague-cuba-as-u-s-sanctions-sharpen-economic-woes-idUSKCN1SX1P1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Hidalgo and his wife left home around 7:30 a.m. to reach a supermarket ac...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students secretly photographed for govt facial-recognition research...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/27/cu-colorado-springs-facial-recognition-research/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A professor at the University of Colorado’s Colorado Springs campus led a project that secretly snapped photos of more than 1,700 students, faculty members and others walking in public more t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>52 TORNADOES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7077917/More-5-million-left-without-power-Ohio-tornadoes-reduced-homes-rubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tornado Watch has been issued in four states after tornadoes touched down in the Midwest, leaving one dead and 90 more injured, as every county in Oklahoma is under a state of emergency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONDS FLASH RECESSION WARNING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/28/morgan-stanley-says-economy-on-recession-watch-amid-bond-warning.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stock market and economic outlook in the United States is "deteriorating," according to Morgan Stanley's chief stock strategist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military members seen with MAGA patches on jumpsuits at Trump speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/u-s-service-members-seen-with-maga-patches-on-jumpsuits-at-trump-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patches could fall under the DoD's strict guidelines against showing partisanship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow in middle of AAA skirmish...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/05/28/tim-tebow-syracuse-mets-scranton-railriders-brawl/1258095001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York's baseball rivalry trickled down to Class AAA overÂ weekend, with the Syracuse Mets andÂ Scranton RailRiders having multiple incidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25% of Americans  worry about money 'all the time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/24/25-percent-of-americans-say-they-worry-about-money-all-the-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are feeling mostly good about their finances, according to analytics firm Gallup. But while 56% describe their financial situation as "good" or "excellent," not everyone is as optimistic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPORTS ILLUSTRATED sold for $110 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91fbe87ac40e42368b65fb5149586452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sports Illustrated magazine has been sold for $110 million to a company that specializes in managing fashion, entertainment and sports brands, including marketing rights to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Living In Van With 21 Dogs, Bird...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/05/28/wethersfield-van-dogs-bird-suzanne-muzaffer-eser-animal-cruelty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She's being charged with animal cruelty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dementia stopped major artist. For some, that spelled lucrative opportunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dementia-stopped-a-major-artist-from-painting-for-some-that-spelled-a-lucrative-opportunity/ar-AAC1HF8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes rules against man in free speech case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2d7f23ba7e3f43d1a8c7afdf222cbaad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court ruled Tuesday against an Alaska resident in a case that gives law enforcement officers significant protection from people who want to sue and claim they were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Players Association Warns Of Potential NFL Lockout...</title>
      <link>http://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/05/28/nflpa-warns-of-future-lockout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to reports, the NFL Players Association is warning about a lockout that could be on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of Disappearing Elephant-Seal Dialects...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2019/05/vanished-dialects-northern-elephant-seals/590008/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first ever documented in another species of mammal, these dialects may have been a side effect of the seals’ encounters with humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON removes books on bleach 'cures' for autism...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/internet/amazon-removes-books-promoting-dangerous-bleach-cures-autism-other-illnesses-n1010861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The books focus on chlorine dioxide, which doctors and federal regulators say amounts to industrial bleach and can cause permanent harm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nuts! Out of control': Robocall outrage...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/nuts-out-control-do-something-american-robocall-outrage-n1009351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FCC and the FTC receive hundreds of thousands of complaints a month about scam calls. Here's a snapshot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-T-R-E-S-S: Spelling Bee tries to ease pressure...</title>
      <link>https://in.reuters.com/article/us-usa-spellingbee/spelling-bee-aces-buzz-through-early-rounds-some-stung-by-stumpers-idINKCN1SY0Y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;in.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Scripps National Spelling Bee got underway on Tuesday with most young spelli...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio Weatherman Snaps at Viewers as Tornado Warning Interrupts 'THE BACHELORETTE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ohio-weatherman-snaps-at-viewers-as-tornado-warning-interrupts-the-bachelorette-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm done with you people, I really am. This is pathetic," Jamie Simpson of Fox 45 in Dayton says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health paradox: Diabetes cases FALL as obesity rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/05/28/obesity-rates-climb-new-diabetes-cases-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New federal data released found the number of new diabetes diagnoses fell to about 1.3 million in 2017, down from 1.7 million in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUTHOR CRIES WOLFF!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/mueller-team-flatly-denies-michael-wolffs-claim-that-special-counsel-drafted-indictment-of-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire and Fury author Michael Wolff is back with a sequel to his 2018 bestseller. And in it, he makes an explosive claim about an action special counsel Robert Mueller strongly considered taking against President Donald Trump. But it's an action that the Mueller team is firmly denying. According to the Guardian, Wolff claims that Mueller drafted an obstruction of justice indictment against Trump, before ultimately deciding not to proceed with it. The indictment, according to Wolff, would have charged the president with three counts including; witness tampering, witness retaliation, and corruptly influencing a pending proceeding. The Guardian reports that it viewed documents relating to Wolff's claim. Yet Mueller spokesman Peter Carr denies the very existence of these documents. "The documents that you've described do not exist," Carr told the Guardian. Wolff claims that the draft indictment alleges that Trump began obstructing justice in the first week of his presidency. He wrote that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYTON DAMAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/large-destructive-tornado-strikes-dayton-as-severe-storms-ravage-ohio/70008380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX THREATENS GEORGIA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/features/abortion-laws-hollywood-studios-netflix-1203225843/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of Hollywood’s most powerful content companies have maintained a deafening silence on the raging abortion legislation debate that’s sweeping the country as their star talent and producers go o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden front-runner by every measure -- except big crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/28/biden-energy-crisis-1345359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former veep is leading the Democratic field in all the important categories except one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST OF PARTICIPANTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/bilderberg-2019-full-agenda-and-participants-list/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Globalists to meet in Montreux, Switzerland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Claims Escalating Use of Wildfire Arson as Terror Tactic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hstoday.us/subject-matter-areas/counterterrorism/isis-claims-escalating-use-of-wildfire-arson-as-terror-tactic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hstoday.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchors from China state TV and FOX facing off...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Anchors-from-China-s-state-TV-and-Fox-are-facing-13900441.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - One is a star of one of President Donald Trump's favorite television networks, Fox Business. The other is a polished debater on Chinese state media known for her confidence in China's rise and scorn for "biased" Western media.  After weeks of back-and-forth sniping on television and Twitter, Trish Regan from the Fox Business Network and Liu Xin from China Global Television Network are facing off Wednesday night on Regan's show to argue on behalf of their respective governments about tariffs and technology.  The debate might be just another weeknight segment for Fox Business, but it's eagerly anticipated in China, where nationalism and distaste for the United States are running high as the White House tightens the screws on Beijing in their ongoing trade dispute.  "With anchorwomen like her, and companies like Huawei, why would China need to worry about its rise?" read a typical patriotic comment on Chinese social media praising Liu, who is one of China's best known faces despite her regular show appearing on an English-language channel.  Hashtags about the upcoming debate have been viewed upward of 150 million times, with some Weibo posts retweeted tens of thousands of times.  Nearly all of China's tightly controlled state media outlets have covered the Liu vs Regan showdown, often framing the anchor as a symbol of Chinese toughness and rationality. Liu's employer CGTN - the international division of China's all-powerful China Central Television network, or CCTV - has hailed the clash between the two anchors as nothing less than a "historic first."  From the Chinese government perspective, the debate may be a small victory before Liu even utters a word on Fox Business. Over the past decade, the ruling Communist Party has invested heavily to push its state media into the global conversation and shape...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYTON DAMAGE</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-05-28-ohio-tornadoes-impact-damage-celina-dayton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tornado-producing storms moved through eastern Indiana and western and central Ohio late Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto Apologizes For Being 'Giant Asshole'...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/28/beto-orourke-senate-documentary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 presidential candidate Beto O'Rourke apologized to campaign staff for being a &amp;quot;giant asshole&amp;quot; at times during his failed Senate bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salvini vows to unite populists yet lacks partners...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4c8b3c5e07e4924833ff072aed10783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy's victorious right-wing leader, Matteo Salvini, says the European elections have created "a new geography" of anti-elite sentiment in the EU. But it is far from certain that he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller drew up obstruction indictment against Trump, Michael Wolff book claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/28/mueller-trump-obstruction-charge-michael-wolff-book-siege-under-fire-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spokesman for special counsel denies existence of document at heart of revelation in Fire and Fury sequel, Siege: Trump Under Fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding stars led to humans walking on two legs, radical study suggests...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2019/may/28/exploding-stars-led-humans-walking-on-two-legs-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say surge of radiation led to lightning causing forest fires, making adaptation vital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University offers 'Problematizing Whiteness' course...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/university-offers-problematizing-whiteness-course/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CU Denver ethnic studies class: ‘educating for racial justice.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Colombia, defectors arm selves to 'liberate' homeland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-colombia-militia/from-colombia-venezuelan-defectors-arm-themselves-to-liberate-their-homeland-idUSKCN1SY1A0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wearing camouflage shirts and combat boots, a Venezuelan militia group stands in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage shows moment Russian rocket struck by lightning during launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7077269/Electrifying-footage-shows-moment-lightning-strikes-Russian-Soyuz-rocket-launch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Roscosmos Soyuz 2-1b rocket thundered into the air from the Plesetsk Cosmodrome near Mirny, northern Russia on May 27, 2019, carrying a GLONASS-M navigation satellite into orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility paradox in male beauty quest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-48396071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men paradoxically damage their ability to have children during efforts to make themselves look more attractive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Underground Base Near Area 51?</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/us/201905281075414371-area-51-ufo-underground-base/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conspiracy buff also directed his attention toward the two fields located near the suspected underground facility, speculating that these crops might be part of some genetic research programme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The hunting has accelerated': Arrests, killings strike fear in Thailand dissidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-thailand-dissidents-20190528-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exiles say Thailand's army is trying to silence opponents in the twilight of five years of military rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: High radiation levels found in clams of Marshall Islands near nuke dump...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/science/environment/la-me-marshall-islands-dome-is-leaking-radiation-20190528-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal researchers have disclosed high levels of radiation in giant clams near where waste from U.S. nuclear testing was buried in the Marshall Islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos ex to give away half her wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/28/mackenzie-bezos-joins-warren-buffett-and-the-gates-giving-pledge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MacKenzie Bezos joined the pledge started by Warren Buffett and Bill and Melinda Gates to give away at least half her wealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared in Mideast to push peace plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/504dd02da3e64fd0b5c65d3842fa37b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's son-in-law and senior adviser Jared Kushner is in the Middle East to drum up support for his as-yet unveiled Israeli-Palestinian peace plan. A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,000-year-old marble head of god Dionysus discovered under Rome...</title>
      <link>http://www.msn.com/en-xl/asia/asia-top-stories/2000-year-old-marble-head-of-god-dionysus-discovered-under-rome/ar-AAC0TPo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILDERBERG '19: FUTURE OF CAPITALISM, WEAPONIZATION OF SOCIAL MEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.ch/20190528/secretive-bilderberg-meeting-to-be-held-in-switzerland-from-may-30th-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2019 edition of the exclusive Bilderberg Meeting will take place at the Hotel Montreux Palace in the Swiss town of Montreux from Thursday to Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Indictment of Assange blueprint for making journalists into felons...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/The-indictment-of-Assange-is-a-blueprint-for-13900193.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government on Thursday unveiled an 18-count indictment against WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange, charging him under the 1917 Espionage Act for his role in the 2010 publication of a trove of secret documents relating to the Iraq and Afghanistan wars and diplomatic communications regarding dozens of nations. So extreme and unprecedented are the indictment's legal theories and likely consequences that it shocked and alarmed even many of Assange's most virulent critics.  The new indictment against Assange bears no relationship to WikiLeaks' publication of Democratic Party and Clinton campaign documents or any of its other activities during the 2016 presidential campaign. Instead, it covers only publication of a massive archive of classified U.S. government documents that revealed a multitude of previously unknown, highly significant information about wars, government and corporate corruption, and official deceit. WikiLeaks, in 2010, published those materials in partnership with some of the largest media outlets in the world, including the New York Times, the Guardian, Der Spiegel, Le Monde and El Pais, outlets that published many of the same secret documents that form the basis of the criminal case against Assange.  With these new charges, the Trump administration is aggressively and explicitly seeking to obliterate the last reliable buffer protecting journalism in the United States from being criminalized, a step that no previous administration, no matter how hostile to journalistic freedom, was willing to take. The U.S. government has been eager to prosecute Assange since the 2010 leaks. Until now, though, officials had refrained because they concluded it was impossible to distinguish WikiLeaks' actions from the typical business of mainstream media outlets. Indicting Assange for the act of publishing would thus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For battles with Congress, president reshapes legal defense team...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-attorneys/for-battles-with-congress-trump-reshapes-legal-defense-team-idUSKCN1SY0Y6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump is restructuring his legal team with lawyers more at home...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chancellor warns against dark forces on rise in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/28/europe/angela-merkel-interview-amanpour-intl-grm/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with CNN, German Chancellor Angela Merkel says "Germany can and will not uncouple itself" from the dark forces that are finding mainstream support in Germany and other parts of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders 2020 looks like Sanders 2016, challenges and all...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3d579c251467429e909d75575cb403fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It was supposed to be different this time. But three months into his second presidential campaign, Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders is struggling with some of the same...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Venezuela, criminals feel the pinch of economic crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1366318d49894d32aab3d6e6354f40a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — The feared street gangster El Negrito sleeps with a pistol under his pillow and says he's lost track of his murder count. But despite his hardened demeanor, he's quick to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK use eroding in USA...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2019-05-facebook-eroding-social-media-pressure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's efforts to crack down on misinformation and sensational content have reduced the time spent at the leading social network eroding, researchers said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg Power Challenged...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-shareholder-meeting-challenge-zuckerberg-100016357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For the fifth straight year, Julie Goodridge has submitted a proposal to Facebook Inc.’s board of directors for a shareholder vote at the company’s annual meeting. Her suggestion: Change the company’s dual-class voting structure — under which Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China deploys Confucius in bid to boost religion controls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14e9ccf4af134e74b6220e27342afc2a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China has begun five-day Confucian culture immersion courses for religious leaders in the sage's hometown as part of a campaign to extend government control over faith communities...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
NYC LYFT Passenger Caught on Camera Savagely Beating Driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Lyft-Passenger-Queens-New-York-Caught-On-Camera-Brutally-Attacking-Driver-News-NYC-510493261.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are looking for the Lyft passenger who was caught on camera savagely attacking his driver in the middle of a ride in Queens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look over here! Dems struggle for recognition in outsize field...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/look-over-here-democratic-candidates-struggle-recognition-outsize-field-n1010556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some contenders are having a tough time busting out. Experts say that's what happens when there are too many choices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer From Hell Coming to U.S. Airports...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-28/a-summer-from-hell-is-coming-to-u-s-airports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Guard talks tough, says has no fear of war with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/47e7b05b2dbf44a6978a66715bc21805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran's influential Revolutionary Guard said Tuesday it doesn't fear a possible war with the United States and claimed that America hasn't grown in power in recent years — the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Top 10 candidates...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445504-the-top-10-democrats-in-the-2020-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race for the Democratic presidential nomination is gathering pace. The first debates will be held next month in Miami, even though the Iowa caucuses will not take place until February 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli election rerun looms as Netanyahu talks falter...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israeli-election-rerun-looms-netanyahu-talks-falter-093759178.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu urgently worked to break a deadlock in coalition negotiations Tuesday as the once far-fetched possibility of fresh general elections only months after April polls loomed ever larger. Netanyahu has until Wednesday night to reach a coalition deal, but he has been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dayton devastated...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcpo.com/weather/weather-news/it-looks-like-this-entire-neighborhood-is-destroyed-tornadoes-hit-miami-valley-area-in-ohio</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcpo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storms and reported tornadoes brought grim images to the Miami Valley: Homes reduced to splinters. A high school with its roof torn off by wind. A snowplow clearing debris from I-75.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People trapped; Buildings cut in half...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7076851/Extremely-dangerous-tornado-touches-Ohio.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple tornadoes tore through Indiana and Ohio on Monday night with the first touching down at around 11pm. The National Weather Service described the first tornado as 'extremely dangerous'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornados leave trail of destruction across Ohio, Indiana...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3ae113ae56e74e7fa8f6248de7edf05e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKVILLE, Ohio (AP) — A rapid-fire line of apparent tornadoes tore across Indiana and Ohio overnight, packed so closely together that one crossed the path carved by another. The storms...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 dead as man stabs 16 schoolgirls, 2 adults in rampage near Tokyo...</title>
      <link>https://english.kyodonews.net/news/2019/05/cd2e013a9973-urgent-11-including-elementary-school-children-stabbed-in-city-near-tokyo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.kyodonews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen pupils waiting for their school bus and two adults were stabbed by a man wielding knives in Kawasaki near Tokyo, leaving an 11-year-old girl and a man dead, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida bans childlike sex dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandoweekly.com/Blogs/archives/2019/05/24/florida-gov-ron-desantis-signs-bill-outlawing-child-sex-dolls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandoweekly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On&amp;nbsp;Thursday Gov. Ron DeSantis signed into law legislation that bans the sale or possession of child-like sex dolls after it unanimously passed the Florida Legislature....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'American Soil' Increasingly Foreign Owned...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/27/723501793/american-soil-is-increasingly-foreign-owned</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of acres of U.S. farmland held by foreign-owned investors has doubled in the past two decades, raising alarm bells in farming communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5,000 LEECHES found in carry-on...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article230885464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have day off? Try doing nothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/memorial-day-how-to-make-use-of-your-day-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We need to be OK with accepting the day for what it is — which is a day off," says New York Times Smarter Living editor Tim Herrera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As ER wait times grow, more patients leave against medical advice...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/as-er-wait-times-grow-more-patients-leave-against-medical-advice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowded emergency rooms are likely to blame. In 2017, the median ER wait time for patients before admission as inpatients to California hospitals was 336 minutes — or more than 5½ hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OF EU</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6152801851684d879999dbcdc62c1e0f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — France's pro-EU president and the leader of Italy's euroskeptic, far-right movement jockeyed for the role of chief powerbroker on the continent Monday after elections to the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY HORROR:  1-year-old killed, 6 family members hospitalized in golf cart mishap...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/1-year-old-north-carolina-boy-killed-in-golf-cart-accident/5318951/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The North Carolina Highway Patrol says a 1-year-old boy was killed when the golf cart he and family members were riding in hit a pothole and overturned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan bus stop stabbing wounds dozens... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20190528_12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www3.nhk.or.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japanese police say 16 people, including schoolchildren, have been injured in a stabbing in Kawasaki City near Tokyo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The value of $1 in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2019/05/25/us-dollar-how-much-its-worth-value-in-every-state/39501091/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The value of a dollar ranges by more than 30 cents across the US, depending on the state. In Mississippi, $1 is worth $1.16; in Hawaii, only 84 cents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 die -- in 10 days...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7075541/American-climber-dies-descent-summit-Mount-Everest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher John Kulish, 62, scaled the 8,850 metre (29,035 feet) peak from the normal Southeast Ridge route in the morning but died suddenly at South Col after descending from the summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 42 inmates strangled to death in clashes...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-brazil-violence-prisons/at-least-42-inmates-strangled-to-death-in-amazon-prison-gang-clashes-idUKKCN1SX1X1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 42 prisoners in Brazil were found strangled to death on Monday in four ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger dies on flight after ingesting 246 cocaine packets...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/man-dies-cocaine-flight-mexico-japan-aeromexico-colombia-a8931831.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump attack on Biden echoes left-wing criticism...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/27/donald-trump-joe-biden-crime-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump attacked 2020 Democratic presidential front-runner Joe Biden on Twitter Monday with a critique that liberal outlets have been using for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptop full of most dangerous malware auctions for $1.2M...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/05/27/persistence-of-chaos-malware-laptop-auction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meant as a work of art, this laptop contains six dangerous viruses and sold for $1.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprecedented photo of first known albino giant panda...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/camera-trap-snaps-photo-of-first-known-albino-giant-pan-1835050847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using a motion-activated camera, scientists at Wolong National Nature Reserve in southwest China have snapped a blurry but unprecedented photograph of the world’s first known albino giant panda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>33 shot, 5 killed so far as Chicago 'floods zone' for holiday weekend...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.suntimes.com/crime/2019/5/26/18639572/11-wounded-in-shootings-may-24-may-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.suntimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were killed and three more wounded Sunday in a shooting on the Near West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran, 95, graduates decades after leaving high school for World War II...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfla.com/news/hillsborough-county/world-war-ii-vet-95-gets-high-school-diploma-more-than-70-years-later/2027358262</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Perricone walked across the stage to fetch his diploma Saturday, more than 70 years after leaving school to join the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True crime with gory footage hottest TV trend in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Brazil-true-crime-is-the-hottest-TV-trend-13898873.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO - A gunman bursts into a family's home as they gather for dinner. The father throws a chair at him and is shot. The father falls to the floor. He lifts his head weakly and is shot a final time.  Car chases, lifeless bodies, pools of blood. It's not an action movie - it's just another Brazilian morning show.  As the country battles a historic crime wave that has claimed tens of thousands of lives, the staples that once dominated morning television here - celebrity news, cooking advice, feel-good stories - have been replaced with increasingly gory footage of real violence. And Brazilians cannot get enough of it.  In January, "Primeiro Impacto," a show that focuses exclusively on true-crime footage, became the second-most-popular morning program on network television.  The gunshots that are fired around the country at night are replayed on television screens the next morning, accompanied by an action-movie soundtrack. The camera zooms in on body bags. Suspects are circled in red.  In a nation suffering a record spike in killing, the fear is palpable - but so is the anger.  "There's no talking to these thugs," says the show's host, known as Marcão do Povo, or Mark of the People. "They deserve a bullet to the back. That's what thugs deserve."  The surge in violence - a record 64,000 people were killed in 2017, many of them in the gang war over the drug trade - has made Brazil one of the most dangerous countries in the world and left Brazilians clamoring for the tough-on-crime approach they see on television.  Politicians are responding. Promises of harsher sentences for criminals and protections for police officers who kill on the job helped catapult the previously obscure right-wing congressman Jair Bolsonaro into Brazil's presidency last November.  "I'm going to stuff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey experiments offer clues on origin of language...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190527-monkey-experiments-offer-clues-origin-language</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkey experiments offer clues on origin of language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuck and Sandberg will defy Canadian subpoena, risking contempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/27/tech/zuckerberg-contempt-canada/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg will not attend a hearing in Ottawa later this week, despite receiving summonses from the Canadian parliament, Facebook confirmed on Monday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
