<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fears raised as Superbug spread far and fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/superbug-from-india-spread-far-and-fast-study-finds-11548633600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gene from an antibiotic-resistant bacteria from India was found 8,000 miles away in the Arctic. Researchers think the gene made the trek in less than three years, raising fears about the speed and scope of so-called superbugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Automation Agenda of Davos Elite...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/25/technology/automation-davos-world-economic-forum.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In public, executives wring their hands over automation’s negative consequences for workers. In private, they talk about how they are racing to automate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Takes Rare Jab At FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-goes-after-fox-news-even-less-understanding-of-wall-than-fake-news-cnn-and-msnbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA KICKOFF DRAWS 20,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2019/01/27/kamala-harris-president-oakland-rally-campaign-kickoff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris kicked off her presidential campaign with a blowout rally in her hometown Sunday, portraying herself as a fighter with the moral force to take on President Trump and unite a divi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO members boost defense spending by $100 billion after Trump called 'delinquents'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/27/nato-members-increase-defence-spending-100-billion-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nato states will increase their defence spending by 100 billion dollars in response to Donald Trump's demands that European allies shoulder a greater financial burden, the alliance's secretary general has said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: 20,000 fans at Harris hometown launch!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/kamala-harris-oakland-rally-presidential-ogawa-13565750.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Kamala Harris, D-Calif., often invokes her East Bay upbringing as the child of civil-rights activists to explain her political philosophy. At a rally Sunday in her hometown of Oakland, she officially launched her presidential campaign by tapping those same populist themes. Before an estimated 20,000 people who filled the streets around an American flag-draped Frank Ogawa Plaza, Harris made her opening 2020 pitch: She will be the candidate who is both “a fighter for the people” and someone who can unite a country severed into partisan corners by saying that “we must seek truth, speak truth and fight for the truth.” “People in power are trying to convince us that the villain in our American story is each other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORSI:  I'm going to do my best to tell the truth...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/01/27/corsi-happy-testify-roger-stone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I'm going to tell the truth, to the best of my ability'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scabies outbreaks at facility in NM...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/border-patrol-struggles-with-flood-of-sick-migrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents have spent nearly 20,000 hours since October driving asylum seekers to and from hospitals for medical evaluations, according to newly released Department of Homeland Security data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri school ponders white-only racism workshop...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“white people need to unlearn racism..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish PM says Hitler's Germany responsible for Holocaust, not Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/polish-pm-says-hitlers-germany-responsible-holocaust-not-170210842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hitler's Germany was responsible for the Holocaust, not the Nazis, Polish Prime Minister Mateusz Morawiecki said Sunday, as Poland marked 74 years since the liberation of the Auschwitz-Birkenau death camp. "Hitler's Germany fed on fascist ideology... But all the evil came from this (German</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN:  Trump down, but not out...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/26/president-trump-is-down-but-not-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battered, bruised and beaten, Donald Trump faces a grim reality. Halfway through his term, his presidency is at low tide. The polls have cratered and his necessary retreat over using a shutdown to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will cooperate with special counsel?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/beta-story-container/Politics/roger-stone-longtime-president-donald-trump-friend-veteran/story?id=60646251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone spoke to George Stephanopoulos two days after being indicted by special counsel Robert Mueller for lying to Congress, obstruction and witness tampering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet addiction spawns treatment programs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190127105154-wfuzc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-INTERNET/ADDICTION (FEATURE, PIX):FEATURE-The digital drug: Internet addiction spawns U.S. treatment programs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Public sours on direction of country...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/wrong-track-public-sours-nation-s-direction-after-shutdown-n963051</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixty-three percent of Americans say the nation is on the wrong track, according to a new NBC News/Wall Street Journal poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic killings 'highest' in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190127-anti-semitic-killings-2018-highest-decades-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Semitic killings in 2018 'highest' in decades: Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Should you smoke pot in front of kids?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/ideas/2019/01/25/ideas-rosenbaum-should-you-smoke-pot-front-kids/NJlN3g1RdxqJt9qT2PKnoK/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapid legalization of marijuana raises a host of etiquette challenges. Is it an acceptable host gift? How do you consume a long-illegal drug without feeling sketchy?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Arab Nation, Christians, Buddhists and Jews Emerge to Worship...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-arab-nation-christians-buddhists-and-jews-emerge-to-worship-11548594001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restrictions on religious worship have gradually loosened in the United Arab Emirates, which will display a more accommodating stance in February when it hosts Pope Francis on the first visit by a sitting pope to the Arabian Peninsula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., Canadian fighter jets scramble to escort Russian bombers...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/27/us-air-force-canadian-fighter-jets-escort-russian-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Military authorities say U.S. Air Force and Canadian fighter jets were scrambled to escort two Russian bombers that were traveling in the Arctic region near the North American coastline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles outbreak expands in northwest US...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/measles-outbreak-expands-in-northwest-us-1582749/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of confirmed measles cases near Portland grew to 31 on Friday — an outbreak boosted by lower-than-normal vaccination rates in what has been called an anti-vaccination U.S. “h...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet addiction spawns treatment programs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-internet-addiction-feature/the-digital-drug-internet-addiction-spawns-u-s-treatment-programs-idUSKCN1PL0AG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Danny Reagan was 13, he began exhibiting signs of what doctors usually asso...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of vacancies for new border, immigration officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-border-patrol-hiring-20190126-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years after President Trump sought to beef-up border security by hiring 15,000 more agents and officers, his administration has thousands more vacancies than when it began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Cars Still Cheap -- But No Longer Ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-cars-are-still-cheap-but-theyre-no-longer-ugly-11548417621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designers from Rolls-Royce, BMW and elsewhere have been recruited to give Chinese cars more style. Their creations could be headed to a dealership near you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADURO READY TO TALK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics/venezuelas-maduro-denounces-election-call-but-says-ready-to-talk-idUSKCN1PL0CR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's embattled President Nicolas Maduro rejected an international ul...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banksy drawing worth millions stolen in Paris...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/01/26/banksy-drawing-stolen-paris-france-bataclan-concert/2688956002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The image had been drawnÂ on theÂ emergency door of the Bataclan concert hall in memory of a deadly terrorist attack in 2015 that killed 90 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIE BROWN: Sure, I dated Kamala Harris. So what?</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/politics/article/Sure-I-dated-Kamala-Harris-So-what-13562972.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been peppered with calls from the national media about my “relationship” with Kamala Harris, particularly since it became obvious that she was going to run for president. Most of them, I have not returned. Yes, we dated. It was more than 20 years ago. Yes, I may have influenced her career by appointing her to two state commissions when I was Assembly speaker. And I certainly helped with her first race for district attorney in San Francisco. I have also helped the careers of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, Gov. Gavin Newsom, Sen. Dianne Feinstein and a host of other politicians. The difference is that Harris is the only one who, after I helped her, sent word that I would be indicted if I “so much as jaywalked” while she was D.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi students who vanish before US trial span states, decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com//news/2019/01/saudi-students-who-vanish-before-trial-span-states-decades.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A university student from Saudi Arabia facing criminal charges in Ohio vanished in 1988, new evidence that the Saudi government intervened decades before it took similar action in several cases recently uncovered in Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Warren proposing asset forfeiture...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/01/elizabeth-warren-tax-plan-is-asset-forfeiture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren is not proposing a tax; she’s proposing asset forfeiture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby 'twins' have two different fathers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6636879/Baby-twins-two-DIFFERENT-fathers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twins Calder and Alexandra Berney Edwards, from London, are actually half siblings despite being born at the same time, because they don't share paternity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan military attache breaks with Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/latest-news/article225123050.html#storylink=topdigest_latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man identifying himself as Venezuela's military attache in Washington has broken with Nicolas Maduro and says he now will report to an opposition leader trying to wrest control of the government.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
