<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER CHANNEL Segment Erupts as Reporter Nearly Struck By Debris...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-weather-channel-segment-erupts-as-reporter-almost-gets-injured-by-hurricane-laura-debris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Channel reporter Stephanie Abrams had a close call live on the air Thursday morning when she was almost hit by debris as she reported on Hurricane Laura, as staff could be heard freaking out off-camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest Ironman plans to keep competing into his 90s...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-oldest-ironman-plans-keep-060252698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hiromu Inada, 87, already has a certificate on his wall that confirms his status as the world&amp;#39;s oldest Ironman, but the Japanese man is still pounding away on his training bike and hopes to continue competing into his 90s. In 2018 at the age of 85 years and 328 days, Inada went to Kailua-Kona in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Newsom proves he's no deer in headlights while managing crises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-proves-hes-no-deer-070050084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now wildfires and blackouts are piled on top of a COVID-19 pandemic — a strange virus that has infected more than 680,000 people and killed more than 12,000 in California. You&amp;#39;d think that might place any governor at political risk, but it apparently hasn&amp;#39;t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Makes His Case After Four Years of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0021462b31830a5cadca8f02d03d01dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Four years ago, Donald Trump accepted the Republican Party’s nomination for president with a dark convention speech that painted a dystopian portrait of America in decline and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100 Bush-McCain-Romney alums go for Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook/2020/08/27/new-more-than-100-bush-mccain-romney-alums-go-for-biden-490201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And major league sports come to a screeching halt over the police shooting of Jacob Blake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Bigger Bubble Than Tech?</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/gold-is-bigger-bubble-than-tech--says--63-billion-asset-manager-57691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of gold has gotten disconnected from fundamentals, he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Service under fire for role...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/513856-park-service-under-fire-for-role-in-gop-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Park Service (NPS) is in hot water with ethics watchdogs for a slickly produced video promoting President Trump along with its plans to host a fireworks spectacle after his acceptance speech at the Repu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Michigan, Cracks Emerge in the Pro-Trump Wall...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/27/in-michigans-upper-peninsula-some-cracks-emerge-in-the-pro-trump-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. IGNACE, Mich. — Michigan’s Upper Peninsula is known for many things: its enviable location, nestled among three of the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Teen arrested after 2 killed during unrest in Kenosha...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/97a0700564fb52d7f664d8de22066f88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (AP) — A white, 17-year-old police admirer was arrested Wednesday after two people were shot to death during a third straight night of protests in Kenosha over the police shooting of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offers assurances about the private Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/3-takeaways-from-the-third-night-of-the-15518001.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican National Convention held its third of four prime-time sessions on Wednesday night, with Vice President Mike Pence headlining and a younger generation of lesser-known Republicans featured on the undercard.  Below, some takeaways.  - - -  1. Pence's and others assurances about the private Trump  Picking up on a thread from first lady Melania Trump's speech on Tuesday night, a focal point Wednesday was assuring that, whatever the public appearance, President Donald Trump is a caring, empathetic and driven leader behind closed doors.  Pence noted that Trump has "certainly kept things interesting" and emphasized their difference in styles. But he said Trump's motivation is clear.  "Over the past four years, I've worked closely with our president. I've seen him when the cameras are off," Pence said. "Americans see President Trump in lots of different ways, but there's no doubt how President Trump sees America. He sees America for what it is: a nation that has done more good in this world than any other, a nation that deserves far more gratitude than grievance. And if you want a president who falls silent when our heritage is demeaned or insulted, then he's not your man."  The "grievance" line was particularly notable, given how much time Trump spends on such things.  White House officials Kellyanne Conway and Kayleigh McEnany both spoke of private moments with Trump. McEnany noted that Trump reached out to her when she underwent a preventive double mastectomy in 2018, before she became White House press secretary.  "As I recovered, my phone rang again," McEnany said. "It was President Trump calling to check on me. I was blown away. Here was the leader of the free world, carrying about my circumstance."  Conway spoke of Trump's empathy and attentiveness to those...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention Stays On Pre-Recorded Script During Night Of Storm...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/mike-pence-republican-convention-review-donald-trump-hurricane-laura-kenosha-shootings-night-3-1203024514/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the most unobtrusive man in America thought tonight was his moment in the spotlight at the Republican National Convention, Mike Pence learned the hard way that Donald Trump always gets the last …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x0JDqw_fFkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence's Full Remarks at the 2020 Republican National Convention. #RNC2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How shocked are we that 17-year-olds with rifles decided they had to maintain order when no one else would?'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/tucker-carlson-on-kenosha-violence-how-shocked-are-we-that-17-year-olds-with-rifles-decided-they-had-to-maintain-order-when-no-one-else-would/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"People in charge from the governor of Wisconsin on down refused to enforce the law. They stood back and watched Kenosha burn. So are we really surprised this looting and arson accelerated to mur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLLYWOOD SAYS FIRE TUCKER CARLSON...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/tucker-carlson-backlash-kenosha-shooting-fox-news-1234750361/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News host Tucker Carlson received immediate backlash on Twitter after saying Kyle Rittenhouse, who was arrested and charged with first-degree intentional homicide for the shootings of two prote…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lara gets tripped up by Lincoln 'quote'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/934050/that-famous-lincoln-quote-lara-trumps-rnc-speech-never-said</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Albert Einstein once notably stated, 'The problem with quotes you find on the internet is they are often untrue.' Lara Trump, President Trump's daughter-in-law, learned that the hard way on Wednesday night. During her speech at the Republican National Convention, Trump declared that Abraham Lincoln 'once famously said, 'America will never be destroyed from the outside. If we falter and lose our freedoms, it will be because we destroyed ourselves.'' Last year, a Facebook meme crediting Lincoln with that statement went viral in right-wing circles, but both PolitiFact and Snopes have debunked it. Lincoln historian Christian McWhirter said this is a 'corruption' of something Lincoln said about 'the perpetuation of our political institutions' during a speech delivered in Springfield, Illinois, on Jan. 27, 1838. Lincoln asked the crowd, 'At what point then is the approach of danger to be expected? I answer, if it ever reach us, it must spring up amongst us. It cannot come from abroad. If destruction be our lot, we must ourselves be its author and finisher. As a nation of freemen, we must live through all time, or die by suicide.' It turns out, Lincoln's words actually are eerily relevant today. Michael Burlingame of the University of Illinois Springfield explained to PolitiFact that Lincoln was 'denouncing mob violence which would lead to chaos, provoking the public to demand law and order, which would be provided by an ambitious leader who would rule tyrannically.' Catherine Garcia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence warns 'you won't be safe' under Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-evangelical-vp-pence-gets-203300270.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump&amp;#39;s vice president Mike Pence took center stage at the Republican convention Wednesday to warn voters they &amp;quot;won&amp;#39;t be safe in Joe Biden&amp;#39;s America&amp;quot; -- and cast Trump as their protector against the &amp;quot;radical left&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM CHASER LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o3kRgdy38AE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow me LIVE on the map here: http://bit.ly/WX4TV-Laura If you like what you see here, please help out with a bit to cover the costs of intercepting and li...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RbYz1orpVw0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before her current role, Kellyanne Conway was the Founder and President of The Polling Company, Inc./WomanTrend, a privately held, woman-owned corporation. K...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KELLYANNE SAYS GOODBYE...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1375673/kellyanne-conway-hails-family-faith-freedom-rnc-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KELLYANNE Conway has hailed “family, faith and freedom” amid her personal turmoil of her daughter’s “estrangement” and the death of her father. Speaking at the Republi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials pressured CDC to change testing guidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/26/brett-giroir-coronavirus-testing-cdc-402524</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health experts have questioned the scientific basis for the testing change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerns about uniformed Marines on camera dismissed by White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2020/08/26/white-house-military-officials-dismiss-concerns-about-uniformed-marines-on-camera-during-republican-convention/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two service members were performing official duties for the president, Marine Corps officials said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stabbing of NYPD cop labeled 'ISIS inspired'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/feds-man-who-ambushed-cops-was-interested-in-isis-and-other-terror-groups</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dzenan Camovic was indicted on state charges including attempted aggravated murder and federal charges including theft and unlawful possession of a firearm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China fires missiles into South Sea in 'warning to USA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1327725/world-war-3-china-missiles-US-south-china-sea-latest-donald-trump-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has launched two missiles in the South China Sea in a furious warning to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOYA CEO removed as speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/national-world/goya-ceo-removed-as-gop-convention-speaker/6GROQRGLNJFU5CMX6LYYBCH7NE/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A speaker who had been expected to deliver remarks on the third night of the Republican National Convention has been unexpectedly removed from the program hours before airtime. Another speaker's appearance is up in the air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business world braces for blue sweep...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/513623-business-world-braces-for-blue-sweep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street and business groups are bracing for the possibility of a blue sweep in Washington that would leave Democrats in charge of the White House and both chambers of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials investigate sailor for arson of Navy warship in San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/513869-officials-investigate-sailor-for-arson-of-navy-warship-that-burned-in-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are investigating a sailor for arson in connection to a fire that engulfed the USS Bonhomme Richard in July,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600,000+ Ordered to Evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bac3a77342fb9d59ada088e9133cb748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DELCAMBRE, La. (AP) — Laura strengthened Wednesday into a menacing Category 4 hurricane, raising fears of a 20-foot storm surge that forecasters said would be "unsurvivable” and capable of sinking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver watching movie when autopilot TESLA crashed into police car...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/distracted-driving/tesla-autopilot-crash-385914</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As his Tesla operated in autopilot mode on a North Carolina highway, a motorist was watching a movie on his phone when the vehicle crashed into a police car early this morning, investigators say. Ac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC NIGHT 3...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200826234123-zt2uu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-Pence to make economic pitch at convention as Trump wades into Wisconsin protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOYA CEO removed as speaker...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75f9fa75bcf07ff87dd3c668243ea102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the Republican National Convention (all times local): 5:15 p.m. A speaker who had been expected to deliver remarks on the third night of the Republican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L I V E...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch 24/7 live news video and breaking news coverage on abcnews.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peoria removing all presidents from school names...</title>
      <link>https://www.pjstar.com/news/20200825/no-more-thomas-jefferson-peoria-school-board-considers-name-changes-of-six-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pjstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEORIA — Peoria Public Schools District 150 Board of Education Vice President Gregory Wilson wants the board to reconsider the names of six district</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Postpones All Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/nba-boycott-live-updates-jacob-blake-shooting-leads-to-bucks-magic-lakers-blazers-okc-rockets-postponement/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA has announced that all three games have been postponed Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could injectable microrobots one day run in your veins?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/could-injectable-microrobots-one-day-150718616.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have created an army of microscopic four-legged robots too small to see with the naked eye that walk when stimulated by a laser and could be injected into the body through hypodermic needles, a study said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Beats MSNBC, All Broadcast Nets COMBINED...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/08/republican-convention-ratings-donald-trump-1203023920/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican National Convention viewership rose to 18 million across six networks on the second night Tuesday, when First Lady Melania Trump was the marquee speaker. The rise was a significant incre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASHPOST: Owner 'personally involved'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/57bc1263669d83c5b8a9d1f1e4326829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Washington Post on Wednesday reported additional examples of workplace sexual harassment inside the Washington Football Team organization, and allegations that owner Dan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Possibly Cured of HIV -- Without Medical Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-Woman-May-Have-Been-Cured-of-HIV-Without-15516582.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who was infected with HIV in 1992 may be the first person cured of the virus without a risky bone marrow transplant or even medications, researchers reported Wednesday.  In an additional 63 people in their study who controlled the infection without drugs, HIV apparently was sequestered in the body in such a way that it could not reproduce, the scientists also reported. The finding suggested that these people may have achieved a "functional cure."  The research, published in the journal Nature, outlines a new mechanism by which the body may suppress HIV, visible only now because of advances in genetics. The study also offers hope that some small number of infected people who have taken antiretroviral therapy for many years may similarly be able to suppress the virus and stop taking the drugs, which can exact a toll on the body.  "It does suggest that treatment itself can cure people, which goes against all the dogma," said Dr. Steve Deeks, an AIDS expert at the University of California, San Francisco, and an author of the new study.  The woman is Loreen Willenberg, 66, of California, already famous among researchers because her body has suppressed the virus for decades after verified infection. Only two other people - Timothy Brown of Palm Springs, California, and Adam Castillejo of London - have been declared cured of HIV. Both men underwent grueling bone marrow transplants for cancer that left them with immune systems resistant to the virus.  Bone marrow transplants are too risky to be an option for most people infected with HIV, but the recoveries raised hopes that a cure was possible. In May, researchers in Brazil reported that a combination of HIV treatments may have led to another cure, but other experts said more tests were needed to confirm that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCKS boycott NBA playoff game...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/id/29747523/bucks-not-taking-court-game-5-vs-magic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Milwaukee Bucks have decided to boycott Game 5 on Wednesday against the Orlando Magic to protest the police shooting of Jacob Blake in Kenosha, Wisconsin, on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALESFORCE cuts 1,000 jobs on day stock hits record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/26/salesforce-cuts-about-1000-jobs-even-as-stock-has-record-surge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salesforce reported blowout earnings on Tuesday, and then informed about 1,000 employees that their jobs are being eliminated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Elite controllers' offer clues...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hiv-positive-elite-controllers-offer-160201132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A handful of people with HIV are able to control the disease without treatment, and now research on these so-called elite controllers is offering clues in the search for a cure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwanese releases video of troops 'fending off attack from mainland'...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/diplomacy/article/3098436/taiwanese-military-releases-video-troops-fending-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any attempt at invasion ‘would have only the effect of triggering the wrath and antipathy of Taiwan’s people’, defence ministry says in statement accompanying footage of training exercise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to defy guidance and continue quarantines...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-york-will-continue-mandatory-quarantines-despite-cdcs-changing-guidance-2020-08-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state, along with New Jersey and Connecticut, will continue to require travelers coming from some areas to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana test for stressed-out zoo elephants...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/marijuana-test-stressed-warsaw-zoo-163033450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Warsaw zoo said Wednesday it will start giving its elephants medical marijuana as part of a ground-breaking pilot project to test how it reduces their stress levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS reveals 'depressing' fall schedule...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/tv/cbs-fall-tv-schedule-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It'll be 'Star Trek: Discovery' reruns and a ton of reality TV on CBS this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tenn. Cops Raid Wrong Home, Point Guns at Naked Woman...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/08/25/tennessee-cops-raid-wrong-home-point-guns-at-naked-woman-while-looking-for-teen-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nashville officers tried to smooth things over with groceries. A traumatized Azaria Hines says what she really needs is "a peace of mind."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rioters try to set fire to Portland City Hall ablaze...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/26/portland-rioters-try-to-burn-city-hall-during-protests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unlawful assembly was declared, with police urging the crowd via loud speaker to disperse or face arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topless women defended by French govt...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/french-sunbathing-defense-scli-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might not have the same gravitas as liberté, égalité, fraternité, but the very French tradition of topless sunbathing has been defended as a vital freedom by a government official after a local police force tried to get a group of women to cover up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT: School trans bathroom policy unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/46c768d4350f782f83e47209d884f924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — A federal appeals court ruled Wednesday that a Virginia school board’s transgender bathroom ban is unconstitutional and discriminated against a transgender male student who...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Becomes World's First $200 Billion Man!</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jeff-bezos-200-billion-fortune-amazon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos became the world's first person ever to hit a net worth of $200 billion on Wednesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Houston Could Be 'America's Chernobyl'...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/environment/a33797370/houston-hurricane-americas-chernobyl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a violent storm hits this crucial shipping channel, it may spell disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>80 Years After Hindenburg, Startup Pitches Hydrogen Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/eighty-years-after-hindenburg-startup-pitches-hydrogen-flight/ar-BB18o41J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and Falwell: Inside life of luxury before sex scandal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/26/inside-jerry-falwell-jr-s-life-of-luxury-before-sex-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Falwell, 58, portrayed himself as the consummate family man on Instagram, posting photos of his daughter’s picture-perfect engagement and riding horses on his sprawling farm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17-Year-Old In Custody...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/08/26/authorities-in-kenosha-search-for-gunman-who-shot-three-people-killing-two-during-another-night-of-unrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one video on social media, a young man with the rifle can be hard saying “I just killed somebody” as he runs away from the scene after several shots rang out at a car dealership in Kenosha.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.weatherbug.com/maps/?layerId=Radar.Global&amp;center=29.29017231402996,-92.89808281248798,6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weatherbug.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest weather radar map with temperature, wind chill, heat index, dew point, humidity and wind speed for Pretty Prairie, Kansas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gut Health Linked To Air Quality, Unprecedented Study Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/gut-health-poor-air-quality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find ozone has the greatest impact on gut health. Those with higher exposure to this gaseous pollutant have less variety in their gut bacteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewd cheerleader videos, more allegations of sexual harassment paint disturbing picture of Washington's NFL franchise...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Lewd-cheerleader-videos-sexist-rules-15516189.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER Reporters Rush to Aid Victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/daily-caller-reporters-at-scene-of-shooting-in-kenosha-capture-dramatic-footage-rush-to-aid-victim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graphic footage captured by the Daily Caller showed some of Tuesday evening's violence in Kenosha, Wisconsin, where at least two people were killed and a third was injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oahu restores stay-at-home-order...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/2020/08/25/live-us-surgeon-general-joins-governor-honolulus-mayor-discuss-covid-response-oahu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement comes as Hawaii sees another triple-digit daily increase in new COVID-19 infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  'What Melania wants, Melania gets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8666375/Melania-complained-Ivanka-didnt-respect-behaved-like-Apprentice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Melania Trump's former close friend and staffer Stephanie Winston Wolkoff is set to release her book Melania and Me next week. It includes claims the First Lady trashed Trump's children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8665383/One-shot-dead-two-wounded-BLM-protesters-defy-curfew-Kenosha.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were killed and another wounded in Kenosha, Wisconsin on Tuesday night during clashes between protesters and militia following a wave of looting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians denounce QAnon as 'cult,' 'satanic movement'...</title>
      <link>https://www.christianpost.com/news/evangelical-leaders-denounce-qanon-as-political-cult-satanic-movement.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.christianpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Christian leaders, including a couple of prominent conservative evangelicals, have denounced the conspiracy theory movement gaining traction in conservative circles known as QAnon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guilfoyle went from San Francisco's first lady to bashing California at the RNC...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kimberly-guilfoyle-went-san-franciscos-031506609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Guilfoyle, a former Fox News personality and current Trump campaign surrogate, used her RNC speech to bash California, her home state, run by Gavin Newsom, her ex-husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Isn't Running Against Biden. He's Trolling the Press...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-isnt-building-a-case-against-biden-hes-running-a-convention-to-troll-the-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and his team openly flouted ethics laws on Tuesday night. They don’t care. In fact, they love the anger it produces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER FORT HOOD DEATH:  Missing soldier's body found hanging in tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1371084/missing-fort-hood-soldier-sexual-abuse-found-hanged-texas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MISSING Fort Hood soldier who reported sexual abuse was allegedly found hanged – becoming the twelfth death linked to the base this year. Cops said the body believed to be that of missing Sgt Eld…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Suit, Proclaimed Dead, Alive and Well For Top Tailors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/fashion/the-suit-proclaimed-dead-is-alive-and-well-for-top-tailors/ar-BB18nOdT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONSTER</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-08-26-hurricane-laura-forecast-rapid-intensification-texas-louisiana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our latest, complete Hurricane Laura forecast briefing, and how it could impact Texas, Louisiana and areas farther inland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions raise Taiwan conflict fears...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-taiwan-china-security-analysis-idUKKBN25M0W1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Numerous Chinese and U.S. military exercises, Taiwan missiles tracking Chinese fighters and plummeting China-U.S. ties make for a heady cocktail of tension that is raising fears of conflict touched off by a crisis over Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/julio_rosas11/status/1298474730966659072?s=21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Republicans will regret...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/933611/trumps-rnc-role-much-bigger-mistake-than-republicans-realize</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Letting Trump completely dominate the convention could have consequences for a party that's more popular than he is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best and Worst Moments From RNC Night 2...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/26/republican-convention-best-and-worst-moments-from-night-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to Opinion’s commentary for Night 2 of the Republican National Convention. In this special feature, Times Opinion writers rank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Armed Citizens' Protect City From 'Thug Looting Scumbags'...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/08/25/armed-group-hoping-to-protect-buildings-confronts-protesters-on-third-night-of-clashes-in-kenosha/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters exchanged words with the armed group as they vowed to protect the city from continued looting and burning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention giving platform to some with fringe views...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/865136eb0e61e763b6780ba30cfa4dd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An advocate of “household voting” in which husbands get the final say. A woman who has argued that school sex ed programs are “grooming” children to be sexualized by predators...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600,000+ Ordered to Evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/71cfc73402496d4ae01f5abbc36b856a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GALVESTON, Texas (AP) — Hurricane Laura rapidly gained strength on Wednesday, forecast to become an “extremely powerful Category 4 hurricane” when it strikes Texas and Louisiana. Officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First lady makes her case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5e5eb504c3b0b570639a800e671c4657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — First lady Melania Trump portrayed her husband as an authentic, uncompromising leader in a Rose Garden address as President Donald Trump turned to family, farmers and the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC abruptly changes position on when to get tested...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/stunning-reversal-cdc-abruptly-position-tested/story?id=72621714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After weeks of encouraging people to get tested if they think they have been exposed, the CDC this week abruptly changed course and said testing might not be necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewd cheerleader videos, more allegations of sexual harassment paint disturbing picture of Washington's NFL franchise...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/2020/08/26/redskins-cheerleaders-video-daniel-snyder-washington/?arc404=true</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest allegations arrive at a perilous time in Daniel Snyder's ownership of the Washington Football Team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane set to rain on parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-mike-pence-republican-convention-trump-20200826-4sacsgbdkvdtdby3r6owu4f7vm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between ongoing civil unrest in Kenosha, Wisconsin and Hurricane Laura expected to make landfall later today, the RNC will be challenged to find focus in tonight's rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCUNIVERSAL Investigating Ron Meyer as Actress Affair Expands to More Moguls...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/nbcuniversal-investigating-ron-meyer-as-charlotte-kirk-affair-expands-to-more-moguls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space oddity: Bacteria can survive cosmic trip...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200826-space-oddity-bacteria-can-survive-cosmic-trip-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space oddity: bacteria can survive cosmic trip, study shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing space station in Argentina shrouded in mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1327190/china-news-beijing-space-station-argentina-patagonia-centre-donald-trump-spt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has a mysterious space station in Argentina, which is said to be for civilian use, but reports to the People's Liberation Army (PLA) and is shrouded in secrecy, leaving locals convinced it's "not a scientific research base".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China fires missiles into South Sea in 'warning to USA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-chinese-military-fires-two-22582179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has fired two medium-range weapons into the South China Sea. According to reports in Asia, a source has claimed it is a warning to the US amid ongoing tensions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Veterans Pass Milestone in Self-Flying Plane Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-08-26/spacex-veterans-pass-milestone-in-self-flying-plane-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How president could pull off another upset...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-upset-biden-2020-election-da37cdd6-1b96-4377-9584-9df9f2554055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are several signs that should give the Trump-is-toast self-assured pause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosion imminent? One of world's most dangerous lakes growing in Hawaii volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article245235215.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France 'turning into new Saudi Arabia' in row over topless female sunbathing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/france-turning-new-saudi-arabia-22580669</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media users say officers telling women to cover up on the beach is evidence of creeping "prudishness", "fascism" and "body-phobia" in the famously nudity-friendly country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Fort Hood soldier's body found hanging in tree...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elder-fernandez-missing-fort-hood-soldier-body-found-hanging-tree-family-lawyer-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She says it was discovered hanging in a tree. Police in Texas say foul play isn't suspected and positive identification was pending completion of forensic work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu vows 'forceful' response if more attacks from Lebanon...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200826-netanyahu-vows-forceful-response-if-more-attacks-from-lebanon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu vows 'forceful' response if more attacks from Lebanon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Berlin bans protests against anti-virus measures...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e560dc916fa9cad96d98df0ba8bcc29d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany will end mandatory coronavirus tests for travelers returning from high-risk areas abroad and again focus its testing strategy on people with symptoms or possible exposure to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Erdogan warns Greece against taking 'path to ruin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.presstv.com/Detail/2020/08/26/632647/Turkey-Greece-Mediterranean-path-to-ruin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.presstv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan warns Greece against making mistakes that would pave the way to its “ruin,” as the two countries remain locked up in a dispute over energy resources in the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un Regime Baffles World With Contradictory Signals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-uns-regime-baffles-world-with-contradictory-signals/ar-BB18nTyB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence Role as Top Loyalist May Mean Boom or Bust in 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mike-pences-role-as-top-trump-loyalist-may-mean-boom-or-bust-in-2024/ar-BB18nPgt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using unsleeved elbow to cover cough 'less effective than hand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-8661867/Coughing-uncovered-elbow-lets-droplets-hand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Indian Space Research Organisation created a model of the flow fields of coughs under different types of mouth covering scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing says U.S. spy plane disrupted military exercises...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/26/asia/china-us-u-2-spy-plane-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China says a US Air Force U-2 spy plane flew into a no-fly zone over its military exercises on Tuesday in a what a spokesman called an obvious provocation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Suit, Proclaimed Dead, Alive and Well For Top Tailors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-suit-proclaimed-dead-is-alive-and-well-for-some-tailors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Suit, Proclaimed Dead, Is Alive and Well ForÂ Top Tailors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors Hoard Gold, Bitcoin, Whisky to Soothe Inflation Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/fearing-inflation-investors-hedge-with-gold-bitcoin-and-whisky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors Hoard Gold, Bitcoin, and Whisky to Soothe Inflation Fear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bette Midler ripped for mocking first lady...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/513693-bette-midler-roasted-for-xenophobic-melania-trump-tweets-get-that-illegal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainer Bette Midler was ripped on social media after mocking Melania Trump's accent during the first lady's Republican National Committee speech from the Rose Garden late Tuesday and for referring to her as an “illegal alien.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does Covid Hit Men Harder? New Clue...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/26/why-does-the-coronavirus-hit-men-harder-a-new-clue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus may infect anyone, young or old, but older men are up to twice as likely to become severely</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
