<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Early Test Case' for China-Led World...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-early-test-case-for-a-china-led-world/ar-AANFZIY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing’s policies now that the Taliban is in charge will provide clues as to how it views global leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon masks required outdoors...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-health-oregon-coronavirus-pandemic-947bd5fe02d802978cf4318f5ab93e40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — People in Oregon, regardless of vaccination status, will once again be required to wear masks in most public outdoor settings — including large outdoor events where physical distancing is not possible — beginning Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Cop Fired for Saying N-Word...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aqwz5/a-black-cop-was-fired-for-saying-the-n-word-he-finally-got-his-job-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delvin White, a Tampa School Resource Officer, was fired last March. He just got his job back this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House authorizes $3.5 trillion of spending as national debt climbs to $29 trillion...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/government/congress/democratic-led-house-authorizes-35-trillion-spending-national-debt-climbs-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pelosi was ultimately able to secure yes votes from nine moderate House Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvanian who coughed on market produce, claimed virus gets jail...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-3600f8f977c8105c3030641787149873</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILKES-BARRE, Pa. (AP) — A Pennsylvania woman who pleaded guilty to coughing and spitting on food at a supermarket in the early days of the coronavirus pandemic was sentenced Tuesday to at least a year in jail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Expect a 'red shift'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/ballots-Gavin-Newsom-recall-counting-when-how-long-16405981.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 2020 presidential election, a few critical swing states reported Election Day...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee Admits to Suspicions About 'Official Explanations' of 9/11 Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/spike-lee-admits-to-suspicions-about-official-explanations-of-9-11-attacks-i-got-questions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spike Lee has admitted to questioning the "official explanations" of the 9/11 World Trade Center attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Herschel Walker running for Senate in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/politics-blog/breaking-herschel-walker-is-running-for-us-senate-in-georgia/6GZ3BDZBHJHRFFJA76PT2K2XLA/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia football legend Herschel Walker launched a campaign for the U.S. Senate at the urging of former President Donald Trump, bringing both his high-profile celebrity and his untested political background to one of the premier national contests on the 2022 ballot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge Funds Hot Again...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/hedge-funds-hot-again-good-040102845.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Confined to their desks in the midst of the global pandemic, former Citadel traders Niall O’Keeffe and Tio Charbaghi made the rounds on video calls to woo investors for their new hedge fund.It should have been a hard sell. The price tag was high for a fledgling fund — a 20% cut of profits on top of a hefty 2% annual fee. The investment style, betting on rising and falling stocks, was out of vogue with investors. The pitch was uncompromising: take it or leave it.And yet, the duo ra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next up for shots: Kids under 12...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/24/health/covid-19-vaccines-kids-next-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Food and Drug Administration has given full approval to Pfizer's coronavirus vaccine for people age 16 and older. Approval for youths ages 12-15 is expected to follow soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS photographer killed after being left behind in retreat...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/investigates/special-report/afghanistan-conflict-reuters-siddiqui/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danish Siddiqui was with soldiers on the front line of an Afghan Special Forces clash with the Taliban. New reporting, and his final photographs, cast light on his final hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD Expands Into Hormone-Therapy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/08/planned-parenthood-jumps-into-the-hormone-therapy-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The abortion group is swiftly becoming one of the nation’s largest providers of ‘gender affirming care,’ without counseling or doctor approval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cellphone catches fire on ALASKA jet upon landing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-3cee65159322ec431f1167807bf77717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATAC, Wash. (AP) — The cellphone of a passenger on an Alaska Airlines jet caught fire after the plane landed at the Seattle–Tacoma International Airport, forcing the crew to deploy evacuation slides to get everyone off, the carrier said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS CEO Blames Banks for Forcing 'Unfair' Porn Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/onlyfans-ceo-banks-forced-unfair-porn-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OnlyFans CEO Tim Stokely on Tuesday said the subscription platform's recent ban on porn is due to "unfair" treatment from banks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNHAPPY ENDING:  Cuomo EMMY rescinded...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824171514-giy9k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK-CUOMO/EMMY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-International TV academy rescinds Cuomo's Emmy for COVID briefings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COINBASE slammed after hackers drain accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/24/coinbase-slammed-for-terrible-customer-service-after-hackers-drain-user-accounts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers of the nation's largest cryptocurrency exchange, Coinbase, say their accounts were taken over by criminals and the company's customer service is poor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Most Diverse Counties in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/slideshows/the-15-most-diverse-counties-in-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communities across the country are melting pots of racial and ethnic diversity, according to new Census Bureau data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONES LEGEND CHARLIE WATTS DEAD AT 80...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/15956054/rolling-stones-drummer-charlie-watts-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROLLING Stones drummer Charlie Watts has died aged 80. The music legend passed away just weeks after pulling out of the band’s US tour following an emergency heart operation. His publicist sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Grid Forecasts Record Power Demand... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/texas-grid-forecasts-record-power-143030205.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Electricity demand in Texas is expected to climb to an all-time high as searing heat continues to grip the region. The National Weather Service issued a hazardous weather outlook for North and Central Texas on Tuesday because of hot and humid conditions that can make it feel like 107 degrees Fahrenheit (42 Celsius). Power consumption on the state’s main grid may surge to a record 75,094 megawatts in the hour ending at 6 p.m. local time, according to the Electric Reliability Counci</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARNIVAL passenger who tested positive on cruise dies ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/carnival-passenger-who-tested-positive-for-coronavirus-on-cruise-dies/ar-AANGPQG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cruise line said it was unlikely the woman caught the virus on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says no end  before spring 2022 -- at earliest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-fauci-spring-2022-20210824-qzhyfahxmjgm7gh43omisyfrqm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world-renowned infectious disease expert predicted the coming months will remain very difficult, with high caseloads and deaths especially in places with low vaccination rates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk warns 'old world dying in blaze'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-sends-spacex-fans-24823480</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla CEO Elon Musk confused and baffled his fans when he wrote out a message that fans speculated meant the end of the world. He appeared to allude to a 'war' looming on the Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican congressional candidate suing Candace Owens for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/politics/bs-md-pol-klacik-owens-lawsuit-20210823-wjt2fepudjcrfbu6wnjaktmpo4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Klacik, a former Maryland congressional candidate, is suing conservative commentator Candace Owens for $20 million in damages over an Instagram video Owens made in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Nightmare: If Something Happens to Feinstein...</title>
      <link>https://ckarchive.com/b/75u7h8hrzvd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ckarchive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;​View in Browser​ ​ ​ Welcome back to The Powers That Be, a private email about politics, media, and technology. I’m Peter Hamby, the host of Snap’s Good Luck America and a foun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN APPROVAL CRASHES TO 41%</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2021/08/24/afghanistan-woes-sink-bidens-approval-41-usa-today-suffolk-poll/8244854002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For President Biden, the cost of the war's chaotic end has been steep. His overall job-approval rating is 41% approve versus 55% who disapprove.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROAD TO AIRPORT NOW BLOCKED...</title>
      <link>https://www.airlive.net/breaking-taliban-have-blocked-the-road-leading-to-kabul-airport-for-non-foreigners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airlive.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taliban have blocked the road leading to Kabul Airport, the terrorist group’s spokesman, Zabiullah Mujahid, has stated. The spokesperson added that from now on, only foreign nationals will be allowed to travel to the airport – the only way out of the country not involving crossing Taliban checkpoints. Mujahid called on Afghanis, who had flocked…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'zero-click' attack evades iPhone security protections...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2021/08/24/nso-pegasus-bahrain-iphone-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The attacks circumvents Apple's new security feature, BlastDoor, built into all versions of iOS 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates run wild on Rikers amid staffing crisis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/inmates-run-wild-on-rikers-island-amid-staffing-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inmates are running wild on Rikers Island amid a staffing crunch that’s left charges free to stab each other, answer phones and destroy equipment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire TX town closes with half affected by virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/08/24/texas-town-iraan-essentially-closes-covid/8253550002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraan, a small oilfield town in west Texas, has seen nearly half of the town's 1,200 people affected by COVID-19, and the school has shut down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems sped up recall to avoid crises. They're happening anyway...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-sped-up-gavin-newsoms-recall-to-avoid-california-crises-theyre-happening-anyway/ar-AANFV20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once the recall effort against Gov. Gavin Newsom qualified for the ballot, Democrats who control statewide offices had a choice. They could delay the vote or speed it along. They chose to set an early recall election date, and changed state law in order to do so in late June, reasoning that things were looking up as the state re-opened and COVID-19 rates declined. Setting the date on Sept. 14 ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO EVACUATION EXTENSION</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-taliban-demands-finishes-evacuations-24827965</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban has said there will be no extension to the August 31 deadline for getting Americans out of Afghanistan, raising the possibility that thousands could be stuck in the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristol endorses McAuliffe in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569132-bill-kristol-endorses-mcauliffe-in-virginia-governors-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime conservative commentator and vocal critic of former President Trump Bill Kristol on Tuesday endorsed Democratic nominee Terry McAuliffe in the Virginia governor's race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican congressional candidate suing Candace Owens for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/569130-former-gop-congressional-candidate-kimberly-klacik-suing-candace-owens-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Maryland GOP congressional candidate Kimberly Klacik has filed a defamation suit against conservative commentator Candace Owens, seeking $20 million in damages after she said the pundit publicly made false allegations about her that cost he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital has plate-smashing booth for stressed staff...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/delta-variant/1004073/oregon-hospital-has-plate-smashing-booth-for-doctors-and-nurses-stressed-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala flight delayed after potential health issue in Vietnam...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/569133-harris-flight-delayed-after-potential-health-issue-in-vietnam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris's departure from Singapore on Tuesday was delayed for several hours after a report of an unexpected health issue in Hanoi, Vietnam, where she was scheduled to travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO EXTENSIONS FOR EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-taliban-a0f7cfd98704e6c2fca340324699a129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of the CIA met with the Taliban’s top political leader in Kabul, an official said Tuesday, as more reports emerged of abuses in areas held by the fighters, fueling concerns about Afghanistan's future and the fate of those racing to leave the country before the looming U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Ricans Live Longer Than Americans. What's Secret?</title>
      <link>http://brevnews.com/costa-ricans-live-longer-than-us-whats-the-secret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;brevnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Vaxxed Israel Crisis Is Dire Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/ultra-vaccinated-israels-debacle-is-a-dire-warning-to-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I don’t want to frighten you,” Israel’s COVID czar Dr. Salman Zarka told parliament this week. “But… unfortunately, the numbers don’t lie.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX  Exposes Dark Side of Bob Ross Painting Empire...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/netflix-exposes-dark-side-bob-073857675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NetflixBob Ross: Happy Accidents, Betrayal &amp; Greed sounds like the title of a true-crime parody, promising a dark and gritty take on the life of one of America’s cheeriest—and most beloved—artistic figures. Nonetheless, there’s nothing jokey about Joshua Rofé’s Netflix documentary (Aug. 25), which serves as both a loving portrait of the landscape painter who inspired millions to pick up a brush, and a disheartening exposé of the various ways in which his work, and legacy, were exploited by the s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Did Larry Elder Become Front-Runner in CA Gov Race?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/24/how-did-larry-elder-become-a-front-runner-in-californias-governor-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — For a generation, Larry Elder has been an AM radio fixture for millions of Californians, the voice they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All female' NFT exposed as founded -- by 3 men...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/nft-fame-lady-squad-all-female-women-created-fls-men-2021-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fame Lady Squad released the "first female avatar project of all time" this week, but it turned out it was all designed and founded by men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More destructive than first estimated...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824120238-hk0m2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-STORM/TENNESSEE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Tennessee flooding was more destructive than first estimated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFGHAN EVACUATION ON 'WAR FOOTING'</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824103402-ow0mj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 6, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):WRAPUP 6-Afghan evacuation on 'war footing' as G7 meets on pullout deadline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Delta cases show 300 times higher viral load...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210824091123-quxc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SOUTHKOREA (PIX):Delta cases show 300 times higher viral load - S.Korea study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Enormously valuable trove': America's race against data...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/24/taliban-afghan-data-target-allies-506638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having seized Kabul, the Taliban can tap into government databases and communications data to go after U.S. allies who don’t get out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milkshakes off menu as MCDONALD'S hit by supply chain issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/aug/24/mcdonalds-runs-out-of-milkshakes-due-to-supply-chain-issues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortage of lorry drivers reportedly to blame for issue affecting 1,250 outlets in England, Scotland and Wales</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA DIRECTOR SECRET MEET WITH TALIBAN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/cia-director-william-burns-held-secret-meeting-in-kabul-with-taliban-leader-abdul-ghani-baradar/ar-AANG6Hb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden dispatched his top spy amid a frantic effort to evacuate people from Kabul ahead of an Aug. 31 deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Elder leader among CA recall candidates. That might help Newsom?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/larry-elder-is-leader-among-california-recall-candidates-that-might-help-gavin-newsom/ar-AANEhRc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aug. 22—Gov. Gavin Newsom talks about Larry Elder everywhere he goes. During a conversation with Planned Parenthood on Wednesday, Newsom blasted the conservative talk show host for opposing abortion. On Monday, at a campaign event in San Jose, Newsom warned Democratic supporters that an Elder victory in the recall could result in a Republican takeover of Congress. And when he rallied ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Shift, Israel Quietly Allows Jewish Prayer on Temple Mount...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/24/in-shift-israel-quietly-allows-jewish-prayer-on-temple-mount/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM — The Israeli government has long forbidden Jews to pray on the Temple Mount, a site sacred to Jews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii gov urges visitors to stay away amid surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/hawaii-governor-urges-visitors-stay-away-amid-covid-surge-2021-08-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii Governor David Ige urged residents and visitors to restrict travel to the U.S. state to essential business activities amid a surge in cases of COVID-19 in the islands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Hill staff say fear of political violence feels like part of job...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/08/23/hill-staff-fear-political-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bomb threat near the Capitol last week has staffers wondering what’s next. “At this point, you get used to it,” said one Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It all happened in six minutes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/survivors-recount-living-nightmare-as-tennessee-s-deadly-floodwaters-swept-them-up-in-moments/ar-AANEa6K?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 21 people were killed, and local officials said Monday afternoon that they believe fewer than 10 people are still missing. The search for victims could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leader sentenced to five months...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/proud-boys-leader-henry-enrique-tarrio-sentenced-to-five-months-in-jail/ar-AANDYch?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tarrio admitted to two crimes, including setting fire to a Black Lives Matter banner stolen from a historic Black church in the District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis covid gamble: Schools, vaccinations, masks --  and his political future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-colossal-covid-19-gamble-schools-vaccinations-masks-and-his-political-future/ar-AANEcNL?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election season is far off, but Gov. Ron DeSantis has been in full-blown campaign mode, crisscrossing the state almost every day in the past week, touting monoclonal antibody treatments for people infected with COVID-19, defending his handling of the pandemic, and excoriating anyone who disagrees with his approach. Delta-variant-fueled COVID infections have surged across Florida for two ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman films rising water before death...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article253693223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The one-minute video was the last time friends and family heard from Linda Almond before she was swept away by floodwaters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought worsens in Southern Cal...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/drought-worsens-southern-california-ventura-185118065.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northwest L.A. County, Ventura County, parts of San Bernardino County and others fall into a federal report's highest range — 'exceptional drought.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer of Extremes...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/western-u-bakes-east-deluged-195348687.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the western U.S. bakes and burns under an unprecedented heat dome, Henri leaves a deluged East Coast staggering after a summer of deadly floods and record-setting tropical storms. Climate scientists say one is due to the other and both come against the backdrop of a warming planet. The high pressure that got stuck across the West causing drought and fire actually created the conditions for low-pressure-driven storms in the East. So while July was the hottest month ever recorded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#APPLETOO: Employees organizing to expose workplace harassment at company...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/8/23/22638150/apple-appletoo-employee-harassment-discord</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort launched August 23rd with a website and Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Disasters Messing With Our Brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/all-these-simultaneous-disasters-are-messing-with-our-brains/ar-AANB1Lv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The earthquakes and wildfires and wars keep piling up. When does our empathy run out?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Struggling News Industry Steps Up Recruitment of Diverse Leaders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/struggling-news-industry-steps-up-recruitment-of-diverse-leaders/ar-AANE7Vn?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With much of corporate America targeting greater diversity in its management ranks, news companies are taking steps to close the gap, offering a glimpse at what more representative leadership might bring in an industry that has lagged behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo to Require Vaccine for Entry Into Restaurants and Events...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/sao-paulo-to-require-vaccine-for-entry-into-restaurants-and-events/ar-AANE7YY?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most populous city in Latin America will begin requiring residents to have received at least one dose of a Covid-19 vaccine in order to enter restaurants, bars and public events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOM LISTS MORE REAL ESTATE:  CBS Studio Center Up For Sale;  Follows Black Rock...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/viacomcbs-eyes-sale-of-la-studio-as-demand-surges-for-stages/ar-AANEsi4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ViacomCBS Inc. is looking to sell a historic Los Angeles movie and television lot as the entertainment company tries to capitalize on the demand for production space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KENTUCKY NEW HOTSPOT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-kentucky-laws-cb3c6191208fe4bd8a8431d8ec0d010a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFORT, Ky. (AP) — Kentucky was hit with record numbers of COVID-19 patients in hospitals and intensive care units Monday as cases were driven up by the fast-spreading delta variant, Gov. Andy Beshear said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survivors grapple with aftermath of deadly Tennessee flood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-tennessee-c7c876734f3ddbafd61fd98989a647f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAVERLY, Tenn. (AP) — Anna Mays woke up in a panic attack Monday, thinking she was back in the rising floodwater. Two days ago, she had been clinging for her life to the front door of her duplex in rural Tennessee as the water inched up to her neck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POT BELLY:  Man denied owning 'very large bag of marijuana' that fell from his shirt...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/iowa/iowa-pot-belly-824593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a “very large bag of marijuana” tumbles out of your shirt after the handcuffs have been applied, do not be surprised when the cops ignore your disavowal of ownership of said weed. Police respond</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC court grants voting rights to felons on probation or parole...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/north-carolina-voting-rights-felons-13e93845-bd27-44e5-a585-13e53aa8bc18.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling restores voting rights to more than 55,000 people who have left prison but are still being supervised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deaths of newlywed women found shot at campsite investigated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/utah-94ccfda803a0c3fec1c76b1ad8d9e4d9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOAB, Utah (AP) — Residents of a Utah tourist town near the campsite where a newlywed couple was recently gunned down say they’re puzzled and concerned as the police investigation unfolds. Crystal Turner and Kylen Schulte were found dead last week at a campsite near Moab, a desert town where they were living that draws visitors from around the world to its sweeping red-rock vistas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough infections rise in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/breakthrough-infections-rise-in-la-county-young-adults-most-infected-with-coronavirus/ar-AANDqVU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By far, the age group now most likely to get infected with the coronavirus in Los Angeles County is younger adults — those 18 to 49.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore PM Questions US Image in Press Conference With Kamala Harris...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/singapore-pm-says-us-image-in-question-during-press-conference-with-kamala-harris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong said he believed global perceptions of America's image after Afghanistan's fall would be determined in the days ahead.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
