<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Teen monitoring Musk jet tracking Gates, Bezos, Drake...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/feb/02/teen-tracking-elon-musk-jet-bill-gates-jeff-bezos-drake-jack-sweeney-tesla-flight-tracker-bot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Sweeney, who wants Tesla CEO to hand over $50k to remove flight tracker bot, sets sights on other celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA drivers report surge in 'phantom braking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/tesla-drivers-report-a-surge-in-phantom-braking/ar-AAToy5E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY Rogan Mess Exposes Larger Rift Over Rules, Streaming Revenues...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/spotify-joe-rogan-streaming-revenue-covid-review-1235085384/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Content advisory labels may be beside the point for the streaming giant's flagship podcast series, and other creators may be wary of taking a stand on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonuses Rain on Wall St Bankers in Biggest Payout in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/wealth/wall-street-s-big-bonuses-are-back-and-bankers-are-buying-yachts-champagne</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten million dollars, $15 million, $25 million, more: Big money is back on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's finely crafted web of digital surveillance for Olympics has been years in making...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/winter-olympics/china-e2-80-99s-finely-crafted-web-of-digital-surveillance-for-the-beijing-olympics-has-been-years-in-the-making/ar-AATodn7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Queen Elizabeth II to mark 70 years on throne...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queen-elizabeth-ii-mark-70-030820803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II on Sunday becomes the first British monarch to reign for 70 years, heralding the start of her Platinum Jubilee year despite her retreat from public view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump heir? Supporters eye DeSantis as alternative...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-florida-donald-trump-texas-d0fb48fb5ccf444dc7b20590201a05ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONROE, Texas (AP) — There was something different next to the “TRUMP WON!” T-shirts, the “MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN” hats and the “LET’S GO BRANDON” flags for sale at former President Donald Trump’s recent Texas rally: a collection of “DeSantis 2024” bumper stickers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New turning point? More countries easing COVID restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-pandemics-united-nations-ca046d38f7e78ad7150a0a8d95d81433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Late-night disco partying. Elbow-to-elbow seating in movie theaters. Mask-free baring of faces in public, especially in Europe and North America: Bit by bit, many countries that have been hard-hit by the coronavirus are opening up and easing their tough, and often unpopular, restrictive measures aimed to fight COVID-19 even as the omicron variant — deemed less severe — has caused cases to skyrocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli police admit use of spyware without warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thevibes.com/articles/world/53367/israeli-cops-appear-to-admit-use-of-spyware-without-warrant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thevibes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice minister had pledged a full investigation following a media report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sets stage for 2024, saying the quiet part louder and louder...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-sets-stage-2024-saying-205742052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may have lost the White House and his social media megaphone but Donald Trump is reminding Americans of his ability to dominate the political conversation as he courts controversy on the comeback trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian province scraps tax on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/canadian-province-scraps-tax-covid-201310878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's Quebec province announced Tuesday it was scrapping plans for a health tax on those who are not vaccinated against Covid-19, following a public backlash over the proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book banning in Texas schools: Titles pulled off library shelves in record numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/texas-books-race-sexuality-schools-rcna13886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing pressure from parents and threats of criminal charges, some districts have ignored policies meant to prevent censorship. Librarians and students are pushing back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar New Year would become the 12th federal holiday under bill before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/lunar-new-year-would-become-the-12th-federal-holiday-under-a-bill-before-congress/ar-AATnkOS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Passenger goes into labor on 11-hour flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/passenger-goes-into-labor-on-11-hour-flight-literally-just-witnessed-a-woman-giving-birth/ar-AATnitK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAMOUNT releases first trailer for 'THE GODFATHER' TV series...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/godfather-the-offer-trailer-1235085164/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10-episode drama from 'The Player' director Michael Tolkin stars Miles Teller and Matthew Goode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST IN 8 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bengals-rams-nfl-playoffs-nfc-afc-championship-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bengals-Chiefs on CBS draws largest audience for early window in 6 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN:  Simonn Cowell rushed to hospital after nearly dying following another e-bike smash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/4591115/simon-cowell-hospital-e-bike-smash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV mogul Simon Cowell was rushed to hospital following another terrifying e-bike smash, The Sun can reveal. Sources said the 62-year-old is lucky to be alive after he was propelled over the handleb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Fatigue: 70% Just Want to Get on With Lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/covid-fatigue-70-of-americans-say-we-just-need-to-get-on-with-our-lives-according-to-new-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not surprisingly, responses indicate a clear partisan divide with 89% of Republicans agreeing with the statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOOPI SUSPENDED FROM 'VIEW'</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2022/02/01/whoopi-goldberg-suspended-the-view-holocaust-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whoopi Goldberg has been suspended from ABC’s The View for two weeks in light of her controversial comments about the Holocaust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital church membership surges...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/virtual-reality-church-worshipping-in-the-metaverse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Membership in Virtual Reality Church increased dramatically during the COVID shutdown. Worshippers attend using virtual reality headsets and create an avatar. Everything from scripture readings to baptisms can take place in the metaverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMS Win Over 49ERS Tops 50 MILLION Viewers for FOX!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/02/nfl-la-rams-win-super-bowl-49ers-fox-viewership-1234923211/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of Sunday’s NFC Championship Game at SoFi Stadium, it looked like the San Francisco 49ers would be heading to Super Bowl LVI in the same venue in two weeks. But looks can be deceiving. Bou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Historic LA Venue Was Transformed for NASCAR Clash at the Coliseum...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/sports/la-memorial-coliseum-clash-nascar-race-track/2812115/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world's historic sports venues will welcome race fans Saturday when NASCAR brings its Clash exhibition race to the Los Angeles Memorial Coliseum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba vaccinates over 95% of toddlers as young as 2...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/prevention-cures/592365-cuba-vaccinates-over-95-percent-of-toddlers-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The island country began vaccinating children as young as 2 years old in September 2021, making it the only country to immunize children that young at the time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>77% at Baltimore High school read at elementary level...</title>
      <link>https://foxbaltimore.com/news/project-baltimore/77-tested-at-baltimore-high-school-read-at-elementary-level-71-at-kindergarten</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foxbaltimore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (WBFF) &amp;mdash; A Baltimore City teacher came forward with devastating information that showed 77% of students tested at one high school are reading at an elementary school level. The teacher works at Patterson High School, one of the largest high schools in Baltimore with a 61% graduation rate and a nearly $12 million budget. We agreed not to identify this source who fears retribution for giving Project Baltimore the results of iReady assessments. &amp;ldquo;Our children deserve better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-UCLA professor arrested for threatening mass shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10463245/Former-UCLA-lecturer-threatens-philosophy-department-mass-shooting-email.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Harris, a former lecturer who was put on leave last year, was arrested in Boulder, Colorado, on Tuesday, according to multiple sources cited by NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleges Owner Offered Bonus to Lose Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebiglead.com/posts/dophins-owner-brian-flores-lose-games-bonus-stephen-ross-2019-01ftvh8cggjj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebiglead.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Brian Flores' racial discrimination suit against the NFL he claims Dolphins owner Stephen Ross offered him bonuses to lose games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elway 'Hungover' at Interview...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/former-miami-dolphins-head-coach-204509878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Flores, fired last month as head coach of the Miami Dolphins, has sued the National Football League and each of its franchises for racial discrimination. Why it matters: The NFL for decades has been criticized for its paucity of Black coaches, and now Flores plans to hold the league's feet to the legal fire.Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free. What the lawsuit says: "Mr. Flores has determined that the only way to effectuate real change is through the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Days as VP numbered?</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/kamala-harris-days-vp-numbered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris is more unpopular than Biden. Her press interviews go viral for all the wrong reasons. Her party is scrambling for alternatives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belichick Texts at Center of Drama...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2022/02/01/bill-belichick-accidental-text-message-brian-flores-racial-discrimination-lawsuit-giants-brian-daboll-hiring/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Belichick texted the wrong Brian to congratulate him for getting the Giants' head coaching a job, according to a lawsuit filed by former Dolphins head coach and former Patriots assistant coach Brian Flores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Sues NFL: 'Rife With Racism'...</title>
      <link>https://au.sports.yahoo.com/brian-flores-sues-nfl-giants-claiming-racial-discrimination-in-hiring-process-211356727.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flores says that Bill Belichick texts show that the Giants knew they were hiring Brian Daboll while he was interviewing with the team</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How old database became hugely profitable dossier on health of 270 million Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2022/02/01/ibm-watson-health-marketscan-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To most Americans, the name MarketScan means nothing. But most Americans mean everything to MarketScan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: 'Positive step, but more that can be done'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/white-house-spotif-joe-rogan-1235085314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press secretary Jen Psaki said Spotify's COVID disclaimers "a positive step, but there is more that can be done."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN:  West has 'ignored' key Ukraine concerns...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2022/02/01/europe/vladimir-putin-west-ignored-russia-concerns-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian President Vladimir Putin said Tuesday that his government was studying the responses from the United States and NATO to his security demands related to Ukraine but that it was clear the Kremlin's main complaints "had been ignored."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publisher halts Anne Frank betrayal book amid questions on research...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2022/02/01/europe/anne-frank-dutch-publisher-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Dutch publisher has suspended printing of a book that suggested a Jewish notary betrayed Anne Frank, saying there were questions about the research behind it, according to an internal email seen by Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy about to slam into wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/01/after-a-huge-year-for-growth-the-us-economy-is-about-to-slam-into-a-wall.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy last year grew at its fastest pace since 1984. Don't expect a repeat performance in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW NORMAL: Surrounded by Doctors -- Not Family -- On Death Bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/overmedicalization-death-study-medicine-68352f60-f053-4937-861f-0ed2a21da7ec.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technological and medical advances fueled the idea that science can defeat death, increasing medical interventions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fear Is Contagious...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fear-is-contagious/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say having more people around you for support won't help. So much for "strength in numbers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-red CA county now recall warzone...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-politics/article/Shasta-County-Republican-recall-warzone-16810959.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I never thought the community I grew up in would act in this manner."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL boy reels in .50-caliber Barrett sniper rifles while fishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2022/02/01/boy-reels-in-50-caliber-barrett-sniper-rifles-while-fishing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magnet fishing duo reels in two sniper rifles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears for freedom of speech at FORBES...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10464133/Forbes-insiders-slam-deal-SPAC-initially-funded-China-sovereign-wealth-fund.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The initial involvement of China's sovereign wealth fund in a deal to take over Forbes is raising concerns about the potential for censorship at the venerable US business news outlet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6-Year-Olds Using Meth in Mexico's Spiraling Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kbwyz/mexico-kids-meth-addiction-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are only a few rehab clinics focused on helping minors with drug addiction, and they are overwhelmed by demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watchdog finds 'concerns' with govt searches of Americans' communications...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/31/politics/nsa-watchdog-concerns-searches-american-communications/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency failed to follow both court-approved and internal procedures designed to prevent officials from using a controversial foreign surveillance law to inappropriately monitor Americans' communications, the NSA inspector general found in a semi-annual report released on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road deaths rise at record pace as risky driving persists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-transportation-pete-buttigieg-a16719e38d72f68e338030103e924cf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The number of U.S. traffic deaths surged in the first nine months of 2021 to 31,720, the government reported Tuesday, keeping up a record pace of increased dangerous driving during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel will have laser to shoot down rockets within year...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-695206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE and APPLE Maps build invisible wall to hide Tim Cook's home...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/google-maps-apple-build-invisible-26108131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The home of Apple CEO Tim Cook has now vanished from Google Maps and Apple Maps following a restraining order against an alleged stalker - who now can't visit any Apple stores</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins researchers: Lockdowns had little or no impact...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2022/jan/31/lockdowns-had-little-or-no-impact-covid-19-deaths-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockdowns in the U.S. and Europe had little or no impact in reducing deaths from COVID-19, according to a new analysis by researchers at Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graham Nash Asks for Removal of Songs...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/02/01/spotify-problems-grow-as-neil-youngs-band-partner-graham-nash-asks-for-removal-of-songs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TIME TO FOCUS ON OTHER THINGS'</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33192441/tampa-bay-buccaneers-tom-brady-officially-announces-retirement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady has retired from the NFL, the future Hall of Fame quarterback officially announced Tuesday on Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S OFFICIAL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/01/tom-brady-announces-retirement-in-instagram-post-following-days-of-confusion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 44-year-old Brady won seven Super Bowls with the New England Patriots and Tampa Bay Buccaneers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOU:   Gave $1M to Meadows...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-gave-1m-meadows-nonprofit-weeks-after-jan-6-panel-n1288334</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The contribution was made to the Conservative Partnership Institute, where Mark Meadows, the former White House chief of staff, is a senior partner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious cases at all-time high in Israel even with 'vaccines'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-695149</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town cancels Groundhog Day --  after groundhog dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/weather-predicting-milltown-mel-dies-just-before-groundhog-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Milltown Mel, a weather-predicting groundhog in New Jersey, died just before his annual big day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai's police fight crime in million-dollar supercars...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/dubais-police-force-fight-crime-26106391</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubai's police force fights crime in a fleet of supercars that include a £1 million Aston Martin and £1.4 million Bugatti Veyron which is considered the fastest police car on the planet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MORNING JOE' HIGHER PROFILE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/31/media/msnbc-rachel-maddow-morning-joe-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new 9am hour of "Morning Joe" is starting to come into focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffet brawl erupts after GOLDEN CORRAL 'runs out of steak'...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2022/01/31/watch-massive-brawl-breaks-out-in-bensalem-golden-corral-over-alleged-steak-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the video, a man is heard saying "all I wanted was some steak."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-Out Effort to Protect Biden From Infection Undercuts 'Normal Lives' Messaging...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-health-pandemics-kamala-harris-648f64eafd0b4f58e05f75e236b65e00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — When President Joe Biden met with U.S. governors at the White House on Monday, he was the only one given a glass of water — lest anyone else remove their mask to take a drink. The president was seated more than 10 feet from everyone, including Vice President Kamala Harris and members of his Cabinet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for ramen noodle battery...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/florida/ramen-battery-arrest-287530</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANUARY 31--A Florida Man is behind bars after allegedly battering a female victim with hot ramen noodles, according to police. Responding Friday morning to a domestic disturbance call at a Fort Pier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In vicious world, guess who became best friends? Cats and dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/lifestyle/pets/in-this-vicious-world-guess-who-became-best-friends-cats-and-dogs/ar-AATmdvF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental HIV vax now in clinical trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/experimental-hiv-vaccine-based-on-moderna-s-mrna-technology-now-in-clinical-trial/ar-AATmSym</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffet brawl erupts after GOLDEN CORRAL 'runs out of steak'...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2022/02/01/buffet-brawl-erupts-after-golden-corral-runs-out-of-steak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brawl resulted Friday night at the Golden Corral restaurant in Bensalem, Pennsylvania, after it allegedly ran out of steak. The footage shows diners swinging punches, hurling chairs and screaming…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls for Jan. 6 Committee to Investigate Pence...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-calls-for-the-jan-6-committee-to-investigate-mike-pence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump called for a Congressional investigation into Speaker Pelosi AND Vice President Pence for their actions of January 6th. Weird, right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Challenge: Politically Fraught Games...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/nbc-china-olympics-beijing-tokyo-politics-1235084890/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights abuses, geopolitics and unprecedentedly strict COVID-19 protocols are just some of the things NBC must balance during its coverage of the global sporting event — all while Olympics television ratings continue to decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto breakthrough? Western states consider taking digital currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/31/crypto-wyoming-arizona-tax-payments-00003910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada truckers block Montana crossing route to protest vax mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10462631/Freedom-Convoy-truckers-blockade-border-Montana-Alberta-protest-against-vaccine-mandates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In solidarity with their Ottawa counterparts, truckers in at the Alberta / Montana border staged what police described as a 'complete blockage' of Highway 4 in Canada's western province</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTON MARTIN DBX707 most powerful luxury SUV in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/01/aston-martin-launches-luxury-suv-dbx707.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launch of the DBX707 comes a year after Aston Martin launched the standard DBX, which has captured a significant percentage of the market, according to Stroll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They thought they were getting home makeover. It turned into fiasco...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thought-were-getting-home-makeover-130026357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An alleged 'construction Ponzi scheme' involving the series 'Home Work' threatens to tarnish the reputation of TV's hottest home renovators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia moves to redefine Islam-bearing green flag...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-dubai-united-arab-emirates-saudi-arabia-5a6ed6013641a7da4dc114c749251af0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Saudi Arabia is inching toward changes that govern its national anthem and green flag, which is emblazoned with a sword and inscribed with Islam’s creed as the birthplace of the faith.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman alleges rape in virtual world...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2022/01/31/woman-allegedly-groped-metaverse/9278578002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman in the U.K. wrote in a December Medium blog post that she was sexually harassed and raped in Meta's virtual game Horizon Worlds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Superyacht Sales Jump 77%...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/superyacht-sales-jumped-77-last-year-as-inventories-shrank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Superyacht Sales Jumped 77% Last Year as Inventories Shrank</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whoopi Goldberg sorry for Holocaust not about race remark...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/whoopi-goldberg-apology-the-holocaust-jonathan-greenblatt-4a4c77055d7bb1c37662fc9b274a8869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The actress Whoopi Goldberg has apologized for saying the Holocaust was not about race, comments that caused a backlash. She made the initial comments on ABC's ‘’The View"’ program on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: FBI urges temporary phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-60215250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new advice comes ahead of the Winter Olympics in Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Brain Really Living 15 Seconds In Past...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-lives-15-seconds-in-the-past/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our brain is like a time machine. It’s like we have an app that consolidates our visual input every 15 seconds," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
