<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Buses leaving Texas border town packed with illegals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/buses-leaving-texas-border-town-packed-with-illegal-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buses leaving the Texas city at the heart of the border crisis are struggling to keep up with business — because they’re full of illegal immigrants released into the US, The Post has le…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly It's Bare Season...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/suddenly-its-bare-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who hasn’t had the nightmare? It’s the one about being caught in public dressed in your undies. Therapists and dream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi Brief in Crucial Supreme Court Abortion Case: Overturn 'Roe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/mississippi-brief-in-crucial-supreme-court-abortion-case-overturn-roe-and-casey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi attorney general Lynn Fitch filed a brief in the most important Supreme Court abortion case in three decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 'ANOTHER PIVOTAL POINT'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-director-warns-us-at-another-pivotal-point-in-pandemic/ar-AAMrGDD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention struck a new tone of urgency on Thursday about the coronavirus pandemic, warning that the United States is “not out of the woods yet” and is once again at “another pivotal point in this pandemic” as the highly infectious Delta variant rips through communities with low rates of vaccination. The warning from the director, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, during a briefing by members of the White...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy to require 'pass' for many activities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-6e5ba18d35f3ac40d4f34e6b3b22d58d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — With daily COVID-19 cases sharply rising again, Italy will soon require people to have passes reflecting their health status to access gyms, museums, movie theaters, the inside of restaurants and other venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK moderators call for end to overly restrictive NDAs...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/7/22/22587757/facebook-content-moderators-ireland-end-restrictive-ndas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook content moderators in Ireland call for change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin sisters forced to kneel, executed in horror INSTAGRAM livestream...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/15655009/twin-sisters-executed-horror-instagram-livestream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWIN sisters were executed in a horrific Instagram livestream. The women, named locally as Amália and Amanda Alves, were forced to kneel before being shot in the back of the head because they ̶…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers detect first 'moon-forming' disc surrounding exoplanet...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-researchers-detect-first-moon-forming-disc-surrounding-exoplanet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers detect first 'moon-forming' disc surrounding exoplanet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAC has not used any of $75M its raised to help fund election audits...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564387-trump-pac-has-not-used-any-of-the-75m-its-raised-this-year-to-help-fund</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump’s leadership PAC has not yet used any of the roughly $75 million raised to help finance election reviews,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Can't Travel Because State Dept. Employees Won't Work...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/22/americans-cant-travel-because-state-department-employees-wont-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive passport-processing delays, due to COVID restrictions and staffing shortages, are ruining summer travel plans and prompting fantastical workarounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL reveals forfeit rule targeting unvaccinated players...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/nfl-reveals-forfeit-rule-to-punish-unvaccinated-players/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has laid out its strongest incentive yet for players to get the vaccine. According to a memo shared on Twitter by NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero, the league has mandated that a game cann…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris' laugh is sound check for divided country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/more-than-a-laugh-kamala-harris-is-a-sound-check-for-a-divided-country/ar-AAMpsMa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI's human protein database 'great leap' for research...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-ai-s-human-protein-database-a-great-leap-for-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI's human protein database a 'great leap' for research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalized man says he'd still rather be sick than get shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/louisiana-covid-19-hospital-unit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hospital's chief medical officer said if people don't get vaccinated, "we are going to accept death."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details on FBI Inquiry Into Kavanaugh Draw Fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/details-on-fbi-inquiry-into-kavanaugh-draw-fire-from-democrats/ar-AAMrpto</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly three years after Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh’s tumultuous confirmation to the Supreme Court, the F.B.I. has disclosed more details about its efforts to review the justice’s background, leading a group of Senate Democrats to question the thoroughness of the vetting and conclude that it was shaped largely by the Trump White House. In a letter dated June 30 to two Democratic senators, Sheldon Whitehouse of Rhode Island and Chris Coons of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST reporter sues paper and former editor Marty Baron, alleging discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/media/washington-post-lawsuit-felicia-sonmez/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco buys $20K GUCCI trash cans...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/kcbsradio/news/local/gucci-garbage-san-francisco-approves-usd20k-trash-cans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco is hoping to replace the long-despised green trash-cans littered throughout the city, as its board of supervisors voted Wednesday to approve using new designer prototype bins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEVIN TOPS NYT LIST AFTER 400,000 IN 1ST WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/nyt-no-1-mark-levins-american-marxism-sells-400-000-in-1st-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They don’t call conservative media mogul Mark Levin the “Great One” for nothing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TESTS ORAL VAX</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israel-to-become-first-in-world-to-test-oral-covid-19-vaccine-674563</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grieving Mother Bear Doesn't Leave Dead Cub's Side After Being Struck By Speeding Car In Yosemite...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/grieving-mama-bear-at-yosemite-wont-leave-her-babys-side-when-cub-gets-hit-and-killed-by-speeding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So please, remember this. Remember that when traveling through Yosemite, we are all just visitors in the home of countless animals and it is up to us to follow the rules that protect them,” wrote the park ranger who discovered the dead cub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy, 5, Dies In GA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/5-year-old-georgia-boy-dies-from-covid-19-as-delta-variant-rapidly-spreads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Wyatt would wave to strangers in the grocery store, because he knew that it absolutely made their day," his dad wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As employers get MORE desperate to fill jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/employers-desperate-worker-openings-8dcad7c2-0844-40a1-9ff6-2477ef3dadad.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health care employers are particularly desperate to fill jobs now, according to new data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme weather wreaks havoc worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/summer-disaster-extreme-weather-wreaks-115720112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change is making the world more prone to floods like those in China and Europe and to heat waves and fires like those in the U.S. and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH FLORIDA HOTSPOT</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/07/20/covid-south-florida-hospitalizations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jackson Health System is sounding the alarm about what they are seeing in their hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND: Expressway Shootings Hit All-Time High...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/07/21/i-fear-getting-hit-from-behind-chicago-area-expressway-shootings-at-an-all-time-high/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Dan Ryan, in particular, has certain intervals where it’s probably repeat offenders here.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Easy making big comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/How-the-Big-Easy-is-making-its-big-comeback-16332352.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TESTING AS CASES SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/white-house-boosts-funding-covid-tests-infections-continue-surge-n1274677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As in early days of a pandemic, confirming illnesses and contact tracing are critical, public health officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In America's least air-conditioned cities, brutal heat changes people's minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/In-America-s-least-air-conditioned-cities-brutal-16332213.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Boise, Idaho, where the temperature topped 97 for a stretch of 14 out of 15 days this...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Fencer Accused of Sex Misconduct...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/u-s-olympic-fencer-accused-of-sexual-misconduct-kept-apart-from-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alen Hadzic, 29, of South Orange, N.J., is an alternate in the men’s epee event with the United States Olympic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Antonoff Doesn't Want to Just Take Up Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/jack-antonoff-doesnt-want-to-just-take-up-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To the outside observer, Jack Antonoff might seem like something of a workaholic. A widely trusted collaborator whose fingerprints are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Self-proclaimed 'incel' planned to kill sorority girls at university, feds say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/self-proclaimed-e2-80-98incel-e2-80-99-planned-to-kill-sorority-girls-at-an-ohio-university-feds-say/ar-AAMqMpI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tres Genco was charged Wednesday with attempting to conduct a mass shooting of women — a hate crime — and illegally possessing a machine gun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Ratings Watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/tokyo-olympics-tv-ratings-preview-1234985186/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Games will almost surely bring NBC and its sibling cable networks their biggest primetime audiences in months. They’ll probably also fall well short of previous Games. How can both statem…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Game Giant Sued Over Sex Harassment, Unequal Pay in 'Pervasive Frat Boy' Culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/activision-blizzard-sued-california-over-095844879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Game giant Activision Blizzard has been hit with a lawsuit from the California Department of Fair Employment and Housing, alleging the company’s “pervasive frat boy workplace culture” resulted in women employees being continuously subjected to sexual harassment and being paid less than men. The California Department of Fair Employment and Housing filed a civil lawsuit […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of Messy Night Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dyv5v7/freedom-day-england-clubbing-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After 16 months, clubs in England are open again. VICE writer Izzy Copestake spent "freedom day" partying (and reporting).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES to go all-electric...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/autos/mercedes-benz-go-all-electric-2030-n1274708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We really want to go for it ... and be dominantly, if not all electric, by the end of the decade," said the head of Daimler, Mercedes-Benz's parent company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over rules gives new impetus to France's Yellow Vests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722113212-4lzpd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustration at government measures to curb the spread of COVID-19, which some people say are an attack on their liberty, has given the movement fresh momentum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Sparks Outcry for Calling Capitol Police Officer 'Angry Left-Wing' Activist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/fox-news-tucker-carlson-harry-dunn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News' Carlson sparked outcry Wednesday when he called Black Capitol police officer Harry Dunn an "angry left-wing political activist."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Reveals Trump Gushing Over Jan. 6 Mob...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/audio-reveals-trump-gushing-over-loving-jan-6-crowd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president got misty-eyed about the Capitol rioters in a newly released audio clip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MAGA's Biggest Porn Star on Being Booted from TPUSA Event...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/maga-biggest-porn-star-brandi-082351801.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ethan Miller/GettyBrandi Love is the most famous MAGA porn star on the planet. The adult-industry veteran boasts 831.5K followers on Twitter, has starred in hundreds of XXX films, penned the book Getting Wild Sex from Your Conservative Woman, and is a columnist for The Federalist. She enthusiastically supports Donald Trump and loathes antifa, BLM, and the Squad.And yet, on Saturday, she was banned from a conservative political conference just for being a porn star.Love, 48, had attended a number</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: The people who signed up for MAGACOIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/pro-trump-cryptocurrency-magacoin-has-racked-up-over-1000-sign-ups-since-launching-report-says/ar-AAMqWWE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most holders of magacoin have only been allocated the 100 free tokens users receive after registering, The Guardian said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young getting very sick. Next Covid chapter worries experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/health/us-coronavirus-thursday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Covid-19 cases rising and vaccination rates on the decline, health experts say they are concerned about the next chapter in the pandemic -- especially for younger Americans, who they say are feeling the impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless claims unexpectedly rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/22/us-weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initial claims for unemployment insurance were expected to total 350,000 for the week ended July 17, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most expensive Manhattan listing drops for $169M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/21/the-432-park-avenue-penthouse-can-be-yours-for-196m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The penthouse would be the second most expensive known New York City real estate sale ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Dunn Lawyers Berate Tucker Carlson for Attack on 1/6 Riot Officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/harry-dunn-lawyers-berate-tucker-carlson-attack-january-capitol-riot-officer-1612072</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawyers called out the Fox News host and said: "Frankly, the last thing Carlson wants is for the truth to emerge of what happened that day and why."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 98 and facing cancer, Bob Dole reckons with legacy of Trump, ponders future of GOP...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/98-facing-cancer-bob-dole-100314687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm a Trumper," said Dole, the only former GOP presidential nominee to attend Trump's convention in 2016. But he added, "I'm sort of Trumped out."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye  to reveal album at massive Atlanta event...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-atlanta-37e148408bef5c3da511d2b69137310a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Kanye West knows how to make a splash even with a listening event. West is expected to unveil his 10th studio album, “Donda” during a listening event Thursday night at the Mercedes Benz Stadium in Atlanta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smog tower to help Delhi breathe?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-smog-tower-to-help-delhi-breathe-but-experts-sceptical</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smog tower to help Delhi breathe but experts sceptical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era of Olympic champions eye glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-new-era-of-olympic-champions-eye-tokyo-glory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New era of Olympic champions eye Tokyo glory</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With cutting-edge hypersonics, Russia leads in new arms race...</title>
      <link>https://www.spacewar.com/afp/210722095748.vpeqhadk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spacewar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Hamptons Home Prices Surge to Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/hamptons-home-prices-surge-to-a-record-as-pickings-get-slimmer/ar-AAMqbgc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamptons home prices reached a record high as New Yorkers stepped up their bidding for a dwindling supply of listings in the Long Island resort towns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate braces for nasty debt ceiling fight...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/564223-senate-braces-for-a-nasty-debt-ceiling-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans are digging in on the federal debt limit, warning Democrats that it will be up to them to avoid a default as President Biden pushes for trillions more in spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troubles in Florida putting pressure on DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/564195-pressure-mounts-for-desantis-in-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. – Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis is facing mounting pressure on the homefront as he looks to cement his superstar status among Republicans nationally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Everyone Has Worst Summer Cold Ever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/why-everyone-has-the-worst-summer-cold-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, the summer cold and cough season really is worse than usual. “I’ve had bad colds, but I’ve never experienced</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grizzly Bear Terrorized Man for Days in Alaska. Coast Guard Saw SOS...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/a-grizzly-bear-terrorized-a-man-for-days-in-alaska-the-coast-guard-saw-his-sos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was sleep-deprived and nearly out of ammunition, alone in the wilderness of Alaska. Well, not really alone. For several</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China opposes studying lab leak in any new origins probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2021/07/22/asia-pacific/china-opposed-virus-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China pushed back against the World Health Organization’s call for another probe into the coronavirus’s origins that includes examining whether it leaked f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening ceremony director fired over old Holocaust skit...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210722-tokyo-olympics-opening-ceremony-director-fired-over-old-holocaust-skit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tokyo Olympics opening ceremony director fired over old Holocaust skit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superyacht Staff Secrets From Cannabis Buffets to Caviar, Sex, Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-07-22/superyacht-staff-secrets-from-cannabis-buffets-to-caviar-sex-and-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From cannabis buffets to choppering in caviar, posh charter life can be a rough ride for the crew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym Banning People Who HAVE Been Vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dbjg8/fearless-boxing-gym-is-banning-people-whove-been-vaccinated-against-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless Boxing Club claims it doesn't want members who "received the experimental Covid vaccine."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hottest Games on record?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/jul/20/tokyo-olympics-fears-athletes-could-face-hottest-games-on-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beach volleyball players have already found sand too hot for their feet during practice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TO LIVE AND DIE IN LA:  Wheelchair-bound Weinstein pleads not guilty; Faces 140 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3325141/harvey-weinstein-not-guilty-charges-los-angeles/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEELCHAIR-bound Harvey Weinstein pleaded not guilty to 11 counts of sexual assault in a Los Angeles courtroom today. Weinstein entered the plea just one day after he was seen with a support strap …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk trolls by supporting rocket-themed dildos...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3324532/elon-musk-trolls-jeff-bezos-rocket-dildos-blue-origin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has trolled Jeff Bezos by lending his support to a new range of rocket-themed sex toys modeled on his rival’s Blue Origin space craft. The Tesla founder replied to a tweet about the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic Athletes Take Knee Against Racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/tokyo-olympics-live-updates/2021/07/21/1018811516/players-take-a-knee-at-tokyo-olympics-as-the-first-competitions-kick-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We want to fight all forms of discrimination, and as a group of women, we wanted to kneel against it," said Steph Houghton, a co-captain of Britain's soccer team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Experiment Placed Foster Children with Pedophiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/07/26/the-german-experiment-that-placed-foster-children-with-pedophiles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the approval of the government, a renowned sexologist ran a dangerous program. How could this happen?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Dream Dying?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-california-dream-is-dying/ar-AAMoqBq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once-dynamic state is closing the door on economic opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE DEBATES NEW MASK PUSH</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/White-House-officials-debate-masking-push-as-16330915.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Top White House aides and Biden administration officials are debating...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron's 'SPACE JAM' Blocked By Xi?</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2021/07/21/lebron-james-bent-the-knee-to-dictator-xi-but-china-still-isnt-releasing-space-jam-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While LeBron James has consistently capitulated to China, Xi Jinping has yet to greenlight the NBA star's new film 'Space Jam: A New Legacy' for release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas City hospitals turning away patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tipping-point-kansas-city-hospitals-193117650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we don’t take it seriously, we could easily end up back where we were in November,” one Kansas City doctor said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric car revolution, designed to save planet, unleashes toll on it...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-electric-car-revolution-designed-100041571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the name of climate action, California pushed the world toward electric cars. But building enough of them is creating its own environmental crises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA RESTAURANTS CLOSE</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/07/21/la-restaurants-close-response-rising-numbers-breakthrough-cases-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants throughout the region are already struggling to staff up to meet the high demand for dine-in meals, but now they are also being hit disproportionately hard by the rise in new infections, especially among people who are unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls Biden 'super human being'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/barrack-held-forth-trump-real-120035863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A week before he was charged with illegal lobbying for the United Arab Emirates, Tom Barrack traveled to New York for an on-camera interview in Midtown Manhattan.Dressed casually in dark jeans and a gray, long-sleeve top by Zegna, he gave no indication that he knew federal prosecutors across the East River in Brooklyn were preparing a seven-count indictment.The investor, 74, spoke comfortably and confidently about his relationships in the Middle East, some of which go back a half-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked Florida Woman, Busted For Skinny-Dipping In Stranger's Pool...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/florida/skinny-dipper-popped-790521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon returning home from a doctor’s appointment Monday afternoon, a Florida retiree discovered a naked woman skinny-dipping in his pool, according to cops who arrested the intruder on trespass and r</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
