<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>First trailer for DISNEY 'CRUELLA' movie more 'JOKER' than '101 DALMATIANS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/2/17/22287149/cruella-trailer-disney-emma-stone-live-action-101-dalmations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruella de Vil leans into the madness of it all in the first trailer for Cruella.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/02/why-covid-19-cases-are-falling-so-fast/618041/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four reasons: social distancing, seasonality, seroprevalence, and shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volunteers race to save thousands of cold-stunned turtles washing up in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/volunteers-race-to-save-thousands-of-cold-stunned-turtles-washing-up-in-texas/ar-BB1dL3c4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turtles along the Texas Gulf Coast have been "cold stunned" by the winter storm affecting the region, washing up comatose on the shore of South Padre Island in a kind of hypothermic shock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lonely, angry, eager to make history: Online mobs likely to remain dangerous reality...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Lonely-angry-eager-to-make-history-Online-mobs-15956567.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the stock market opened one morning last month, Jake was working a job he hated...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Raoni on 'final mission' to protect Amazon lands...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210217-chief-raoni-on-final-mission-to-protect-amazon-lands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Raoni on 'final mission' to protect Amazon lands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission Could Rock Our World...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nasas-mars-2020-mission-could-rock-our-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Perseverance Rover has a really cool camera and will also be collecting samples of the surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable Chip Tells You When Stress Level Growing Dangerously High...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/wearable-chip-detects-stress-in-sweat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new device developed by Swiss researchers might warn you if your stress levels are growing dangerously high.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN: NASA rover on track for daredevil landing on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-space-exploration-mars/nasa-rover-perseverance-on-track-for-daredevil-landing-on-mars-idUSKBN2AH19E </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Philip admitted to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/wireStory/british-queens-husband-prince-philip-admitted-hospital-75945001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buckingham Palace says 99-year-old Prince Philip has been admitted to a London hospital after feeling unwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In first for world, Britain OKs challenge trial exposing volunteers to virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210217124109-cwikk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-CHALLENGE (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-In first for the world, Britain OKs challenge trial exposing volunteers to COVID-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Retail spending bursts higher...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/17/us-retail-sales-january-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Tragedy of Dianne Feinstein...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/news-analysis-tragedy-dianne-feinstein-120032770.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;History will be a lot kinder to Sen. Dianne Feinstein than today's dismal approval polls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress takes another look at slavery reparations...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/racial-unrest-us-congress-takes-reparations/story?id=75925706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As local governments across the country take on the issues of reparations, Congress will hold a hearing on the study of reparations on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area exodus leading edge of pandemic housing reshuffle...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-economy-cities/bay-area-exodus-leading-edge-of-pandemic-housing-reshuffle-idUSKBN2AH1O8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long one of the nation's "it" destinations, San Francisco was already a land of unaffordable housing before the coronavirus hit, and with the median single-family home price still hovering above $1.5 million even as of December thousands of residents are leaving the Golden...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kambo: Why Americans poisoning selves with frogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health_and_wellbeing/kambo-dots-medicine-frogs-healing-b1803396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is kambo?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon rethinking how to array forces to focus on China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-lloyd-austin-china-russia-united-states-a527916527940705a0aa9fb7d1f36eaf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Biden administration faces a conundrum as it rethinks the positioning of military forces around the world: How to focus more on China and Russia without retreating from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM ROGERS: Bonds Everywhere Full-Fledged Bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/famed-investor-jim-rogers-says-dont-buy-america-stocks-at-highs-heres-what-he-likes-instead-11613565144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It shouldn't be surprising that Jim Rogers, who famously moved from New York to Singapore because of his belief in the rise of China, isn't a fan of U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubrick Daughter Proud Boys Fanatic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stanley-kubricks-daughter-vivian-is-a-far-right-proud-boys-and-qanon-fanatic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent months, Stanley Kubrick’s daughter Vivian has tweeted anti-Semitic memes, joked about the murder of AOC, cheered on the Proud Boys, and promoted QAnon conspiracies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorsese attacks streaming services for 'devaluing' cinema...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/martin-scorsese-streaming-services-netflix-b1803347.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘The art of cinema is being systematically devalued, sidelined, demeaned, and reduced to its lowest common denominator,’ director wrote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to 'Recalibrate' Saudi Arabia Ties Away From Crown Prince...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-downgrades-saudi-crown-prince-061632309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden intends to “recalibrate” the U.S. relationship with Saudi Arabia and will emphasize outreach to King Salman, in a move that signals a downgrade in ties with Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Salman, the country’s de facto ruler.It is the latest sign Biden’s team is taking a different track from former President Donald Trump toward the world’s largest oil exporter. Trump established close ties with Prince Mohammed and made Saudi Arabia the centerpiece of his strategy toward the Middle East after taking his first trip abroad as president there.That’s all being scaled back. In Biden’s first few days, the U.S. put a hold on some key weapons sales to the kingdom and announced new efforts to bring an end to the Saudi-led war in Yemen. Biden has also called on Saudi Arabia to improve its human rights record.“We’re going to recalibrate our relationship with Saudi Arabia,” Press Secretary Jen Psaki told reporters on Tuesday. “Part of that is going back to engagement counterpart-to-counterpart. The president’s counterpart is King Salman.”Instead of engaging primarily with Biden, the crown prince’s most appropriate counterpart is Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin, according to a person familiar. While Prince Mohammed’s official role is deputy prime minister and defense minister, he has a vast range of responsibilities as heir to the throne his father, 85, has held since 2015.He runs the country’s day-to-day affairs, and it’s common for foreign leaders to liaise with him directly, including Russia’s Vladimir Putin and France’s Emmanuel Macron. Snub to Crown PrinceThe changes suggest U.S.-Saudi relations will return to “more structured, routine channels,” according to Aaron David Miller, a senior fellow at the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace and a former Mideast official at the State Department. “This is a slapdown of MBS, who the administration views as reckless and ruthless.”A White House official, who asked not to be identified discussing the change, said Psaki’s comment signals a return to longstanding diplomatic process.There was no response from Saudi officials as of Wednesday morning, and the Saudi government’s Center for International Communication didn’t immediately reply to a request for comment. However there’s been disquiet in Saudi elite circles over how Biden might change the U.S. relationship with the kingdom -- and with Iran, Saudi Arabia’s regional rival.“Tehran sees Biden as weak,” read the headline of a column on Wednesday in Al Sharq Al Awsat, written by Abdulrahman Al Rashed, a Saudi commentator close to the government.U.S. Weighs Saudi Immunity Request in Assassination Plot CaseThe relationship isn’t entirely broken. U.S. officials have said they want to help the Saudis be better able to defend themselves against Iranian aggression, and the U.S. is expected to work closely with the kingdom’s authorities to help bring about an end to the Saudi-led war in neighboring Yemen.The crown prince became a pariah in much of official Washington after the 2018 killing of Washington Post columnist Jamal Khashoggi inside the Saudi consulate in Istanbul. An investigation by a United Nations special rapporteur implicated senior Saudi officials who reported directly to the crown prince, an accusation rejected by the kingdom’s officials.Trump and his administration, in particular his son-in-law Jared Kushner, remained close to Prince Mohammed after the murder and avoided blaming him for it. Trump defended the relationship, saying billions of dollars in U.S. weapons sales to the kingdom would just go to China or Russia if the U.S. pushed back.Avril Haines, Biden’s director of national intelligence, has vowed to release an unclassified CIA report into Khashoggi’s killing that is likely to embarrass the crown prince.Recasting the relationship is “meant to send a signal that President Biden wants certain things from the crown prince, such as an end to the war in Yemen and a different approach to dissent at home,” said Martin Indyk, a former U.S. special envoy to the Middle East, now at the Council on Foreign Relations.Saudi Arabia Frees Women’s Rights Activist Amid U.S. ScrutinyResponding to a question about the administration’s broader outreach to the Mideast, Psaki said Biden intends to talk to Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu “soon” and this would be his first call with a regional leader. Israeli government officials have publicly complained that Biden hasn’t called him.(Updates with Saudi government mum on Biden’s remarks in ninth paragraph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Era in Atlantic City Ends With 3,000 Sticks of Dynamite...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/17/trump-era-in-atlantic-city-will-end-with-3000-sticks-of-dynamite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. — It will not be the biggest or the best implosion ever. An auction for the rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Lonely Americans Turning to AI Chatbots for Comfort...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/02/covid-19-has-made-americans-lonelier-ever-heres-how-ai-can-help/172067/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm tired of talking about Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9268459/Im-tired-talking-Donald-Trump-Joe-Biden-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden dodged questions Tuesday on Donald Trump's impeachment trial, saying he didn't want to talk about his predecessor in the Oval Office anymore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Pleasing Performance...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/joe-biden-town-hall-review-donald-trump-cnn-anderson-cooper-covid-1234695039/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking centerstage for the first time since assuming office, President Joe Biden returned tonight to the town hall format that served him so well as a candidate last year in an attempt to assure a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to 'Recalibrate' Saudi Arabia Ties Away From Crown Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-to-e2-80-98recalibrate-e2-80-99-saudi-arabia-ties-away-from-crown-prince/ar-BB1dJIJJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden intends to “recalibrate” the U.S. relationship with Saudi Arabia while emphasizing outreach to King Salman, in a move that signals a downgrade in ties with Crown Prince Mohammed Bin Salman, the country’s de facto ruler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos reclaims title of world's richest after Musk slips...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/bezos-reclaims-title-of-world-e2-80-99s-richest-after-musk-slips/ar-BB1dJRH3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s reign as the the world’s richest person was brief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon report reveals inroads white supremacists have made in military...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/02/16/pentagon-report-reveals-inroads-white-supremacists-have-made-in-military/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pentagon report paints a stark picture of white supremacist inroads in the U.S. military and reveals several steps under review to kick such people out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Most New Yorkers approve of Cuomo handling...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-covid-cuomo-nursing-homes-approval-siena-20210216-tdsp6onyifb4bbwdbubkpbjgpu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The survey, conducted earlier this month and released Tuesday, found that 61% of voters give the governor high marks for his management of the pandemic, down slightly from 63% in a previous poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations Plummeting In USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/plummeting-cases-in-u-s-show-a-path-to-crushing-covid-19/ar-BB1dIHkz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 cases and hospitalizations are dropping dramatically across the U.S., suggesting that measures to interrupt transmission are working, at least for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman killed in dispute over Trump sign...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/woman-killed-in-dispute-over-political-sign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One woman is dead and another faces murder charges in an incident involving a political sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: Biden confronts leadership moment in CNN town hall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/joe-biden-town-hall-02-16-21/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will participate in a CNN town hall tonight in Wisconsin. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell 'physically abused' during jail search, lawyer says...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/16/ghislaine-maxwell-losing-hair-abused-by-guard-behind-bars-lawyer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell was physically abused by a jail guard during a pat down search and is “withering to a shell” behind bars, dropping weight and losing her hair, an attorney for the accu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID FADING AWAY?  Cases Down 16% last week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-cases-down-16-233021005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new cases of Covid-19 reported worldwide fell by 16 percent last week to 2.7 million, the World Health Organization said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muted Mardi Gras: Closed bars, barricaded Bourbon Street...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/muted-mardi-gras-closed-bars-buourbon-st-1902f20dcd06d9326cbc058e25e46a39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Music blared from the courtyard of a French Quarter restaurant on Mardi Gras morning but nobody was there to hear it until Tom Gibson and Sheila Wheeler of Philadelphia walked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss Wealth Tax Rakes in Cash as Covid Stokes Global Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/swiss-wealth-tax-rakes-cash-050000510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Switzerland’s wealth tax offers a rare real-world example of how a levy on assets can work, just as such ideas gain traction elsewhere in the wake of the coronavirus crisis.The measure forces residents in one of the world’s richest nations to tally the value of their investments, real estate, cars, fine art, Bitcoin, and even beehives and cows. A percentage is then skimmed off by cantonal governments, varying in size and method depending on the canton. Switzerland, among only a handful of countries with the levy, can make a claim that it has the most effective one.With the Covid-19 fallout causing government debt to swell, and hurting poorer people most, wealth taxes are being debated from California to the U.K. as a tool both to pay down debt and address inequality. U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren, Nobel laureate Joseph Stiglitz and economist Thomas Piketty are among proponents.Criticisms range from the view that it’s wrong to target assets accumulated through income that is already taxed, to more practical questions of how to fairly operate such a levy. The Swiss don’t seem to be very bothered by all of that.“It works for us,” said Stefan Kaufmann, a farmer from Wetzikon in the canton of Zurich, who describes the policy as a good Swiss compromise. “The wealth tax isn’t a lot. It doesn’t hurt.”On the final day of each year, Kaufmann -- who sits on the town’s local legislature for the nationalist Swiss People’s Party -- counts up his livestock and enters the totals on a tax return with the rest of his assets. His 50 bulls are worth about 2,000 francs ($2,239) each, according to the rules. His two donkeys are 500 francs a pop.Kaufmann’s untroubled attitude is common. Switzerland’s cantonal wealth tax just isn’t as emotive a matter as elsewhere. In January, a bid to cut the levy in Zug, the jurisdiction near Zurich known as a low-tax home for hedge funds and commodity giant Glencore Plc, was defeated by lawmakers.Switzerland is among very few countries left with a recurring annual wealth tax. The number of OECD countries imposing it dropped to four in 2017 from 12 in 1990.The coronavirus has prompted calls to change tack, often led by left-leaning politicians. The idea won endorsement from Germany’s Social Democrats, part of the ruling coalition. Argentina implemented a one-time wealth tax in December.“A lot of European countries have tried wealth taxes, certainly wealth taxes on an annual basis, and they’ve almost inevitably retreated from it because it’s highly complicated,” U.K. Conservative lawmaker Mel Stride told Times Radio on Monday. A one-off wealth tax is “nearer the end of the spectrum of the possible.”The most common riposte to the policy, also in Switzerland, is that it hits citizens again after they’ve already paid dues on their incomes.Christian Frey, deputy head of finances and taxes at pro-business group economiesuisse, says it particularly hurts some company owners, who face having to withdraw money from firms to pay the levy, suffering dividend tax in the process.“It’s an additional burden,” Frey said.Another criticism is that rich people can avoid it by shifting jurisdiction, just as Elon Musk announced his departure from California, the U.S. state with the highest income tax.Switzerland’s rationale is the constitutional principle of everyone paying according to their means. Inheritance tax is low, and there’s no capital gains levy on movable property such as equities.The measure also comes with safeguards. There’s a formula to ensure people who are asset-rich but with low incomes can still afford it. In Kaufmann’s case, the farmers’ association sets the valuation of livestock annually to help keep filing simple.The result is that Switzerland derives a bigger share of total tax revenue from the levy than any other industrialized country, according to OECD data.That’s not to say its effectiveness is unimpeachable. A study by University of Lausanne economics Professor Marius Bruelhart found that a cut in the wealth tax rate in Lucerne was followed by a rise in declared assets, hinting at prior evasion.Whatever the case, Switzerland appears comfortable with the policy.“It takes some of the tension out of that political debate around tax between the haves and the have-nots,” said David Wigersma, a Lausanne-based partner at Deloitte SA.(Updates with U.K. lawmaker in 10th paragraph)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal courts demand double masking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wearing-2-masks-required-to-enter-federal-courthouses-in-ny</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll need to double mask to go inside federal courthouses in Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minor League Baseball Disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/minor-league-baseball-watch-2021-6121f637-4e7a-446c-995b-3ae79ec77132.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Minor League Baseball starts its 2021 season, there will be 25% fewer teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINION to Sue MYPILLOW Lindell...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/dominion-says-it-will-sue-mypillow-ceo-mike-lindell-over-election-fraud-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominion sent letters to Lindell in December and January demanding that he retract false claims about their machines, instead the MyPillow CEO doubled down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit TV News Anchor Dies Day After Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/02/16/former-detroit-tv-anchor-dies-one-day-after-taking-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karen Hudson-Samuels’ career in broadcast journalism spanned over four decades in Detroit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bipartisan' earmarks come back...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/02/16/earmarks-coming-back-congress-469131</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appropriators hope to recast the politically taboo spending practice as funding for “community projects."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Please don't rush the border, White House asks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/16/white-house-asks-asylum-seekers-not-to-rush-the-us-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House on Tuesday urged potential Central American asylum seekers not to rush the US-Mexico border as President Biden ends former President Donald Trump’s “Remain in Mexico&amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Star Dismisses Accusations Against Him as 'Recovered Memories'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-times-reporter-donald-mcneil-201006181.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jonathan Torgovnik/GettyThe veteran New York Times reporter who resigned following reports that he said the “n-word” during a 2019 trip with students has privately dismissed the high-schoolers’ claims in an email obtained and reviewed by The Daily Beast.“I’m amazed at what's happening. I feel like I’m facing students ‘recovered memories’ from two years ago,” Donald McNeil Jr. wrote in the email sent this week to close friends. “And other papers are eating it up. I said ‘racism is over?’ Huh?”He continued: “I said ‘ghetto’? I don't think I’ve said ‘ghetto’ except 1. about Warsaw or 2. ironically, with air quotes, since Elvis released that ridiculous song in 1969. A teenager ‘corrected’ me and was upset that I failed to apologize to her/him? I don’t even know how to respond to that. Somehow I think I’d remember it if it had happened.”The note was sent following a report from Times media columnist Ben Smith, in which Sophie Shepherd, a student on the 2019 trip, recounted several uncomfortable conversations she had with McNeil.In one allegation, which McNeil referenced in his private email, Shepherd recalled the reporter saying: “It’s frustrating, because Black Americans keep blaming the system, but racism is over, there’s nothing against them anymore—they can get out of the ghetto if they want to.”Star NY Times Reporter Accused of Using ‘N-Word,’ Making Other Racist CommentsEarlier this month, McNeil, who’d become one of the most prominent American journalists covering the coronavirus pandemic, left the paper after The Daily Beast reported that several students complained that he made racist and offensive remarks, including saying the “n-word,” while accompanying the high-schoolers on a Times-sponsored trip to Peru.In public, the longtime reporter has stayed largely mum on the allegations. But following his resignation he joked in a note to friends and family that he “always knew my big mouth would be me into trouble one day.”And in a separate email to Times colleagues announcing his departure, he directly apologized for saying the “n-word,” and attempted to explain how the word came up during a conversation about one student’s classmate who’d been suspended for a video in which she used the racial slur.“To understand what was in the video, I asked if she had called someone else the slur or whether she was rapping or quoting a book title,” McNeil wrote. “In asking the question, I used the slur itself. I should not have done that. Originally, I thought the context in which I used this ugly word could be defended.”McNeil’s departure, and the way in which the paper wavered on how much “intent” matters in his case, set off a heated debate inside the paper. Numerous staffers called for additional investigation into the trip, while top editors attempted to assuage the concerns of prominent employees who were alarmed by the student complaints against McNeil, and by the paper’s initial handling of the ordeal.And while current and former staffers at the Times have been hoping the media conversation around McNeil’s departure will eventually subside, the science writer has other plans.In this week’s email, he told friends he has been “writing out long answers to everything” which he promised to have finished by March 1—the same day he is due to leave the Times.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France passes anti-radicalism bill that worries Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/polygamy-radicalism-secularism-elections-france-cbee2c916aa8c35380562277f0025c2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Lawmakers in the French parliament's lower house on Tuesday overwhelmingly approved a bill that would strengthen oversight of mosques, schools and sports clubs to safeguard France...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas at One U.S. Hub Trading at $999. Last Week It Was $4...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/gas-one-u-hub-trading-173155074.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A polar blast in the central U.S. has pushed natural gas prices at one trading hub up 24,000% from a week ago.Supply for next-day delivery at the Oneok Gas Transportation hub in Oklahoma traded at $999 per million British thermal units for two contracts on Tuesday, according to David Hoy, a trader at Dynasty Power in Calgary. That compares with $4.19 a week earlier.Gas at the Henry Hub in Louisiana, the benchmark for futures in New York, traded at $19 at about 11:45 a.m. in New York after earlier soaring to $30, Hoy said. Supply at the hub traded at $3.24 a week ago.Production of gas in the Lower 48 states has plummeted to a three-year low as frigid weather triggers blackouts and causes liquids to freeze inside pipes, forcing wells and processing plants to shut. Underpinning the rally is the prospect of tighter inventories by the end of the winter as heating demand soars. Liquefied natural gas export terminals shut or curtailed operations amid a disaster declaration in Texas.“It’s a shocking situation,” said Cody Moore, head of gas and power trading at Mercuria Energy America LLC. “It’s chaos. It’s crazy with the prices.”Gas futures also rose, though they didn’t fully reflect the turmoil in the day-ahead market. Contracts for March delivery rose 10% to a three-month high before settling up 7.5% at $3.129.The spread between March and April futures -- essentially a bet on how well supplied the market will be at the end of winter -- rose to the highest since November.The cold ravaging the central U.S. should persist for days to come, with temperatures from South Dakota to Texas remaining well below average at least through Saturday, according to private forecaster Commodity Weather Group.“With bitterly cold air dropping all the way down to the Gulf Coast, the natural gas market is experiencing some of its most chaotic conditions ever,” Andy Weissman, chief executive officer of EBW AnalyticsGroup, said in a note to clients. “Massive amounts of production are offline, but so is a huge number of gas-fired power plants.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOURNALISM: Kudlow Caught on FOXNEWS Hot Mic Berating Kamala Harris...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/bullsht-fox-news-hot-mic-catches-larry-kudlow-raging-at-kamala-harris-for-claim-about-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump economic adviser Larry Kudlow was caught on a hot-mic profanely screaming about Vice President Kamala Harris' recent comments on the federal government's vaccine distribution plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Ending Use Of Term 'Illegal Alien'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/hamedaleaziz/illegal-alien-uscis-biden-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigrants and advocates say it represents a shift away from “dehumanizing” language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA opens mass vax sites...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fema-opens-mass-vaccination-sites-4cd95c115ac455169b63ae109d179f4a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEMA opened its first COVID-19 mass vaccination sites Tuesday, setting up in Los Angeles and Oakland as part of an effort by the Biden administration to get shots into arms more quickly and reach...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cuomo Aide Is Top Candidate to Replace CNN Zucker...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/media/zucker-lieutenant-top-candidate-replace-cnns-helm-rcna287</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allison Gollust, a CNN executive and top lieutenant to Jeff Zucker, has emerged as the leading internal candidate to take over the network if Zucker steps down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubai princess claims being held 'hostage' in new videos...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/16/dubai-princess-says-she-is-being-held-hostage-in-new-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Latifa Al Maktoum made the whispered pleas for help in a series of clandestine videos recorded on a phone that was smuggled to her in her villa “prison” in the Kingdom, the Fre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain betting on vaccine passports to revive summer visitors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-spain-tourism/spain-betting-on-vaccine-passports-to-revive-summer-tourism-idUSKBN2AG2CW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain hopes the introduction of vaccination passports combined with pre-travel COVID-19 testing will allow British tourists to return to Spanish destinations this summer, a tourism ministry source told Reuters on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Black church having a moment...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/16/us/black-church-pew-pbs-moment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pew is publishing a major study on African Americans' attitudes towards religion on Tuesday, the same day PBS premieres a two-part special on the history of the Black church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Printed in days, a house: 3D printing hits next level...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tech-3d-printed-house/printed-in-days-a-house-new-york-firm-takes-3d-printing-to-the-next-level-idUSKBN2AG2CA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most homes are built block by block, or brick by brick. But a demo house in Calverton, New York, was constructed scan by scan - its walls made using a giant three-dimensional printer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle woman, 90, walks 6 miles through snow for jab...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/seattle-storms-coronavirus-pandemic-2527c61138a14a5229c03bd221419196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A rare winter storm that dumped a foot of snow on Seattle couldn’t keep a 90-year-old woman from her first appointment for the coronavirus vaccine. The Seattle Times reports...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4th wave looms if USA fails to contain variants...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/02/16/covid-19-us-fourth-wave-variants-coronavirus/4460958001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts urge continued vigilance against the spread of coronavirus variants as some state officials lift mask mandates and ease restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA restricts edits...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/wikipedia-lincoln-project-edits-john-weaver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wikipedia is classifying The Lincoln Project's page on its site as "semi-protected," meaning many users are restricted from editing the page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners At Firm Hired to 'Review' Scandal Are Donors...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/paul-hastings-lincoln-project/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Hastings, the law firm hired to conduct a "comprehensive review" of the Lincoln Project's "operations and culture," could be hard-pressed to deliver a credible result given several of its senior partners have donated to the scandal-plagued super PAC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates: All rich countries should move to 100% synthetic beef!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/16/bill-gates-all-rich-countries-should-move-to-100-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft cofounder Bill Gates said in a new interview that all rich countries should transition to 100% synthetic beef in order to significantly curb the greenhouse-gas emissions driving climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Escape Confines of Time, Space According to CIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7k9qag/how-to-escape-the-confines-of-time-and-space-according-to-the-cia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the 80s, the spy agency investigated the "Gateway Experience" technique to alter consciousness and ultimately escape spacetime. Here is everything you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing off limits' in Oprah interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14064983/meghan-markle-prince-harry-determined-not-upset-queen-oprah-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THERE will be “nothing off limits” in Meghan Markle’s sit down interview with Oprah, Gayle King said today. The Duke and Duchess of Sussex will appear in a bombshell 90-minute spe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA reports back-to back days of more than 1 million travelers over Presidents' Day weekend...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/TSA-reports-back-to-back-days-of-more-than-1-15954004.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two days in a row over the holiday weekend, the Transportation Security...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echos rhetoric from the 1930s...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/spain-probes-anti-semitic-speech-at-neo-nazi-rally-01613495105?tesla=y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors in Madrid on Tuesday said they had opened an investigation into anti-Semitic comments made at a neo-Nazi rally held at the weekend which drew ire from Spain's Jewish community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain probes anti-Semitic speech at neo-Nazi rally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-media-social-media-barcelona-crime-9babe2c97e7be859f139789be3a0ea22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Prosecutors in Spain have launched two separate investigations involving a far-right party and extremist neo-Nazi sympathizers for possible hate crimes against Muslims and Jews,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID FADING AWAY?  India's dramatic fall in cases leaves experts stumped...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/india-dramatic-fall-coronavirus-cases-199585f8d5cb023abe241c4c463d88ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — When the coronavirus pandemic took hold in India, there were fears it would sink the fragile health system of the world’s second-most populous country. Infections climbed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside chilling torture dungeons run by Putin-backed sadist 'The Maniac'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14027442/ukrainian-basement-torture-cells-putin-the-maniac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORTURE dungeons where victims are mutilated with surgical tools, beaten with hammers and shocked with electricity are being run by Putin’s thugs in war-torn Ukraine, civil rights groups clai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare snow blankets Acropolis!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-athens-greece-be193363451279cc4d105d025d0fb2b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Heavy snowfall blanketed the Acropolis and other ancient monuments in Athens and halted COVID-19 vaccinations in the Greek capital Tuesday as the weather brought many...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle meeting with Newsom sparks talk about her political potential...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/meghan-markle-s-meeting-with-gov-newsom-sparks-talk-about-her-political-potential/article_82df15c1-05a0-5407-9fb3-10e2e784b326.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan Markle may be pretty busy these days, expecting her second child with Prince Harry while handling the demands of her new career as a philanthropist, Netflix producer, Spotify podcaster</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
