<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bombshell Suit Has 'GMA' Co-Hosts at Each Other's Throats, Sources Say...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bombshell-lawsuit-has-gma-co-hosts-george-stephanopoulos-and-robin-roberts-at-each-others-throats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources said a lawsuit accusing GMA’s former executive producer of sexual assault has opened a new rift between the show’s hosts and raised the anger of staffers demanding answers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian cosmonauts find new cracks in ISS module...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/science/russian-cosmonauts-find-new-cracks-iss-module-2021-08-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian cosmonauts have discovered new cracks in a segment of the International Space Station that could widen, a senior space official said on Monday, the latest in a series of setbacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavily armed criminal group ties hostages to getaway cars after laying siege to Brazilian city...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/heavily-armed-criminal-group-ties-hostages-to-getaway-cars-after-laying-siege-to-brazilian-city/ar-AANTWyl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even in a country long accustomed to random spasms of violence, Brazilians reacted with shock and fear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand reports first death following PFIZER shot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/569958-new-zealand-reports-first-death-following-pfizer-vaccine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand on Monday announced it had recorded its first death linked to Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine after a woman suffered from myocarditis, which is known to be a rare side effect of inflammation in the heart muscle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon acknowledges reports of civilian casualties in U.S. drone strike...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/569952-pentagon-acknowledges-reports-of-civilian-casualties-in-us-airstrike-targeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military officials are acknowledging reports of civilian casualties as the result of a drone strike on an explosives-laden vehicle carrying would-be suicide bombers in Kabul over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records rebut claims of unequal treatment of Jan. 6 rioters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/records-rebut-claims-jan-6-rioters-55adf4d46aff57b91af2fdd3345dace8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a common refrain from some of those charged in the Jan. 6 riot at the U.S. Capitol and their Republican allies: The Justice Department is treating them harshly because of their political views while those arrested during last year's protests over racial injustice were given leniency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In defense of Elon Musk: 'Smartest person in any room anywhere'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/29/the-smartest-person-in-any-room-anywhere-in-defence-of-elon-musk-by-douglas-coupland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s the Silicon Valley Übermensch who wants us to colonise Mars and who can wipe out billions of dollars with a single tweet. So what’s not to love?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No cash or gas to run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-stranded-3afc25cdcb7f5d8347d86f7cc69817e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Owens felt defeated and helpless Sunday as he waited in Louisiana's capital city for landfall by one of the most powerful hurricanes ever to strike the U.S. The 27-year-old had spent days anxiously watching long lines of cars evacuating from Baton Rouge, bound for safer locations out of state as Hurricane Ida approached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel doubles down on boosters as daily cases set new record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/30/israel-doubles-down-on-covid-booster-shots-as-breakthrough-cases-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli lawmakers are keen to avoid another lockdown after overseeing one of the world's fastest vaccination drives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Trapped In Homes...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/30/tropical-storm-ida-power-out-new-orleans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ida is now a tropical storm after spending 16 hours as a hurricane over Louisiana and Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S, others consider closing indoor seating...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/retail-consumer/mcdonalds-others-consider-closing-indoor-seating-amid-delta-surge-us-2021-08-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some U.S. fast-food restaurants are closing indoor seating areas or limiting hours of operation because of the spread of the Delta variant of COVID-19, according to franchisees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catastrophic damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/hurricane-ida-louisiana-2021-08-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ida, which crashed ashore as an "extremely dangerous" Category 4 hurricane, is now a tropical storm but still packing a powerful punch. Louisiana has more than a million power outages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar emerges as key player...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-afghanistan-qatar-6c1e9e4ef1a9f0c3d19eac20b9321339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Qatar played an outsized role in U.S. efforts to evacuate tens of thousands of people from Afghanistan. Now the tiny Gulf Arab state is being asked to help shape what is next for Afghanistan because of its ties with both Washington and the Taliban, who are in charge in Kabul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew Gilded Cage Closes in as DOJ Reiterates Desire to Speak to Disgraced Royal...</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/prince-andrew-gilded-cage-closes-103339629.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Furlong - WPA Pool/Getty ImagesPrince Andrew has abandoned public life, given up trans-Atlantic travel, and spends much of his free time sheltering behind the high walls of various properties owned by his mother, the sovereign, as he attempts to evade scrutiny from U.S. authorities over his links to Jeffrey Epstein, and specific allegations that he raped, on three occasions, the then-17-year-old sex-trafficking victim Virginia Roberts.For a man once so addicted to leaping on private</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Still Short of Everything. Get Used to It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/30/the-world-is-still-short-of-everything-get-used-to-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most people in the developed world, Kirsten Gjesdal had long taken for granted her ability to order whatever she</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MPH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge asked mother if she got vaccine. She said no, and he revoked custody of son...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-judge-asked-a-mother-if-she-got-the-covid-vaccine-she-said-no-and-he-revoked-custody-of-her-son/ar-AANThRw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Firlit told a Chicago judge she didn't get the coronavirus vaccine because she's had bad reactions to vaccines in the past. The judge then revoked her custody until she's inoculated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland Warns of Terror Attacks on Vaccine Sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/switzerland-warns-of-terror-attacks-on-covid-19-vaccine-sites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The authorities are concerned about attacks from militant groups, according to a newspaper report.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida radio host 'Mr. Anti-Vax' dies of covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.news-journalonline.com/story/news/local/volusia/2021/08/28/marc-bernier-30-year-daytona-beach-talk-host-dies-after-covid-battle/5639816001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news-journalonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Daytona Beach talk radio host Marc Bernier has died, his station, WNDB and Southern Stone Communications announced Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humorless politics a sad sign of our times...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/569895-humorless-politics-a-sad-sign-of-our-times</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When criticized for soaring deficits, Regan replied, “I am not worried about the deficit. It is big enough to take care of itself."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas anti-mask movement leader dead...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/569921-texas-anti-mask-movement-leader-dies-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of an anti-mask movement in Texas has died from COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek police use tear gas, water canon during protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210829184501-8bnzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GREECE-VACCINES/PROTESTS (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Greek police use tear gas, water canon during Athens vaccine protest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing Weeks of Darkness...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/orleans-facing-three-weeks-darkness-173547496.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- New Orleans may be without power and air conditioning for more than three weeks in the wake of Hurricane Ida, which roared ashore with more powerful winds than Hurricane Katrina, according to utility owner Entergy Corp.Almost 750,000 homes and businesses were without power across Louisiana as of 7:26 p.m. local time on Sunday, according to Poweroutage.us, which tracks utility outages. The blackouts were concentrated in the southeastern tip of the state that includes New Orleans an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM CHASER</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=itgNM2TLMgQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks for watching! Join this channel to get access to perks and become an OFFICIAL StormSeeker!:https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCJHA...___________________...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE:  WLTV...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3D7pQxnOIjI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on Hurricane Ida, projected to be a dangerous Category 4 hurricane at landfall Sunday.WWL-TV, New Orleans' Tegna affiliate, is covering Hur...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120 MPH...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCUAT4+shtml/291855.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Picnics and Snipers at Family Dollar: Life in a Town With a Government-Approved Militia...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/08/virginia-militia-bedford-campbell-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Virginia, paramilitarism gets a rebrand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will levees hold?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210830001941-cd3uw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/LEVEES (PIX):New Orleans' levees got a $14.5 billion upgrade. Will they hold?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals brimming with virus patients...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-hospitals-5f68dc3f11842ad3b2effbc5d202ffb4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Southern Lousiana's hospitals, already packed with coronavirus patients from a fourth surge of the virus, were dealing Sunday with another challenge — the howling Category 4 hurricane pounding the coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind, storm surge from Hurricane Ida lash Louisiana...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hurricane-ida-115ff1a54e18d9eee61a81afa8df9fad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Hurricane Ida blasted ashore Sunday as one of the most powerful storms ever to hit the U.S., blowing off roofs and reversing the flow of the Mississippi River as it rushed from the Louisiana coast toward New Orleans and one of the nation’s most important industrial corridors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostile school board meetings have members calling it quits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-school-boards-35db5c9eec87b85ca8eb95a64c2f6dd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Nevada school board member said he had thoughts of suicide before stepping down amid threats and harassment. In Virginia, a board member resigned over what she saw as politics driving decisions on masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weather heats up as California fire inches toward Lake Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-lakes-california-weather-643a876ab9a501480bdc74a8915eebce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH LAKE TAHOE, Calif. (AP) — Spiking temperatures and increasing winds on Sunday added to the challenges faced by firefighters battling blazes across Northern California, including one that continued its march toward the Lake Tahoe resort region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record onslaught of landfalls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-science--85bbaba49c4b8374a29ecfc1cfb5cbbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the past two years, hurricanes have been brewing, strengthening and hitting the United States at a record pace, and Ida will likely go down as one of the nastiest of a dangerous bunch. While not quite record-setting, Ida is among some of strongest and fastest intensifying storms in more than 150 years of hurricane records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone kills ISIS targeting airport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-kabul-us-taliban-9da4da11b5c8d00445b57aee297bd270</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — A U.S. drone strike blew up a vehicle carrying “multiple suicide bombers” from Afghanistan's Islamic State affiliate on Sunday before they could attack the ongoing military evacuation at Kabul's international airport, American officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden attends grim homecoming for troops killed in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/afghanistan-biden-troops-killed-509f29aaca012ee8e83871d2c03384bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOVER AIR FORCE BASE, Del. (AP) — In hushed reverence, President Joe Biden stood witness with grieving families Sunday under a gray sky as, one by one, the remains of 13 U.S. troops killed in the Kabul suicide bombing were removed with solemnity from a military aircraft that brought them home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landfall with 150mph winds and 185mph gusts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT4+shtml/291752.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APT BUILDING FIRE IN MILAN... DEVELOPING......</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-milan-fire-huge-blaze-24864639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The massive apartment block home to at least 70 families in the northern Italian city has been completely engulfed in flames. Reports say the blaze broke out on the building's 15th floor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ED ASNER DEAD AT 91...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/ed-asner-dead-lou-grant-1235004802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-time Emmy winner was funny on 'The Mary Tyler Moore Show' and serious on his own newspaper drama, then delighted movie audiences with 'Up.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden attends transfer of bodies after 13 troops killed at Kabul airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3562434/biden-receive-bodies-military-killed-kabul/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden is set to receive the bodies of the 13 US troops in the Kabul airport suicide bombing at Dover Air Force base. The President and his wife, First Lady Jill Biden, will meet the families of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of country running out of oxygen...</title>
      <link>https://www.wdsu.com/article/oxygen-supply-covid-19-cases-increase/37423857</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdsu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the continued uptick in COVID-19 cases, there has been more demand on the oxygen supply, and hospitals cannot keep up the pace to meet those needs, an expert says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Powerful Rocket Explosion Hits Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/afghanistan-powerful-rocket-explosion-hits-kabul-home-say-reports-2021-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rocket has hit a house near Kabul airport, say sources inside the Afghan capital. A child was killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss. Gov.: South's response impacted by belief in 'eternal life'...</title>
      <link>https://dailymemphian.com/article/23792/mississippi-governor-tate-reeves-covid-response-impacted-faith</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymemphian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi Gov. Tate Reeves talked about the pandemic Thursday, Aug. 26, at a re-election fundraiser in Shelby County held at a replica of the Mississippi governor’s mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran thieves attack car, steal shots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-middle-east-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-7a4207ef9a1590665b262e1886bc43d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran — The police chief for Iran’s capital says a gang of thieves has robbed scores of COVID-19 vaccines after attacking a hired car carrying the doses, media reported. The robbery comes as Iran, with over 106,000 virus-related deaths, has the highest death toll in the Mideast but only 8% of its people are fully vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
