<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uiBrForlj-k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naomi Osaka becomes the first Japanese player to win a Grand Slam after she defeated Serena Williams 6-2, 6-4 in the final of the 2018 US Open but the match ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Things Can Get Worse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/obama-campaign-mode-back-promoting-hope-over-fear-041514906--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — Former President Barack Obama says the November midterm elections will give Americans "a chance to restore some sanity in our politics," taking another swipe at his successor as he raises his profile campaigning for fellow Democrats to regain control of the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama MCDONALD's shooting leaves 1 dead, 4 wounded...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/09/09/shooting-at-alabama-mcdonald-s-leaves-1-dead-4-wounded-police-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person was killed and four others were wounded early Sunday after shots were fired at a McDonald’s near Auburn University, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showdown Tests Limits of Duterte's Authoritarian Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/philippine-showdown-tests-limits-of-dutertes-authoritarian-power-1536493618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte’s attempt to force the arrest of a leading critic has run into unexpected resistance from institutions that had previously done his bidding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson: May 'wrapping suicide vest around Britain' with Brexit plan...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/09/09/boris-johnson-says-theresa-may-is-wrapping-a-suicide-vest-around-britain-over-brexit-7927543/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-foreign secretary has been slammed for the 'disgusting' comments by members of his own party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL won't implement new national anthem policy this season...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/24622089/nfl-not-expected-implement-new-national-anthem-policy-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is not expected to implement a new policy on trhe national anthem this season, league sources tell ESPN, no matter how many meetings and conversations occur about the topic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss America Contestant Slams Trump During Pageant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/miss-america-contestant-slams-trump-division-madeline-collins-west-virginia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Donald Trump is the biggest issue our country faces," a Miss America contest told judges. "Unfortunately, he has caused a lot of division in our country."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA rancher wins legal battle in bald eagle attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/news-to-me/georgia-rancher-wins-compensation-bald-eagle-attacks/mMotH8bCF2Xptra86hJ9CP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgia rancher’s battle against bald eagle attacks on his pasture-raised chickens continues...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Cuts ICBMs Out of Military Parade..</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/north-korea-cuts-icbms-out-of-military-parade-1536477004</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intercontinental ballistic missiles were absent from a military parade marking the 70th anniversary of North Korea’s founding, amid a monthslong detente between Pyongyang and Washington that has appeared precarious at times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthodox Jewish women slammed for wearing 'slutty' wigs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/09/09/orthodox-jewish-women-slammed-for-wearing-slutty-wigs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People always say the longer it is, the sluttier it is,” said Esther Adina Sash, a 30-year-old mother of two from Flatbush. Specifically, she’s referring to the sheitels, or wigs, that she and oth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi homecoming queen boots game-winning extra point...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2c27a4fe1e9948c7a0195c135dd28168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCEAN SPRINGS, Miss. (AP) — One Mississippi high school senior had to quickly discard her crown after being named homecoming queen — and put on a football helmet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist: Catholic Church Sex Abuse Scandal Demonic, Likely to Get Worse...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/leading-u-s-exorcist-catholic-church-sex-abuse-scandal-is-demonic-likely-to-get-worse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The clouds are just starting."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serena Williams blowup jolts U.S. Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6146903/Im-not-cheater-Serena-Williams-argues-umpire-U-S-Open-womens-final.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Serena Williams came to blows with the umpire in the US Women's final as she accused him of 'stealing a point from her'. Williams crashed out of the final with Osaka winning 6-2, 6-4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPhones aim for momentum in sputtering smartphone market...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/iphones-aim-momentum-sputtering-smartphone-market-014210889.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple is set to unveil new iPhones, aiming to gain fresh momentum in the premium segment of a global smartphone market showing signs of fatigue. In its usual secretive style, Apple has remained mum about revelations planned for Wednesday's event at its spaceship campus in Silicon Valley, but the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Masterpiece'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/cuarons-mexican-masterpiece-wins-venice-film-festival-204556245.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican director Alfonso Cuaron won the Golden Lion top prize at the Venice film festival Saturday for "Roma", which critics have called not merely a movie but "a vision". With its highly emotional story centred on an indigenous maid working for a middle-class family in Mexico City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Why Trump's Record Trumps the Media's Spin...</title>
      <link>https://nationalinterest.org/feature/why-trumps-record-trumps-medias-spin-30757</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalinterest.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The media is determined to prove that Donald Trump is unfit to be president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make products in USA to avoid China tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-tells-apple-products-u-avoid-china-tariffs-195918839--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company told trade officials in a letter on Friday that the proposed tariffs would affect prices for a "wide range" of Apple products, including its Watch, but it did not mention the iPhone. Trump, speaking on Friday aboard Air Force One, said the administration had tariffs planned for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWEDEN SWINGS RIGHT</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/anti-immigration-party-set-election-gains-sweden-swings-220942202.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The influx of 163,000 asylum seekers in 2015 has polarized voters and fractured the cozy political consensus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  APPLE bans Alex Jones app for 'objectionable content'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-infowars/apple-inc-bans-alex-jones-app-for-objectionable-content-idUSKCN1LO04G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc said on Friday that it had banned from its App Store the Infowars app belonging to popular U.S. conspiracy theorist Alex Jones after finding that it had violated the company's rules against "objectionable content".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA URGES 'SANITY'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/697572f93a024d2bb322208537c45e1e/Obama,-on-campaign-swing,-urges-'sanity-in-our-politics'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANAHEIM, Calif. (AP) — Former President Barack Obama said Saturday that November midterm elections would give Americans "a chance to restore some sanity in our politics," taking a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Ocasio-Cortez, Dem candidates dance their cares away; Nixon shakes chest as women cheer...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-ocasio-cortez-dem-candidates-dance-their-cares-away-nixon-shakes-chest-as-women-cheer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-left gubernatorial candidate Cynthia Nixon, Attorney General candidate Zephyr Teachout and Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez broke out the dance moves as they campaigned in New York today. The trio was seen salsa dancing has photogs captured the moment. Nixon shook her hips, appearing to back into Cortez and grinding on her. ﻿ A person wearing a New …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  Odds Rising Florence Will Strike East Coast... </title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Cone-Florence-Takes-Aim-Southeast-US</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outer edge of the 5-day uncertainty cone for Tropical Storm Florence is now over North Carolina and South Carolina, as the dangerous storm heads west toward the Southeast U.S. coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump adviser says Cruz could lose Senate race...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/trump-adviser-suggests-cruz-isn-t-likable-enough-to-be-re-elected/17829485/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump’s budget chief, Mick Mulvaney, expressed confidence to Republican donors Saturday that the party would overcome a Democratic “movement of hate” in November, but he acknowledged Republicans could lose races where they have nominated candidates who are not seen as “likable” enough, like Sen. Ted Cruz of Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary to appear at 'Lesbians Who Tech' event...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/shes-back-too-hillary-to-appear-at-lesbians-who-tech-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move over Back Obama: Hillary Clinton isn’t going away, either. As the midterms approach, the throwbacks of the Democrat Party are taking center stage. This week, Clinton will be appearing at a “Lesbians Who Tech” conference in New York, according to a promotional video put out by the group. HILLARY AT SUMMIT. THIS IS NOT …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA: Chance to restore sanity...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/09/08/obama-says-midterms-are-chance-to-restore-some-sanity-to-our-politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Obama on Saturday hit the campaign trail in California, where he struck an optimistic note for activists ahead of November’s midterms a day after a speech in which he ripped into President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice: Cuaron Wins Golden Lion for 'ROMA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/venice-film-festival-awards-unveiled-updating-live-1141199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuaron previously conquered Venice after launching Gravity on the Lido in 2013, which went on to win seven Academy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of emergency in Carolinas...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/09/08/tropical-storm-florence-prompts-north-and-south-carolina-to-declare-states-emergency-as-it-approaches-east-coast.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in South Carolina and North Carolina have both declared a state of emergency ahead of Tropical Storm Florence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Venice Film Festival Winners...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/09/venice-film-festival-2018-awards-winners-full-list-1202460207/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Refresh for latest…: The 75th Venice Film Festival draws to a close tonight with the winners about to be announced from inside the Sala Grande here on the Lido. Guillermo del Toro’s jury has …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Trump Admin Discussed Coup Plans With Rebel Venezuelan Officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/trump-administration-discussed-coup-plans-with-rebel-venezuelan-officers/17828936/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration held secret meetings with rebellious military officers from Venezuela over the last year to discuss their plans to overthrow President Nicolás Maduro, according to U.S. officials and a former Venezuelan military commander who participated in the talks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'End of days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/bible-prophecy-realised-first-red-13213028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't call Alamo defenders 'heroic,' TX school curriculum panel urges...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2018/09/07/dont-call-alamos-defenders-heroic-texas-school-curriculum-panel-urges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas News: your source for breaking news and analysis for Dallas-Fort Worth, Texas and around the world. Read it here, first.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos makes $11,000,000 -- an hour!</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/business/437939-besoz-net-profit-amazon-wages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos makes over $11,000,000 an hour, lowest paid Amazon worker gets $12</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag and Burlesque Shows Keeping Berlin Edgy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-drag-and-burlesque-shows-keeping-berlin-edgy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city’s reputation as an epicenter for fetish and fantasy is part of what draws more than 12 million tourists per year; but locals know that hedonism is only the beginning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive boom will corral Pacific's plastic trash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47a3d74f8a3f4a6e917b32c371b85568/Massive-boom-will-corral-Pacific-Ocean's-plastic-trash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — Engineers will deploy a trash collection device to corral plastic litter floating between California and Hawaii in an attempt to clean up the world's largest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonbelievers Seek Political Power to Match Growing Numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/nonbelievers-seek-political-power-to-match-their-growing-numbers-1536418801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the midterm elections approach, the growing number of nonbelievers in the U.S. are trying to build something that has long eluded them: political power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 1 In 4 College Students Diagnosed With Mental Health Condition...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-quarter-college-students-diganosed-mental-health-condition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College brings about new experiences and challenges for young adults that can be difficult to adapt to and overcome, so perhaps it's no surprise that a new study reports high rates of stress and mental health conditions among students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened on Space Station? Leak Remains Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2018/09/international-space-station-nasa-russia-leak/569692/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The puzzling story of a mysterious malfunction 250 miles above Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Presidents: First 600 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/09/a-comparison-of-two-presidents-president-trump-versus-president-obama-their-first-600-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside AMAZON 'hellish' warehouses where staff forced to perform cult-like chants...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7207232/amazon-warehouse-underpaid-staff-unrealistic-targets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON workers have described the “hellish” conditions inside the company’s warehouses where they are reportedly made to hit “crushing” targets. Staff at the web giant…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oktoberfest backlash over 'porn' outfits...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7207106/oktoberfest-beer-festival-backlash-sex-clothes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STEIN swilling female tourists who flock to Oktoberfest for a knees up are being slammed for wearing outrageous versions of the traditional Bavarian dress. Cultural leaders believe much of what is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New material to speed spacecraft to 134,000,000 mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/728251/nasa-space-light-speed-caltech-solar-sail-nanomaterial-silica-silicon-technology</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right expected to make historic gains in Swedish election...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1a21129a48924d2495165824ba6ac955/Swedes-weigh-choices-before-vote-likely-to-boost-far-right</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM (AP) — Swedish political candidates are making their final pitches to voters on the eve of a general election expected to see a far-right anti-immigrant party make histo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBERS stressed, lonely; 'Algorithm loves you most'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/sep/08/youtube-stars-burnout-fun-bleak-stressed </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why are so many YouTubers finding themselves stressed, lonely and exhausted?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prison and hospital: Primary battle grounds in Brazil's election race...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180908-prison-hospital-primary-battle-grounds-brazils-election-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial recognition touted as 'user friendly' system for airports...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-09-facial-recognition-touted-user-friendly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As facial recognition technology use generates intense scrutiny, a new system unveiled at Washington's Dulles airport is being touted as a "user friendly" way to help ease congestion for air travelers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Trade Surplus With USA Hits New Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-trade-surplus-with-u-s-hits-new-record-1536397753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s trade surplus with the U.S. widened to $31.05 billion in August from $28.09 billion the previous month, while its total trade surplus narrowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Pulls INFOWARS From App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-pulls-alex-joness-infowars-from-its-app-store-1536382593</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple removed Alex Jones’s Infowars website from its App Store, eliminating one of the few remaining digital platforms available to the right-wing provocateur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Trump Admin Discussed Coup Plans With Rebel Venezuelan Officers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/09/08/world/americas/donald-trump-venezuela-military-coup.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan military officers seeking to overthrow President Nicolás Maduro sought help from the Trump administration, which met with them several times.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
