<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Next smartphone might have camera that's always watching...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/your-next-smartphone-might-have-a-camera-that-e2-80-99s-always-watching/ar-AARwjKv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black couple says appraiser lowballed them. So, they 'whitewashed' home and say value shot up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/a-black-couple-says-an-appraiser-lowballed-them-so-they-whitewashed-their-home-and-say-the-value-shot-up/ar-AARwbJG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin calls ties with USA 'lamentable'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211206120656-ud5gn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RUSSIA/KREMLIN (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Kremlin calls U.S.-Russia ties ' quite lamentable' on eve of Putin-Biden call</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: People Who Meditate Have Better Focus, Sleep, Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/meditation-better-focus-sleep-mental-health-apps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The self-care tools they’ve found most beneficial for achieving this include meditation apps (52%), in-person therapy (45%), and virtual therapy (43%).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists bask on battlefield as drug gangs fight over Mexican resort town...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tourists-bask-battlefield-drug-gangs-100051334.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tulum, jewel of the Mayan Riviera, risks emulating Acapulco, another once glamorous resort now overwhelmed by violence Members of the national guard patrol Playa Pescadores in Tulum. Photograph: Artur Widak/NurPhoto/Rex/Shutterstock Bright yellow police tape fluttered in the breeze outside a restaurant just off the main strip in the Mexican resort town of Tulum, as the lights of a nearby police truck flashed blue and red. Troops in camouflage fatigues stood guard outside the deserted late-night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Robbers Hit Home During Holiday Party...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/12/05/exclusive-armed-robbers-hit-palisades-home-during-holiday-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the bulk of partygoers were in the backyard, the suspects entered the home and robbed two guests inside the house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's New Moon Landing Schedule Escalates Race With USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/china-s-new-moon-landing-schedule-escalates-race-with-u-s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s New Moon Landing Schedule Escalates Race With U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Workers Shrug Off Omicron as More Return to Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/city-of-london-workers-shrug-off-omicron-as-more-return-to-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;City of London Workers Shrug Off Omicron as More Return to Work</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Blood Pressure Rising? You're Not Alone...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/the-pandemic-has-your-blood-pressure-rising-youre-not-alone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last year was a tough one. Americans grappled with a global pandemic, the loss of loved ones, lockdowns that splintered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners or Partners in Crime? Maxwell-Epstein Bond Key to Case...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/partners-or-partners-in-crime-maxwell-epstein-bond-is-key-to-her-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Visoski, the silver-haired pilot who flew Jeffrey Epstein and his prominent friends all over the world, believed Ghislaine Maxwell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TESLA as Musk Pushed Unflinching Vision for Self-Driving Cars...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/inside-tesla-as-elon-musk-pushed-an-unflinching-vision-for-self-driving-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To hear more audio stories from publications like The New York Times, download Audm for iPhone or Android. Elon Musk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TIKTOK Reads Mind...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/06/how-tiktok-reads-your-mind/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are four main goals for TikTok’s algorithm: 用户价值, 用户价值 (长期), 作者价值, and 平台价值, which the company translates as “user</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight wolves poisoned in Oregon, stumping police and renewing calls for protections...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Eight-wolves-have-been-poisoned-in-Oregon-16677692.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oregon authorities are seeking help after the state's dwindling gray wolf population was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems plot escape from Biden poll woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/06/democrats-biden-polling-woes-523719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party's own polling has the president in the red. Lawmakers know they need to get better at selling his agenda to avert midterm disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven days: Following Trump's reckless coronavirus trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Seven-days-Following-Trump-s-reckless-16676950.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When he first learned he had tested positive for the coronavirus, President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonds' Faith in Fed Set For Biggest Test Since '80s...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bond-market-s-faith-in-fed-set-for-biggest-test-since-the-1980s-1.1691116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bond traders’ faith in the Federal Reserve’s power to curb inflation is about to face its biggest test in four decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing attacks potential diplomatic boycott of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-sports-boycotts-beijing-2020-tokyo-olympics-7727b98d708447ae24457d910a8f1ae8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China on Monday threatened to take “firm countermeasures” if the U.S. proceeds with a diplomatic boycott of February’s Beijing Winter Olympic Games. Foreign Ministry spokesperson Zhao Lijian accused U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed Italians face new restrictions as holidays near...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-lifestyle-health-milan-894002a958b201b5ac255152294d3fa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Italy is making life more uncomfortable for unvaccinated people this holiday season, excluding them from indoor restaurants, theaters and museums starting Monday to reduce the spread of coronavirus and encourage vaccine skeptics to get their shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Tells USA to look in 'Mirror' Before Accusing Kremlin of Aggression...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/ukraine-russia-vladimir-putin-joe-biden-anthony-blinken-invasion-1656092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian foreign affair's spokeswoman Maria Zakharova referred to NATO campaigns in Iraq, Libya and Syria and Yugoslavia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of young adults obese or overweight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/over-half-of-young-adults-are-obese-or-overweight-study-says/ar-AARtSVq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Congressman's gun-toting family Christmas photo sparks outrage days after school shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gop-congressman-e2-80-99s-gun-toting-family-christmas-photo-sparks-outrage-days-after-school-shooting/ar-AARuSV1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB DOLE DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/05/politics/bob-dole-dies/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, a Republican Party stalwart and presidential hopeful who espoused a brand of plain-spoken conservatism as one of Washington's most recognizable political figures throughout the latter half of the 20th century, died Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise ship with at least 17 virus cases aboard docks in New Orleans...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Cruise-ship-with-at-least-17-coronavirus-cases-16678395.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Norwegian Cruise Line ship docked in New Orleans over the weekend with at least 17...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock to Crypto Daredevils Joins List of Scary Market Omens...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/shock-to-crypto-daredevils-joins-list-of-scary-omens-in-markets-1.1691526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brutal bout of selling that wiped billions of dollars from profitless growth companies, IPO stocks and SPACs has now caught up with Bitcoin, further stressing risk tolerances and brokerage balances among small-time traders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decades of service...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/bob-dole-dead-98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Senate Majority Leader Bob Dole died Sunday morning at age 98 after he was treated for lung cancer earlier this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN FIRES CUOMO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/04/media/cnn-fires-chris-cuomo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN said Saturday that anchor Chris Cuomo has been "terminated" by the network, "effective immediately." The announcement came after an outside law firm was retained to review exactly how Cuomo aided his brother, former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX ALLEGATION...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/05/chris-cuomo-hit-with-sexual-misconduct-allegation-from-former-co-worker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former co-worker of Chris Cuomo made a sexual misconduct allegation against the former CNN anchor, who was fired Saturday for his involvement with trying to mitigate sexual harassment accusations…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Plunges in Another Sign of Global Market Nerves...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-plunges-over-20-another-063422558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin plunged along with other cryptocurrencies on Saturday, in another indication of the risk aversion sweeping across financial markets.Most Read from BloombergThe Hot New Trend For Hedge Funds Is—Finally—Female FoundersAutomating the War on Noise Pollution‘Ghost Signs’ Haunt London’s Reviving NeighborhoodsThe largest digital token fell as low as $42,296 before paring some of the tumble. It was trading at about $48,300 as of 10:31 a.m. in New York on Saturday, a drop of about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle with cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4210410/bob-dole-cancer-republican-cause-of-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER Senate majority leader and Republican presidential candidate Bob Dole has died at the age of 98. The Elizabeth Dole Foundation confirmed that Dole, who had been diagnosed with stage 4 lung c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier and Stalwart of Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/05/us/politics/bob-dole-dead.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Dole, a son of the Kansas prairie who was left for dead on a World War II battlefield, became one of the longest-serving Republican leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia planning military offensive against Ukraine with 175,000 troops, U.S. intel warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-planning-massive-military-offensive-against-ukraine-involving-175000-troops-us-intelligence-warns/ar-AARrLIF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WWII veteran and three-time presidential candidate passes away at 98...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/05/bob-dole-wwii-vet-and-3-time-presidential-candidate-dead-at-98/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bob Dole, a decorated veteran who overcame near fatal wounds in World War II to become a respected Senator and three-time Republican presidential candidate, died on Sunday. He was 98. “It is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer robbed at gunpoint...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/san-francisco-chronicle-photographer-robbed-at-gunpoint-in-west-oakland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Francisco Chronicle photographer was robbed at gunpoint on Friday afternoon in West Oakland, California, during an assignment, the newspaper reported. The robbery came on the heels of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$7B startup gets flack as CEO lays off hundreds over ZOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/tech/article/Better-mortgage-firm-has-mass-layoff-Zoom-16673576.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The last time I did this, I cried,' the CEO said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Iran's Natanz nuke facility just attacked for third time in two years?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/sabotage-at-irans-natanz-nuclear-facility-30-analysis-687849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Most mutated virus ever seen'...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/scientists-call-omicron-most-mutated-virus-wed-ever-seen-why-does-that-matter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawrence Young, a virologist at the University of Warwick, described omicron as “the most heavily mutated version of the virus we have seen,” including potentially worrying changes never before see…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
