<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>If Taylor Swift album drops in pandemic, does it make sound? </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/If-a-Taylor-Swift-album-drops-in-a-pandemic-does-15432249.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The freakiest thing about Taylor Swift's never-freaky music is how politely it trespasses on your brain tissue. It doesn't really matter where your head is at. With an automatic omnipresence - in restaurants, rideshares, retail spaces and everywhere else we do our everyday things - her biggest songs literally change the world.  Maybe not this time. The tiniest perk of pandemic life is that we actually have the luxury of choosing whether or not to invite Swift's eighth album, "Folklore," into our lives. And Swift knows it. Presenting herself as a gracious guest rather than an imminent ubiquity, she's made the quietest, most sophisticated album of her career.  That might not be saying a lot, considering how Swift spent her twenties blasting the planet with melodic confetti, but at least "Folklore" isn't the predictable girl-and-guitar-quarantined-in-Nashville album that it could have been. Instead, these spartan pop ballads sound as if they were written entirely on Swift's terms, artfully co-produced by Aaron Dessner, (who makes hygienic rock-like music in the National) and Jack Antonoff (who also recently helped Lana Del Rey make her greatest album by staying out of the way). Don't let the negligible duet with Justin Vernon of Bon Iver distract you, either. The triumph of "Folklore" isn't that Swift has suddenly become tasteful and tuned-in. Having so thoroughly crashed the pop charts like a fluorescent tidal wave, she's finally making enough space in her music for her modest voice to sound like itself.  "I've never been a natural," she asserts with paradoxical ease during "Mirrorball," a declaration of self-awareness that aptly makes the room spin. "All I do is try, try, try ... I'm still trying everything to keep you looking at me." Her voice is plain and true, vulnerable but steady, and nothing can pull your ears...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass resignations at Hungary's largest news site as press freedom slides...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-53531948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 70 staff resign at top independent site Index, in a row over media freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dogs CAN sniff out infections...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/german-sniffer-dogs-show-promise-at-detecting-coronavirus/a-54300863</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in Germany have found that army sniffer dogs can discern between samples from coronavirus-infected and healthy patients. So high is the level of accuracy, they hope this can be used in real-life scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player Refuses To Kneel For BLM, Citing Christian Faith...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/news/i-just-cant-get-on-board-sf-giants-player-cites-christian-faith-as-reason-for-refusing-to-kneel-for-blm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only baseball player who refused to kneel during a moment honoring Black Lives Matter in Dodger Stadium on Thursday claimed he did so because of his Christian faith. Sam Coonrod, a 27-year-old reliever for the San Francisco Giants, explained his act by saying he only kneels before God, according to TMZ Sports. Coonrod also [&amp;hellip;]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of U.S. tourism hurts Italian economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/italy-tourism-without-americans-covid-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have long had a love affair with Italy. This summer, that love affair is on hiatus, and Italy is feeling the heartache as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police investigating fire at AZ Dem HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/phoenix-breaking/2020/07/24/fire-damages-arizona-democratic-party-headquarters-building-phoenix-overnight/5501305002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No one was in the building at the time of the fire, and police believe the fire was intentionally set.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/nation-world/2020/07/23/a-band-aid-on-a-bullet-wound-workers-are-getting-laid-off-anew-across-us-as-ppp-program-runs-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Layoffs are beginning to spike again around the country as coronavirus cases soar, spurring cities and states to backtrack on reopenings only a month after appearing to turn the corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for fourth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/1286793355742126080?s=20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Health anxiety' Soars...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/508863-health-anxiety-in-the-time-of-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health anxiety, excessive concern about one’s health, is one important psychological factor that is affecting people’s reactions to the stress that comes along with COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he 'often' regrets his tweets and retweets...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/508947-trump-says-he-often-regrets-his-tweets-and-retweets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump acknowledged in an interview released Friday that he “often” regrets his tweets and retweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More military bases increase health protections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e6be6854547fd32fbb43633e7f37d970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. military has increased health protection requirements in at least 21 bases in recent weeks, particularly across Texas and Florida, as the COVID-19 rate continues to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC orders two-week quarantine for travelers from hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c421a2ba9d349fcc7ad56f3b7c3496c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Seeking to address newly rising infection numbers, Washington, D.C., is mandating that anyone arriving in the nation's capital after non-essential travel to a coronavirus hot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 88, former Sheriff Joe makes another comeback bid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ca10f3a6316f149c61a9179bfa5e080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — Joe Arpaio is trying to win back the sheriff’s post in metro Phoenix that he held for 24 years, facing his former second-in-command in the Aug. 4 Republican primary in what has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra PPP aid expires...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0255528817e87bcee9087f4b8649b571</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — As public health officials warned Friday that the coronavirus posed new risks to parts of the Midwest and South, enhanced federal payments that helped avert financial ruin for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES Top Editor Accused of Verbal Harassment, Retaliation Against Reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/la-times-guild-letter-norman-pearlstine-verbally-harassed-reporter-ethical-lapses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a letter to management obtained by TheWrap, the guild protested "an environment of hostility, intimidation and harassment"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for fourth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/COVID19Tracking/status/12867933557421260800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk, Who Made $2 Billion This Week, Opposes More Cash For the Unemployed...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2020/07/tesla-elon-musk-oppose-coronavirus-stimulus-plan-heroes-act/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Another government stimulus package is not in the best interests of people,” Musk tweeted Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Eyes Building Nuke Power Plants for Moon, Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2020-07-24/us-eyes-building-nuclear-power-plants-for-moon-and-mars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WARNING TEXAS</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/242050.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1/3 not hospitalized have long-term illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/monumental-acknowledgment-cdc-reports-long-term-covid-19-patients-n1234814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One patient whose symptoms have lingered for months called the report "monumental."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Eases Restrictions On Armed Drone Sales Abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/politics/2020/07/trump-eases-restrictions-armed-drone-sales-abroad/167202/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans increasingly boycotting brands over politics...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/americans-are-increasingly-boycotting-brands-over-politics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of Americans are putting their money where their political values are. According to a survey by CompareCards, roughly 4 in 10 Americans are boycotting at least one company because it doesn't align with their political ideology or values. More than half of those boycotters are avoiding more than one company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas police investigate possible drowning at BELLAGIO fountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/las-vegas-police-investigate-possible-drowning-at-bellagio-fountains-2080586/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Las Vegas police were investigating a possible drowning Friday morning at the Bellagio fountains on the Strip. A dive team recovered a body from the fountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN draws 4 million viewers, up 232%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/24/espns-mlb-opening-day-games-draws-average-of-4-million-viewers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Yankees' game against the Washington Nationals was also the highest-rated MLB regular-season game on ESPN in the New York market since 2015, according to the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAVES Lose Both Catchers on Opening Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.barstoolsports.com/blog/2696692/covid-baseball-is-here-braves-lose-both-catchers-on-opening-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barstoolsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Giphy Images.It's fitting the Braves are playing the Mets today, because this is the most Mets shit I've ever seen in my life. With new closer Will Smith still out after testing positive for COVID an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Cluster Linked To High School Party; Teens Won't Cooperate With Tracers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/23/middletown-nj-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 20 young adults between the ages of 15-19 contracted the virus either while there or from someone who was there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gang loyal to Maduro beats residents for refusing to cover faces...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8557663/Venezuelan-regimes-gang-beat-residents-disobeyed-COVID-19-preventive-measures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gang that is known for enforcing the law for Maduro regime recorded itself beating two individuals who reportedly were ignoring the country's preventive measures to combat COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOD mulls mobile hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/24/dod-is-scouting-contractors-to-set-up-potential-mobile-coronavirus-hospitals-in-florida-as-outbreak-worsens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army is helping Florida in case it needs to quickly build out more surge capacity at its hospitals as Covid-19 cases continue to rise, seeking contractors who can build temporary facilities with 10 days notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to Bypass Arms Control Pact to Sell Large Armed Drones...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/24/trump-administration-plans-to-bypass-arms-control-pact-to-sell-large-armed-drones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The Trump administration plans to announce on Friday that it will allow the sale of armed drones to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC to require 14 day quarantine for those traveling from hot spots...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/508913-dc-to-require-those-traveling-from-hot-spots-to-quarantine-for-14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Mayor Muriel Bowser (D) on Friday announced that all visitors arriving in the District on nonessential business from hotspot areas will now need to quarantine for 14 days, as the country continues to see a surge in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan prays with Muslims in Hagia Sophia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dispatch-erdogan-prays-muslims-hagia-151744384.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People had travelled thousands of miles and slept on the cobbled streets to get a spot inside. In Istanbul, a city famed for its towering minarets and echoing calls to prayer, Friday Islamic prayers on Friday returned to the Hagia Sophia for the first time in almost 90 years. Wearing a white skull cap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young, healthy with mild cases take weeks to recover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200724165404-ktkli</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/RECOVERY:Young, healthy adults with mild COVID-19 also take weeks to recover - CDC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau strains to contain political scandal engulfing his family...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/24/trudeau-political-scandal-family-381002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving forward, Trudeau and Morneau may have to deal with more problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Michael Cohen released from federal prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/24/micheal-cohen-released-from-federal-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen was walked out of Otisville prison in Central New York shortly sometime after noon, his lawyer told the Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents dispatched to Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://ktiv.com/2020/07/24/us-agents-dispatched-to-seattle-to-protect-federal-buildings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktiv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory masks becoming rule amid Europe's virus uptick...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/mandatory-masks-becoming-rule-amid-122636738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New rules on wearing masks in England came into effect Friday, with people entering shops, banks and supermarkets now required to wear face coverings, while Romania reported a record for daily infections and France announced mandatory testing for arrivals from 16 countries, including the United States</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DODGERS' star drops extremely loud F-bombs in fan-less stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/giants/article/Dodgers-Joc-Pederson-curse-F-bomb-empty-stadium-TV-15430777.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior to professional sports leagues resuming without fans and crowd noise amid the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Trump could lose reelection in 100 days -- and USA is on edge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-could-lose-reelection-100-days-us-edge-014927857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cratering in the polls, canceling his showcase convention event, and struggling to land punches on his opponent, Donald Trump has only 100 days from Sunday to save his presidency -- and it's not going well. In the latest blow to momentum ahead of November 3, the president announced late Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica reopens -- but NOT TO AMERICANS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200723231639-ub8sl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/COSTA RICA:Costa Rica to reopen two airports to tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia evicts Confederate monuments from state Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/899c05e1b9b8550bd7e1db30932dbe30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Virginia has removed from its iconic state capitol the busts and a statue honoring Confederate generals and officials. That includes a bronze statue of Gen. Robert E. Lee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK REPORT:  Dems favored to take back Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/cook-political-report-democrats-favored-to-take-back-senate-with-just-over-100-days-until-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the current political climate and just over 100 days until Election Day, Republicans are at risk of losing their Senate majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medicated Chewing Gum Future Of Prescription Drugs?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/medicated-chewing-gum-future-prescription-drugs-robotic-mouth-reality/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the University of Bristol say medicated chewing gum is a very effective way of getting drugs into a patient's body. The problem is there's no proven method of testing how well gum releases medicine into the mouth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE WARNS:  'Do Not Underestimate Evil Genius Trump'...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/07/24/michael_moore_do_not_underestimate_the_evil_genius_that_is_donald_j_trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Moore warned Democrats not to get too excited and underestimate a Trump victory in 2020 in an interview on Joy Reid's new MSNBC program. Moore also encouraged Joe Biden to act as if he is currently the president and start holding a "Morning Meeting" and have fireside-type chats with Americans from his basement. if I were advising him, I would tell him just to start running the country right now, just act as if you are the president. That means nobody can assume the election is over. "I want to caution everyone, do not underestimate the evil genius that is Donald J. Trump," Moore warned. "There are many examples throughout history, whether it's Henry V facing the French on Saint Crispin's Day, they outnumbered him 4 to 1 and he was supposed to lose and he didn't. And or jump ahead to the 1995 NBA playoffs [ed. 1994], the Knicks are ahead with 15 seconds left, way ahead of the Indiana Pacers, and Reggie Miller scores eight points in nine seconds. With 15 seconds left." Reid and Moore also discussed their appearance on a 2016 episode of 'Real Time' with HBO host Bill Maher where the filmmaker predicted a Trump victory. "We've been fooled by polls before. Listen, Trump has got a number of tricks up his sleeve to suppress the vote, to try to postpone the election, blaming the coronavirus, to any of the number of things where he will try to weasel his way out of this," Moore said of the election. "And our side, and Joe Biden -- Joe Biden, I think, you know, honestly, if I were advising him, I would tell him just to start running the country right now, just act as if you are the president. That means nobody can assume the election is over." "Everybody's got to show up the vote and bring ten people with them, but right now every morning we could have a morning meeting with Joe Biden from the basement. The basement is fine. We want him safe, he's doing the smart thing and have the morning meeting with America. Tell us what we're going to do today to save this country. At night sit by the fireside and do what he does best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT08/refresh/AL082020_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/150135_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems want to prevent swing voters from defecting back...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article244286797.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP CANCELS REPUBLICAN CONVENTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/newslocalpolitics/trump-abruptly-cancels-republican-convention-in-jacksonville-its-not-the-right-time/ar-BB177hFy?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci gets security detail after threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article244460877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA Thought Police caution editors about using FOX as source...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/24/media/wikipedia-fox-news-reliable-sources/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wikipedia community recently engaged in a spirited debate over whether Fox News is a reliable enough source to use as a citation in entries on the encyclopedia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL STORM WARNING ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF  TEXAS COAST... </title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-hanna-forms-and-heads-for-texas-coast/781953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Hurricane Douglas Weakening, But is Likely to Strike Hawaii Sunday...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-07-24-hurricane-douglas-hawaii-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on Douglas's journey to Hawaii this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSE CALL:  Mel Gibson was hospitalized for week with covid...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/movies/mel-gibson-hospitalized-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gibson, 64, fell ill with the potentially deadly virus back in April</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big lead in polls shifts search...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-lead-polls-biden-shifts-110054292.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many on Biden's team once felt he needed a running mate who'd generate excitement. Now, with his polling lead, a "do no harm" strategy gains ground. But pressure for a Black candidate mounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL Deaths Set Record For 2nd Day In Row...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/24/coronavirus-at-a-glance-florida-breaks-record-for-single-day-increase-in-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are the latest numbers and information you need to know at-a-glance as of 11 a.m. on July 24, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden VP selection down to Karen Bass or Tammy Duckworth?</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/congress/source-coelho-pushing-biden-to-pick-bass/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order Requires Quarantine Upon Entering Massachusetts...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2020/07/24/coronavirus-massachusetts-governor-charlie-baker-update-friday-july-24-travel-order-fine-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new travel order says visitors and in-state residents returning home must fill out a "Massassachusetts Travel Form" and quarantine for 14 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Germans received neo-Nazi death threats. Now police under suspicion...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Prominent-Germans-received-neo-Nazi-death-15431323.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN - When German comedian Idil Baydar heard last week that investigators suspect a police officer may have been involved in sending her neo-Nazi death threats, she was aghast.  She was especially distressed to learn that the suspected police link had been known for at least nine months and she had not been told. Instead, she had been informed that the investigation into the hate-filled text messages she received throughout 2019 was closed.  "I don't know who to trust or believe anymore," said the 45-year-old actress. "I am completely in shock."  Baydar is one of more than two dozen German public figures threatened over the past two years in a case that has cast a shadow over police since the outset. In 2018, it emerged that a police computer was used to access information on lawyer Seda Başay-Yıldız shortly before she received threats containing personal details.  Now, revelations that police computers in Frankfurt and Wiesbaden were also used pull data on Baydar and left-wing politician Janine Wissler have triggered uncomfortable questions for Germany about racism and far-right networks in its institutions.  It comes amid a flurry of public debate on issues such as racial profiling and systemic racism as the global Black Lives Matter movement increases scrutiny. Earlier this month reports of extremism within Germany's special forces led the defense minister to disband one combat unit and announce a restructuring.  While suspicions of a police role have not been confirmed, the scandal forced the police chief in the state of Hesse to resign this month. Meanwhile, each day brings reports of new threats, with a slew of left-wing and minority politicians, journalists and lawyers receiving new emails in recent days.  Pressure has mounted against regional Interior Minister Peter Beuth, who answered questions from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorcist claims possessed woman threw 4 men across room...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/exorcist-claims-possessed-woman-threw-22400635</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exorcist Bishop Plato Angelakis has claimed he witnessed a victim of demonic possession gain superhuman strength and throw four men across a room after speaking in a demonic language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumatran tiger cub born in Polish zoo...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sumatran-tiger-cub-born-polish-zoo-135714320.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sumatran tiger -- a critically endangered species -- was born in a zoo in Poland, officials said on Friday. The female cub was born during the coronavirus lockdown on May 20 at the Wroclaw Zoo in the southwestern city by the same name, but news of her arrival was only made public now. &amp;quot;We were</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOS:  Federal Officers Battle With Rioters in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/07/24/exclusive-videos-unlawful-assembly-portland-fires-federal-officers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An &amp;quot;unlawful assembly&amp;quot; was declared after a large, peaceful protest turned into another night of battling in front of the Federal Courthouse in Portland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold Tops $1,900...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/commodities/spot-gold-tops-1900-first-time-2011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Reasons Election Day Could Be Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/24/2020-election-disaster-perfect-storm-372778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may think you know how bad Nov. 3 will be. But all signs point to something far, far worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbus statue in Chicago taken down under cover of darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8556221/Statue-Christopher-Columbus-removed-Chicagos-Grant-Park.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after news spread that Chicago mayor Lori Lightfoot had sanctioned the statue's removal, crews used a large crane to remove the monument from its pedestal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet freedom group alleges harassment by Trump administration...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/U-S-Internet-freedom-group-alleges-harassment-by-15431135.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Leaders of the Open Technology Fund accused the Trump administration...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional poker player found dead with badly burnt body...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/sport/other-sports/professional-poker-player-susie-zhao-22408354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI has joined the investigation involving professional poker player Susie Zhao after her badly burned body was found in a Michigan parking lot earlier this month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death in Florida every 8 mins...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19-death-every-8-044632133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 has taken a heavy toll on Florida residents older than 65, who account for just 13% of the state&amp;#39;s coronavirus cases but 82% of the fatalities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professor forced to retire after 'slave' tweet found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/education/article244449237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ranked among worst countries to raise family?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/23/america-ranked-among-worst-countries-to-raise-a-family-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We get an “F” for family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar Losing Luster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dollar-losing-luster-investors-line-052258429.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- After rocketing higher in March as the ultimate haven currency, the dollar is now headed for its worst month since the beginning of 2018, and many strategists see the sell-off continuing.Negative real rates in the U.S., the relentless spread of the coronavirus in America and a pickup in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Star of This $70 Million Sci-Fi Film Is Robot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/24/the-star-of-this-70-million-sci-fi-film-is-a-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strangest part of Matthew Helderman’s video call came when he bit into an apple. Or rather, what followed. “What</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Harvesting DNA From Millions. Is This Future of Policing?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/24/china-is-harvesting-dna-from-millions-of-people-is-this-the-future-of-policing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For several years now, the police and other authorities in China have been collecting across the country DNA samples from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Hurricane Douglas hurtling toward Hawaii with 130 mph max sustained winds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP3+shtml/240847.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks federal agents from arresting observers in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/847341576e44e4d9e717128db08faad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — A federal judge specifically blocked U.S. agents from arresting or using physical force against journalists and legal observers at protests in Oregon's largest city where...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA ORDERS USA TO CLOSE CONSULATE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5979db970a71ec5a0fdd3ba6ac92e03d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China ordered the United States on Friday to close its consulate in the western city of Chengdu, ratcheting up a diplomatic conflict at a time when relations have sunk to their...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients will be 'sent home to die' if deemed too sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article244443257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birx warns 11 major cities including Indianapolis, Pittsburgh and Baltimore...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8554281/Dr-Birx-warns-11-major-cities-aggressive-steps-mitigate-COVID-outbreaks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 11 cities Dr Birx mentioned include: Baltimore, Cleveland, Columbus, Indianapolis, Las Vegas, Miami, Minneapolis, Nashville, New Orleans, Pittsburgh and St Louis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayors urge residents to wear masks --  at home!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/508836-two-florida-mayors-urge-residents-to-wear-masks-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Florida mayors who govern Miami and Miami-Dade County encouraged their residents on Thursday to wear masks inside to lower the transmission rate of COVID-19 between family members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meghan and Harry file lawsuit over drone photos taken at LA pad...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/harry-meghan-sue-unnamed-paparazzi-224159426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After settling in Los Angeles, the couple and their young child allege they have been harassed daily by eager photographers invading their privacy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
