<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ice preserved tiny puppy in near-perfect condition for 18,000 years. Scientists fascinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Ice-preserved-a-tiny-puppy-in-near-perfect-14871919.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have big outstanding questions about the puppy they have named Dogor - "friend" in a language of the Siberian area where the creature spent 18,000 years in permafrost.  They're still trying to figure out if the tiny animal is a dog or wolf. They wonder whether he could be part of the evolutionary bridge that turned a fierce wild animal into man's best friend.  They don't have to speculate about what Dogor looked like, however, because icy conditions have left him remarkably frozen in time. Scientists can touch his fur, lift his padded paws and pull back his lips to bare small, yellowed teeth.  "Fantastic, right?" says Dave Stanton, a research fellow at the Centre for Palaeogenetics in Stockholm who has been scrutinizing the long-lost canine. "We have quite a lot of ancient samples. . . . But this has got be one of the best-preserved."  The puppy was discovered last year by locals in Yakutia, said Sergey Fedorov, who heads the exposition hall at the Mammoth Museum of Russia's North-Eastern Federal University. Dogor left the wilderness as a lump of soil and ice, but scientists could make out the head and paws of what they believed at first to be a young wolf.  Federov told The Washington Post that he carefully cleaned off dirt and debris to reveal near-intact fur - "extremely rare for animals of that time period."  "It's an amazing feeling, to see, touch and feel the history of earth," he said.  The puppy, whose name was announced earlier this week, remains in Russia. But he has caught the attention of researchers in Sweden and England who want to better understand Dogor's life and place in a still-mysterious evolution.  Testing on a rib bone has revealed the animal's age: about two months, said Stanton, a postdoctoral scholar who's been working for over a year on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BOWL PREVIEW? </title>
      <link>https://www.ninersnation.com/2019/11/29/20986214/super-bowl-preview-49ers-ravens-baltimore-san-francisco</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ninersnation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2 hottest teams in football face off, round 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces of the heroes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/london-bridge-heroes-who-risked-20994292</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usman Khan's rampage left two people dead and three injured before he was dragged to the ground by members of the public outside Fishmongers' Hall. He was then shot by elite police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genealogical databases goldmine for police, but with few rules and little transparency...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/genealogical-databases-are-a-goldmine-for-police-but-with-few/article_a15200f8-30cd-5423-991d-cfb15b8b5209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orlando police detective Michael Fields was sure he had the break he needed right in front of him to close in on a serial rapist: a list of people whose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing impeachment inquiry, Trump strives to look hard at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Facing-impeachment-inquiry-Trump-strives-to-look-14872290.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. - As Democrats in Congress push to impeach him, President Donald Trump has toured a manufacturing plant in Texas, boasted about economic gains and signed numerous bills. He served turkey to U.S. troops in Afghanistan on Thanksgiving and grieved with the families of fallen service members at Dover Air Force Base in Delaware.  And next week, Trump is scheduled to jet to London to meet with European allies and be received at Buckingham Palace by Queen Elizabeth II.  Sure, Trump has been consumed by the impeachment proceedings, popping off daily, if not hourly, about what he dubs a "hoax." But he and his aides also have staged photo opportunities and public events designed to showcase the president on the job - a strategy one year out from the election to convince the American people that he is hard at work for them at the same time that Democrats are trying to remove him from office.  "I'm working my ass off," Trump told a thunderous rally crowd of roughly 20,000 on Tuesday night in Sunrise, Florida. He added: "The failed Washington establishment is trying to stop me because I'm fighting for you and because we're winning. It's very simple."  Trump is taking a page out of the Clinton playbook. Then-President Bill Clinton survived his 1998 impeachment in part because the economy was roaring and because he appeared to many voters to be relentlessly focused on doing the business of the American people. When Clinton left office in 2001, Gallup measured his job approval rating at 66%.  Clinton had a built-in advantage that Trump does not enjoy: popularity. Throughout his second term, Clinton's approval rating hovered in the high 50s and 60s, whereas Trump's has been mired below 50%.  Still, Clinton's experience has been instructive to Trump, who recently met in the Oval Office with former Clinton strategist Mark...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu-hit PATS hope they're past worst...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/flu-hit-pats-hope-theyre-past-worst-193317046--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New England coach Bill Belichick is hoping the Patriots will be close to full strength for their trip to Houston on Sunday after illness sidelined eight from mid-week practice. &amp;quot;We&amp;#39;ve had some guys miss,&amp;quot; Belichick told reporters on Friday. Four of the ailing players returned to action</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIRAL: Iraqis keep up anti-regime demos despite PM's vow to quit...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iraqis-keep-anti-regime-demos-despite-pms-vow-073400257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iraqis kept up their anti-government protests in Baghdad and across the south on Saturday, unsatisfied with the prime minister's planned resignation and insisting "all corrupted people" must step down. Prime Minister Adel Abdel Mahdi announced on Friday he was planning to submit his resignation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany's far-right AfD elects new leaders as radicals rise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germanys-far-afd-elects-leaders-radicals-rise-034202709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany's far-right AfD party will elect new leaders on Saturday, with its increasingly influential radical wing seeking to tighten its grip on the group after a series of electoral victories. Underlining the polarising effect the party has on Germany, up to 12,000 protesters are expected to gather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 25: The day it all began...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ed77e5d517054816b51d2285ed4efe88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The forecast for July 25 was typical for Washington: sunny, mid-80s. President Donald Trump had good reason to be feeling bright and sunny himself. It was the morning after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bystanders used whale tusk, fire extinguisher to subdue...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/nov/30/narwhal-tusk-and-fire-extinguisher-used-to-tackle-london-bridge-attacker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the public, including a convicted murderer, bring terrorist to the ground</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to blitz Iowa back roads by bus in 800-mile hunt for support...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-biden/biden-to-blitz-iowa-back-roads-by-bus-in-800-mile-hunt-for-support-idUSKBN1Y40AK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden will crisscross Iowa by bus for eigh...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge 'for death of ISIS leader'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/london-bridge-terrorist-plotted-revenge-20995155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security source revealed Usman Khan was also taking part in a mandatory Government de-radicalisation course after being jailed for terrorism offences. al-Baghdadi was killed during a military raid last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One city's plan to combat: Bulldoze homes, rebuild paradise...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/One-city-s-plan-to-combat-climate-change-14863871.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. - Swinging cranes and clawing excavators have reshaped the landscape here, elevating Charlotte's skyline, expanding its girth and transforming this former cotton-shipment town into the South's financial hub and one of America's fastest-growing cities.  But the Queen City also has been steadily unbuilding itself, bulldozing houses and razing apartment complexes along its creeks, ripping up a mall parking lot to reveal a hidden waterway and then stripping away its concrete banks, all in a bid to prevent the flash flooding that turns communities into deathtraps.  The county has removed 460 structures and replaced them with absorbent grasslands, winning national praise as a prototype for regional flood planning that anticipates the impact of projected development and the growing effects of extreme weather. The innovative strategy was ahead of the curve when it launched in the 1990s, by calculating future flood risk and then purchasing - and demolishing - vulnerable homes, businesses and office buildings.  But the region is facing more-complex challenges as climate change threatens bigger and more-lasting deluges. Six out of North Carolina's seven wettest storms have occurred in the past 20 years. In June, following an 11-inch downpour upstream, the Catawba River burst its banks here in a catastrophe that can't be cured by opening up a few extra acres of flood plain.  "We just can't engineer ourselves out of this problem," said Bill Hunt, a civil engineer at North Carolina State University who predicts that more-drastic steps will become necessary to move entire communities out of danger.  "What Charlotte has done works very well for two- or three-inch rains," Hunt said. "But we don't have tools to fix 11- or 12-inch rains."  The program, operated jointly by the city of Charlotte and Mecklenburg County, has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bows to 'fake news' law with post 'correction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50613341</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first time the social media giant has added a correction to a post under the new law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALISM: Students Fainting From Hunger in Venezuela Schools...</title>
      <link>https://theunionjournal.com/college-students-fainting-from-starvation-in-venezuelas-failing-college-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theunionjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOCA DE UCHIRE, Venezuela — Tons of of kids filed into their college courtyard to listen to a neighborhood Catholic bishop lead prayers for his or her scho</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority of Republicans say Trump better president than Lincoln...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/472460-poll-majority-of-republicans-say-trump-better-president-than-lincoln</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of Republicans say President Trump is a better leader than former President Abraham Lincoln, according to this week’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INCIDENT AT FORT BRAGG' MOVIE SET TO TELL 'TRUE STORY' OF SOLDIER'S EXORCISM...</title>
      <link>https://sofrep.com/news/incident-at-fort-bragg-movie-set-to-tell-the-true-story-of-a-soldiers-exorcism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sofrep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Osgood Perkins is slated to direct the new film,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper gives beat to Chile street revolt...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/rapper-tijoux-gives-beat-chiles-street-revolt-094116817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilean singer Ana Tijoux says she is scared of cameras. Latin America's richest country has been rocked by more than six weeks of protests sparked by a 30 peso (four US cents) rise in metro fares. Tijoux -- who Rolling Stone magazine has hailed as the "best rapper in Spanish" -- is just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack began at rehabilitation event...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/how-the-london-bridge-terror-attack-unfolded-11874155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the London Bridge terror attack began at a prisoner rehabilitation event</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELEGRAPH CEO heralds digital growth as takeover talk swirls...</title>
      <link>https://gulfnews.com/business/telegraph-ceo-heralds-digital-growth-as-takeover-talk-swirls-1.68171705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gulfnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turning casual online readers into paying subscribers is critical for Hugh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Posts First Month in 70 Years as Net Petroleum Exporter...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-posts-first-month-70-154903996.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. solidified its status as an energy producer by posting the first full month as a net exporter of crude and petroleum products since government records began in 1949.The nation exported 89,000 barrels a day more than it imported in September, according to data from the Energy Information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Set, Billions Minted: Will Be Hard to Top 2019 Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/records-set-billions-minted-hard-181030572.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In a bull market almost everyone thought was living on borrowed time, the S&amp;P 500 is poised to post one of its best years in two decades. Extraordinary returns like those are complicating the lives of people paid to predict what happens next.Stretches like this are only raising the stakes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON EVERYWHERE: How Tech Giant Wove Self Into Life of American City...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/30/prime-mover-how-amazon-wove-itself-into-the-life-of-an-american-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE — Another big Prime Air 767 takes off from Baltimore-Washington International Airport — where Amazon’s shipping last year eclipsed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia tests hypersonic missile in Arctic...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130114502-1lz1m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-ARCTIC/MISSILES:Russia tests hypersonic missile in Arctic - TASS cites sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters burn tires in Iraq in renewed anti-govt rage...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191130085156-dqa7o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-PROTESTS/ (PIX):Protesters burn tyres in southern Iraq in renewed anti-government rage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY WAS HE FREE?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-attack-usman-khan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE London Bridge terrorist was free to kill an innocent man and woman despite the judge who jailed him ruling he should never be let out. Usman Khan, 28, from Staffordshire, was released from pris…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belonged to jihadist group that admired Hitler...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/30/london-bridge-stabber-belonged-to-jihadist-group-that-admired-hitler-plotted-to-bomb-us-embassy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knife-wielding terrorist who was subdued by civilians, then shot dead by police on London Bridge on Friday was a paroled bomb plotter who once hoped to start a jihadist training camp in Kashmir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state lawmaker faces backlash against white nationalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/far-right-washington-state-lawmaker-faces-backlash-against-white-nationalism/ar-BBXwDbc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Miami-Dade officer rebuilt his life after prison. Then, a nephew had him murdered, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article237872849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu clings to office while calling criminal charges against him a 'witch hunt'... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Netanyahu-clings-to-office-while-calling-criminal-14871331.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This appears in Saturday's Washington Post:  - - -  When former Israeli prime minister Ehud Olmert came under criminal investigation on bribery charges a decade ago, he took the honorable route and resigned, opening the way for new elections that brought Benjamin Netanyahu to power. Now it's Netanyahu's turn: Israel's attorney general announced Nov. 21 that he plans to indict the sitting prime minister on charges of bribery, fraud and breach of trust. To the detriment of Israel and its democracy, Netanyahu is taking the low road.  Rather than accede to the many calls for him to resign - and a poll showing that a majority of Israelis want him to go - Netanyahu has adopted what might be called, and what probably deliberately is, a Trumpian defense. The charges against him, he claims, are an "attempted coup"; the police investigators and prosecutors who spent years preparing them are guilty of a "witch hunt" and should themselves be investigated.  On Tuesday, Netanyahu staged a public rally in Tel Aviv and bused in supporters to demonstrate against the "coup." The result was a welcome sign that he may have gone too far: Key leaders of his Likud party declined to attend. One of them, Gideon Saar, has said he will challenge Netanyahu for the party leadership in a primary.  Netanyahu's intransigence is particularly worrying because it is the primary reason Israeli politicians have been unable to form a government following elections in April and again in September. Neither the Likud's right-wing alliance nor its center-left opposition commands a majority in the Knesset. The centrist Blue and White party, which holds the most seats, says it will not form an alliance with Likud unless Netanyahu agrees to give up the prime minister's post, at least while his criminal case plays out.  Netanyahu appears to hope that remaining in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pardons likely for Flynn, Manafort, Stone...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/It-s-a-good-bet-Trump-will-pardon-his-felon-14871149.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future isn't promised, but it is a good bet that three felons and close allies of President Donald Trump - Roger Stone (found guilty of obstruction of a congressional investigation, witness tampering and lying to Congress), Paul Manafort (serving prison sentence for tax evasion and bank fraud) and Michael Flynn (pleaded guilty to lying to the FBI) - will be granted executive clemency. The only question is when.  It might be a tad bit premature for Manafort to start humming "I'll Be Home for Christmas." But he will be there next year.  To be sure, Trump could free his friends before voters cast their ballots in 2020. But that's politically risky, as President Gerald Ford's 1976 defeat can attest. His approval rating dropped more than 30 points after he pardoned Richard Nixon.  Trump's safest course of action would be to wait to do the dirty deed until after Election Day, Nov. 3, 2020. Trump's impulsiveness, however, is a wild card.  Impeached or not, Trump can still grant pardons without fear of a citizens' revolt - once the polls close. Even if the voters serve him with an eviction, Trump can still cut his boys loose, provided he acts before turning off the lights in the Oval Office.  The Stone, Manafort and Flynn prediction is offered with confidence because of Trump's demonstrated disregard for the integrity of the criminal-justice system.  That disdain was on display in his recent chiseling of the military judicial process. Against the advice of experienced, respected leaders in the Pentagon, Trump intervened in three cases involving war crimes accusations, overturning decisions of military juries and issuing full pardons to two soldiers convicted of war crimes, as well as reversing disciplinary action against a third service member, Chief Petty Officer Edward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ask Trump if he wants lawyers at impeachment hearings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/88646b56c71641b9906a9cab82379315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The chairman of the House Judiciary Committee asked President Donald Trump on Friday to say whether he’ll send his attorneys to participate in impeachment proceedings before the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attending CAMBRIDGE conference -- on prisoner rehabilitation...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/london-bridge-attacker-identity-attack-video-stabbing-incident-latest-a9227061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Still wearing ELECTRONIC TAG'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7740295/Knife-attacker-shot-dead-London-Bridge-known-police-security-sources-reveal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The knife attacker shot dead on London Bridge was known to police and had connections to terror groups, a security source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. tells Israeli audience he'd 'rather be in Auschwitz than NYC'....</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/29/louis-c-k-tells-israeli-audience-hed-rather-be-in-auschwitz-than-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The off-color comment came as Louis C.K. continues an international comedy tour, meant to bring him back into the mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KID ROCK GOES ON DRUNKEN RANT ABOUT OPRAH...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/29/kid-rock-escorted-off-stage-after-drunken-rant-against-oprah-winfrey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rock is heard yelling “F–k Oprah” during his rant against the media mogul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu Season Takes off Quickly in Deep South States...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-11-29/flu-season-takes-off-quickly-in-deep-south-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you 'brain-dead'? Erdogan raps Macron before NATO summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-turkey-security-france-idUSKBN1Y31I0?taid=5de1967f86d8c600013cfbed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan said on Friday that Emmanuel Macron's warn...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARDINALS player caught betting on NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/28189546/cardinals-josh-shaw-suspended-least-2020-season-betting-nfl-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cardinals' Josh Shaw has been suspended through at least the 2020 season for betting on NFL games on multiple occasions, though the league says no contests were compromised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Vicious Brawl Outside FOREVER 21; Woman's Wig Goes Flying...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/black-friday-2019-fights-prove-deal-hunting-is-as-perilous-as-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because what would this American shopping tradition be without brawls and f-bombs?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S GHOST TOWN</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/29/macys-a-ghost-town-on-black-friday-thanks-to-web-shoppers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of online retail has eased the Black Friday hoards of yesteryear, but many bargain-seekers still turned out across the Big Apple on Friday to splash some cash in person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China mixing military and science in push...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-arctic/china-mixing-military-and-science-in-arctic-push-denmark-idUSKBN1Y3116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's military is increasingly using scientific research in the Arctic as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans 'absolutely disgusted' by President, ex-GOP congressman says...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/29/politics/charlie-dent-congress-trump-behavior-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Republican congressman Charlie Dent said Thursday some of his former colleagues in the House of Representatives have privately told him they are "absolutely disgusted and exhausted by the President's behavior."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA arrests cryptocurrency scientist for assisting NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-authorities-arrest-ethereum-research-200109230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office of the U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York and the FBI announced today that it has arrested and charged Virgil Griffith for violating the U.S.The post U.S. authorities arrest Ethereum research scientist Virgil Griffith for assisting North Korea in evading sanctions appeared</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 wounded in The Hague stabbing attack... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f698b4dc05949cbb2bfca45f98d39ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — The Latest on stabbings in The Hague (all times local): 9:30 p.m. Dutch police say three people were injured in a stabbing on The Hague’s main shopping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several wounded in stabbing in The Hague... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/29/several-people-wounded-in-stabbing-on-shopping-street-in-the-hague.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears mount about Biden's SC firewall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/472330-fears-mount-about-bidens-south-carolina-firewall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent weeks, Biden has been losing ground in the first two early voting states, according to polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack on city's main shopping street...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/the-hague-several-hurt-after-stabbing-in-shopping-area-11873848</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police have begun a manhunt after several people were hurt in a stabbing in The Hague.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor treating Amish sees rarest diseases on Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/in-depth/news/nation/2019/11/29/wisconsin-rural-doctor-treats-amish-studies-rare-genetic-diseases/3995625002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When James DeLine became a rural doctor, he had no experience treating the Amish, and no idea he'd be at the cutting edge of genetic medicine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Teacher of the Year' gave student oral sex in classroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article237863534.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois town to use marijuana sales tax to fund reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/suburbs/evanston/ct-evr-evanston-reparations-marijuana-tax-tl-1205-20191126-g3ifwaikrjfmrillfv6ytvwgii-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evanston council members voted to earmark the city's marijuana sales tax revenue to a local reparations program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 KILLED...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/live/uk-50601491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say they have shot dead a man suspected of being behind a stabbing attack near the bridge in central London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON exec 'main suspect' in wife's horrific murder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/29/juan-carlos-garcia-ex-ceo-of-amazon-mexico-suspected-in-wifes-murder-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former head of Amazon Mexico is wanted for questioning in his estranged wife’s murder after she was ambushed in Mexico City, according to reports. Juan Carlos García and his wife, Abril P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shut down AMAZON warehouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10447003/black-friday-protest-warehouse-climate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOZENS of protesters shut down an Amazon warehouse in France on Thursday in protest at Black Friday – claiming it harms the planet. Activists from climate group Amis de la terre (Friends of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French prosecutor drops charges against killer of Jewish teacher...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/french-prosecutors-drop-murder-charges-jewish-kindergarten-teacher-sarah-halimi-killer-kobili-traor%C3%A9-1.493649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'IRISHMAN' to Mister Rogers, what it means to be a man is getting real... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/entertainment/article/From-The-Irishman-to-Mister-Rogers-what-it-14870480.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Fonda visited The Washington Post the other day. At breakfast, just before going onstage with Diane Lane to talk about oceans in crisis, she responded to a question about the intersection of environmental politics and feminism. The veteran actress and advocate observed that women have always gravitated toward working together in the collective interest.  "It's not that we're better than men," she quipped, quoting her good friend Gloria Steinem. "It's just that we don't have our masculinity to prove."  It's a great line - classic Gloria. And it turns out to be apropos, not just in the world of activism, but in movies. Among the dozens of awards contenders that are crowding theater screens between now and the end of the year, a significant number seem to be grappling with men's roles, reflecting disruptions that are roiling the film establishment itself. At a time when the white male gaze is being challenged as Hollywood's default setting, the very essence of manhood - the postures, attitudes and behaviors that movies have portrayed as "male" for more than a century - is being reappraised. Films that once might have been positioned as celebrations of brotherhood, bonding and bromance instead are examining their hidden costs.  There was a time, after all, when part of the enjoyment of watching a Martin Scorsese film was being seduced by the same codes of honor among thieves he romanticized so convincingly in films like "Raging Bull" and "Goodfellas." In his new movie "The Irishman," which began streaming this week on Netflix, Scorsese rep players Robert De Niro and Joe Pesci go through many of the familiar rituals of violence and mayhem. But now they're slowed down, repeated to the point of boredom, leeched of vicarious pleasure. The threats, hair-trigger arguments and ruthless hit jobs that once exuded the thrill of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco breaks cold record as Bay Area freezes...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/San-Francisco-cold-Bay-Area-weather-frost-record-14870555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you thought Thanksgiving Day was unusually cold this year in San Francisco, you were correct. In fact, it was record-breaking cold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil President Blames DiCaprio for Rainforest  Fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/brazil-president-blames-leonardo-dicaprio-amazon-rainforest-fires-1258511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jair Bolsonaro told supporters Friday: "DiCaprio is a cool guy, isn't he? Giving money to set the Amazon on fire."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of reviews fake?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90437753/shopping-online-this-black-friday-beware-a-third-of-online-reviews-are-fake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s how to tell which reviews are legit and which are not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many children does he have? </title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/11/29/boris-johnson-refuses-say-many-children-11238199/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He refused to answer questions about his own children when challenged on his comments about the children of single mothers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Knifeman wearing fake suicide vest shot dead in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10450979/london-bridge-police-breaking-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE have shot dead a terrorist wearing a fake suicide vest after at least 12 people were injured in a shocking attack at London Bridge today. Terrifying footage from the scene shows armed office…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hero stopped more slashings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/hero-filmed-bravely-taking-knife-20990893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the dramatic footage, a group of people are seen tackling the knifeman to the floor</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds flee bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7739057/Gun-shots-heard-London-Bridge-police-confirm-incident-area.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One video filmed on London Bridge today shows what appears to be police pulling equipment out of a vehicle nearby. Those in the video can be heard saying: 'They've actually got guns out.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOMEN IN HIJABS FIGHT OVER VACUUM CLEANER AT WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/seasons-beatings-women-in-hijabs-fight-over-vacuum-frenzy-over-walmart-towels/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many stores sought to open earlier than Black Friday to relieve some of the pressure of shoppers swarming for good deals, but there have already been incidents at Walmarts around the country. At one Walmart, two women in hijabs fought over a vacuum, forcing several employees to intervene: ﻿ The two women argued as the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No invasion since 1914'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129150659-vs2y4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEXICO/CARTELS (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump First to Use PATRIOT Act to Detain Man Forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-invokes-patriot-act-to-detain-palestinian-adham-amin-hassoun-forever</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never in 18 years has the government used Section 412 of the PATRIOT Act, which permits indefinite detention of resident aliens on national-security grounds. Until now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Videos...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/breaking-shots-fired-on-london-bridge-possible-suspect-shot-police-lock-down-scene-of-major-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LATEST: A "major incident" took place on London Bridge on Friday when reports of shots being fired quickly developed into news that police evacuated and locked down the bridge. Eventually po</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey infects human with fatal herpes strain in first case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-infects-human-fatal-herpes-20986967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The herpes B disease – which is fatal in nearly 70% of cases – was transmitted to a worker at an animal experimentation lab in Kagoshima</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customers 'already swapping humans for AI dolls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-customers-already-swapping-20876938</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A sex doll manufacturer has told Daily Star Online that its customers are already replacing human companions with AI girlfriends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screaming Heard From COWBOYS Locker Room Following Loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/sports/2019/11/screaming-heard-from-cowboys-locker-room-following-lopsided-thanksgiving-day-loss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the loss, the Cowboys’ record falls to 6-6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-pop suicide sparks reckoning on revenge porn, sexual assault...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-kpop-suicide-reaction-20191129-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea The suicide of a popular South Korean singer has prompted calls in the country to overhaul laws on sexual assault and to more harshly punish</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party like a spy: Spookstock is intel world's hush-hush bash...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e4d72eb630c459aa71303b22e5a880d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Sometime earlier this year, one of the most elite social events in Washington took place, but without any fanfare or news coverage. It drew about 1,800 attendees and...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
