<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA BURNS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b609fb38cbb24be4b83fee915a428470/Massive-Northern-California-fire-gets-even-bigger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters battling a huge wildfire in Northern California kept it from doing more damage to the city of Redding but three smaller communities were in dan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA BURNS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6f5fefa581554c8eb5b2a5e77c9eb849/The-Latest:-Trump-declares-emergency-in-California-wildfires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on wildfires burning in California (all times local):        11 a.m.        President Donald Trump has issued an emergency declarat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama Foundation delays presidential center groundbreaking until next year...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/obamacenter/ct-met-obama-center-delayed-20180727-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obama Foundation officials had hoped to break ground this year, but delays in the federal review process prompted them to push back the date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man yells at Spicer during book signing: 'Not scared to fight you'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/399343-man-yells-at-spicer-during-book-signing-im-not-scared-to-fight-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Therapists say they've seen rise in anxiety...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/399339-therapists-say-theyve-seen-a-rise-in-anxiety-over-trump-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Therapists in the U.S. say they have seen a rise in politically-related anxiety under the Trump presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump seeks to revive 'Arab NATO' to confront Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-gulf-alliance/trump-seeks-to-revive-arab-nato-to-confront-iran-idUSKBN1KH2IK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is quietly pushing ahead with a bid to create a new security and political alliance with six Gulf Arab states, Egypt and Jordan, in part to counter Iran's expansion in the region, according to U.S. and Arab officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAFFER: American prosperity marks real turning point in history...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/399324-american-prosperity-of-trump-era-marks-real-turning-point-in-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no denying the economy is growing stronger than ever under the policies of this president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots 'will make make women interchangeable with technology'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/28/sex-robots-will-makemake-women-interchangeable-technology-campaigners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ministers are &amp;ldquo;lagging behind&amp;rdquo; in efforts to tackle sex robots, experts have warned, amid concerns they could &amp;quot;make women interchangeable with technology&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking pictures show eerie aftermath...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6002225/Eerie-images-devastation-left-wildfires-raging-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Saturday morning, some 3,400 firefighters on the ground and in helicopters and airplanes continued to battle the 48,300-acre fire as it ripped through the city of Redding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee new blaze, governor asks aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/thousands-flee-california-blaze-governor-asks-aid-143955297.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people in Southern California had fled a deliberately set blaze southeast of Los Angeles by Saturday morning, after the state's governor requested federal aid to help battle a deadly fire elsewhere. A blaze known as the Cranston Fire, and the Northern California Carr Fire in which two</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'MISSION' BIG AT BOX OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/tom-cruise-mission-impossible-fallout-opening-weekend-1202434739/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EARLY SATURDAY AM: With chart It’s another box office weekend where the movie star actually pulls the audience in as Tom Cruise sixthquel Mission: Impossible – Fallout heads for a franc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECS HAVE HIS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2018/07/28/sharon-osbourne-cbs-executives-support-leslie-moonves/854615002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wife Julie Chen isn't the only person speaking up in support of CBS chief Leslie Moonves, who was accused of sexual harassment in a bombshell report published by the New Yorker Friday. Now stars and other CBS executives are tweeting their support for Moonves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is America's birth rate about to start booming?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/27/is-americas-birth-rate-about-to-start-booming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes a society’s values change sharply with almost no one noticing. In 1968, according to a Gallup survey, 70 percent of American adults said that a family of three or more children was “ideal…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthem protesting 'takes away from the joy' of football...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/399330-dallas-cowboys-quarterback-anthem-protesting-takes-away-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The game of football has always brought me such a peace, and I think it does the same for a lot of people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK freezes Alex Jones for 30 days, targets INFOWARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/27/facebook-says-its-getting-close-to-pulling-alex-jones-infowars-pages.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;InfoWars and Alex Jones' official profiles are close to being removed from the Facebook platform because of numerous community standard violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dak Prescott already using voice as new face of COWBOYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dak-prescott-already-using-voice-face-cowboys-023244958--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OXNARD, Calif. (AP) — Dak Prescott's best test yet as the new face of the Cowboys came two days after owner Jerry Jones once again declared that all Dallas players will stand for the national anthem and even said they wouldn't be afforded the alternative of staying in the locker room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands of Russians protest retirement age hikes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/07039ed986a54d43940144282f0c431a/Tens-of-thousands-of-Russians-protest-retirement-age-hikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Tens of thousands of demonstrators have rallied throughout Russia to protest plans to substantially hike the age at which Russian men and women can receive their sta</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOWHERE TO HIDE: Bomb that can see through bad weather...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/tech/2018/07/27/stormbreaker-powerful-bomb-penetrates-bad-weather-spells-bad-news-for-bad-guys.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enemies of the United States will never be able to use bad weather to hide again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam 'lawless jungle' at night, ombudsman warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/206/amsterdam-lawless-jungle-night-ombudsman-warns-doc-17z7o61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least five killed in shootout near Mexico's Cancun...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180728-least-five-killed-shootout-near-mexicos-cancun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinal steps down amid mushrooming sex abuse scandal...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180728131404-mnmrn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN-ABUSE/MCCARRICK (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. cardinal steps down amid mushrooming sex abuse scandal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Oil Industry Recovers From Glut, Supply Crunch Might Be Looming...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-oil-industry-recovers-from-a-glut-a-supply-crunch-might-be-looming-1532775605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crude across the globe is being used up faster than it is being replaced, raising concerns among some industry watchers of a massive price spike that could hurt businesses and consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orban Rallies Europe's 'Illiberal' Forces for 2019 Elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/28/orban-rallies-europe-s-illiberal-forces-for-2019-elections#gs.hWOoaPo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orban Rallies Europe's `Illiberal' Forces for 2019 Elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What Does Trucker Look Like?' It's Changing, Amid Big Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/-what-does-a-trucker-look-like-it-s-changing-amid-a-big-shortage/17730142/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — America’s booming economy has a problem: a shortage of truck drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Anti-Semitism in France: 'They Spit When Walk in Street'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/-they-spit-when-i-walked-in-the-street-the-new-anti-semitism-in-france/17729267/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — The solemn boulevards and quiet side streets of the 17th Arrondissement in Paris suggest Jewish life in France is vibrant: There is a new profusion of kosher groceries and restaurants, and about 15 synagogues, up from only a handful two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Space Station in Argentina, China Expands  Reach in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/28/world/americas/china-latin-america.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our correspondent went to the deserts of Patagonia to examine how China secured its new base, a symbol of its growing clout in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So big making own weather!</title>
      <link>https://wattsupwiththat.com/2018/07/28/carrfire-in-northern-california-so-big-it-is-making-its-own-weather/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wattsupwiththat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video of a “fire tornado” folows. My friend Kris Kuyper writes on Facebook: BIG Pyrocumulus clouds now forming above the smoke plume of the #CarrFire! The dirty part on the bottom is th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The $1 Billion Property? Hilltop Plot in LA Most Expensive Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/would-you-pay-1-billion-for-this-view-/17729925/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A property about to go on the market here consists of 157 acres of hilltop land in the coveted Beverly Hills 90210 ZIP code, a 10-minute drive from Rodeo Drive. With its 360-degree views, you can spot many of Los Angeles’ major landmarks in the distance, from Century City to downtown, and even — on a clear day — the Pacific Ocean. There are winding, private roads that lead to big, flat lawns the size of football fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope accepts cardinal resignation following sex scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-abuse-mccarrick/pope-accepts-mccarrick-resignation-as-cardinal-following-sex-abuse-scandal-idUSKBN1KI0AD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis on Saturday accepted the resignation as a cardinal of Theodore McCarrick, the former archbishop of Washington, D.C. and one of the U.S. Catholic Church's most prominent figures, who has been at the center of allegations of sex abuse with minors and young seminarians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ex-lawyer criticizes Giuliani for 'damaging case immeasurably'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/27/politics/jay-goldberg-rudy-giuliani-michael-cohen-cnntv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, substantially weakened his case against Michael Cohen by going back and forth as to whether Cohen could tell federal prosecutors the truth, said Jay Goldberg, President Donald Trump's friend and former lawyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST asks for help identifying president's golf partners...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/399313-washington-posts-asks-for-help-identifying-trumps-golf-partners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midterms likely to be most expensive ever as TV ads pass billion-dollar mark...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/399221-midterms-likely-to-be-most-expensive-ever-as-tv-ads-surpass-billion-dollar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaigns, parties and outside groups have booked or aired more than $1 billion in TV advertising, in what is likely to become the most expensive midterm campaign in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destroys 500 structures, nearly levels community...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/47e6296ea13043c68fcd0147acddc544/Wildfire-destroys-500-structures,-nearly-levels-community</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — In the small northern California community of Keswick, only a handful of homes remain.        The air is thick with the smell of smoke and chemicals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster wildfire in California rages on after killing two firefighters... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180728080450-6ux2l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-WILDFIRES/ (PIX, TV):Monster wildfire in California rages on after killing two firefighters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER STOCK TANKS ON DECLINING USERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/business/article/As-Twitter-deals-with-many-woes-user-numbers-13111112.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter might have packed in more characters per tweet — but the move hasn’t helped it assemble more users. In its second-quarter earnings report, the company announced it had 355 million monthly active users, down 1 million from the first quarter. Wall Street closely watches Twitter’s user count as a proxy for the health of the company. Twitter shares dropped 20.5 percent to $34.12 Friday, wiping $6.6 billion off its value. While not as momentous as Facebook’s historic $119 billion loss in market capitalization following an earnings report that showed a slowdown in user growth, it’s the largest drop Twitter’s stock has seen in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUSPICIOUS PACKAGES' FOUND AT TRUMP TOWER...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/NYPD-Investigating-Suspicious-Packages-Trump-Tower-New-York-City-489381241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD bomb squad is investigating several suspicious packages left outside of Trump Tower on Friday afternoon, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROADCAST ROW ROCKED...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/27/les-moonves-accused-of-sexual-misconduct-by-6-women-in-bombshell-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS chief has been accused of sexual misconduct by six women, including actress Illeana Douglas, in a bombshell new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forcible touching and kissing during business meetings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/27bd1ce961f94077bcdc17f36bc47fd8/CBS-looks-into-misconduct-claims-amid-report-on-CEO-Moonves</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CBS said Friday it is investigating personal misconduct claims after the company's chief executive, Les Moonves, was the subject of a New Yorker story detailing se</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying tornados of flame...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/arson-wildfire-forces-entire-california-063907460.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. (AP) — A wildfire that roared with little warning into a Northern California city claimed two lives as thousands of people scrambled to escape before the walls of flames descended from forested hills onto their neighborhoods, officials said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report: CEO To Stay On Job During Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/les-moonves-to-stay-on-the-job-new-yorker-ronan-farrow-cbs-investigation-sexual-misconduct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS CEO Les Moonves plans to stay on the job during CBS's investigation of a Ronan Farrow New Yorker story, an insider says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nude sunbathers stunned as migrants storm beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6881644/costa-del-sol-nudist-beach-migrants-north-africa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the dramatic moment dozens of migrants stormed a Spanish holiday beach popular with Brits today – leaving naked sunbathers stunned. The migrants landed on the shore of Del Canuelo bea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW STRIKES AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2018/08/06/les-moonves-and-cbs-face-allegations-of-sexual-misconduct</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six women accuse the C.E.O. of harassment and intimidation, and dozens more describe abuse at his company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkey herds dwindle as hungry Venezuelans slaughter for food...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article215644840.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burro, or donkey, herds have nearly disappeared in one section of Venezuela as thousands were slaughtered for their meat by hungry Venezuelans suffering through a near-famine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'RESILIENT SURVIVOR' ON HOT SEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/leslie-moonves-accused-by-six-women-sexual-misconduct-new-yorker-expos-1085436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I recognize that there were times decades ago when I may have made some women uncomfortable by making advances," admitted the network chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian-spy hookers eye tech big shots at 'cougar nights?'</title>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/07/27/are-russian-spy-hookers-targeting-tech-leaders-and-vcs-at-infamous-silicon-valley-cougar-nights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eastbaytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The region is crawling with Chinese and Russian spies amid an ‘epidemic’ of espionage, report says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LES: Times when I may have made women uncomfortable by making advances...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/leslie-moonves-sexual-misconduct-new-yorker-ronan-farrow-1202888614/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS chairman-CEO Leslie Moonves has been accused of sexual misconduct by six women, including actress Illeana Douglas, who asserts that Moonves had her fired from a comedy pilot after she rebuffed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISCONDUCT EXTENDED TO OTHER DIVISIONS...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/cbs-ceo-les-moonves-sexual-harassment-allegations-1202435122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS chairman and CEO Leslie Moonves is being accused of sexual misconduct by six women in a much-anticipated exposé by New Yorker magazine. Investigative reporter Ronan Farrow interviewed six women…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social, Search Giants Face UK Tax To Fund 'Fake' Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/facebook-twitter-google-face-tech-145524484.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Twitter and Google are facing the threat of new taxes to help fund a crackdown on a tide of fake news and misinformation which is poisoning British democracy, according to MPs. A damning report from the Digital Culture Media and Sport Select Committee proposed that Facebook and other social</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury developers tout 'mindful mansions' to curb stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/luxury-homes-that-promise-to-reduce-stressfor-4-million-1524146400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury developers are touting wellness real estate, offering private and communal spaces for meditation and yoga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female teacher describes painful year after cleared of sex charges with male student...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressherald.com/2018/07/26/former-kennebunk-teacher-pressed-by-prosecutor-in-sexual-assault-trial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After deliberating two hours, a York County jury acquits 30-year-old Jill Lamontagne of 14 charges of sexual misconduct involving a former Kennebunk High student who was 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Special Counsel Witnesses Against Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/special-counsel-releases-witness-list-for-manafort-trial-00fea585-3272-4720-9c08-b9c622087bed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It includes 35 people who could testify against Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronan Farrow Urges Patience...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/RonanFarrow/status/1022934331235463168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A quick reminder that I don’t comment on reporting I haven’t published, and if you’re reading about my work from secondary sources you’re often not getting the full or correct story—especially in cases where parties have an interest in downplaying or otherwise spinning.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 60, NASA shoots for revival of moon glory days...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180727-60-nasa-shoots-revival-moon-glory-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posh dog food linked to heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/07/27/posh-grain-free-dog-food-may-linked-heart-disease-vets-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gourmet dishes with bison, sweet potato and chickpeas may seem like the perfect way for loving dog owners to treat their pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 4 In 10 Men Experience 'Inexplicable Sadness' After Sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-pcd-men-experienced-sadness-after-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having sex may feel like a badge of honor for many men, but for others, it's an act that, once finished, brings about intense feelings of sadness thanks to a condition known as PCD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal housing chief investigated for sex harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/27/federal-housing-chief-sexual-harassment-investigation-714779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mortgage regulator taped making suggestive comments to employee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Flag Found Intact In Rubble Of Veteran's Home...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/27/carr-fire-flag-saved/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Carr Fire is now 44,450 acres and only 3% contained as of 9:17 am Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller defensive after airport pic with Don Jr...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/07/27/mueller-trump-jr-photographed-waiting-in-same-dc-airport-terminal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One flight out of D.C. certainly brought awkward to new heights.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
