<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY in dark about Florida move to dissolve self-govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/disney-in-the-dark-about-florida-move-to-dissolve-self-government/ar-AAWFBKE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Keeps Trying to Call Zelensky Drug Addict...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gpd3/russia-zelenskyy-drug-addict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If Russians believe lies on Russian TV, why not believe this?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to skip eating portion to limit risk...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3469215-biden-to-skip-eating-portion-of-correspondents-dinner-to-limit-covid-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will take added precautions while at the White House Correspondents’ Association Dinner this weekend amid concerns about exposure to COVID-19, but White House press secretary …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN WARNS HE'LL NUKE WEST</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5213926/putin-warns-nukes-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has warned he will use nuclear weapons against the West if anyone interferes in Ukraine. The threat comes as the Russian leader said the response to counterstrikes will be “lig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal's biggest water supplier limit irrigation to day per week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/socal-s-biggest-water-supplier-to-limit-outdoor-irrigation-to-one-day-per-week-starting-june-1/ar-AAWEHV0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge knocks down Elon's bid to end SEC consent decree...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/27/judge-knocks-down-elon-musks-bid-to-end-sec-consent-decree.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Lewis J. Liman shot down an argument Musk attorneys made suggesting that the settlement agreement had chilled the CEO's rights to free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYPAL shuttering San Fran office...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2022/04/27/paypal-shuttering-its-san-francisco-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PayPal is closing its San Francisco office on June 3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBAT DOLPHINS DEPLOYED</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/04/27/trained-russian-navy-dolphins-are-protecting-black-sea-naval-base-satellite-photos-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has deployed trained dolphins during its invasion of Ukraine to protect a Black Sea naval base, USNI News has learned. The Russian Navy has placed two dolphin pens at the entrance to Sevastopol harbor, sheltered just inside a sea wall. The pens were moved there in February, around the time of the invasion of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott to Make First Festival Performance Year After Astroworld...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/travis-scott-to-make-first-festival-performance-one-year-after-astroworld-tragedy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis Scott has announced his first music festival appearance since last year's Astroworld Festival tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: CDC, FDA 'altered' guidance under political pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10759403/CDC-FDA-altered-Covid-guidance-pressure-bombshell-report-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators spoke to more than two dozen top-level directors and managers who worked at the agencies behind the country's public health guidance that aimed to keep Americans safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Champion looter' sends ton of stolen goods home to wife...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/russias-champion-looter-sends-almost-500-kg-of-stolen-goods-home-to-his-wife-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don feared 'dangerous' fruits could be thrown at him by protesters...</title>
      <link>https://africa.businessinsider.com/politics/donald-trump-worried-dangerous-fruits-could-be-thrown-at-him-by-protesters-a-new/z50lnrf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;africa.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump said pineapples, tomatoes, bananas, stuff like that could be thrown at him at protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Jared Polis, Most Libertarian Gov in America?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/podcast/2022/04/25/jared-polis-the-most-libertarian-governor-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado's Jared Polis might be the most libertarian governor in America, at a time when his big-state Democratic colleagues are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Shortages Of Few Items Will Evolve Into Hundreds?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/chronic-shortages-few-items-now-will-evolve-chronic-shortages-hundreds-products-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKING THE PFIZER PILL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10758917/Kamala-Harris-treated-Pfizers-Paxlovid-pills-testing-positive-COVID.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her press secretary Kirsten Allen said in a statement that Harris - who is fully-vaccinated and double boosted - received positive rapid and PCR test results after returning from a week in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell Phone Radiation Driving Alzheimer's Spike?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cell-phone-radiation-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say excessive cell phone use and even Wi-Fi radiation can lead to increases in intracellular calcium levels in the brain -- another hallmark of the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans give McCarthy standing ovation, brush off tapes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/house/3468729-house-republicans-give-mccarthy-standing-ovation-brush-off-tapes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) got a standing ovation in a Wednesday House GOP conference meeting after he addressed leaked recordings of his comments in the aftermath of Jan. 6, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Prophet Rumored to Have Putin's Ear...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/aleksandr-dugin-putin-brain-russian-prophet-bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aleksandr Dugin hates America and is obsessed with Nazis, the occult, and the end times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Robbery in Front of FBI HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/thief-armed-robbery-fbi-hq-1701293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brazen thief carried out an armed robbery right under the FBI's nose — with an audacious hold-up just outside the agency's headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of Israelis fear second Holocaust is coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/article-705210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll, which found that women and the ultra-Orthodox are more worried about another Holocaust, was conducted just days ahead of Holocaust Remembrance Day, starting Wednesday evening, April 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wine-loving nun named world's oldest person!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/worlds-oldest-person-french-nun-sister-andre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sister André, born Lucile Randon, has lived through two world wars, the 1918 influenza pandemic, and even survived a COVID-19 infection last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Meteor Crashed to Earth. Astronomer Wants to See If Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gpv3/an-interstellar-meteor-crashed-to-earth-this-astronomer-wants-to-see-if-its-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meteor that crashed into the Pacific was confirmed to be interstellar by secret government data. Harvard astronomer Avi Loeb wants to recover it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  KAMALA COVID 'NO SYMPTOMS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/harris-tests-positive-covid-a3953375-2285-4789-bf7a-3edd035089d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is fully vaccinated and received a booster dose in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren tries to 'light fire of urgency' for Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/27/elizabeth-warren-midterm-elections-00028068</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts progressive is going all-out to try to push her party to emerge from a morass of bad polling and stalled priorities before Election Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That chill music when you board flight? There's reason for it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/that-chill-music-when-you-board-a-flight-there-e2-80-99s-a-reason-for-it/ar-AAWEh77</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress members tiptoeing into crypto raise conflict concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/congress-members-tiptoeing-into-crypto-raise-conflict-concerns/article_a7729881-6fc7-55b2-b363-13fd45845a93.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As efforts to regulate the rapidly-growing cryptocurrency market increase, some observers are raising concern about the rising number of U.S. lawmakers beginning to dabble in digital assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on French Fiber Networks Causes Internet Outages...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/attacks-on-french-fiber-networks-causes-internet-outages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks on French Fiber Networks Causes Internet Outages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Sound Hack Helping People Get Happy, Horny, High...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sound-hack-called-binaural-beats-000012719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyIan Griffiths, a 36-year-old school custodian in Massachusetts, said he started warming to spirituality when his dad had a near-death experience and was saved by what he can only describe as fate. Since then, in order to achieve an altered state of higher consciousness and explore the spiritual world, Griffiths started meditating and turned to YouTube and Spotify to listen to “binaural beats”—a term used to describe auditory illusions that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolt Brewing at Prince Harry's Silicon Valley Gig...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/revolt-brewing-prince-harry-silicon-074245368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyPrince Harry signed on as the chief impact officer of BetterUp last spring, promising to help promote the startup’s mission of “mental fitness” and its army of more than 2,000 professional coaches. It’s likely a lucrative gig for the British royal: BetterUp raised $300 million at a $4.7 billion valuation in October.But just six months later, an uprising has been brewing among the company’s career coaches following BetterUp’s recent annou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran attempts to kill Pompeo, current officials real and ongoing, Blinken says...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article260788747.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s attempts to assassinate former Secretary of State Mike Pompeo are real and ongoing, his successor, Antony Blinken, told Congress on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE now warning of major recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/26/economy/inflation-recession-economy-deutsche-bank/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank raised eyebrows earlier this month by becoming the first major bank to forecast a US recession, albeit a "mild" one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasting techno, Kharkiv youth brave bombs to deliver food...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220427-blasting-techno-kharkiv-youth-brave-the-bombs-to-deliver-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their red Opel Astra blaring techno music and the boot full to the brim with supplies, three Ukrainian volunteers deliver aid to Kharkiv neighbourhoods targeted by Russian rockets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks attempt rebound after NASDAQ biggest drop since 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/nasdaq-futures-fall-following-tuesdays-sharp-losses-for-stocks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures bounced Wednesday as the market attempted to recover from April's technology-led sell-off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing market headed for correction?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/3466071-is-the-us-housing-market-headed-for-a-price-correction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At present, the very tight labor markets and strong household balance sheets offer sufficient ballast to sustain real estate demand despite elevated home prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Gap Soars to Record, Surpassing All Estimates...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/u-goods-trade-gap-soars-124214990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. merchandise-trade deficit widened unexpectedly to a new record in March as the value of imports dwarfed that of outbound shipments, reflecting a surge in inflation.Most Read from BloombergRussia to Cut Gas to Poland and Bulgaria, Making Energy a WeaponFour European Gas Buyers Made Ruble Payments to RussiaRussia Warns of Nuclear War Risk as Ukraine Talks Go OnUkraine Latest: Russia Says It Cut Gas Flows to Poland, BulgariaElon Musk Lands Deal to Take Twitter Private for $4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery fires at sensitive facilities compound Russia's war challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mystery-fires-at-sensitive-facilities-compound-russia-e2-80-99s-war-challenge/ar-AAWDqtT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci declares America 'out of pandemic phase'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10758759/America-pandemic-phase-says-Fauci.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fauci, who has been one of the most vocal proponents of draconian Covid measures throughout the pandemic, made the statement during a PBS broadcast yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another rare puzzle: They got sick, got treated, got virus again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/another-rare-virus-puzzle-they-got-sick-got-treated-got-covid-again/ar-AAWEiJq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son of world's most powerful drug boss missing amid cartel crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/missing-son-worlds-top-drug-26810049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vicente Zambada Niebla, son of Sinaloa Cartel boss El Mayo, has not been seen since his release from prison last year but may now be his dad's last hope for an heir to his criminal empire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House correspondents' dinner returns to changed world...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/3465669-white-house-correspondents-dinner-returns-to-a-changed-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To party or not to party, that is the question in Washington, where a pandemic that doesn’t let up is forcing D.C.’s movers and shakers to choose whether or not to attend the White House Corr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Ulysses S. Grant Due for Promotion?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/27/is-ulysses-s-grant-due-for-a-promotion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’ll observe the birthday of a famous Army general who deserves a promotion, according to his fans, even though it’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Covid Lockdown Outrage Tests Limits of Triumphant Propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/27/chinas-covid-lockdown-outrage-tests-limits-of-triumphant-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immediately after Beijing said it had detected a new coronavirus outbreak, officials hurried to assure residents there was no reason</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 46 days in office, Chile's leftist leader runs into trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/just-46-days-in-office-chile-s-leftist-leader-runs-into-trouble/ar-AAWBjdw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New corporate activism wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98free-speech-e2-80-99-takeover-part-of-new-corporate-activism-wave/ar-AAWEazb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjustable-rate mortgage demand doubles as rates spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/27/adjustable-rate-mortgage-demand-doubles-as-interest-rates-hit-the-highest-since-2009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sharply rising mortgage rates caused mortgage demand to plunge and pushed more borrowers to riskier, adjustable-rate loans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING IS BLEEDING: Households No Longer Adding More Services...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/u-s-consumers-stop-adding-new-streaming-services-survey-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Households Are No Longer Adding More Streaming Services</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details show extent of Republican effort to unwind Trump loss...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/3466785-new-details-emerge-on-extent-of-gop-effort-to-unwind-trumps-loss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents and texts stemming from the House investigation into Jan. 6, 2021, offer new details about the extent House Republicans, particularly members of the Freedom Caucus, were involved in plans…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos, gang violence again erupt in Haiti. Even disarmament chief is target...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/ap/international/chaos-gang-violence-again-erupt-in-haiti-even-the-nation-s-disarmament-chief-is-a/article_245ca2ae-cdde-570f-b62a-cfd45503c683.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chaos and violence is once more erupting in Haiti, where armed clashes between warring violent gangs are once more forcing residents to flee their homes under a hail of bullets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA CUTS OFF THE GAS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-kyiv-business-bulgaria-moldova-2505307f5dcc882d38bab642ffce649f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POKROVSK, Ukraine (AP) — Russia opened a new front in its war in Ukraine on Wednesday, cutting two European Union nations that staunchly back Kyiv off from its gas, a dramatic escalation in the conflict that is increasingly becoming a wider battle with the West .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Shortages Of Few Items Will Evolve Into Hundreds?</title>
      <link>/https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/chronic-shortages-few-items-now-will-evolve-chronic-shortages-hundreds-products-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ELVIS' biopic wows CINEMACON with 'superhero' story, rap remix...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/elvis-biopic-wows-cinemacon-superhero-073237650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Doja Cat song sampling "Hound Dog" is just one of many ways that director Baz Luhrmann hopes to bring "Elvis" into the 21st century with new biopic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports first human case of H3N8 bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-reports-first-human-case-of-h3n8-bird-flu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The H3N8 variant has previously been detected elsewhere in the world in animals, but no human cases have been reported. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid talk of WWIII, diplomacy losing steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amid-talk-of-world-war-iii-diplomacy-is-losing-steam/ar-AAWDy5S </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis fight with DISNEY helps him break fundraising records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-fight-with-disney-helped-him-break-fundraising-records/ar-AAWBJpX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive TWITTER accounts lose followers, conservatives gain?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220427-progressive-twitter-accounts-lose-followers-conservatives-gain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key figures on the American left, Barack Obama among them, have shed thousands of followers since Elon Musk's planned purchase of Twitter emerged, while numbers have soared for right-wing politicians…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin eyes tax hike to 'combat inflation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/manchin-and-schumer-discuss-new-tax-hike-deficit-cut-proposal-1.1757248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key holdout Senator Joe Manchin said Tuesday he discussed a tax increase and deficit reduction bill with Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer as a way to reduce soaring inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World faces biggest price shock in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-61235528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine is pushing up prices of commodities including food, cotton and energy, the World Bank says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Giants Duped Into Giving Up Data Used to Sexually Extort Minors...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-giants-duped-giving-data-173424811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Major technology companies have been duped into providing sensitive personal information about their customers in response to fraudulent legal requests, and the data has been used to harass and even sexually extort minors, according to four federal law enforcement officials and two industry investigators.Most Read from BloombergRussia to Cut Gas to Poland and Bulgaria, Making Energy a WeaponRussia Warns of Nuclear War Risk as Ukraine Talks Go OnUkraine Latest: Russia Says It Cut G</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Feared Republicans Put 'People in Jeopardy' After Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/26/mccarthy-feared-g-o-p-lawmakers-put-people-in-jeopardy-after-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Kevin McCarthy, the House Republican leader, feared in the aftermath of the Jan. 6 attack that several far-right members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump drawn to celebrity in weighing midterm picks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-entertainment-business-pennsylvania-ohio-5adc976efa97debf1613f3eb13fa0cfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Republicans hoping to emerge from crowded primaries this year stacked up on operatives with ties to former President Donald Trump , betting those connections would give them a leg up on landing critical endorsements that would help them win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily blood pressure pills could be replaced by injection...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/health/2022/04/26/twice-yearly-injection-could-replace-daily-tablets-to-treat-high-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK scientists are running a trial to see effectiveness of managing hypertension through new injection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youth voters not pleased by EITHER party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2022/04/25/youth-voters-not-pleased-by-either-party-according-to-harvard-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This edition shows significant concern, relative to our previous polls, about the motivation of elected officials, a growing disdain for our political discourse, and young people are seriously que…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci eyeing exit?</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/local/interview-anthony-fauci-birx-resignation-pact-covid-19-pandemic-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci wouldn’t comment Tuesday when asked by 1010 WINS if he had a resignation pact with other doctors in Donald Trump’s White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz flaunts Trump endorsement in PA showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/politics/politicalnews/s-2668662?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. — Pennsylvania Republican U.S. Senate candidate Mehmet Oz debuted a new Trumpian confidence inspired by the former president's endorsement, as the five candidates tried to set themselves apart as the "most Pennsylvanian" candidate in Monday's debate for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis fight with DISNEY helps him break fundraising records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-fight-with-disney-helped-him-break-fundraising-records/ar-AAWBJpX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDIDATE CARLSON?  Tucker named keynote speaker at Iowa conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/tucker-carlson-to-speak-at-iowa-summit-raising-eyebrows-and-speculation-of-a-presidential-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ox New’s top-rated host Tucker Carlson will headline the 2022 FAMiLY Leadership Summit in Des Moines, Iowa this July, the group announced Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FREE SPEECH' RECORD SKETCHY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/elon-musk-and-free-speech-track-record-not-encouraging.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's free speech advocacy seems to apply mostly to his own speech or that of his fans and promoters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implanting microchip in dogs, cats to become mandatory in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1588233/implanting-microchip-in-pet-dogs-cats-to-become-mandatory-in-june-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsinfo.inquirer.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO -- Implanting a microchip in pet dogs and cats and registering the owner’s contact information will become mandatory in June under the revised Law on Welfare and Management of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANKEES stole signs; Fined by MLB...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/texas-sports-nation/astros/article/New-York-Yankees-sign-stealing-2015-2016-fine-17125599.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB letter offers few details into New York's use of replay room to relay signs and led...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDIO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/04/26/us/politics/mccarthy-republican-lawmakers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New audio recordings reveal Kevin McCarthy worried that comments by his far-right colleagues could incite violence. He said he would try to rein in the lawmakers, but has instead defended them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows' texts reveal new details about key role of little-known GOP congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/26/politics/mark-meadows-texts-scott-perry-key-role-overturn-election/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly obtained text messages and recent court filings fill in significant gaps about the key role a little-known Pennsylvania Republican congressman played at almost every turn in scheming to reverse or delay certification of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
