<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Farm family struggles to recover after rising debt pushes husband to suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-farm-family-struggles-to-recover-after-rising-14822724.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PLATTE, S.D. - Amber Dykshorn stood at her kitchen window and watched the storm come in.  It was a very dark Saturday night in the middle of the summer in the middle of a year that is on track to be the wettest in more than a century. The wind blew over the farm, the rain came down and she heard the ominous pings on her roof - pea-sized hail, striking the still-fragile stalks of the only corn her husband, Chris Dykshorn, was able to plant before he took his own life in June.  Did their crop insurance cover hail damage? She had no idea. That was something Chris would have taken care of, if he were here. Instead she was alone, with nearly $300,000 in farm debt, three kids ages 5 to 13 and a host of grief-fueled questions. Why hadn't she been able to save him? What would happen to them now?  She scrolled through his final texts, rereading his words, leaning on the kitchen counter next to a whiteboard with the kids' chore list - Kahne: dishwasher, Kalee: dust living room - and a book someone gave her titled "Through a Season of Grief: Devotions for Your Journey from Mourning to Joy."  Chris had been despondent over the couple's finances, crippled by surplus grain he couldn't sell because of the trade war and flooded fields.  "I'm struggling so bad today. I don't know what to do anymore," he texted on May 31. "I seriously don't know how we r gonna make it."  On June 1: "I just want to sit in the house and cry."  And then: "What am I supposed to do. I am failing and feel like I'm gonna lose everything I've worked for the past how many years."  She was still asleep the morning of June 13 when he went to the utility room to get his gun.  In farm country, mental health experts say they're seeing more suicides as families endure the worst period for U.S. agriculture in decades. Farm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIMON: RICH AND POWERFUL SHOULDN'T BE VILIFIED FOR BEING SUCCESSFUL...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jamie-dimon-jp-morgan-chase-ceo-speaks-to-60-minutes-sunday-2019-11-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The notion that I'm not a patriot... that's just dead wrong." JPMorgan Chase chairman and CEO Jamie Dimon responds to criticism from presidential candidate Elizabeth Warren. See the full interview, Sunday on 60 Minutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept Freed Ukraine Money Before Trump Says He Did...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-09/state-department-freed-ukraine-money-before-trump-says-he-did</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest 1% Close to Surpassing Wealth of Middle Class...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-09/one-percenters-close-to-surpassing-wealth-of-u-s-middle-class</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Wall anniversary, Germany urges USA to reject 'egoism'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/divisions-rife-germany-marks-30-years-since-berlin-031311425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German President Frank-Walter Steinmeier urged the United States to be a "mutually respectful partner" and reject nationalism, in a clear salvo aimed at US leader Donald Trump as Germany on Saturday marked 30 years since the fall of the Berlin Wall. Recalling the United States' key role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercury will pass in front of sun on Monday...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2019/11/08/in-rare-show-mercury-will-transit-across-sun-on-monday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mercury is putting on a rare celestial show next week, parading across the sun in view of most of the world. The solar system's smallest, innermost planet will resemble a tiny black dot Monday as it passes directly between Earth and the sun. It begins at 7:35 a.m. EST. The entire 5 ½-hour event will be visible, weather permitting, in the eastern U.S. and Canada, and all Central and South America. The rest of North America, Europe and Africa will catch part of the action. Asia and Australia will miss out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Unveil Wishlist of Witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gop-wants-to-call-hunter-biden-and-the-whistleblower-to-testify-at-impeach-hearings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ranking Republicans issued their own list Saturday including Hunter Biden and the unnamed whistleblower, who they say will help treat the President with “fundamental fairness.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside sex robot factory that is churning out 'hyper-realistic' dolls...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-factory-looks-like-20841261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Silicone Lovers told Daily Star Online it is using a workshop that mirrors fictional HBO hit Westworld to produce sex robots with advanced human-like technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronaut says we need shield around world, before too late...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/nasa-astronaut-says-need-shield-20848441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It doesn’t take much to destroy civilisation' says Apollo 9 astronaut Rusty Schweickart</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkeys share human bed, wear clothes and live in house like married couple...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/monkeys-share-human-bed-clothes-20847735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two rescued macaque monkeys are living like humans in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's Next Electricity Headache Is Looming Shortage...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-next-electricity-headache-looming-201332447.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As if California doesn’t have enough problems with its electric service, now regulators warn the state may be short on power supplies by 2021 if utilities don’t start lining up new resources now.In the hopes of heading off a shortfall, the California Public Utilities Commission has ordered</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer trio of opportunities...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/House-Democrats-engineer-a-trio-of-opportunities-14822517.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It's rare in politics to get a second chance, let alone a third, at making a first impression. But that is the opportunity presented to House Democrats in the week ahead, as they take their impeachment inquiry public, searching for a much sharper focus than previous oversight hearings that tended to backfire.  The House Intelligence Committee, in a pair of hearings with career diplomats, hopes to do what other panels have failed to do in their previous attempts at high-profile investigations of President Trump: deliver a dramatic rendering of the facts that are easily understood by the average voter and make clear how those actions represent abuses of power that are considered high crimes and misdemeanors.  Having learned lessons about those previous mistakes, Democrats fashioned the resolution formalizing the impeachment inquiry to address several procedural hiccups that they believe will make these new hearings more dramatic. And, more broadly, House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., has recently begun to hold weekly huddles with the Democrats who are most often on TV news shows talking about the investigation. The purpose is to work on message and drive home the importance of keeping the focus on Trump's actions and not getting distracted by side characters, such as the president's personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani.  So far, Rep. Adam Schiff, D-Calif., chairman of the Intelligence Committee, has won accolades from Democrats for an approach that is getting three bites of the media apple with each witness. First, Schiff and two other committees conducting the investigations brought them behind closed doors for depositions - some portions of which got leaked. Then, over the past week, the committees publicly released the transcripts of key witnesses, confirming what had already leaked and revealing new damaging...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Shia LaBeouf 'HONEY BOY' Is 94 Minutes of Misery...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/11/honey-boy-review-shia-labeouf-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I don’t know about you, but this is not what I go to the movies for.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freed From Jail, Lula Says Ready to Fight in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/freed-jail-lula-says-ready-154607535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Brazil’s former President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva has pledged to travel around Latin America offering support for leftist leaders at a moment when the region is engulfed by growing political turmoil.“I’m finally free and willing to fight,” Lula said in a video message that was broadcast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE JUDY: He can unite 'fractured American family'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/judge-judy-bill-maher-michael-bloomberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Judge Judy" Sheindlin made the case for a Michael Bloomberg presidency Friday night during her debut appearance on "Real Time with Bill Maher," arguing that the billionaire former mayor of New York City is the "only" candidate who can bring civility back to the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66% of Americans workers would move abroad for better-paying job...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/09/randstad-66percent-of-us-workers-would-move-abroad-for-a-better-paying-job.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interest in working for a company that allows international travel is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divisions rife as Germany marks 30 years since Berlin Wall fell...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/15/divisions-rife-germany-marks-30-years-berlin-wall-fell-doc-1m42o73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-ABCNEWS staffer, fired by CBS, denies leaking Epstein bombshell...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/08/megyn-kelly-interviews-ashley-bianco-abc-news-producer-accused-of-leaking-amy-robach-clip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly launched her news comeback Friday with an exclusive interview with a former ABC News producer who was accused of leaking the Amy Robach “hot mic” clip– but who tearful…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is $450m Salvator Mundi really on Saudi yacht?</title>
      <link>http://www.theartnewspaper.com/analysis/is-the-usd450m-salvator-mundi-really-on-a-yacht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theartnewspaper.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia’s luxury vessel has unexpectedly circumnavigated Europe and docked in the Netherlands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Bahamas, hard-hit island beckons again...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhregister.com/lifestyle/travel/article/In-the-Bahamas-a-hard-hit-island-beckons-again-14820327.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tip Burrows dropped a low-grade expletive when she saw the beach by Banana Bay Restaurant, on the south side of Grand Bahama Island.  "Holy (bad word)!" said the islander, peering into a freshly carved trench. "That wasn't here before."  Nearly two months after Hurricane Dorian battered the Bahamas, Tip, who runs the Humane Society of Grand Bahama, was still discovering new evidence of destruction. On this mid-October afternoon, she had unearthed an inlet on Fortune Beach. As if that weren't alarming enough, the storm surge that had swept away a section of the beach had not come from the ocean lapping at Fortune's feet. It had traversed the island from the north and pushed the sand out to sea like a scene from an eco-horror film.  "We lost two feet of beach," said Danilo Rulli, the restaurant's owner, "but it will slowly come back."  And so will the Bahamas, at possibly an even faster clip than Mother Nature.  "We're going to bring the sparkle back to Grand Bahama," said Steven Johnson, an official with the Grand Bahama Tourism Office who is already working on new initiatives, such as expanding the West End as a seafood destination.  To be sure, Dorian was devastating. The strongest storm ever to strike the Bahamas caused at least 65 deaths and damaged or destroyed more than 13,000 homes on Grand Bahama Island and the Abaco Islands, both in the upper reaches of the 500-mile-long archipelago. Economic loss could rise to $7 billion, more than half of the country's gross national product. But the Bahamas are moving forward - rebuilding homes, reopening businesses, and restoring the spirit of the islands and its people.  "We'll be back bigger and better than before," exclaimed a resident who lives in the East End, the hardest-hit area on Grand Bahama Island.  The Bahamas can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hundreds of records could fall in next week's cold snap...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Hundreds-of-records-could-fall-in-next-week-s-14820980.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Arctic blast engulfing the eastern half of the Lower 48 will make mid-November feel like mid-January. Between Sunday and Wednesday, temperatures will sink to levels 15 to 30 degrees colder than normal from the Plains to the East Coast.  The National Weather Service is predicting that about 250 cold records will be established as a result of this polar plunge, from the Gulf Coast to the Great Lakes.  Next week's cold is the second and stronger of back-to-back Arctic fronts sweeping across the nation.  The first front raced from the Midwest to the East Coast between Wednesday and Friday this week. It caused temperatures to drop 15 to 20 degrees in 24 hours along the Eastern Seaboard between Thursday and Friday morning and supported the season's first snow flurries in Washington, D.C.  But temperatures are poised to take an even deeper dive as the second front invades.  The cold front will drop into the Northern Plains and Upper Midwest on Saturday night into Sunday, passing through Minneapolis and Chicago.  On Monday morning, the front will have rapidly progressed eastward, stretching from interior New England southwest to Texas, having sliced through Buffalo, Detroit, Cleveland, Kansas City, St. Louis and Oklahoma City.  By Tuesday morning, it will have reached the East Coast, having passed through all but southeast South Carolina and Florida, which it will cross by Wednesday morning.  On Monday, when the core of the cold grips the Upper Midwest and Great Lakes, Minneapolis will not escape the high teens while Chicago hovers in the 20s. Both cities are likely to see their coldest Veterans Day on record.  "Record low-max and record low mins could be in jeopardy of being tied/broken for both Monday and Tuesday," wrote the National Weather Service office serving Chicago....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish with 'human face' spotted swimming in lake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/fish-human-face-spotted-lake-20846470</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People on social media have been thoroughly creeped out by a video doing the rounds of a fish, with a very human-like face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whips, chains and fancy food: S&amp;M fetish restaurant opens to rave reviews...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/whips-chains-fancy-food-new-20846224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slave collar-wearing waitresses serve food and also engage in bondage-themed displays</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female jihadis filmed slaughtering soldiers in 'Baghdadi revenge strikes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/isis-female-jihadis-filmed-slaughtering-20842411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Militants attacked an army outpost in northern Mali and killed 53 troops and one civilian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: NASA forced to cut ISS feed when UFOs appear...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/government-forces-nasa-cut-iss-20839773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The head of a UFO disclosure group believes NASA is the "victim" of government laws – and that it is possible UFOs are being seen on ISS live feeds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchwoman accuses Polanski of raping her as teen...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/frenchwoman-accuses-polanski-raping-her-teen-204841844.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French former model and actress on Friday accused Oscar-winning director Roman Polanski, whose new film on the persecution of French Jewish army officer Alfred Dreyfus premieres next week, of raping her in a Swiss ski resort when she was a teenager. It is the latest accusation against the 86-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global debate gets underway over married Catholic priests...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3cd8c5c7a4b4811b9cc3ba4452a9963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany's Catholics reacted enthusiastically when bishops from across the Amazon called for the ordination of married men as priests to address the clergy shortage in that region....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on Texas gov as calls grow to halt execution...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d99026ae9cf4d88b8da8b020162af6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — In his five years as Texas' governor, Republican Greg Abbott has overseen the execution of nearly 50 prisoners while only once sparing a condemned man's life, after a victims'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgian police arrest more than 25 in clashes at gay movie premiere...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108173745-a5bue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators blocked the road outside a movie theatre ahead of the first screening of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Collective Suicide in Turkey in Week Highlights Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-09/second-collective-suicide-in-turkey-in-a-week-highlights-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci: Trump sees threat...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/469721-scaramucci-trump-sees-bloomberg-as-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci said late Friday that there is “no question” that Michael Bloomberg would be “the No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Red Alert Now Flashing on Bond Trader's Radar Screen...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/red-alert-now-flashing-bright-050001839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A bond-market warning light that glowed green for years is suddenly flashing red. The bad news for bondholders is that the last time this happened, it was accompanied by the biggest sell-off since the aftermath of the global financial crisis.That indicator is the term premium, which, for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM TO START HIDING LIKES IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/digital/news/instagram-likes-like-counts-hidden-1203399222/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instagram likes are about to disappear from public view for many more users: The Facebook-owned photo sharing service is getting ready to hide like counts from U.S. users as early as next week, CEO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN PLAYS TO EMPTY HALL</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/sahilkapur/status/1192957650742513664?s=21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“ORANGEBURG — Elizabeth Warren takes the stage at an Environmental Justice forum in South Carolina before a sparse audience. Tom Steyer spoke before her; numerous rivals skipped it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PLAYS IT COOL...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-flirts-white-house-bid-challenge-biden-172847056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York business tycoon Michael Bloomberg has paved the way for a shot at the US presidency, registering as a candidate in the Alabama Democratic primary race before Friday's filing deadline. Although the 77-year-old billionaire has not publicly announced his run, his inclusion among a crowded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth gives him options rivals don't enjoy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a480a660c9e42488662398498e240d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — There are many questions surrounding Michael Bloomberg's potential presidential candidacy. Whether he'll have enough money to sustain a lengthy and bruising campaign is not one...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIALS SPREAD WRONG NAME OF 'WHISTLEBLOWER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumpkins-thought-this-man-was-the-whistleblower-they-were-wrong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Obama staffer has been erroneously accused by the pro-Trump internet of blowing the whistle on the Ukraine affair. He didn’t. But now he’s getting death threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO PLAYED WHO?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7666103/DJ-Randy-Credico-says-feared-guy-helped-Trump-win-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Bannon told a federal court Friday that Roger Stone was considered  the Trump Campaign's 'access point' to WikiLeaks and Julian Assange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia far-right protest at gay film premiere...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/georgia-far-groups-threaten-disrupt-gay-film-premiere-101909930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of far-right activists burned a rainbow flag and cried "Shame!" during a protest in the Georgian capital against an Oscar-nominated Swedish-Georgian gay-themed film which premiered amid a heavy police presence. The drama has won worldwide critical acclaim but was denounced by the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Detains Nuke Inspector, Bans From Key Atomic Site...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/state-department-slams-iran-for-blocking-nuclear-inspector-from-accessing-contested-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Department officials described Iran's blocking of an international nuclear inspector from accessing key nuclear sites as "outrageous and unwarranted."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White restaurant owner gets 10 years for enslaving black man...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/08/south-carolina-white-restaurant-manager-sentenced-jail-enslaving-black-man/2527814001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white restaurant manager in South Carolina was sentenced to 10 years in prison for enslaving and torturing an African American cook</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEN ONLY:  'IRISHMAN' lead actress speaks just SIX words in entire 210-minute film...	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/10309008/the-irishman-anna-paquin-only-speaks-six-words-netflix-film/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE IRISHMAN viewers have been left outraged after noticing “lead” actress Anna Paquin only speaks SIX words in the three and a half hour Netflix film. The Martin Scorsese movie is the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business braces for 2020 recession...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/businesses-spending-indicators-recession-533481fc-dba7-4b5c-add4-c11628c335bc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firms are trying to protect themselves, but their spending pullback itself could lead to a recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon testifies Stone was campaign link to WIKILEAKS...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/469654-bannon-testifies-that-trump-campaign-saw-stone-as-link-to-wikileaks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Bannon, President Trump's former White House adviser and campaign CEO, testified in court on Friday that the campaign saw Roger Stone as a potential intermediary with WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boies Sues  Dershowitz in Clash of Marquee Lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/08/alan-dershowitz-being-sued-by-jeffrey-epstein-accusers-lawyer-for-defamation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Boies filed a defamation suit in Manhattan Supreme Court on Friday — just one day after Dershowitz made accusations against him and his clients in his own suit in federal court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House impeachment hire Bondi winding down foreign work...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d533bfca6c934034be0ed745cad8c611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An agent of the Qataris. Lobbying for a Kuwaiti firm. A decision to steer clear of a lawsuit against Trump University. As she prepares to defend President Donald Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TO SKIP IA, NH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/653386c5e7e040d09836d0e013558815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Michael Bloomberg plans to skip early voting states like Iowa and New Hampshire if he launches a presidential bid and instead focus his efforts on the crush of states that vote...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcast, cable networks to televise hearings...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/44078e878efc4077b59a55ec10de8c2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — ABC, CBS, NBC and PBS will set aside scheduled programming next week to cover the House's first open impeachment hearings on President Trump. The cable news networks CNN, Fox...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OJ Simpson sues Vegas casino, contends he was defamed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a8f45d3164b4b9e82e9c2bd209c7a72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — O.J. Simpson is suing a Las Vegas hotel-casino that banned him in November 2017, alleging that unnamed employees defamed him by telling a celebrity news site he had been drunk,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil braces...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191108221210-00gea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-CORRUPTION/COURT (UPDATE 4):UPDATE 4-Lula leaves prison, firing up Brazil's left and right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff bootlegging out the back door?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7666295/Chaos-Popeyes-staff-fight-accusations-selling-chicken-sandwiches-side.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers have been filmed fighting at a Popeyes over claims staff bootlegging sandwiches out the back door, as another video shows a woman being body slammed by a worker in a parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=87PVEXMN5qE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former ABC producer Ashley Bianco reveals the inside story to Megyn Kelly about the hot mic moment from anchor Amy Robach. #mkInterview #MegynKelly #JeffreyE...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Witnesses Finger Mulvaney In Quid Pro Quo...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/key-ukraine-witnesses-finger-mick-mulvaney-in-the-quid-pro-quo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two top national security officials say that the chief of staff was the one who’d outlined the investigations that the Ukrainians needed to launch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG journalists 'unnerved'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/08/bloomberg-news-michael-bloomberg-candidacy-068113</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Company Claims To Have Cure For HIV, AIDS...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/11/08/maryland-medical-company-claims-to-have-hiv-aids-cure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Maryland medical company has submitted an application to the U.S Food and Drug Administration for a gene therapy it says will eliminate HIV.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
