<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DC ramps up security ahead of white nationalist rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-capital-ramps-security-ahead-white-nationalist-rally-193428896.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington authorities said they will ramp up the capital city's emergency level when white nationalists and counterprotesters demonstrate Sunday at the same park outside the White House. The National Park Service said Wednesday it issued a permit for a rally in Lafayette Park by Unite the Right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller to bring out the big guns?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/time-for-mueller-to-bring-out-the-big-guns/2018/08/09/df77b0d2-9b31-11e8-b55e-5002300ef004_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s clear the president and his lawyers are trying to play you. Don’t let them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI TURNS TOXIC</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pelosi-is-the-star-of-GOP-attack-ads-worrying-13145559.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - While Democrats grow optimistic about their chances of taking control of the House in November, they are increasingly anxious that the presence of their longtime and polarizing leader, Nancy Pelosi, is making it harder for many of their candidates to compete in crucial swing districts. Republicans, clinging to a 23-seat majority in the House, have made the House minority leader a central element of their attack ads and are portraying many of their opponents as inextricably tied to the liberal from San Francisco. At the same time, some Democrats are expressing alarm that she is standing in the way of the next generation of leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Young people drinking less alcohol...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/philly/health/young-people-drinking-less-alcohol-millennials-mocktails-20180806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may seem surprising amid discussions of Greek life gone wild and alcohol-involved sexual assault but young people in the U.S. today are drinking less alcohol than their counterparts two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THROWAWAYS: Homeless couple struggle with addiction, uncertainty since being forced from tent city...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/projects/la-me-oc-homeless-couple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Laura and John Kasten, a homeless couple forced from an Orange County riverbed into temporary motel living — the road ahead looms empty, filled with hunger, loneliness, drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French court orders TWITTER to change smallprint after privacy case...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-court-orders-twitter-change-smallprint-privacy-case-222338830.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Paris court on Thursday ordered Twitter to change its smallprint, according to a consumer group which accused the tech giant of having "abusive" clauses in its terms and conditions. UFC-Que Choisir claimed victory in its case against the US social media platform, saying "the conviction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada asks for help in Saudi dispute...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/canada-asks-help-saudi-dispute-175948008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada is quietly nudging allies including Germany and Sweden for help with resolving its row with Saudi Arabia, a government source confirmed Thursday. The senior official, who asked not to be identified due to the sensitivity of the diplomacy, said Foreign Minister Chrystia Freeland had spoken with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91 VOTES...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-backed-candidate-kansas-governors-lead-cut-91-204920712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kobach, the current Kansas secretary of state and a staunch ally of Trump, now leads current Governor Jeff Colyer in the Republican primary by a razor-thin margin of 126,257 to 126,066 with potentially thousands more provisional and absentee ballots outstanding. This is why you have canvas, this is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee hopes Trump watches 'BLACKKKLANSMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/spike-lee-hopes-trump-watches-kkk-film-blackkklansman-224234618.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Spike Lee says he wants U.S. President Donald Trump to see his new movie "BlacKkKlansman," an impassioned, tense but often funny movie about race relations in the United States across the decades. "BlacKkKlansman," based on the true story of an African-American police detective</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles spreads...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/brazil-slams-venezuela-measles-spreads-across-border-214302036.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since February, four people - three of them Venezuelan - have died of measles in the remote Brazilian border state of Roraima where health authorities have confirmed 281 cases of the disease, mostly among children. Although many Brazilian children are already vaccinated against the disease, the vaccination</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue team rushes to help ailing orca spotted off Canada...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d6310f14267f4a4ab81bb0daf4a67f71/Rescue-team-rushes-to-help-ailing-orca-spotted-off-Canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Teams of whale experts on Thursday were racing out to sea to help an ailing young killer whale, but they don't plan to intervene to help a mother orca in the same c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor fun dwindles as smoky haze hangs over California...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8ca67ca2d46c4094a3cb439ea423403b/Outdoor-fun-dwindles-as-smoky-haze-hangs-over-California</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A dull haze and the faint smell of smoke from distant blazes have blanketed many California cities for two weeks, forcing summer campers to stay inside,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire drops quest to split state into 3 parts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8bbf09e779cf47148065cdfdfc066e06/Billionaire-drops-quest-to-split-California-into-3-parts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — The billionaire behind a measure to split California in three said he's giving up on the effort to reimagine the nation's most populous state after the s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas governor's race turns nasty as Kobach lead dwindles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26c62b01e86e4f73b55586fe86dbd82c/Kansas-governor's-race-turns-nasty-as-Kobach's-lead-dwindles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kan. (AP) — Kansas Gov. Jeff Colyer demanded Thursday that Secretary of State Kris Kobach stop advising county elections officials while their battle for the Republican no</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil breaks own record for  murders in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/brazil-murder-rate-record-homicides-killings-rio-de-janeiro-police-a8485656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapes also up 8 per cent to 60,018, while 4,539 women were murdered, a rise of 6.1 per cent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala 2020 Has Martha's Vineyard Abuzz...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/darrensands/as-2020-talk-continues-kamala-harris-to-headline-marthas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three sources confirmed that Kamala Harris, who held a fundraiser there last year, will make another trip this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  For Most Trump Voters, 'Very Warm' Feelings for Him Endure...</title>
      <link>http://www.people-press.org/2018/08/09/for-most-trump-voters-very-warm-feelings-for-him-endured/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.people-press.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of Donald Trump’s 2016 election victory, an overwhelming majority of those who said they had voted for him had “warm” feelings for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge concedes error after 'Pit Bull' protests...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/08/09/mueller-team-files-complaint-against-manafort-trial-judge-over-latest-reprimand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After days of being dressed down by the judge overseeing the Paul Manafort case, federal prosecutors sought Thursday to put their foot down -- filing a motion complaining that Judge T.S. Ellis III had unfairly admonished them in front of the jury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swimmer at TX beach survives leg chomp...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/neighborhood/galveston/article/Man-bitten-by-shark-near-Crystal-Beach-13144198.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 42-year old man was bitten by a shark while swimming near Crystal Beach on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed of death measured: 2 millimeters an hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2176397-we-have-measured-the-speed-of-death-and-its-2-millimetres-an-hour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biologists have watched death spread across a living cell for the first time, and discovered that it travels in a steady wave in the same way that wildfires do</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside GOOGLE'S China Censored Search Efforts...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/08/google-censorship-china-blacklist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company sampled searches from a Beijing-based website to hone its blacklists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Judge Authorizes Seizure of CITGO...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-judge-authorizes-seizure-of-venezuelas-citgo-1533853734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. federal judge authorized the seizure of Citgo Petroleum to satisfy a Venezuelan government debt, a ruling that could set off a scramble among Venezuela’s many unpaid creditors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant 67-year-old defies doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2158828/chinese-woman-pregnant-twins-age-67-defies-doctors-advice-have</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing couple sought IVF treatment after their only son died in a road crash but medical staff fear pregnancy will be too risky</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research: How blue light from electronics leads to blindness...</title>
      <link>http://www.wtol.com/story/38852544/new-research-shows-blue-light-from-electronics-leading-to-blindness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our cell phones are practically connected to us. Now, scientists at the University of Toledo say the blue light that comes from electronics is doing permanent damage to our vision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional candidate charged with murder of her campaign staffer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article216405150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Aiken County Sheriff’s Office charged Kellie Lynn Collins with the murder of Curt Cain, treasurer on her failed campaign in Georgia’s 10th Congressional District. Cain was found dead in his SC apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less than 2,000 seized Cohen docs deemed off limits...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/ny-metro-special-master-review-concludes-michael-cohen-20180809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Special Master, Barbara Jones, wrote that she had concluded her review of documents and other material seized by the FBI for attorney-client privilege.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Walk of Fame Covered in Trump Stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/trumps-walk-fame-star-multiplies-hollywood-1133678</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crew laminated vinyl stars and placed them on blank squares in Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: S Florida officials say NO EVIDENCE Russians breached voter systems...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-reg-florida-russian-hacking-20180809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Bill Nelson claims that the Russians have hacked into some Florida counties' voter registration systems, but state officials said they have no information to support that claim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25-million-year-old teeth reveal shark-eat-shark world...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/fossils-on-an-australian-beach-reveal-a-shark-eat-shark-world/17758239/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2015 Philip Mullaly was strolling along a beach in Victoria, Australia, when he spotted what looked like a shining serrated blade stuck in a boulder. Using his car keys, Mullaly carefully pried from the rock a shark tooth about the size of his palm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY:  IT'S GOING TO BLOW!</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2018/08/08/giuliani_mueller_investigation_much_worse_than_the_no-crime.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani, attorney for President Trump, appeared on Hannity Wednesday night to explain why the legal team rejected special counsel Robert Mueller's term for an interview.  Giuliani said the only collusion involved in this case is the intel community using the Steele dossier to obtain "several fraudulent FISA wires."   "Can it get any worse? I mean, what do we need to know that this is a totally illegitimate investigation based on a report, a dossier that was paid for by Hillary Clinton and the Democrats -- probably the biggest illegality so far, the biggest collusion so far. Completely made up. Completely made up. Led to nothing except several fraudulent FISA wires," Giuliani said.  Well, may be if Mueller and his band of whatever they are, Democrats, right, were fair-minded, maybe they'd investigate -- maybe that's the collusion. Maybe that's the collusion," he said of the infamous dossier.  Giuliani said what is going on by the Mueller investigative team is a "different kind of Watergate," calling them corrupt "through and through."  "And I believe that when this plays out over the next year or two, it's not going to be about President Trump. It's going to get over with. It's going to be about all the things they did," he said of Mueller's team.  "You know how sometimes the cover-up is worse than the crime? In this case, the investigation was much worse than the no-crime," the former NYC mayor said.  "I think it's going to lead to some very strict -- very big reforms, just like Watergate," he said. "It's a different kind of Watergate. It's on the side of the investigator."  Hannity said when we get to the bottom of the investigation, it will "shock the heart, the soul, and the mind" of fair-minded Americans.   "My sources are telling me that when the American people get to the bottom of all of this, it will shock the heart, the soul, and the mind of any fair-minded American," the host said.  Transcript, via FOX News:  SEAN HANNITY, FOX NEWS HOST: All right. Joining us now in studio responding to all this breaking news, it is President Trump's attorney, Rudy Giuliani.  Mr. Mayor, good to see you, sir. How are you?  RUDY GIULIANI, ATTORNEY FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP: Good to see you, Sean.  HANNITY: All right. Let's start with tonight's breaking news. So, you got Ohr, Steele, Nellie Ohr. We got Russian lies.  GIULIANI: Can it get any worse? I mean, what do we need to know that this is a totally illegitimate investigation based on a report, a dossier that was paid for by Hillary Clinton and the Democrats -- probably the biggest illegality so far, the biggest collusion so far.  HANNITY: Or conspiracy.  GIULIANI: Completely made up. Completely made up. Led to nothing except several fraudulent FISA wires.  And now, we have Mueller, who doesn't seem to care that he's sitting on top of a totally illegitimate investigation.  HANNITY: But the dossier, thinking about the dossier that she paid for and the fact that the FBI paid Steele, it was designed to misinform the American people with Russian lies to influence the election.  GIULIANI: Yes.  HANNITY: There's a great irony here, if it wasn't --  GIULIANI: Well, may be if Mueller and his band of whatever they are, Democrats, right, were fair-minded, maybe they'd investigate -- maybe that's the collusion. Maybe that's the collusion.  HANNITY: Did you ever hear the Adam Schiff tape that we played?  GIULIANI: Yes.  HANNITY: Adam Schiff, he's just dying to get naked pictures of Trump with a Russian on tape. There's your evidence, Mueller. You can't make it up. If it wasn't so seriously -- not only did they try to lie to the American people with Russian lies, now we know after the election, they tried to destroy the president with lies.  And now, they are connected to Mueller perhaps?  GIULIANI: Yes, I've never been involved in an investigation on either side that's more illegitimate than this one, that is so obviously more illegitimate. And I wonder where is the sense of justice on the part of Mueller, on the part of the Justice Department.  After all, the Justice Department -- this is a Justice Department investigation. He is working for Rosenstein. And at some point, you've got to say the irregularities, the unethical conduct --  HANNITY: Double standard.  GIULIANI: -- the double standard, the way in which people who hate Trump will put into primary positions of power has completely tainted this investigation.  HANNITY: My family is families from law enforcement, my mom was a prison guard, you know, my dad, New York City, family court probation, so many cops in my family, FBI agents. I cannot believe this is such -- these are -- the rank-and-file are so good.  Here's the thing, you responded today to Mueller's latest request and you think this could be over by September. Let's start with the request.  GIULIANI: Well, I think of it isn't over by September, then we have a very, very serious violation of the Justice Department rules that you shouldn't be conducting one of these investigations in the 60-day period.  Look, he's got plenty of time to either decide -- we offered him an opportunity to do a form of questioning. He can say yes or no. We can do it. If he doesn't want to do it, he knows the answers to every question that he wants to ask. He's going to ask them, did you tell Comey to go easy on Flynn? The president will say no I didn't.  Hey, Bob, you know it. Why do you want to get him under oath? Do you think we're fools?  You want to get him under oath because you want to trap him into perjury. Well, we're not going to let you do that.  HANNITY: It's -- there's two separate issues: collusion and so-called obstruction. There's a report today that you said no questions on obstruction. Am I assuming here that your -- that your response to him was maybe a couple of written answers only?  GIULIANI: No, I can't tell you what it is yet because we haven't -- no, I can't. I can't. Jay will get very angry at me. My co-counsel --  HANNITY: I understood.  GIULIANI: -- is much stricter about this than I am. So, he'll get very angry and Jay (ph) will -- I'd love to tell you.  But the reality is, the reality is he doesn't need to ask a single question on obstruction, he has all the answers. They are not going to change. The president is not going to change his testimony.  So, stop the nonsense. You are trying to trap him into perjury because you don't have a case.  HANNITY: Mr. Mayor, the Constitution as our good friend Mark says, Mark Levin, is on the president's side. I agree it's illegitimate, has been, the double standard is so glaring. We have been pointing it out now every night and with new details every night.  My question is, I wouldn't give him a thing. You don't owe him a thing and if he wants a fight, then there's going to be a fight.  GIULIANI: Well, we don't like to fight, you know that.  (LAUGHTER)  HANNITY: Mr. Mayor, I used to watch your press conferences, I disagree with that.  GIULIANI: The reality is, the real story is not that this case isn't going to fizzle. It's going to blow up on them. The real question is, what we talked about before, there's a lot more to what they did that nobody knows about yet.  HANNITY: I know some of it.  GIULIANI: A lot more -- a lot more to the obstruction of justice, to the collusion, to the fake dossier.  HANNITY: Oh, I know a lot.  GIULIANI: They're trying to bring Steele back in after he was completely discredited.  HANNITY: And then feed it to Mueller.  GIULIANI: Yes. And Mueller is going to have a lot to answer for.  HANNITY: Mr. Mayor --  GIULIANI: I said a long time ago, the investigation here has to be of the investigators, because we can't let this happen again in American history. We may not have a president as strong as President Trump. A lesser president could have really been cracked by this.  HANNITY: Mueller, then you got Jeanie Rhee, you got Andrew Weissmann.  Here's my question: we know the Department of Justice has absolutely denied congressional subpoenas. Now, I don't -- as great a lawyer as you are, I don't think you'd get me out of trouble if I was ignoring a subpoena.  GIULIANI: No, I don't think I could.  HANNITY: But the president has the power to go through these documents through FISA and unre -- make it unredacted and let the American people see that the bulk of information was what Christopher Steele himself said wasn't verified.  GIULIANI: Well, that's something -- that something that as his private lawyers -- that he has to deal with and his government lawyers. And he's going to do it right now.  HANNITY: Would you suggest he should?  GIULIANI: I can't tell you what I suggest. It's privileged.  (LAUGHTER)  HANNITY: OK. Let me ask you about the FISA lies. The bulk of information, the Grassley-Graham memo says, came from the phony dossier that Hillary paid for. That turns out to be a lie. The author of it says he can't corroborate it.  GIULIANI: Right.  HANNITY: Now, here's my question: so, they used it four separate times, to spy on an American citizen, an opposition party candidate campaign associate, in the lead-up to the election, after the election. Again, what if I lied to a judge? I wouldn't think of lying to a judge without getting my life in jail afterwards.  GIULIANI: You'd be investigated for perjury. You'd be investigated for contempt. Your career would be ruined. Your life would be ruined.  And I believe that when this plays out over the next year or two, it's not going to be about President Trump. It's going to get over with. It's going to be about all the things they did.  This -- you know how sometimes the cover-up is worse than the crime? In this case, the investigation was much worse than the no-crime.  HANNITY: Mr. Mayor --  GIULIANI: The president did nothing wrong.  HANNITY: My sources are telling me that when the American people get to the bottom of all of this, it will shock the heart, the soul, and the mind of any fair-minded American.  GIULIANI: I think it's going to lead to some very strict -- very big reforms, just like Watergate. It's a different kind of Watergate. It's on the side of the investigator.  HANNITY: OK.  GIULIANI: Corrupt investigations through and through.  HANNITY: Why would you even consider a counterproposal?  GIULIANI: When it's over with, I will explain it to you.  (LAUGHTER)  HANNITY: Boy, I'm not getting anything out of you tonight. Good to see you, Mr. Mayor. Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge concedes error after prosecutor protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/09/paul-manafort-trial-day-8-judge-ellis-769889</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say a back and forth over an expert witness in front of the jury could have left a negative impression in their minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS INTENSIFY TESLA PROBE</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/09/tesla-is-said-to-face-broader-sec-scrutiny-over-musk-statements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission is intensifying its scrutiny of Tesla Inc.’s public statements in the wake of Elon Musk’s provocative tweet Tuesday about taking the electric-car company private, according to two people familiar with the matter.SEC enforcement attorneys in the San Francisco office were already gathering general information about Tesla’s public pronouncements on manufacturing goals and sales targets, according to the people who asked not to be named because the review is private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller request signals Gates still cooperating beyond Manafort case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/09/politics/gates-manafort-mueller-cooperation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A court filing from special counsel Robert Mueller signals that Rick Gates may be assisting the investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 election beyond the case against Paul Manafort.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA board plans meet to ramp up going-private, likely to ask Musk to recuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/09/tesla-board-tells-elon-musk-to-recuse-himself-prepares-to-review-take.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board plans to meet with advisors next week about taking Tesla private, and has told Musk that he needs his own separate set of advisers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: FACEBOOK Shedding Massive Traffic...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2018/08/08/facebook-traffic-down-youtube-gaining-ground/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four billion. That, according to a new study shared with CNBC by market research firm SimilarWeb, is how many monthly page visits Facebook has shed in a slow-drip but nevertheless huge decline over…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver dead after fighting passenger outside hotel...</title>
      <link>http://www.nbc12.com/story/38845025/police-uber-driver-died-after-fight-with-passenger-outside-east-louisville-hotel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An argument between an Uber driver and passenger outside an east Louisville hotel escalated to a deadly level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenger fights for attention as Feinstein avoids campaigning...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-feinstein-recess-plans-20180809-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A solid lead in the campaign means a low key August for Feinstein</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election worker tells man can't vote wearing MAGA hat...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/politics-government/election/article216254035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clay County man was told he couldn’t wear his Make America Great Again hat while voting in Tuesday’s primary. But the Secretary of State’s Office ruled he could because the hat doesn’t pertain to this election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan migrants throng border high up in Andes Mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.nasdaq.com/article/venezuelan-migrants-throng-ecuadorcolombia-border-high-up-in-andes-20180809-01276</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nasdaq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling of US trade dispute reveals rare Communist Party cracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/09/handling-of-us-trade-dispute-causes-rift-in-chinese-leadership-source.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Xi Jinping still has a firm grip on power, but an unusual surge of criticism about economic policy and how the government has handled the trade war has revealed rare cracks in the ruling Communist Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates Trash Election Results BEFORE Brazil Even Votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/09/candidates-trash-election-results-before-brazil-even-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candidates Trash Election Results Before Brazil Even Votes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIBUNE Terminates SINCLAIR Merger, Sues Broadcast Rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tribune-media-terminates-merger-agreement-with-sinclair-broadcast-group-1533810907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tribune Media terminated its merger agreement with rival TV station-owner Sinclair Broadcast Group and sued the company, alleging it failed to make sufficient efforts to get their $3.9 billion deal approved by regulators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumner Redstone Trust Restricts Sale Options for CBS, VIACOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/sumner-redstone-trust-restricts-sale-options-for-cbs-viacom-1533833418</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sumner Redstone doesn’t want his heirs to have an easy time selling off his family’s controlling stakes in media companies Viacom and CBS. And he put it in writing in his estate-planning documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: 'CRAZY RICH ASIANS' Isn't Quite Crazy Enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2018/08/crazy-rich-asians-movie-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s opulence galore in this adaptation of Kevin Kwan’s best-seller; if only it had a little more bite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgery centers don't have to report deaths in 17 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2018/08/09/surgery-center-deaths-medicare-reporting-colonoscopy/868703002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 17 states, surgery center deaths don't have to be reported to officials – let alone patients – and doctors ousted from hospitals can operate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA astronaut reveals encounter with alien-like object...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6973957/nasa-astronaut-encounter-alien-like-object-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NASA astronaut has claimed he once saw an “alien-like, organic object” floating outside his space shuttle. Leland Melvin, 54, worked as an engineer on board Atlantis when he spotted t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prayers in bars?</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/article215389120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As church attendance declines across South Carolina, some churches are taking new tacks to reach their communities, including meeting in a West Columbia bar, a Myrtle Beach pier, a Bluffton dance studio and a Columbia movie theater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC abandons its churches: Attendance drops, closures rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/article215014375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolina Protestant churches are losing thousands of members each year, and many are in danger of closing, signaling a major “post-Christian” culture shift in the traditional Bible Belt of the American South.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Threatens U.S. Space Program Over Fresh Sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/russia-reacts-angrily-to-draconian-new-sanctions-from-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New sanctions leveled as punishment for Skripal poisonings in Britain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professors allow students to pick their own grade...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/post/47730/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Contract grading’ billed as revolutionary education practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK tests giving homeless people barcodes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/08/homeless-people-wearing-barcodes-new-project-increase-donations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeless people are wearing barcodes around their necks in an attempt to increase donations in a cashless society, under an Oxford University backed initiative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Russians have penetrated Florida election systems...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/08/08/bill-nelson-the-russians-have-penetrated-some-florida-voter-election-systems/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA — Russian operatives have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Pet Owners Happier, Wealthier, More Fit...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/survey-pet-owners-happier-wealthier-more-fit-than-non-owners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you think pets are the pits, you may not be living to your potential. A new survey finds that people who own pets are happier, earn more money, and exercise more frequently than those who don't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue message in Chinese broadcast over intercom at National Weather Service...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/technology/businessinsider/article/Employees-at-a-National-Weather-Service-office-in-13142835.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adam Berry/Getty Images   Federal officials are trying to figure out how a random Chinese-language message suddenly blared over the intercom at a National Weather Service office in Maryland on Wednesday. Minutes before the voice of a Chinese woman was broadcast, employees received a similar message on their phones at the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) affiliate office in College Park, Maryland, The Washington Post reported. An approximate English translation of the message said, "you have a package from Amazon at the Chinese Embassy. Press 1 for more details," The Post said. In an email to Business Insider Wednesday evening, an NOAA representative said the agency is still investigating the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court bans popular pesticide...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article216372085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 9th Circuit Court of Appeals ordered the Trump administration Thursday to ban widely used farm pesticide chlorpyrifos. Environmentalists said the chemical causes brain damage in children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ministers, governors, Congress, White House working on prison reform...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/article216302455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Efforts to merge a House prison reform bill with a Senate sentencing reform measure are picking up steam after months of inaction. The Trump administration is working to make it happen even after voicing earlier opposition to relaxing federal sentencing requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Should U.S. Air Force Bomb Forest Fires?</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/military/weapons/a22674251/air-force-bomb-forest-fires/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds ridiculous, but it’s an idea that's grounded in physics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media boost security at president's rallies...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/09/media-boosts-security-as-trump-ramps-up-enemy-rhetoric-768666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV networks are employing security guards at the president's high-octane rallies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More evacuations in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2018/08/08/milder-temperatures-could-help-firefighters-battling-holy-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some schools will close Thursday because of air quality or evacuations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Gird for House Battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/08/us/politics/ohio-kansas-elections-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voting across the Midwest and West this week laid bare the party’s precarious position in the November midterm elections, particularly its vulnerabilities in suburbs and with moderate voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders plane carrying deported mother and child turned around...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/storyline/immigration-border-crisis/judge-orders-plane-carrying-deported-mother-child-turned-around-blocks-n899311</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court learned that the Trump administration had put a mother and a daughter who are plaintiffs in the lawsuit on a flight to Central America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for offering $500 to kill ICE agent...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/crime-courts/boston-area-man-arrested-threatening-ice-agents-twitter-n899146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brandon Ziobrowski, 33, was arrested after allegedly tweeting that he would give $500 to anyone who kills an ICE agent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre plight of 1,000 crocodiles left homeless at failed tourist attraction...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/bizarre-plight-1000-crocodiles-left-13055272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Defense Ministry has been forced to admit is has no idea what to do with the snappy reptiles, who are in a farm in Petza'el</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVIDENCE:  Dominant approach to Alzheimer's completely wrong?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/theres-new-evidence-that-the-dominant-approach-to-alzheimers-may-be-completely-wrong-2018-08-09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts are questioning a major scientific theory of the disease, which could mean two Biogen drugs won’t be successful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL POUNDS HAMAS AFTER 19 INJURED IN ROCKET BARRAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Two-injured-as-Gazan-rockets-land-in-Sderot-564411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IDF strikes over 100 Hamas terror targets after over 150 projectiles fired towards southern Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sirens wail...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Rocket-sirens-wail-across-southern-Israel-as-IDF-strikes-Gaza-564454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 200 mortars and rockets were fired towards southern Israeli communities since Wednesday evening by Hamas and other terror groups in the coastal enclave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch Out, America: 'LOVE ISLAND' Is Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/love-island-is-coming-cbs-american-adaptation-1133157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reality show has drawn record ratings for ITV2, particularly among younger viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt's second sphinx found: Ancient statue discovered during road work...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1001190/egypt-sphinx-giza-pyramids-luxor-karnak-thebes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SECOND sphinx from the time of ancient Egypt has been discovered, after workers accidentally dug up the renowned artefact during road works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone Volcano: 153 quakes in month...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1000808/Yellowstone-volcano-eruption-super-volcano-eruption-big-one-earthquake-USGS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YELLOWSTONE National Park has been struck by a shocking 153 earthquakes during the month of July, sparking fears the ‘Big One’ earthquake or a super volcano could be due.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election results spur debate over Trump's midterm role...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Lackluster-election-results-spur-debate-over-13142445.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A new round of lackluster showings by Republican candidates reignited a debate Wednesday within the GOP over whether President Donald Trump will be a drag on the party's chances in November and should stay out of some of the country's most hotly-contested races. Inside the White House, Trump aides are mapping out plans for the fall that would offer a variety of options to Republican candidates, be it a visit from the president's daughter, Ivanka Trump, to a blue state or a presidential tweet for a red-state ally. But mounting apprehension about Trump's political capital lingered in Washington and on the campaign trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE:  'Ladies and gentlemen, the LAST PRESIDENT of United States'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/craig-bannister/michael-moore-f-k-hope-seriously-f-k-hope-trump-will-be-last-president-us </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities:  Kids trained to commit school shootings at extremist Muslim compound in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/siraj-wahhaj-arrested-amalia-new-mexico-father-imam-possible-link-1993-world-trade-center-bombing-court-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Siraj Wahhaj, arrested Saturday, shares name with his father who heads a mosque in Brooklyn, New York, that has attracted radical speakers over the years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10 stories that will drive the day, from the world’s most wired reporter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta school: No more Pledge of Allegiance to start day...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/breaking-news/atlanta-school-eliminates-morning-pledge-allegiance-recitation/B073XeDsSGP0khan64taOJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Atlanta charter school will not recite the Pledge of Allegiance as part of its morning meeting ag...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father, son caught killing bear, shrieking cubs in den...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/crime-courts/2018/08/08/troopers-game-camera-captures-wasilla-men-shooting-bear-and-cubs-in-den/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two are accused of killing a collared bear and her cubs that were part of a state and federal study on an island in Alaska's Prince William Sound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYLAN BYERS</title>
      <link>https://us11.campaign-archive.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=505046f69e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Philly Rapper Killed In Drive-By Shooting...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/08/09/north-philly-drive-by-shooting-six-shot-two-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people, including popular Philly rapper General Reezy, have died and four others were wounded in a drive-by shooting on Wednesday night in North Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINDSAY LOHAN: #MeToo accusers are weak for not reporting rape to cops...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/08/09/lindsay-lohan-slams-metoo-accusers-as-weak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lindsay Lohan says she’s met women who’ve spoken up about sexual assault and harassment in light of the #MeToo movement “who do it for the attention.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrong Tommy Fleetwood got massive British Open check...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/09/the-wrong-tommy-fleetwood-got-massive-british-open-check/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tommy Fleetwood’s British Open prize money of $154,480 was paid into the bank account of an American PGA professional with the same name. The blunder was noticed when a friend of the American…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Mulls Passing Strictest Food Allergy Laws...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/08/08/edison-new-jersey-food-allergy-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new proposal would require eateries to list all ingredients on their menus that trigger food allergies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth while overdosing on heroin in BURGER KING bathroom...</title>
      <link>https://fox2now.com/2018/08/08/woman-gives-birth-while-overdosing-on-heroin-in-burger-king-bathroom-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox2now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLICOTHE, Ohio - A mother believed to be overdosing on heroin gave birth in an Ohio Burger King bathroom stall, and first responders found the baby alive in the toilet Friday afternoon, according to Chillicothe police.  Police initially responded to reports of a man who had passed out in a vehicle and that a woman, who was with him, had overdosed, according to WSYX.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic 19,000-Square-Foot MCDONALD'S Opens In Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/08/08/river-north-rock-n-roll-mcdonalds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of McDonald’s arrives in Chicago this week, with the opening of a sleek, brand new 19,000-square-foot contemporary restaurant that has risen from the ashes of the iconic Rock-N-Roll McDonald’s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Endures Hottest First Week Of August Ever Recorded...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/08/08/boston-hottest-first-week-of-august-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's supposed to be hot this time of year, but the first week of August was one for the record books in Boston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration raids in Nebraska, Minnesota target businesses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f2332b8cec5a4fb69ac82ef5e53e0331/Immigration-raids-in-Nebraska,-Minnesota-target-businesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — A large federal law enforcement operation conducted Wednesday targeted businesses in Nebraska and Minnesota that officials say knowingly hired — and mistr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child remains recovered from father who wanted to perform exorcism...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b2d26511bc484ad9829fa41b58871480</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAOS, N.M. (AP) — A severely disabled Georgia boy who authorities say was kidnapped by his father and marked for an exorcism was found buried at the ramshackle compound in the New</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battling 18 blazes; May face worst fire season...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/98951c2a39874837a22ba4beab116d6d/Battling-18-blazes,-California-may-face-worst-fire-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKIAH, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters said for the first time Wednesday that they have made good progress battling the state's largest-ever wildfire but didn't expect to have it fully</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donkeys at mini ranch help people de-stress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4448eea413ce436d837ec9c4b7d5fb14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ULSTER PARK, N.Y. (AP) — In most of the world, donkeys are beasts of burden, but the only job of the long-eared denizens of Donkey Park is to nuzzle, bray and beguile the diverse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Jr. becomes Republican superstar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a2ebb4a541c4e9d80e159f1911f8715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — If Donald Trump Jr. is worried, he sure doesn't show it.        His father, the president, is reported to be fretting about his eldest son's entanglement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kobach lead in Kansas race falls to 91 votes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/26c62b01e86e4f73b55586fe86dbd82c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kan. (AP) — Kansas Secretary of State Kris Kobach's lead over Gov. Jeff Colyer in the Republican primary has shrunk to only 91 votes after election officials discovered a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And media outlets boost their security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NY DAILY NEWS] CONFIDENTIAL</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/confidential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read celebrity gossip around New York and Hollywood from the New York Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-the-grid...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox26houston.com/news/prosecutors-man-was-training-kids-for-school-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox26houston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A father arrested at a ramshackle New Mexico compound where 11 hungry children were found living in filth was training youngsters to commit school shootings, prosecutors said in court documents obtained Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH DRUDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melania's parents become U.S. citizens...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6044565/Melania-Trumps-parents-U-S-citizens-attorney-says-got-NO-special-treatment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Melania Trump's parents were sworn in as U.S. citizens in New York City on Thursday. They live mostly in Maryland where they help their daughter and grandson, Barron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police testing saliva swab to catch stoned drivers...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/local_coverage/2018/08/state_police_testing_saliva_swab_to_catch_stoned_drivers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State police — expecting a surge in drugged driving now that pot is legal, and looking for a way to prove a driver is high — are finalizing a test of swabs they administered on about 170 people at roadside sobriety checks and a drug treatment center.The Massachusetts State Police assessment is part of a nationwide effort by police to deal with the lack of chemical tests for drug intoxication comparable to Breathalyzers that are used to measure drunkenness. Legal experts say any chemical test is likely to face challenges in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One has been a Fox Newser for 17 years, and the other for 23 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lieutenant becomes first woman to lead Marine infantry platoon...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/defense/marine-corps/401042-lieutenant-becomes-first-ever-woman-to-lead-marine-infantry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First Lt. Marina Hierl has reportedly made history by becoming the first woman in the Marine Corps to lead an infantry platoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems eyeing smaller magic number for majority...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/400993-dems-eyeing-smaller-magic-number-for-house-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The magic number of seats Democrats need to hit to win back the House majority is 23. But in reality, it’s almost certainly a much smaller number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/article/declarations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Assange considering offer to appear before U.S. Senate committee...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180809132406-ofzt8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ECUADOR/ASSANGE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Assange considering offer to appear before U.S. Senate committee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador declares state of emergency over migrants at border...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180809033206-yvi67</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ECUADOR-VENEZUELA/:Ecuador declares state of emergency over Venezuelan migrants at border</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE NEWS</title>
      <link>http://news.google.com/nwshp?hl=en&amp;tab=wn&amp;q=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap produces a wide range of news contents and provides print, broadcast media as well as state and private institutions with real-time news products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
