<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady to host weekly radio show...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-12960b1420e79684491c5807dba23253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady and Larry Fitzgerald are branching out, even as training camps have opened and the 2021 season beckons. The seven-time Super Bowl-winning quarterback and star wide receiver will host “Let's Go!” a weekly SiriusXM Radio show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORNHUB star arrested after 'luring woman into making films with fake promise of career'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3396272/pornhub-star-arrested-luring-women-films/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN adult film star allegedly lured young women into pornography by falsely promising them a big break into Bollywood. Nandita Dutta, 30, was charged by police after two models accused her of forcin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran warns against any action over attack on Israeli-managed tanker...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210802-iran-warns-against-any-action-over-attack-on-israeli-managed-tanker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran on Monday vowed to respond to any "adventurism", its foreign ministry said, after the US and Britain joined Israel in blaming Tehran for a deadly tanker attack, claims it denies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT FUNNY: Kathy Griffin reveals she has lung cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3396760/kathy-griffin-lung-cancer-surgery-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KATHY Griffin has revealed that she’s suffering from lung cancer and will soon undergo surgery to “remove half of her left lung.” Griffin was diagnosed with lung cancer although s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I F--king Hope He Sues Me': Inside TWITTER Explosion that Nearly Sunk Musk...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/07/inside-the-twitter-explosion-that-nearly-sunk-elon-musk-tesla-power-play-excerpt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his new book, “Power Play: Tesla, Elon Musk, and the Bet of the Century,” reporter Tim Higgins chronicles the behind-the-scenes meltdowns at Tesla sparked by Musk’s unhinged online presence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back-To-School Anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/back-to-school-anxiety-children-school-bus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With COVID-19 rates starting to tick back up this summer, parents are more anxious than usual about back-to-school season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitians Say They Got Death Threats for Refusing to Tamper With Assassination Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/02/haitians-say-they-got-death-threats-for-refusing-to-tamper-with-moise-evidence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Haiti — They examined the bodies of Haiti’s slain president and of the mercenaries who are accused of conspiring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks fleeing toxic red tide take refuge in Florida canal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/aug/02/sharks-toxic-red-tide-florida-canal-lemon-blacktip-bonnethead-nurse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lemon, blacktip, bonnethead and nurse sharks retreat from sea as state struggles to contain pollution problem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: OPTIMISM PLUMMETS</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/353003/americans-optimism-covid-dashed-cases-surge.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans' assessments of the COVID-19 situation have dramatically worsened, and their worry about getting the disease has increased. At the same time, social distancing behaviors are largely unchanged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans weightlifter out of Olympics after making history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9851409/New-Zealands-Laurel-Hubbard-appears-stage-prepares-make-Olympic-history.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurel Hubbard, 43, who gender transitioned in 2012, is competing in the 87+kg category in Tokyo after a controversial rule change by the International Olympic Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada upsets American women's soccer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-soccer-womens-soccer-megan-rapinoe-alyssa-naeher-fb4f8643be44d87ee88cfd29594963ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KASHIMA, Japan (AP) — Jessie Fleming scored on a penalty kick in the 74th minute and Canada earned a 1-0 semifinal victory over the United States in the Olympic women’s soccer competition on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well-known wild horse found dead on Outer Banks beach. Heat may have been factor...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article253184858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The horse was nearly 30 years of age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At extraordinary Games, acts of kindness abound...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-acts-of-kindness-sportsmanship-f7484946288e2a078b2a1f9eccbc1232</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A surfer jumping in to translate for the rival who’d just beaten him. High-jumping friends agreeing to share a gold medal rather than move to a tiebreaker. Two runners falling in a tangle of legs, then helping each other to the finish line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Social Network Flooded With ISIS Propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/02/trump-gettr-social-media-isis-502078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GETTR, the new platform started by members of the former president’s inner circle, is awash with beheading videos and extremist content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Matt Damon slammed after admitting using gay slur until 'just few months ago'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-9850187/Matt-Damon-admits-stopped-using-homophobic-slur.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Damon admitted that his daughter wrote him a long essay detailing how the homophobic slur is 'dangerous' after the Hollywood actor said it at the dinner table as a 'joke'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama defies CDC guidance inviting 500 people to celeb-studded 60th bday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9850927/Obama-defies-CDC-guidance-inviting-500-people-60th-birthday-party-Marthas-Vineyard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama is planning to celebrate his 60th birthday with nearly 500 guests and 200 staff members on Martha's Vineyard, drawing some criticism online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Using AI To 'See Days In Advance'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41771/the-pentagon-is-experimenting-with-using-artificial-intelligence-to-see-days-in-advance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon aims to use cutting-edge cloud networks and artificial intelligence systems to anticipate adversaries' moves before they make them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters swarmed St. Louis council meeting. Then, attendee tested positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-mask-protesters-swarmed-a-st-louis-county-council-meeting-then-an-attendee-tested-positive-for-covid/ar-AAMPN8r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The City of St. Louis Department of Health is trying to identify anyone who had close contact with the infected person and urged everyone who attended the council meeting to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats of violence spark fear of election worker exodus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/565722-threats-of-violence-spark-fear-of-election-worker-exodus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is growing concern that election workers will leave their posts in droves following a 2020 presidential contest that saw an unprecedented rise in violent threats against administrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Rouses Supporters in Protests Against Voting System...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/brazils-bolsonaro-escalates-rhetoric-over-232911585.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA (Reuters) -Brazil's far-right President Jair Bolsonaro pleaded on Thursday for the adoption of printed ballots that can be counted, alleging that it is necessary to avoid fraud in the country's electronic voting system in next year's election. Bolsonaro showed a series of internet video clips as alleged evidence of past fraud, maintaining that democracy was at risk in Brazil. Critics say that Bolsonaro, like former U.S. President Donald Trump, is sowing election doubts to pave the way for him not to accept defeat in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transgender weightlifter in debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9837615/Laurel-Hubbard-Tokyo-Olympics-Petition-calling-rule-change-removed-hate-speech.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 30,000 people signed the petition, which argued Hubbard's inclusion in the division put her competitors at a significant disadvantage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEALTHY AMERICANS TARGETED BY US IN PANAMA TAX-FRAUD PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://bermudapost.com/wealthy-americans-targeted-by-u-s-in-panama-tax-fraud-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bermudapost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. authorities obtained a court order allowing them to demand financial information from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy is a fiction in the internet age. Priest's case proves it...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/08/01/privacy-is-fiction-internet-age-priests-case-proves-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress's failure to act permits an insidious data free-for-all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big tech's big week raises fears of 'Blade Runner future' of mega-company rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/01/big-techs-big-week-blade-runner-future-amazon-google-apple-microsoft</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon, Google, Apple and Microsoft all reported record-breaking profits but recent Biden administration moves suggest US tech’s easy ride is over</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCIAL MEDIA GIANTS FAIL TO CURB 90% OF ANTISEMITISM...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/aug/01/a-safe-space-for-racists-antisemitism-report-criticises-social-media-giants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube and TikTok failing to act on most reported anti-Jewish posts, says study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Groups still spending donor money at his properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/his-campaign-is-over-but-trump-e2-80-99s-political-groups-are-still-spending-donor-money-at-his-properties/ar-AAMNNtc?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former president Donald Trump's political action committees have continued spending money at his properties, filings show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires' space race just the beginning...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/565759-the-billionaires-space-race-is-just-the-beginning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suborbital jaunts accomplished by some billionaires were not just expressions of egos. They constituted the next steps in the creation of a brand-new industry, space tourism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lollapalooza drops DaBaby over AIDS comments...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-music-fest-lollapalooza-drops-221830181.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US music festival Lollapalooza announced Sunday it had dropped DaBaby from its lineup after the rapper made homophobic comments and false statements about AIDS during a recent performance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican lawmaker who once spurned masks urges people to take covid seriously after eight-month illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gop-lawmaker-who-once-spurned-masks-urges-people-to-take-covid-19-seriously-after-eight-month-illness/ar-AAMOMFZ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee state Rep. David Byrd, a Republican, had become so ill from infection that he had to get a liver transplant in June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has more than $100 million in political cash after first six months of 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-has-built-war-chest-of-more-than-100-million/ar-AAMLDWg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite departing from office and being barred from the leading social media platforms, former President Donald J. Trump was the Republican Party’s most dominant fund-raiser in the first half of 2021 and ended June with a war chest of more than $100 million, according to new federal campaign filings made this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE removes dating app for unvaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/apple-removes-anti-vaxx-covid-dating-app-unjected-app-store-2021-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple said an anti-vaxx app called Unjected breached its App Store rules. Unjected's owners fought back, saying the decision was "censorship."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spray of bullets injures 10 people in NYC gang shooting...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazen-coordinated-attack-spray-bullets-231500246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — Ten people were wounded when a pair of gunmen fired more than 40 shots down a Queens street in a brazen gang-related shooting, police said Sunday. The barrage of bullets on 37th Avenue near 99th Street in North Corona kicked off a bloody night in the city, where 18 people were either killed or wounded in seven separate shootings, police said. The masked and hooded Queens gunmen, who ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Doom...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fauci-covid-cases-rise-26bea820b736cf4d9ac1692ccc0203ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci warned Sunday that more “pain and suffering” is on the horizon as COVID-19 cases climb again and officials plead with unvaccinated Americans to get their shots. Fauci, the nation’s top infectious disease expert, also said he doesn’t foresee additional lockdowns in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPPFACEBOOK, GMAIL users warned over Israeli spyware that can hack encrypted apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3391800/whatsapp-facebook-gmail-users-warned-hacking-startup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHATSAPP, Facebook, and Gmail users are being warned about a new Israeli surveillance startup, Paragon, that can “hack encrypted apps.” The Tel Aviv-based surveillance startup’s p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia deploys helicopters and soldiers to keep people inside during lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3388310/australia-deploys-military-to-enforce-covid-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUNG ho Aussie politicians have deployed the army and helicopters to order people to go home in what is one of the world’s strictest Covid lockdowns. One man caught a chopper shouting out sta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China overtakes USA in GOLD medal count...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/olympic-medal-count-see-who-has-won-the-most-gold-and-overall/3179265/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States secured its spot back atop the medal throne at the Tokyo Olympics through Day 9 of competition. Team USA has the lead at the 2020 Tokyo Games with 59 overall medals — 20 gold medals, 23 silver and 16 bronze. The women of Team USA have won 35 medals, which is almost double the medals of the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran TV claims attack on 'Israeli ship' was revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-tv-report-says-attack-on-israeli-ship-was-revenge-for-syria-raid-675430</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian TV network reported on Friday that the attack on the Israeli-owned ship off the coast of Oman was a response to an Israeli attack in Syria, indicating Iranian involvement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE suspends SKY NEWS Australia citing 'misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210801-youtube-suspends-sky-news-australia-channel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube suspends Sky News Australia channel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New mask guidelines create more and more confusion...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/565712-new-mask-guidelines-trigger-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s (CDC) new mask guidance is spurring confusion and backlash as the country tries to respond to the shifting threat of the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN 'DECLARED VICTORY TOO SOON'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/president-biden-absolutely-declared-a-victory-too-soon-leana-wen-says-140703432.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I am hopeful as I look to the future,” Dr. Leana Wen writes in her new book, “Lifelines: A Doctor’s Journey in the Fight for Public Health.” On the day she spoke to Yahoo News, however, case counts were spiking across the United States, due almost entirely to the increased transmissibility of the Delta variant. Masks were back. So were concerns that schools might reopen in the fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER and MODERNA raise prices for vaccines in EU...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/1-pfizer-moderna-raise-prices-121400124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer Inc and Moderna Inc have raised the prices of their COVID-19 vaccines in their latest European Union supply contracts, the Financial Times reported https://on.ft.com/3j8mbTb on Sunday. The new price for the Pfizer shot was 19.50 euros ($23.15)against 15.50 euros previously, the newspaper said, citing portions of the contracts seen. The price of a Moderna vaccine was $25.50 a dose, the contracts show, up from about 19 euros in the first procurement deal but lower than the previously agreed $28.50 because the order had grown, the report said, citing one official close to the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Trump be spoiler in Newsom recall?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-california-coronavirus-pandemic-race-and-ethnicity-racial-injustice-db3a54763d961ece9b33c94fbe405e20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California could witness a stunning turnabout in a nation of deeply polarized politics if the liberal state dumps Democratic Gov. Gavin Newsom and elects a Republican to fill his job in a September recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  FLORIDA MOST CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-7ca97f0d685ab25559cf9b51cfc077eb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — A day after it recorded the most new daily cases since the start of the pandemic, Florida on Sunday broke a previous record for current hospitalizations set more than a year ago before vaccines were available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri hospital treats record number of patients...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-michael-brown-8b3940fe31b030bcbf17c96ff905eb94</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Mo. (AP) — A Springfield hospital reached a “sad new record” on Sunday when the number of coronavirus patients in its care rose to 187, an administrator said. CoxHealth CEO Steve Edwards urged residents via Twitter to get vaccinated “to protect others, to protect children, to protect our community.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House frustrated with 'hyperbolic' and 'irresponsible' coverage...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/07/30/media/variant-media-coverage-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter. You can sign up for free right here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
