<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DEAD HEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/canada-election-dead-heat-liberals-drop-candidate-2021-09-18/?taid=614620f7a5c42200013c4fa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's election is in a dead heat two days before the Sept. 20 vote, according to a new poll on Saturday, as Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and his Conservative rival both campaigned in the same seat-rich region to scour up votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahm Emanuel, target of left, may be rescued by Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rahm-emanuel-a-target-of-the-left-may-be-rescued-by-republicans/ar-AAOAotp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emanuel, Biden’s nominee for ambassador to Japan, has earned the hostility of many liberals during his long career. But some Senate Republicans say they will support his confirmation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ramps up plan to expel Haitian migrants gathered in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-mexico-texas-caribbean-immigration-9a95f12bd4e425bcdc87d38fa2cad298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — U.S. officials said Saturday that within the next three days, they plan to ramp up expulsion flights for some of the thousands of Haitian migrants who have gathered in a Texas city from across the border in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland volcanic eruption longest in half century...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210918-iceland-s-volcanic-eruption-the-longest-in-half-a-century</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iceland's volcanic eruption the longest in half a century</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Entire Presidential Agenda Rests on Expansive Spending Bill...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/18/bidens-entire-presidential-agenda-rests-on-expansive-spending-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — No president has ever packed as much of his agenda, domestic and foreign, into a single piece of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In escalation over sub deal, France recalls envoys from USA, Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/asia-pacific/australian-pm-says-he-made-clear-france-possibility-scrapping-submarine-deal-2021-09-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France plunged into an unprecedented diplomatic crisis with the United States and Australia on Friday after it recalled its ambassadors from both countries over a trilateral security deal which sank a French-designed submarine contract with Canberra.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran looks east after China-led bloc OKs entry...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210918-iran-looks-east-after-china-led-bloc-oks-entry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran looks east after China-led bloc OKs entry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would-Be NFT Millionaires Throw Dart and Usually Hit Dud...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-18/would-be-nft-millionaires-throw-a-dart-and-usually-hit-a-dud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As co-founder of a website tracking the spectrum of digital collectibles, Gauthier Zuppinger has seen it all. Drawings of toads, apes, abstract blobs, octopuses on heads, fire-breathing devils, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In red California, anger over recall blowout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-red-california-anger-over-recall-blowout-the-democratic-party-is-the-new-york-yankees/ar-AAOzZXG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's next for rural California, which heartily supported recalling Gov. Gavin Newsom?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big gap between PFIZER, MODERNA vaccines for preventing hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/big-gap-between-pfizer-moderna-034719881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna's COVID-19 vaccine does a significantly better job of preventing COVID-19 hospitalizations compared with Pfizer's shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics warn of tech giant 'chokepoint' repression...</title>
      <link>https://www.digitaljournal.com/tech-science/critics-warn-of-apple-google-chokepoint-repression/article</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.digitaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global dominance of tech giants serves as a convenient online chokepoint for authoritarian governments to crack down on dissent or rig elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One stunning afternoon: Setbacks imperil Biden reset...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-europe-business-health-france-516d7c24943c830823ff1602e4ab604e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It was an hour President Joe Biden would no doubt like to forget. On Friday, the Pentagon acknowledged that a drone strike in Afghanistan killed 10 civilians , including seven children, not terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Only 3% Prehistoric Humans Mated With Cousins -- Compared To 10% Today...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/prehistoric-humans-mated-cousins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex between cousins or second cousins has become over three times more common, according to an international team working on the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Filthiest Part Of Bathroom -- Towel Rack!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/bathroom-dirtiest-spot-towel-rack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find these common spots where towels hang to dry off are among the places people rarely clean while scrubbing the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 4.4 mag quake rattles Los Angeles...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/magnitude-44-earthquake-rattles-los-angeles-area-2021-09-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 4.4 earthquake shook Los Angeles shortly before 8 p.m. Pacific time on Friday (0300 GMT on Saturday), the United States Geological Survey said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's fraught politics leads to fear, scars, exits...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/572803-nations-fraught-politics-leads-to-fear-scars-and-exits</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation’s increasingly polarized politics are creating new fears for lawmakers and staff, a fact highlighted by Saturday’s planned rally at the Capitol where people will be demonstrating in support of those arres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian police clash with anti-lockdown protesters...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210918080701-ovyr6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 2, TV):UPDATE 2-Australian police clash with anti-lockdown protesters, arrest nearly 270</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unconventional Weapon Against Future Wildfires: Goats...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/18/the-unconventional-weapon-against-future-wildfires-goats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When megafires burn in unison and harsh droughts parch the West, local governments, utilities and companies struggle with how to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scientist and the A.I.-Assisted, Remote-Control Killer Robot...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/18/the-scientist-and-the-a-i-assisted-remote-control-killer-robot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran’s top nuclear scientist woke up an hour before dawn, as he did most days, to study Islamic philosophy before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Counting Antibodies 'Like Calories'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/18/some-rich-people-are-counting-their-antibodies-like-calories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Juhi Singh, 46, who owns a high-end wellness center on the Upper East Side, jetted off to the Amalfi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook Faces Surprising Employee Unrest at APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/17/tim-cook-faces-surprising-employee-unrest-at-apple/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — Apple, known among its Silicon Valley peers for a secretive corporate culture in which workers are expected</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious exemption may be difficult to obtain, as Amish case shows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/572756-religious-exemption-to-vaccine-mandates-may-be-difficult-to-obtain-as-amish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In our world of bureaucrats gone wild, what counts as a “sincerely held religious belief” is anything but simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Crisis Now Garbage Crisis, Too...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/18/the-covid-crisis-is-now-a-garbage-crisis-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across Brazil, recycling plants stopped running for months. In Uganda, a junkyard is short on reusable plastics. And in Indonesia’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: USA to expel migrants from border, fly to Haiti...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-migrants-haiti-del-rio-border-mexico-14cc4765f758df5aaf6fa546525416b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — The Biden administration plans the widescale expulsion of Haitian migrants from a small Texas border city by putting them on flights to Haiti starting Sunday, an official said Friday, representing a swift and dramatic response to thousands who suddenly crossed the border from Mexico and gathered under and around a bridge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police say they're ready for rally supporting Jan. 6 rioters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prisons-violence-capitol-siege-law-enforcement-agencies-us-national-guard-4dd5188eeb846965b88073f549982974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The fence around the Capitol is back up. The D.C. police department is at the ready, and U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London fashion week comes back to life;  Nerves remain...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/fashion/2021/sep/17/naomi-for-president-london-fashion-week-comes-back-to-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In-person events are part of industry’s ‘reset’ as models return to the catwalks and the party restarts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson and Lou Dobbs Job Reviews Sought in FOXNEWS Election Suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/tucker-carlson-and-lou-dobbs-job-reviews-sought-in-election-suit/ar-AAOyLQw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News may have to hand over the performance reviews of Tucker Carlson and other top on-air personalities if its foe in a defamation lawsuit over election rigging gets its way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Trump's CFO Won't Be Easy for New York Prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-17/turning-trump-s-cfo-won-t-be-easy-for-new-york-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Getting Donald Trump’s longtime chief financial officer to turn on his boss may prove tough, as Allen Weisselberg’s unlikely to get a lengthy sentence even if convicted on tax fraud and other charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Haven't Been This Down on Housing Market Since 1982!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/americans-haven-t-down-housing-174212114.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The last time Americans were this turned off by the U.S. housing market, borrowing costs were over five times the current rate. The share of people who think now is a good time to buy a home fell in September to 29%, extending the plunge from March when the proportion was more than twice as high, data from the University of Michigan consumer sentiment survey showed Friday. It’s also the smallest chunk of respondents since 1982.Back then, the average for a 30-year fixed rate mortga</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel sees highest-ever covid cases despite more than 80% of population vaxxed...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/health-ministry-chief-says-coronavirus-spread-reaching-record-heights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As over 10,000 new cases are diagnosed, Nachman Ash tells lawmakers he had hoped recent downward trend would continue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO 'LOST $27 BILLION'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3683077/tycoon-fortune-slashed-biggest-wealth-drops-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TYCOON has had his fortune slashed by a whopping $27 billion as China cracks down on tech firms. Chinese billionaire Colin Huang, the founder of the e-commerce platform Pinduoduo Inc (PDD) saw hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal workers can be fired for refusing vax, but must show up to work until their cases are determined...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/federal-workers-can-be-fired-for-refusing-vaccination-but-must-show-up-to-work-until-their-cases-are-determined-new-guidance-says/ar-AAOz6Yx?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The guidance follows a mandate for federal workers announced by President Biden last week as part of a series of measures to blunt the growth of the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 CIVILIANS DRONED IN LAST ACT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/17/politics/kabul-drone-strike-us-military-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A United States military investigation into a deadly Kabul drone strike on a vehicle in August has found it killed 10 civilians and the driver and that the vehicle targeted was likely not a threat associated with ISIS-K, announced Gen. Frank McKenzie, the top general of US Central Command, at the Pentagon on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA panel rejects PFIZER booster for general public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/17/fda-panel-begins-voting-on-pfizers-covid-booster-doses-rejecting-shots-for-general-public.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists continued debating the need for a third dose of the vaccines for older Americans, leaving open the possibility of other votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Biden berates Trump in private: 'What a f---ing ---hole'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Book-World-Trump-and-Biden-living-in-different-16468370.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Bob Woodward and Robert Costa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE remove Navalny app as elections begin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/572726-apple-google-remove-navalny-app-as-russian-elections-begin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An app created by allies of jailed Russian opposition leader Alexei Navalny that has drawn the ire of Russian authorities appeared to have been removed from Apple and Google stores Friday ahead of the country’s parl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Drops Drugs To Inmate In Prison Courtyard...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/09/16/drone-drops-drugs-into-orange-county-jail-courtyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bizarre delivery happened inside an Orange County jail courtyard when drugs were dropped off by a drone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska had the highest jab rate. Now it's rationing care...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/alaska-highest-vaccination-rate-now-covid-19-crisis/story?id=80037643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In January, Alaska had the highest per capita vaccination rate in the nation. Now, hospitals are overwhelmed with COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals get ready to grab wheel...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/17/liberals-progressives-democrat-agenda-512621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Congressional Progressive Caucus' chief says more than half her 96-member group is willing to block the Senate-passed infrastructure bill later this month without a separate party-line measure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chess icon sues NETFLIX over 'QUEEN'S GAMBIT'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/entertainment-arts-58600453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nona Gaprindashvili files a defamation lawsuit claiming she was incorrectly portrayed in the series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surrounded by controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/17/after-years-of-being-squeaky-clean-the-federal-reserve-is-surrounded-by-controversy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Reserve has a big meeting on tap next week, one that will be held under the cloud of an ethical dilemma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centenarians Reveal Secrets To Living Past 100: Active, Social, Optimistic...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/09/16/what-is-the-key-to-a-long-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's something that used to be rare, but it’s becoming much more common. More people are living to 100, especially in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken deletes tweet saying US would 'stand with people of Hong Kong'...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/blinken-deletes-tweet-saying-us-070259808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Secretary of State Antony Blinken deleted a tweet that said the United States would “stand with the people of Hong Kong”, a post in which he accused Beijing of weakening the city’s long-term political stability. He posted the message after seven Hong Kong opposition district councillors were disqualified this week, with authorities declaring that the oaths taken by them were invalid. A spokesman for the Chinese foreign ministry’s Hong Kong office issued a statement on Friday strongly opposing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France recalls envoys...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-58604677</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "exceptional decision" follows a pact between Australia, the US and UK, which scuppered a French deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER redirects 'Taiwan' search to 'China'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/twitter-cedes-taiwan-to-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has finally taken control of Taiwan, according to social networking giant Twitter, which redirects some searches for the word Taiwan to results for the word China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC restaurant host attacked over status request...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-texas-new-york-new-york-city-coronavirus-pandemic-355b61677d4996c42c11b1f12dd8106c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A host at a popular New York City restaurant was assaulted by three women from Texas after she asked for proof they had been vaccinated against COVID-19, police said. The three women punched the host at Carmine's on the Upper West Side repeatedly and broke her necklace Thursday afternoon after she asked for proof of vaccination, which is required to dine inside at a restaurant in New York City, police said in a news release.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
