<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T Ad Tech Interest Gets Madison Ave. Thumps Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/at-ts-interest-in-ad-tech-gets-thumbs-up-on-madison-avenue-1529692570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of AT&amp;T’s talks to acquire advertising tech firm AppNexus was welcomed by marketers, who are eager to have more options in the online ad sector beyond the dominant players Google and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAcTc-hFhYQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President meets with 'Angel Families'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/22/trump-meet-families-loved-ones-killed-illegals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid the outcry over illegal immigrant children separated from their families, President Trump is meeting at the White House Friday with “Angel Families” — U.S. citizens whose loved ones were killed by illegal immigrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parmesan Thefts Grate on Cheesemakers; 'Fort Knox' security measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/who-stole-my-cheese-parmesan-thefts-grate-on-italian-cheesemakers-1529682856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parmigiano-Reggiano thieves are driving producers to drastic measures, from installing alarm systems to a storing wheels in a bank’s secure warehouse; “This is Fort Knox for cheese.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Pride parades used to mean protests. Now an excuse for straight kids to party...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/LGBT-issues/2018/06/22/pride-parades-excuse-straight-kids-party/712068002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pride parades were born from radical protests. Recently, however, they've become the latest excuse for straight kids to party. Not everyone is happy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugmakers target growing male clientele with 'Brotox'...</title>
      <link>http://nationalpost.com/news/canada/not-just-for-women-cosmetic-targets-men-in-new-brotox-campaign-reports-gradual-increase-in-male-clients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In April, the drugmaker rolled out print, television and social media ads during baseball games and the Stanley Cup finals in attempt to lure male customers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex crimes alleged at Hawaii home for naked parties...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38482865/child-sex-crimes-prostitution-alleged-at-nuuanu-home-for-naked-parties</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Freedom House in upper Nuuanu advertises for parties like Naked Yoga.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For second year, Bernie earns $1,000,000+...</title>
      <link>https://vtdigger.org/2018/06/22/second-year-sanders-earns-1m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;vtdigger.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Parents grab baby after priest SLAPS it during baptism...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5875197/French-Catholic-priest-89-suspended-slapping-baby-baptisim-ceremony-Champeaux.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Footage of Father Jacques Lacroix, 89, slapping the baby boy at a church in Champeaux, near Paris, France was posted on Twitter yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masterpiece Mystery: Da Vinci 'earliest' work found after 600 years?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6597726/leonardo-da-vinci-first-ever-painting-discovered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEONARDO da Vinci’s first painting may have been unearthed by eagle-eyed sleuths who claim to have found a fascinating detail unnoticed for 600 years. Using infrared analysis, Italian experts…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver streaming HULU before fatal self-driving crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-uber-selfdriving-crash/uber-driver-was-streaming-hulu-show-just-before-self-driving-car-crash-police-report-idUSKBN1JI0LB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Tempe, Arizona said evidence showed the "safety" driver behind the wheel of a self-driving Uber was distracted and streaming a television show on her phone right up until about the time of a fatal accident in March, deeming the crash that rocked the nascent industry "entirely avoidable."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus-size models may fuel obesity epidemic, researchers claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/06/22/plus-size-clothing-overweight-models-may-fuel-obesity-epidemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The normalisation of 'plus-size' clothing and overweight models could be fuelling the obesity epidemic because it leads people to underestimate their own weight, a new study has shown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates engineered mosquitos kill each other using SEX...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6597909/bill-gates-mosquitos-kill-themselves-during-sex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICROSOFT founder Bill Gates is pouring £3million into a project to create killer mosquitoes that destroy each other through sex. It’s a bold bid to curb malaria, a deadly disease typically t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big brands drop social 'influencers' over fake follower fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/22/wane-social-media-influencers-big-brands-drop-stars-fears-fake/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appeal of social media &amp;ldquo;influencers&amp;rdquo; to advertise products may be slipping, as Unilever called for &amp;ldquo;urgent action&amp;rdquo; to address the problem of fake followers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON: END OF PELOSI REIGN?</title>
      <link>https://www.salon.com/2018/06/22/is-the-nancy-pelosi-era-coming-to-a-close-at-least-20-democrats-running-for-the-house-oppose-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trend may have caught fire following Conor Lamb's razor-thin in a special election in Pennsylvania this March</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says warrant necessary for phone location data...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/supreme-court-says-warrant-necessary-for-phone-location-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US justices say law enforcement needs a warrant to follow your digital footprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Erdogan faces biggest election challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkeys-master-campaigner-erdogan-faces-biggest-election-challenge-131243223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dominating Turkish politics for a decade and a half, President Tayyip Erdogan now faces his biggest electoral challenge, from a combative former teacher who has revitalised a dispirited opposition in less than two months. Turkey holds presidential and parliamentary elections on Sunday that are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation of Americans Entering Old Age Least Prepared in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-generation-of-americans-is-entering-old-age-the-least-prepared-in-decades-1529676033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Low incomes, paltry savings, high debt burdens, broken family structures, failed insurance—the U.S. is upending decades of progress in securing life’s final chapter. According to a Wall Street Journal tally, more than 40% of households headed by people aged 55 through 70 lack sufficient resources to maintain their living standards in retirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: For Love of God, Will Someone Put 'JURASSIC' Out of Its Misery?</title>
      <link>http://observer.com/2018/06/jurassic-world-fallen-kingdom-movie-review-please-just-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As brainless summer-escapism movies go, this one can’t go fast enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Hair extensions fly during wild brawl between women inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5872533/Shocking-moment-hair-extensions-flying-wild-brawl-four-women.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hair extensions went flying during a wild brawl inside a Walmart in Ohio. A shocking video shows the moment four women exchanged blows shortly after walking through the doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Hunting Serial Tip Jar Thief -- Who Flees In MERCEDES...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/police-hunt-for-tip-jar-thief-who-escapes-in-a-mercedes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grand total of loot taken from both businesses? Only $35.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France faces suit over no-sex rule for blood donations by gay men...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/france-faces-suit-over-no-sex-rule-blood-130322962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Frenchman has filed a discrimination suit at Europe's top rights court over a rule that requires gay men to refrain from having sex for a year before they donate blood, his lawyer said Friday. Laurent Drelon, 48, has been prohibited from giving blood several times since he first tried to do so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery extinct ape discovered in ancient tomb...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/22/mystery-extinct-ape-discovered-ancient-chinese-imperial-tomb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An entirely new species of ape has been discovered buried in an ancient tomb in central China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPEC strikes deal on production levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/22/opec-ministers-strike-deal-on-oil-production-levels.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPEC ministers meeting in Vienna have agreed on oil production levels for their countries and crude-producing nations cooperating with the cartel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caffeine protects heart?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/caffeine-protect-heart-helping-make-energy-mouse-study/story?id=56026309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The research builds on human studies that showed coffee has health benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing news costs companies $43.6 million -- every minute...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/disturbing-news-costs-u-s-companies-43-6-million-every-minute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers reading and dwelling on stories like those of immigrant children taken from parents harm productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelicals back self-styled top pimp...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/age-trump-evangelicals-back-self-styled-top-u-113200418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He styles himself as America's best-known pimp, a strip-club owner who runs multiple brothels and looks set to win a seat as a Republican in the Nevada legislature with the blessing of many conservative Christian voters. Meet Dennis Hof, whose political rise reflects fundamental changes in electoral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He 'has all the tapes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-mugs-trump-critic-tom-arnold-n885611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arnold is hunting for 'incriminating' tapes of Trump as part of a show for Vice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOM ARNOLD: Cohen and I are teaming up to take Trump down...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/393598-tom-arnold-cohen-and-i-are-teaming-up-to-take-trump-down </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian Tom Arnold said Friday that he and President Trump’s former, longtime personal lawyer are teaming up to “take down” the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: First summer in 20 years no comedy grosses $100 million...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/movies/la-ca-mn-comedy-box-office-struggles-20180622-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Studio comedies used to be a reliable staple of summer moviegoing. But, even as many proclaim we're in a golden age of comedy, lately the genre has been stumbling badly at the box office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Cities see spike in cheating spouses...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/22/cities-most-ashley-madison-accounts-cheating-husbands/720864002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheating husbands and wives might be most common in Seattle, Washington, according to a report from infidelity website Ashley Madison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Positive Death Movement Comes to Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/22/nyregion/the-positive-death-movement-comes-to-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death cafes, death doulas, ‘Ask a Mortician,’ DeathLab — once the province of goth subculture, death is having a moment in the sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKI publishes identities, info about ICE employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/WikiLeaks-publishes-identities-and-information-13016546.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks on Thursday published a database identifying more than 9,000 supposed current and former U.S. Immigration Customs Enforcement employees, saying it is important for "increasing accountability." The database contains the employees' publicly available personal information and job history scraped from LinkedIn, including deportation officers, IT workers, human resource interns and legal assistants, among others. The list includes their LinkedIn profile photos and information on educational background and the city and state where they're based.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, gender and social change: Cambodian blogger tackles taboos...</title>
      <link>http://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2018/06/22/sex-gender-and-social-change-cambodian-blogger-tackles-taboos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freemalaysiatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hosted on Facebook, the show by a 23-year-old Cambodian woman tackles the finer points of sex education, women's health and gender imbalances in a country where the #MeToo movement has barely registered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vomiting, headaches: At least 33 children fall ill at Florida camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/health/33-children-examined-after-getting-sick-at-lake-placid-4-h-camp/67-566530714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtsp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children at a summer camp in Highlands County are being monitored after falling ill, county officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Faces 'Unprecedented Threat' From China on Tech Takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-22/china-s-thousand-talents-called-key-in-seizing-u-s-expertise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s “Thousand Talents” program to tap into its citizens educated or employed in the U.S. is a key part of multi-pronged efforts to transfer, replicate and eventually overtake U.S. military and commercial technology, according to American intelligence officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirty Years On, How Well Do 'Global Warming' Predictions Stand Up?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/thirty-years-on-how-well-do-global-warming-predictions-stand-up-1529623442 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Hansen issued dire warnings in the summer of 1988. Today earth is only modestly warmer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shari Redstone's Path to Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shari-redstones-path-to-power-1529659921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the heiress overcame a falling out with her father to become the most significant female media owner in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busted flush: Fans spark plumbing pinch in World Cup bathroom dash...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/sport/busted-flush--japan-fans-spark-plumbing-pinch-in-world-cup-loo-dash-10459732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armchair Japan fans following their team's 2-1 World Cup win over Colombia risked triggering a plumbing disaster of biblical proportions when ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAUTHAMMER DEAD...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/21/charles-krauthammer-conservative-commentator-and-pulitzer-prize-winner-dead-at-68.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles Krauthammer, a longtime Fox News contributor, Pulitzer Prize winner, Harvard-trained psychiatrist and best-selling author who came to be known as the dean of conservative commentators, has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientist Claims Majority Of Diseases Caused By Negative Thoughts...</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/as-loneliness-rises-among-americans-experts-warn-its-making-many-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts weigh in on how loneliness has become a major problem today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAD:  GIRL ON 'TIME' COVER WAS NEVER SEPARATED FROM MOTHER...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5869829/Father-two-year-old-face-child-separation-crisis-speaks-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denis Javier Varela Hernandez said that he had not heard from his wife for a month until he saw the image of her and their daughter being apprehended in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROSEANNE' WITHOUT ROSEANNE GETS ABC GREENLIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/roseanne-spinoff-conners-officially-a-go-at-abc-1117397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After canceling the comedy following star Roseanne Barr's racist tweet, the Disney-owned network has found a way to move forward with the original cast, creators and likely crew as 'The Conners.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED MIDEAST PEACE PUSH IN EGYPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/kushner-egypts-sissi-discuss-israel-palestinian-peace-process/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian president calls for two-state solution, with East Jerusalem as Palestinian capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venomous Caterpillar Sends Teen To Emergency Room...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/venomous-caterpillar-sends-teen-to-emergency-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager in Florida experienced "the worst pain of his life" after coming in contact with a venomous caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sessions on the Bible and His Critics...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/politics/2018/june/i-dont-think-it-was-an-extreme-position-i-took-jeff-sessions-on-the-bible-immigration-and-his-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Jeff Sessions addressed some of the criticism he and the White House have received in recent weeks regarding the administration's immigration policy in an exclusive interview Thursday with CBN News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority Blame Illegal Parents For Crisis...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/rasmussen-parents-to-blame-border-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;54 percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unaccompanied Alien Children Charged in Execution-Style Murder, Media Calls Them 'Baby-Faced Boys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.judicialwatch.org/blog/2016/02/unaccompanied-alien-children-charged-in-execution-style-murder-media-calls-them-baby-faced-boys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.judicialwatch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears that the recent execution-style murder of a Massachusetts man was committed by two Central American teens that came to the U.S. as Unaccompanied Alien Children (UAC) under President Obama’s open border free-for-all. Tens of thousands of illegal immigrant minors—mostly from El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras—have entered the country through the Mexican border sinceRead the full post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Moving All Its Data to Top Secret Cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/06/nsa-systematically-moving-all-its-data-cloud/149179/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency is all-in on cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Canada uses massive US anti-terrorist database at borders...</title>
      <link>https://amp.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/21/canada-us-tuscan-anti-terrorist-database-at-borders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;amp.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuscan is separate from Canada’s official no-fly list and has more than 680,000 names provided to every border guard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST LADY FASHION FIREWORKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf927d4412604313af8ac0d81b8c540f/Melania-Trump-dons-'I-really-don't-care,-do-u?%27-jacket</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Melania Trump went to Texas to show she cared about migrant children. Her fashion choice carried a baffling counter-message.        The first lady wore a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Already Made Record $2B At Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-already-made-2-billion-domestic-box-office-this-year-black-panther-infinity-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Does West have will to survive?</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/has-the-west-the-will-to-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If you’re … pathetically weak, the country is going to be overrun with millions of people, and if you’re strong, then you don’t have any heart, that’s a tough dilemma. … I’d rather be strong.” So said President Donald Trump, on issuing his order halting the separation of children from parents caught breaking into the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST Won't Cover AMAZON Warehouse Conditions...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/democracy-dies-in-amazons-warehouses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why not?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Star NFL QB Suspension Looms Over UBER Groping Accusation...</title>
      <link>http://www.tampabay.com/blogs/bucs/2018/06/21/three-game-suspension-looms-for-bucs-qb-jameis-winston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA — The Bucs will open the upcoming season without the face of their franchise, as quarterback Jameis Winston will be suspended three games by the NFL for violating the league's personal co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist: WASH POST Killed Story Over Retweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/analysis/washington-post-twitter-apology.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacket Sends Message To Media...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-melanias-jacket-was-a-message-to-fake-news-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Military Aircraft Targeted By Lasers in Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-military-aircraft-targeted-by-lasers-in-pacific-ocean-u-s-officials-say-1529613999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials say pilots of American military aircraft operating in the Pacific Ocean have been targeted by lasers more than 20 times in recent months, incidents that follow a series of similar ones in which officials say Chinese personnel used lasers against American pilots in East Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Accuses NYT, WASH POST Of 'Irresponsible' Reporting...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/awkward/its-not-responsible-muellers-office-calls-out-new-york-times-for-incorrect-story-about-picking-manaforts-lock/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Electromagnetic Railgun War Ready By 2025...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/china-will-have-worlds-most-powerful-naval-gun-by-2025-us-intelligence-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The warship-mounted electromagnetic railgun is expected to enter China's arsenal by 2025, ahead of the U.S. and Russia, according to sources with direct knowledge of a U.S. intelligence report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Who  Wrote The Book On Corruption Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/crazy/judge-who-literally-wrote-the-book-on-corruption-indicted-on-fraud-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street slumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dow-drops-open-technology-stocks-boost-nasdaq-133905565--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - U.S. stocks fell on Thursday, with the Dow marking an eighth straight decline, as industrials wobbled again on trade war concerns while Amazon and other online retailers weakened after a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on state sales tax collection. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow extends 8 day losing streak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/us-stock-futures-data-trade-oil-and-politics-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Thursday as fears of an impending trade war between the U.S. and China dragged investor sentiment lower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELANIA SURPRISE BORDER VISIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/21/politics/melania-trump-border-visit-immigration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Melania Trump touched down in McAllen, Texas, Thursday making a publicly unannounced and hastily planned trip to get a first-hand look at the crisis affecting immigrant families at the US border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viruses may play a role in Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8e4ebccd8f09446d982eb63b85aafa9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Viruses that sneak into the brain just might play a role in Alzheimer's, scientists reported Thursday in a provocative study that promises to re-ignite some long</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
