<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FOX DUMPS DOBBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2021-02-05/fox-news-cancels-lou-dobbs-tonight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lou Dobbs remains under contract at Fox News but won't be back on the air after he hosted his last show Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG:  'We should be teleporting, not transporting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9229465/Mark-Zuckerberg-says-teleporting-not-transporting-believes-AR-VR-it.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Zuckerberg appeared in the audio-only social app Clubhouse to talk about VR and AR. He said the technology will help us 'teleport' to physical places - such as the office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Sized Security Despite Smallest Crowd; 70 Agencies Flanking Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/super-bowl-2021-security-tampa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seventy federal, state and local agencies will flank Raymond James Stadium for the Super Bowl's most sparsely attended game ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast Guru Resigns After Resurfaced Sex Harassment Accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/ny-times-caliphate-producer-andy-mills-resigns-after-resurfaced-sexual-harassment-accusations/ar-BB1dr0Qb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andy Mills, the New York Times audio producer who helped lead the now-discredited "Caliphate" podcast and has been accused of sexual harassment, has resigned. In a note posted to his personal website on Friday, Mills said he made "mistakes" in the past that he now looks back on with "extraordinary regret and embarrassment." Though he said he "strived to continue to grow and be a better co-worker and person" when at the Times, the accusations...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica's marijuana shortage branded 'cultural embarrassment'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/jamaicas-marijuana-shortage-branded-a-cultural-embarrassment-12209752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricanes, drought and the COVID-19 pandemic have all taken their toll on farmers and their crops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Brain-altering bioweapons' to DNA surveillance: The next threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/worse-than-covid-next-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most distressing topics researchers list is the immediate concern of DNA's use in government surveillance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Business Sought Stake In PARLER...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/ryanmac/trump-parler-ownership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents seen by BuzzFeed News show that Parler offered Trump 40% of the company if he posted exclusively to the platform. The deal was never finalized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NYTIMES Star Reporter Fired for 'Slur'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-times-star-reporter-fired-214228379.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DON EMMERTThe New York Times on Friday announced the ouster of science and health reporter Donald McNeil Jr., who The Daily Beast reported had allegedly used racist language while on a 2019 trip with students to Peru.McNeil, formerly the paper of record’s top reporter on COVID-19, leaves amid fallout from an incident that occurred during a Times-sponsored educational trip to Peru when he used the “n-word” and made other racist comments, according to complaints first reported by The Daily Beast. At least six students or their parents claimed McNeil had made racist and sexist remarks throughout the trip.“I should not have done that,” McNeil confessed in a Friday email shared with Times staff. “Originally, I thought the context in which I used this ugly word could be defended.”The science reporter further described the “n-word” incident as having occurred during a dinner discussion about the use of racial slurs, in which one student on the trip asked whether a classmate should have been suspended for using racist rhetoric in a video. “To understand what was in the video, I asked if she had called someone else the slur or whether she was rapping or quoting a book title. In asking the question, I used the slur itself,” McNeil wrote. He apologized for “extraordinarily bad judgment” to both the staff of the Times, singling out those he worked closely with, and to the students on the trip. “I am sorry. I let you all down.”McNeil’s departure comes just days after Times staffers wrote a letter to the paper’s top brass expressing outrage over the allegations that McNeil had used racial slurs; and over the response from Times leadership which the signees suggested was wholly insufficient.Baquet had previously said McNeil should be “given another chance” because his comments were not “hateful or malicious” in intent, but in a message to staff on Friday, the top editor wrote: “We do not tolerate racist language regardless of intent.”McNeil’s behavior on the trip had been hotly debated between Times staffers, including some who took part in a meeting with executive editor Dean Baquet and assistant managing editor Carolyn Ryan last Friday. At that meeting, Pulitzer Prize winner Nikole Hannah-Jones said she planned on calling the parents and students on the trip to determine what McNeil had said and in what context, according to people familiar with the situation.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arson suspected in massive fire at Texas courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-arson-courts-texas-896fbf8e5052512e62ad02fb94a24845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MASON, Texas (AP) — A suspect has been arrested been taken into custody following a massive fire that destroyed all but the rock outer walls of an 111-year-old Texas courthouse, an official...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamaica faces marijuana shortage...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/jamaica-faces-marijuana-shortage-farmers-struggle-75710269</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamaica is running low on ganja</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 5,077 deaths...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/05/us-records-record-5077-covid-deaths-after-audit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US recorded its deadliest day of the pandemic Thursday — tallying 5,077 COVID-19 deaths and exceeding the previous pandemic peak set in January by more than 600, according to Johns Hopkins Univ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dems, Republicans competing to throw cash at you...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/blog/meet-press-blog-latest-news-analysis-data-driving-political-discussion-n988541/ncrd1256872#blogHeader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden wants to send parents up to $300 a month per child. Sen. Mitt Romney wants to boost it to $350. They're both part of a broader trend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of no-ad advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/the-hottest-super-bowl-ad-trend-not-running-an-ad/ar-BB1dq0sG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a time and place for mourning an anthropomorphized legume, but the midst of a pandemic is not it. This is the short way of telling you that there will be no second attempt to kill off Mr. Peanut this year, after the advertising logo initially died in a pregame Super Bowl ad in 2020. Planters originally intended for Mr. Peanut's funeral to air during last year's Super Bowl — as the dramatic precursor to his Lazarus moment, when he was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas announce 6 new NETFLIX projects...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-9229287/Obamas-production-company-Netflix-announces-new-shows-movies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Higher Ground Productions, which President Barack Obama and Michelle Obama formed in partnership with Netflix, announced a new lineup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Americans Shouldn't Be Treated Like ISIS...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/02/05/americans-shouldnt-be-treated-like-isis-insurgents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adopting "counterinsurgency" tactics for use against wide swaths of Americans can only make the situation worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal divided over massive King of Hammers off-road event...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-news/article/Joshua-Tree-King-Hammers-Yucca-Valley-SoCal-15924814.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s good old-fashioned American freedom out here.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All New Orleans bars closed for Mardi Gras...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/news/politics/article_2abead06-67c3-11eb-adce-5b477745ca7b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bars will be closed, people will have to pass through checkpoints to get to major streets like Bourbon and Frenchmen streets and a heavy police presence will patrol New Orleans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First U.S. Funeral Home That Turns Bodies Into Compost Now Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93wmd5/the-first-us-funeral-home-that-turns-bodies-into-compost-is-now-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recompose, located outside of Seattle, has turned its first customers into soil after years of development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia to become first southern state to abolish death penalty...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/feb/05/virginia-first-southern-state-abolish-death-penalty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State house’s vote makes abolition assured, a historically important step since capital punishment emerged from the south as a legal alternative to lynching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder gained unauthorized access, entered jet at Andrews... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/02/05/intruder-gained-unauthorized-access-entered-c-40-jet-at-joint-base-andrews-home-of-air-force-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was arrested after gaining unauthorized access to Joint Base Andrews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going big, fast and alone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/senate-ok-fast-track-coronavirus-aid-c497b8cda93486d9f0a09abb88235291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden laid out the case Friday for moving fast and without Republicans, if necessary, to pass $1.9 trillion in coronavirus relief, armed with new signs of economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military grapples with widespread skepticism...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/us/survey-finds-military-families-less-trusting-of-the-coronavirus-vaccine-than-general-population-1.661092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of military families found just 33 percent would receive an approved coronavirus vaccine should it become available at no cost. A Gallup survey of the general U.S. population found 58 percent of respondents were willing to receive the vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops deploy for vaccine campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210205-us-covid-cases-down-61-since-peak-troops-deploy-for-vaccine-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Covid cases down 61% since peak, troops deploy for vaccine campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christopher Plummer Dead at 91...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/02/christopher-plummer-dies-91-sound-of-music-all-the-money-in-the-world-star-1234688379/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Plummer, who starred in The Sound of Music, won an Oscar for Beginners and was nominated for All the Money in the World and The Last Station, died peacefully today at his home in Connec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says next stimulus check with be for $1,400...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2276071/joe-biden-act-fact-stimulus-checks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Joe Biden vowed “to act fact” to get $1,400 stimulus checks to Americans after the new $1.9trillion Covid budget plan has passed. During a press briefing on Friday, Biden told…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients asphyxiate as Latin America battles oxygen crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210205-patients-asphyxiate-as-latin-america-battles-oxygen-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patients asphyxiate as Latin America battles oxygen crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER HUMAN?</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/02/05/tom-brady-legacy-beyond-the-scope-of-understanding-super-bowl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That Tom Brady is playing in his 10th Super Bowl at the age of 43 is a testament to the quarterback's indomitable drive to just keep winning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only fools bet against Brady. Or against Mahomes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-tampa-bay-buccaneers-super-bowl-football-coronavirus-pandemic-081ffc7ce4ccaf5f93fc418073559ff0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the dilemma prognosticators face for Sunday's Super Bowl: Only fools bet against Tom Brady. Or against Patrick Mahomes. So here we are, with an on-time NFL championship game...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filmmakers use secret interviews and archival material...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/woody-allen-scandal-mia-farrow-dylan-hbo-kirby-dick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Woody Allen scandal will again be brought into the spotlight, this time in a new, four-part docuseries, "Allen v. Farrow," coming Feb. 21</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of no-ad advertising...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/the-hottest-super-bowl-ad-trend-not-running-an-ad/ar-BB1dq0sG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Scandal to Get HBO Docuseries Treatment in 'ALLEN V. FARROW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/secret-explosive-woody-allen-doc-series-from-kirby-dick-amy-ziering-coming-to-hbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen v. Farrow goes behind decades of sensational headlines to reveal the private story of one of Hollywood’s most notorious and public scandals: the accusation of sexual abuse against Woody Allen involving Dylan, his then 7-year-old daughter with Mia Farrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed robber steals chicken from restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/angry-maskless-customer-armed-with-gun-robs-roscoes-chicken-waffles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pasadena police are looking for an armed robber who hit the Roscoe’s Chicken and Waffles on Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI Can Detect Emotion With Radio Waves...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2021/02/new-ai-can-detect-emotion-radio-waves/171863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are national security and privacy implications to an experimental UK neural network that deciphers how people respond to emotional stimuli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payrolls barely grow to start 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/05/jobs-report-january-2021.html'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodell gives 'greatest' tribute to Brady 5 years after suspending...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/02/05/sports/roger-goodell-gives-tribute-tom-brady-five-years-after-suspending-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All Brady has done since his suspension is qualify for four of the next five Super Bowls, including this weekend’s game between the Buccaneers and Chiefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAM IT THROUGH: KAMALA HARRIS BREAKS FIRST SENATE TIE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/senate-budget-resolution-advances-43b5f08b-bc93-470d-827e-0a1818b026cd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Harris served as the tie-breaking vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS Gets Sued Over Its Social Media Surveillance Tactics...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/dhs-sued-over-its-social-media-surveillance-tactics-1846092273</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security is being slammed with a new lawsuit after spending just over a year failing to respond to repeated attempts at investigating its long-term data hoovering practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Threatening, 'Menacing' People Who Paid Their Taxes: 'They're Freaked Out'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/02/04/irs-threatens-coloradans-who-already-paid-taxes-theyre-frightened-and-they-dont-understand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accountants along the Front Range are telling CBS4 that dozens of clients who paid their 2019 taxes are nonetheless getting menacing letters from the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why global travel unlikely to resume 'till 2024...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/coronavirus-in-israel-vaccination-doesnt-equal-liberation-657898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH AFFAIRS: Vaccination doesn’t equal liberation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago's Deep Feb Freeze Could Become Longest Cold Stretch on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/weather/chicagos-deep-february-freeze-could-become-longest-such-cold-stretch-on-record/2429315/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cold spell hitting the Chicago area this weekend isn’t going to let up anytime soon, and could become the longest stretch of such February temperatures the city has ever seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Wagers Fire Up Rally in Gambling Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/record-super-bowl-wagers-fire-up-rally-in-sports-gambling-stocks-60216.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Bowl will be the first time users in states like Colorado, Illinois, Michigan and Virginia can lawfully bet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Race war evident long before Capitol siege...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-news-race-and-ethnicity-conspiracy-theories-philanthropy-f8f793b94b0dd7e8ec62957dcbeb53d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A war rages on in America, and it didn’t begin with Donald Trump or the assault on the Capitol. It started with slavery and never ended, through lynchings and voter suppression, the snarling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Motherships To Launch Drone Swarms From Sea, Underwater, Air, Near-Space...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidhambling/2021/02/05/robot-motherships-to-launch-drone-swarms-from-sea-underwater-air-and-near-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metal Shark's unmanned vessel is just the latest for a swarms of attack drones -- new motherships in the form of robot submarines, unmanned jets and stratospheric balloons are also on the way as different arms race to equip with swarming drones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer model can determine whether you'll die...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-02-youll-die-covid-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artificial intelligence is able to predict who is most likely to die from the coronavirus. In doing so, it can also help decide who should be at the front of the line for the precious vaccines now being administered across Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Challengers Line up As Recall Threat Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/gavin-newsom-rivals-recall-petition-california-governor-1567078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several rivals have voiced their desire to stand against Newsom if a recall petition hits the required number of signatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears and trauma of being young, female and famous in '90s...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/britney-spears-and-the-trauma-of-being-young-female-and-famous-in-the-e2-80-9990s/ar-BB1dq01e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Framing Britney Spears," a new documentary, reframes the star’s rise in the sex-obsessed post-Clinton years and how it affects her current predicament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside story of how secretive billionaire masterminded biggest tax-evasion scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/christopherhelman/2021/02/05/americas-most-manipulative-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The inside story of how a secretive Texas billionaire allegedly masterminded America's biggest tax-evasion scheme, used "Darth Vader" contracts to overcharge Ford dealers and finance Robert F. Smith's private equity empire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dystopia Prime:' AMAZON AI van cameras spark surveillance concerns...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210205132207-c0mz7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Equipping Amazon's fleet of delivery vehicles with AI cameras could set a dangerous precedent for privacy, advocates say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Threats and Hate Force Hedge Funds to Step Up Security...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/death-threats-hate-force-hedge-125914926.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Hacking into an investment portfolio. Breaking into a Caribbean villa. Even -- it has happened -- kidnapping.To the list of personal-security concerns for hedge fund magnates, add one more: short positions.As millions of amateur investors, cheered on by social media, take on Wall Street, the uproar is changing the security calculus for some of the world’s wealthiest investors.The level of vitriol has experts wondering if merely owning a certain stock, or betting against it, might pose new safety risks.“We now say to clients, ‘Tell us about your positions,’” said Insite Risk Management President Christopher Falkenberg, a former Secret Service special agent whose company designs and implements risk-management programs for financial firms, funds and large nonprofits. “We’ve never done that before. And we have clients with short positions who are saying to us, ‘We need a new security program.’”Security worries for the rich are hardly new. One infamous example: Almost two decades ago, hedge fund billionaire Eddie Lampert was forced into the back seat of a Ford SUV and held hostage at a motel for 28 hours (he was released unharmed and the perpetrators were quickly caught).Read more: Extortion Charges Filed in Abduction of ESL’s LampertSecurity for Gold Coast mansions, St. Barts getaways, prized Picassos and more is, of course, routine, as are, in many cases, personal bodyguards. But the events of the past few weeks are about more than just money. It’s also an ideological battle against those seen as the Wall Street establishment.Gabe Plotkin, whose Melvin Capital Management lost billions shorting GameStop Corp., hired extra security for his family after he was the target of anti-Semitic slurs and other insults, according to people familiar with the matter. Billionaire Steve Cohen said his family received personal threats, prompting him to cancel his Twitter account.Read more: Melvin Lost 53% in January, Hurt by GameStop, Other Bets“The vitriol is more extreme, focusing not only on their stock positions but also their cultural positions,” Falkenberg said. “It becomes inherently more personal, and the trader becomes more of a personal enemy.”The sheer volume of people posting online -- the vast majority of whom merely type in rage and then move on -- makes it more burdensome to monitor and evaluate risks, he said. And the threats may linger even after a firm or person exits a particular trade.The threats coincide with a general increase in hostility toward institutions, said Falkenberg, who drew parallels to the Jan. 6 storming of the U.S. Capitol by those who refused to accept that then-President Donald Trump had lost the election.QuickTake: What to Know About Trump’s Second Impeachment Trial“Even if they unwound the trades, they represent the establishment,” he said. “This is going to change things for our clients.”While spending on security is routine for hedge funds, much of their attention in the past had been focused on cybersecurity, Falkenberg said. But even before the events of the past month, his clients had begun to bulk up their physical defenses at home, where they’ve been spending more time than ever because of the pandemic.The online zealotry also prompted one of Wall Street’s most venerated contrarians, Citron Research founder Andrew Left, to alter course. He announced that his firm would no longer publish short-selling research after an enraged mob of investors threatened him and his family. Citron had previously suspended a live-stream event because too many people were hacking its Twitter account.“I’ve never seen such an exchange of ideas of people so angry about someone joining the other side of a trade,” Left said in a video.Read more: Wall Street’s Bounty Hunter Abandons Short Selling ResearchHis capitulation prompted discussions in the short-selling world about whether there was still room for them to publish reports criticizing companies.Still, not everyone is giving up. On Thursday, Clover Health Investments Corp., the health insurer backed by Chamath Palihapitiya, tumbled after Hindenburg Research published a report that said the firm misled investors.Clover said Friday that it received a notice of investigation from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission. The company believes the inquiry is based on Hindenburg’s report, which is “rife with ad-hominem attacks, sweeping inaccuracies and gross mischaracterizations,” Clover said in a filing.Read more: Clover Says SEC Started a Probe in Wake of Hindenburg ReportShort sellers have long been the subject of opposition from those who disagree. Some companies they targeted used scare tactics or sought to discredit them through teams of lawyers, PR professionals or private investigators.Some short sellers, who asked not to be identified because they feared for their safety, described previous death threats, attempts to hack their phones, people trying to enter their offices and obscene messages sent to spouses.But sometimes it goes further. In 2019, the Financial Times reported how investors who bet against German payments firm Wirecard AG were under surveillance, including from a group led by a former Libyan intelligence chief.Matthew Earl, an early critic of Wirecard, said a suspicious car once followed his young son and nanny and took pictures of them, and that he was being watched from vehicles parked outside his home -- once they even accosted him at his front door.“It was a lurking constant threat,” he said. “It’s very traumatic, and psychologically it’s very difficult to deal with.”(Updates with Secret Service in fifth paragraph, Clover comment in 18th.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC reports 618 variants across 33 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/02/05/covid-news-cdc-coronavirus-variant-cases-fda-vaccines/4395234001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California lawmakers aim to reopen Disneyland, other theme parks. FDA preps for "all eventualities" of virus variants. Latest COVID-19 news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies charging hidden 'covid fees.' May be illegal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/companies-are-charging-hidden-e2-80-98covid-fees-e2-80-99-to-make-up-for-lost-profits-they-may-be-illegal/ar-BB1dqdfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys general and consumers say surcharges between $5 and $1,200 are being charged to cover PPE and cleaning at dentist offices, restaurants and senior living facilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Plotting revenge tour targeting defectors'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9227607/Donald-Trump-plotting-campaign-revenge-tour-targeting-disloyal-Republicans.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strategists at Trump's Florida Mar-a-Lago private resort where he now lives are planning potential trips against GOP members who voted in support of his removal from office, sources have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate approves budget bill as Harris casts tie-breaker vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-coronavirus-pandemic-bills-kamala-harris-c497b8cda93486d9f0a09abb88235291</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Senate early Friday approved a measure that would let Democrats muscle President Joe Biden’s $1.9 trillion coronavirus relief plan through the chamber without Republican...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Preparing To Blitz Moon?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/china-preparing-blitz-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm 'Switch' Would Allow Men To Turn Fertility On And Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sperm-switch-men-control-fertility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experiments on mice find the "winner" who fertilizes the egg carries a set of toxic mutations that poison rival sperm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force investigating intruder at Joint Base Andrews, home to Air Force One...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/us-air-force-investigating-intruder-joint-base-andrews/story?id=75702407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Air Force is investigating an incident of an intruder at Joint Base Andrews, which houses Air Force One, the aircraft that carries the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Super Bowl classic!</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/lebron-v-jordan-brady-mahomes-013427685.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The greatest quarterback in NFL history faces off with the pretender to his throne on Sunday when Tom Brady and Patrick Mahomes go head-to-head in a Super Bowl clash of generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hug tent' provides safe embraces at elderly home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-colorado-coronavirus-pandemic-denver-suburbs-8d97da7f60ac0da30d04e22abd84a5f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOUISVILLE, Colo. (AP) — Lynda Hartman needed a hug. It had been at least eight months since she touched her 77-year-old husband, Len, who has dementia and has been at an assisted living...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ads aim to comfort and connect...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-awkwafina-super-bowl-will-ferrell-football-b61073098231118a22ee9b3a8fa951fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Super Bowl ads each year offer a snapshot of the American psyche. And this year, it's a doozy. After a year of pandemic fear and isolation, a tumultuous election capped by a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party eyes path to power by making peace with far right...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-new-york-conspiracy-theories-impeachments-john-thune-5f4b9e7f7a4a20894905981817c47011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Over the course of 24 hours this week, House Republicans voted to defend a freshman conspiracy theorist with a history of violent rhetoric and a mainstream party leader who backed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Will Pandemic End? Jab Calculator Shows 7 Years!</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/when-will-life-return-to-normal-in-7-4-years-at-todays-vaccine-rates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There Are Spying Eyes Everywhere -- and Now They Share Brain...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/there-are-spying-eyes-everywhere-and-now-they-share-a-brain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Security cameras. License plate readers. Smartphone trackers. Drones. We’re being watched 24/7. What happens when all those data streams fuse into one?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax faction that shut down DODGER STADIUM not done...</title>
      <link>https://www.register-herald.com/cnhi_network/radical-anti-vaccine-faction-that-shut-down-dodger-stadium-says-it-is-not-finished/article_f0970ece-6750-11eb-9707-2fe3e8f74222.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.register-herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A year ago, before coronavirus changed the world, stand-up comedian Jason Lefkowitz was shopping a script, working three nights a week as a Beverly Hills waiter and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporting or rioting? Grand jury indicts pair from insurrection who claim they're journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/reporting-or-rioting-grand-jury-indicts-pair-from-insurrection-who-claim-they-re-journalists/article_6b12b5db-c6b3-5503-9ac6-9da3b6010d58.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — Two men who claimed they were covering the Capitol riot as journalists were indicted by a federal grand jury this week in connection with the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Age Jocks: Superstar Athletes Getting Mystical...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/new-age-jocks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Athletes have always been superstitious. Are manifestation parties and smudge sticks the new frontier of peak performance?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing warns off US warship from South China Sea islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/beijing-warns-off-us-warship-from-south-china-sea-islands-01612524915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Friday warned off a US warship sailing near contested islands in the South China Sea, Beijing said, the first such encounter made public since the inauguration of President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia alliance in Georgia signals new phase for extremist paramilitaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/militia-alliance-in-georgia-signals-new-phase-for-extremist-paramilitaries/UD2JMQV5A5EABHHAKBQZBK2IVY/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leader of a private Georgia paramilitary group that provided security for Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene said he has formed alliances with other far-right groups to advocate for Georgiaâ€™s secession from the United States, following the arrests of participants in the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SASSE: Republicans must decide between 'conservatism and madness'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/537476-gop-senator-warns-his-party-must-decide-between-conservatism-and-madness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ben Sasse (R-Neb.), who's said he may vote this month to convict former President Trump on an article of impeachment, is pushing back against possible retaliation from the Nebraska Republican State Central Committee by warning that his party must choose between “conservatism and madness.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thomas makes history as first female official...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thomas-makes-history-first-female-011346968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Thomas will blaze a trail for female officials everywhere on Sunday when she becomes the first woman to officiate at the Super Bowl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>*EXIT END OF YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/jeff-zucker-staying-cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Zucker, the president of CNN and head of WarnerMedia news and sports, will continue in that role at least through the end of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: COVID cases cut in HALF...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9226829/COVID-cases-cut-HALF-Seven-day-average-nearly-50-peak-January-12.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The seven-day average for new COVID-19 cases in the United States has fallen by 47.5 percent to 130,569 since its peak on January 12 when it was close to 250,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER STICKS WITH CNN*...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cnn-chief-jeff-zucker-stay-140130599.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After contemplating leaving while the channel is on top, the CNN president will work through his contract.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
