<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit hits ANOTHER record...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1923752000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government spent a record $1,923,752,000,000 in the first four months of fiscal 2021 (October through January), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For decades Trump bullied Palm Beach to get his way. Now he's determined to make it home...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/article/For-decades-Donald-Trump-bullied-Palm-Beach-to-15942737.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night in late January 1994, fireworks sparkled in the sky above Mar-a-Lago, a grand...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Prophets on Rise. What Happens When They're Wrong?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/11/christian-prophets-are-on-the-rise-what-happens-when-theyre-wrong/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeremiah Johnson, a 33-year-old self-described prophet, was one of the few evangelical Christians who took Donald J. Trump’s political future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pileup Involving 100 Vehicles Traps Drivers, Shuts Down TX Interstate...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/02/11/pileup-100-cars-trucks-trapped-drivers-interstate-35w-fort-worth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fort Worth police spokesperson Officer Daniel Segura has confirmed at least 3 people were killed in the crash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperation grows in battered Honduras, fueling migration...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/honduras-hurricane-iota-mexico-storms-immigration-3cf340e556ee767d1dd3dce351c934b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN PEDRO SULA, Honduras (AP) — Nory Yamileth Hernández and her three teenage children have been living in a battered tent under a bridge on the outskirts of San Pedro Sula since Hurricane Eta...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems will wrap prosecution with Donald's 'lack of remorse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/democrats-will-wrap-prosecution-with-trumps-lack-of-remorse-after-capitol-attack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats will conclude a final day of arguments in former President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial by highlighting his “lack of remorse,” following the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol by hundreds of his supporters, and the impact of the deadly and destructive incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-day-3-2021-02-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment managers plan to examine the aftermath of the Capitol attack on the third day of the trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home Prices Post Record Gain, Topping Peak From 2005...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-11/u-s-home-prices-post-14-9-jump-in-pandemic-real-estate-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson Sponsors Face New Boycott Calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tucker-carlson-floyd-boycott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carlson asserted on his Wednesday night Fox News primetime program that George Floyd died of a drug overdose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Shelley Duvall: Reclusive Icon on Fleeing Hollywood and Scars of Making 'SHINING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/searching-for-shelley-duvall-the-reclusive-icon-on-fleeing-hollywood-and-the-scars-of-making-the-shining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After leaving L.A., and making only one public appearance since — on a widely condemned mental illness episode of 'Dr. Phil' — the complicated actress sat down for a conversation with The Hollywood Reporter about her legacy and the trauma of the Stanley Kubrick film: "To wake and realize that you had to cry all day, I don’t know how I did it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden ghosting Bibi?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/israelis-ask-why-hasn-e2-80-99t-the-us-president-called-their-prime-minister-yet/ar-BB1dBbXe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three weeks into Biden’s term, some are ready to declare a diplomatic snub.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ZOOM Town Boom in Bozeman, Montana...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-02-11/the-zoom-town-boom-in-bozeman-montana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal from 'habitable planet' found by scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/alien-hope-signal-habitable-planet-23483061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential planet is in a "habitable zone" of Alpha Centauri, a binary star system 4.37 light-years away from Earth, and could have liquid water on its surface</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap old homes draw millennials escaping pandemic cages...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211115836-p6nqm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CHEAP HOMES (TV, PIX):Cheap old homes draw millennials escaping pandemic cages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Actress fired from 'MANDALORIAN' after social media post...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-gina-carano-social-media-the-holocaust-16a438e51f1c0fd1ca96ba163021caf8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Lucasfilm says Gina Carano is no longer a part of “The Mandalorian” cast after many online called for her firing over a social media post that likened the experience of Jews...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S3F1vZYpH8c&amp;t=2s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Creating convincing digital humans has traditionally been hard, slow, and expensive. With MetaHuman Creator, the time to create a unique digital human of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 4 In 10 Republicans Say Violence May Be Necessary...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/02/11/966498544/a-scary-survey-finding-4-in-10-republicans-say-political-violence-may-be-necessa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll shows significant support in the U.S. for political violence. Most white evangelicals and Republicans say Biden's election was illegitimate and Trump was not behind the attack on the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now out of office, The Don may face tax questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/now-out-of-office-trump-may-have-to-face-tax-questions/ar-BB1dB2mE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether or not Trump is convicted at his impeachment trial, he faces an IRS decision on a massive refund and may no longer be able to conceal his tax returns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company just made it shockingly easy to create lifelike people...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90603474/the-company-behind-fortnite-just-made-it-shockingly-easy-to-create-life-like-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Realistic-looking humans are becoming easier and easier to make from thin air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED PLANET: Mars mission inspires growing fan base back in China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-beijing-china-planets-mars-77509554dcb24ebd5b7bf5c155515cfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Cui Tingting dyed her hair Mars red for the arrival of China’s spacecraft at the planet known in Chinese as the Fire Star. “This is a great era for space, and the future of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How leading anti-Trump group ignored crisis in its ranks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-b14be5f06588b8f1d78125d4141394cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Last June, the Lincoln Project was on a high. Led by several prominent former Republican consultants, its slickly produced ads attacking President Donald Trump made it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUNDER ROAD: Springsteen DWI arrest 'after drinking one shot of tequila in front of cops'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/14016718/bruce-springsteen-dwi-arrest-shot-tequila-front-of-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUCE Springsteen was arrested for DWI after doing only one shot of tequila with fans. The Born To Run singer was booked in November, though news of the incident only broke yesterday. But it has no…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MATRIX'-style bracelets turn humans into batteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSKBN2AA2KV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a move that will give chills to fans of the dystopian movie "The Matrix", scientists have developed a wearable device that could use the human body to replace batteries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obesity drug cuts weight 20%; 'Game-changer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/health/new-obesity-fighting-drug-could-23481754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New obesity-fighting drug semaglutide could cut body weight by up to 20%. The average participant in the trial lost nearly three stone - with the new drug being called a 'game-changer'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broke Americans stripping down on ONLYFANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hulu-explores-why-americans-are-stripping-down-on-onlyfans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ABC News Original documentary on Hulu explores how the sex worker-friendly subscription service boomed during the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oh Naaaaaaancy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/capitol-rioters-searched-for-nancy-pelosi-in-a-way-that-should-make-every-woman-e2-80-99s-skin-crawl/ar-BB1dAkp4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Oh Naaaaaaancy’ became an ominous tune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROUD BOY BLAMES PRESIDENT</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/proud-boys-member-tells-court-trump-to-blame-for-inciting-capitol-riot/ar-BB1dztqO?dpir=1&amp;ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of the far-right Proud Boys charged for his role in the riot at the U.S. Capitol blamed former President Donald Trump for his conduct, claiming he was “misled by the president’s deception.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S WORDS COME BACK TO HAUNT HIM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-riots-trials-impeachments-db62d4da8ab8233acd32244006e8c99d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democrats opened their first day of arguments in former President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial Wednesday with searing footage of the U.S. Capitol riot as they painted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's followers 'wanted to lynch the VP'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9246189/Democrats-say-Donald-Trump-reveling-bloodshed-MAGA-riot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats began their prosecution of former President Donald Trump , laying the ground work for their accusation he should be impeached for inciting the January 6th MAGA riot on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of former Republican officials in talks to form  third party...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210211013256-gp1g4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/PARTY (EXCLUSIVE, PIX):EXCLUSIVE-Dozens of former Republican officials in talks to form anti-Trump third party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Misled by the President's deception'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210210220817-pz76c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/CAPITOL-ARRESTS (PIX):U.S. judge orders detention for alleged Proud Boy who blames Trump for Capitol riots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting tech company set to sue NEWSMAX?</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-smartmatic-newsmax-fox-defamation-20210210-asy2scwn2vchblt6pphxhvswnq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The voting technology company Smartmatic, pilloried by former President Donald Trump’s supporters in the conservative media world, has already gone after the most prominent player —Fox News — with an eye-popping $2.7 billion defamation suit. Newsmax, the smaller-but-surging presence in right-wing media, could be next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In historic first, women begin boot camp at Marine Corps Recruit Depot San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2021-02-09/in-historic-first-women-begin-boot-camp-at-marine-corps-recruit-depot-san-diego</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new integrated company is the first step toward fully integrating the Corps' West Coast boot camp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Use Trump's Words to Build Impeachment Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-use-video-trumps-words-to-build-impeachment-case/ar-BB1dA8Hu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Democrats showed chilling new video of the storming of the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6 as they portrayed the siege and assault on Congress as the inevitable result of former President Donald Trump stoking rage among his supporters over his defeat in the election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's self-employment expansion leaves key sectors out  --  including independent journalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/cubas-self-employment-expansion-leaves-key-sectors-out-e2-80-94-including-independent-journalism/ar-BB1dAizV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A much-anticipated expansion of the private sector in Cuba will not include a wide range of professional services, wholesale trade or major industries like sugar and tobacco and prohibits the creation of media outlets, according to a list of banned activities published Wednesday. The government will also not allow competition with the state in other vital sectors such as health care, education ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New push for slavery reparations commission in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Uncomfortable-truth-The-new-push-for-a-slavery-15939436.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weeks after Democrats took control of Congress and the White House, a Black lawmaker is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Prosecutors Open Criminal Investigation of Donald's Call...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/fultons-da-opens-criminal-investigation-into-trump-demand-to-overturn-election/YWJPS4B4BREHDLHQCZYDDWBVIA/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fulton County’s top prosecutor launched a wide-ranging criminal investigation into Donald Trump’s efforts to reverse his presidential election defeat in Georgia, sending letters to state officials urging them to preserve documents related to his demand that Secretary of State Brad Raffensperger “find” enough votes to overturn the outcome.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UC Berkeley  bans OUTDOOR exercise...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/uc-berkeley-tightens-covid-19-013612120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UC Berkeley has banned outdoor exercise and extended dorm lockdowns after more than 160 people tested positive for COVID-19 the coronavirus in the first week of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST AMENDMENT CHAMPION</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/larry-flynt-built-porn-empire-233605744.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was shot and left paralyzed in 1978 by a white supremacist as he was arriving for an obscenity trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Preps Movie About Murderous Sex Robot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/florence-pugh-dolly-movie-murderous-sex-robot-apple-tv-plus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vanessa Taylor and Drew Pearce are writing the script for Apple TV+'s sci-fi courtroom drama "Dolly" with Florence Pugh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger inside NYT as divided newsroom erupts in debate over recent controversies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/10/media/new-york-times-donald-mcneil-andy-mills/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departure of two high-profile journalists from The Times has spurred what some staffers have described as unprecedented levels of divisiveness and controversy inside the newsroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget deficit hits ANOTHER record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-8b942743cca428374f52d0b05c77c142</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. government's budget deficit hit $735.7 billion through the first four months of the budget year — an all-time high for the period — as a pandemic-induced recession cut...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial video shows vast scope, danger...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trump-impeachment-trial-update-2-10-2021-4f49705a5f92bd4129941ec409642ecd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Prosecutors unveiled chilling new security video in Donald Trump’s impeachment trial on Wednesday, showing the mob of rioters breaking into the Capitol, smashing windows and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLYNT DEAD AT 78</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/larry-flynt-dead-0ae38f6dca115aed20cb88d5fc547e99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Porn purveyor Larry Flynt, who built Hustler magazine into an adult entertainment juggernaut that included casinos, films, websites and other enterprises as he relentlessly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS abruptly cuts off impeachment manager during testimony...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-television-trials-eric-swalwell-impeachments-4fa2686e7bfd558d650f8c8801a130dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fox News Channel cut off an impeachment manager in mid-sentence Wednesday as he was presenting dramatic video footage of the mob attacking the U.S. Capitol last month and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95 YEAR OLD charged with murder in assisted living...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boulder-shootings-d2a08410e554bb7298f69c72d7e311aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 95-year-old resident of an assisted living facility accused of shooting and killing a maintenance worker has been charged with first-degree murder. The suspect, Okey Payne, appeared in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's own impeachment lawyer  'called him a f***ing crook'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9243289/Donald-Trumps-impeachment-lawyer-Michael-van-der-Veen-called-f-ing-crook-sued-him.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael van der Veen, 57, is one of three lawyers representing Trump at his impeachment trial. On Tuesday it emerged van der Veen had disparaged Trump, donated to Democrats and sued him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORN KING</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Larry-Flynt-porn-king-and-self-styled-First-15940968.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Flynt, one of America's most notorious pornographers and self-proclaimed champions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST AMENDMENT CHAMPION</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210210221948-neblh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PEOPLE-LARRY FLYNT/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Larry Flynt, porn publisher and free speech activist, dead at 78 -Washington Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY FLYNT DEAD AT 78...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/02/10/larry-flynt-dead-dies-hustler-founder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Flynt -- the famous and controversial publisher known for launching a porn empire -- has died ... TMZ has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence evacuating...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/live-news-updates/2021/02/09/trump-impeachment-trial-live-updates-online-coverage-highlights-210209</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest news, headlines, analysis, photos and videos on Live updates: Trump impeachment trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEEP scraps ad...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9247265/Jeep-SCRAPS-Bruce-Springsteens-Super-Bowl-ad-arrested-DWI-reckless-driving.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Springsteen's Jeep ad has been pulled from company's YouTube page. The 71-year-old singer was arrested for DWI in Sandy Hook, New Jersey, on November 14, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is 1 day a week enough? Biden school goal draws blowback...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-jen-psaki-6de489a8be366b836067a6acd8528912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is being accused of backpedaling on his pledge to reopen the nation’s schools after the White House added fine print to his promise and made clear that a full reopening is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play deadliest moment inside Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/live-blog/trump-impeachment-live-updates-democrats-deliver-arguments-senate-trial-n1256974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House impeached Trump last month for his role in the Jan. 6 Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to start paying UK news publishers for content...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/10/google-to-start-paying-uk-news-publishers-for-content/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google is rolling out a plan to pay for news to the UK. The web search giant, which has been under pressure to share digital ad revenue with web content providers that drive traffic to its services…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage shows moment officer diverted Romney from rioter's path...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/trump-impeachment-trial-02-10-2021/h_f3c310e7fb2df7ff2e468d433ecca4d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House impeachment managers present their case against former President Trump in the second day of the Senate trial. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad tech company that bought MYSPACE surges 90% in IPO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/10/viant-dsp-ipo-shares-surge-90percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viant saw shares pop significantly after the company launched its initial public offering Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOMBED BRADY?</title>
      <link>https://www.thebiglead.com/posts/tom-brady-drunk-buccaneers-super-bowl-victory-boat-parade-01ey6tz8qhxd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebiglead.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady may have been drunk at the Tampa Bay Buccaneers Super Bowl LV victory parade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC subway ad pops up for ridiculed lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/we-ll-make-rudy-giuliani-look-good-nyc-subway-ad-pops-up-for-trump-lawyers-ridiculed-over-impeachment-defense/ar-BB1dzX5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“IMPEACHED? Will literally no one represent you? Call Castor &amp; Schoen,” reads the fake ad, which was spotted on a C train in lower Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tosses Lombardi Trophy to another boat during parade!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/10/tom-brady-throws-lombardi-trophy-during-super-bowl-boat-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This was the boldest pass of Tom Brady’s career. During the Tampa Bay Buccaneers’ boat parade Wednesday on the Hillsborough River to celebrate their Super Bowl 2021 victory, the 43-year…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAKEUP:  FOXNEWS Moves Gutfeld Moves to Weekday Nights...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/just-in-greg-gutfeld-moves-to-weekday-nights-on-fox-news-replacing-a-news-hour/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News is replacing its 11 p.m. news show, Fox News at Night with Shannon Bream, with Greg Gutfeld.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY BOMB...</title>
      <link>https://www.barstoolsports.com/blog/3333029/tom-brady-seems-to-be-having-a-very-good-time-in-tampa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barstoolsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well deserved, Tommy. Well deserved.  PS: Hilarious.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire risks at nuke lab...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/wildfires-los-alamos-environment-fires-new-mexico-df654c925182c1ef289e2c0f80f7aa56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — One of the nation’s premier nuclear laboratories isn’t taking the necessary precautions to guard against wildfires, according to an audit by the U.S. Energy Department’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivery Apps Using Child Labor...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3v5xx/delivery-apps-are-using-child-labor-in-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor inspectors found underage youths delivering for Rappi, but the problem extends to Uber Eats and other delivery apps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawley ignores; Sits in gallery reviewing paperwork...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/trump-loyalist-josh-hawley-ignores-impeachment-trial-evidence-by-sitting-in-gallery-to-review-paperwork/ar-BB1dzR2i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senator Josh Hawley, a bellwether of Donald Trump's "stop the steal" movement to overturn the 2020 election results, was watching the second day of impeachment proceedings against the former president from the gallery above the chamber. The Trump loyalist, a first-term Missouri Republican, was seen at various points with his legs crossed, his feet propped up on the chair in front of him, and reviewing some sort of paperwork in a manila folder,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado shatters marijuana sales record...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/feb/10/colorado-marijuana-sales-shatter-record-with-219-b/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado’s first-in-the-country recreational marijuana industry reported nearly $2.2 billion in sales during 2020, and more than $10 billion since it started in early 2014, regulators said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA SAYS NO!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/sports/nba-requiring-national-anthem-mark-cuban-mavs-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA is requiring that all teams play the national anthem before games “in keeping with longstanding league policy,” just one day after Dallas Mavericks owner Mark Cuban told The Athletic the team decided not to play it at home games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  Real Unemployment Rate 10%!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/10/fed-chair-powell-citing-bleak-jobs-picture-says-policy-will-need-to-stay-patiently-accommodative.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addressing the jobs issue will require a "patiently accommodative monetary policy that embraces the lessons of the past."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases falling. Could be calm before variant-driven storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/02/10/covid-19-cases-are-falling-variant-driven-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask experts how the B.1.1.7 coronavirus variant might reshape the U.S. epidemic and you’ll hear “it depends” or “it’s the wild card."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Rips Biden Appointee Mean Tweets: 'You've Called [Bernie] Everything BUT an Ignorant Slut!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/sen-john-kennedy-rips-biden-appointee-neera-tandens-mean-tweets-youve-called-senator-sanders-everything-but-an-ignorant-slut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John Kennedy (R-LA) grilled Neera Tanden, President Joe Biden's appointee for director of the Office of Management and Budget, on her past tweets, faulting her for calling Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-VT) "everything but an ignorant slut."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot Stock Shorts Smoked As REDDIT Raiders Chase Prices Higher...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/10/cannabis-stocks-soar-as-reddit-crowd-that-spiked-gamestop-jumps-in-tilray-surges-25percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trio of cannabis companies are garnering attention from the same Reddit army that contributed to the epic short squeeze in GameStop last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery Russian bought most expensive Florida home for $140M in cash...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/10/mystery-russian-bought-most-expensive-florida-home-for-140m-cash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palm Beach manse is located on land once owned by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ANNUAL' COVID SHOT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/09/covid-vaccine-jj-ceo-says-people-may-get-annual-shots-for-the-next-several-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People may need to get vaccinated against Covid-19 annually, just like seasonal flu shots, over the next several years, J&amp;J CEO Alex Gorsky told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrible defense left senators stunned and perplexed....</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article249145995.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They did everything they could but to talk about the question at hand.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald eagle found in Missouri with 2 bullet wounds dies after attempted surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksdk.com/article/news/crime/bald-eagle-shot-in-washington-county-conservation-officials-need-tips/63-716b354e-6fc6-4e27-8e59-251e704084d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksdk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bald eagle had to be euthanized due to severe tissue and bone damage, MDC confirmed. The shooting happened in southern Washington County earlier this month</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC recommends wearing TWO masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-90ef98d5047318c2e95fafc1e78f594e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. government researchers found that two masks are better than one in slowing coronavirus spread, but health officials stopped short of recommending that everyone double...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Third of adults skeptical of shots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-norc-poll-3rd-adult-skeptical-vaccine-3779574a6d45d38cfc1d8615eb176b2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — About 1 in 3 Americans say they definitely or probably won’t get the COVID-19 vaccine, according to a new poll that some experts say is discouraging news if the U.S. hopes to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'UFO' off Florida coast turns out to be Navy missile test...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2305144/florida-ufo-navy-missile-test-biden-bombers-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FLASH in the South Florida sky on Tuesday evening had some spectators thinking they saw a UFO – but it turned out to be a US Navy missile. The Navy tested a missile shortly after President …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agencies, Studios Debate: When to Drop a Star Who Becomes Toxic?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/agencies-studios-debate-when-to-drop-a-star-who-becomes-toxic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
