<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Costliest election...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/non-stop-ads-robocalls-welcome-americas-costliest-election-111706396.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Campaign advertisements bombard her favorite TV shows. Dozens of election pamphlets fill her mailbox. "I've had to block my calls." Welcome to the most expensive race in the hard-fought battle between Republicans and Democrats for control of the U.S. House of Representatives, which will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65% of all Americans: Economy good or excellent...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/democrats-lead-in-house-preferences-but-positive-views-of-the-economy-and-concern-about-border-security-may-buoy-republicans-poll-finds/2018/11/03/c98f184a-dee4-11e8-b3f0-62607289efee_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Washington Post-ABC News poll also finds President Trump’s popularity low but holding steady as Election Day nears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran marks anniversary of U.S. Embassy takeover with rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/trump-restores-sanctions-iranians-rally-mark-anniversary-u-s-embassy-n930986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anger and distrust of the United States is surging again following President Donald Trump's decision to withdraw from Iran's nuclear deal with world powers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazi Group Targets Oprah in Robocalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/neo-nazi-group-targets-oprah-ga-gov-candidate-stacey-abrams-in-racist-robocalls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The call mocks both women in vile, racist terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney criticizes Trump characterization of media as 'enemy of the people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.stgeorgeutah.com/news/archive/2018/11/03/apc-on-campaign-trail-romney-criticizes-trumps-characterization-of-media-as-enemy-of-the-people/#.W95U05NKhhF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stgeorgeutah.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Former GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney is stumping for fellow Republican candidates as he sails toward a likely victory Tuesday in the race for a U.S. Senate seat in Utah and a return to public office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive group targets Cruz with audio of 'Lyin' Ted'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/414706-progressive-group-targets-cruz-with-audio-of-trump-calling-him-a-liar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Progressive Change Campaign Committee announced Saturday that it is targeting Texas Sen. Ted Cruz (R) with a new ad featuring audio of President Trump repeatedly calling him a liar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  El Chapo's sons now running his drug empire...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/03/el-chapos-sons-are-now-running-his-drug-empire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican drug kingpin Joaquin Guzman “El Chapo” Loera may be going on trial tomorrow in Brooklyn federal court, but the billion dollar cartel he founded is still flourishing under the direction of h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Nation in Turmoil... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-nation-in-turmoil-prepares-to-deliver-a-verdict-on-trump/ar-BBPiphB?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY'' Nears $50M Opening...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/11/bohemian-rhapsody-nutcracker-weekend-box-office-tiffany-haddish-nobodys-fool-1202494598/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3rd Update, Saturday 1:18 AM: It’s funny, whenever a movie fails at the box office, the immediate go-to excuse in analyzing what went amiss is pointing to whatever problems occurred during pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militia groups head to border, stirred by Trump call to arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-militia-groups-head-to-border-stirred-by-trump%E2%80%99s-call-to-arms/ar-BBPiGxA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE RIPS MICHAEL COHEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/roger-stone-rips-michael-cohen-for-claims-about-trumps-racist-talk-hes-become-a-tool-of-his-new-handlers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VERDICT!</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Voters-set-to-render-fresh-verdict-on-Trump-13360929.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two years of political volatility will culminate Tuesday when voters for the first time since the stunning 2016 election render a nationwide judgment on whether Trumpism is a historic anomaly or a reflection of modern-day America. As the midterms roared into their final weekend - with the biggest names in both parties exhorting their followers to vote - uncertainty enveloped the contest amid signs that tightening races appeared headed toward dramatic finishes. Just how many House seats Democrats might pick up - they need a net gain of 23 to win the majority - remained unclear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury awards $105 million in lawsuit against pH Miracle author...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/courts/sd-me-phmiracle-civil-verdict-20181102-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Diego jury ordered the author of the bestselling pH Miracle books to pay $105 million to a cancer patient who said he held himself out as a doctor and counseled her to forego traditional treatment. The amount Robert O. Young was told to pay was more than twice what the woman had sought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California at center of fight for control of House...</title>
      <link>http://www.hastingstribune.com/this-year-the-nation-can-t-ignore-california/article_9f0a62f8-3118-5d44-91fb-e615603d0f2f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California — big, bounteous, beautiful — is pretty much used to irrelevancy come election day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing iPhone Troubles, APPLE Tries to Change the Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facing-iphone-troubles-apple-tries-to-change-the-story-1541253601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2009, Steve Jobs took a swipe at Amazon.com’s Kindle, saying the online retailer’s decision not to report unit sales was evidence it wasn’t selling many reading devices. Now, Apple is following a similar path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates Scramble...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-midterm-elections-loom-candidates-scramble-to-get-out-the-vote-1541269461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With just three days until Election Day, candidates are all but done with trying to persuade undecided voters, and they are using the last weekend before the midterm elections to encourage supporters to turn out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle for suburban voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/midterms/article220964575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans struggle with moderate voters in the final days of the midterm campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON hiring fewer holiday workers, a sign robots replacing...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1449634/amazons-reduced-holiday-hiring-is-a-bad-sign-for-human-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2018 is the first time Amazon plans to hire fewer holiday workers than it did the previous year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump election test: Movement or moment...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/insight-trump-supporters-election-test-movement-moment-103449120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In rally after rally, President Donald Trump exhorts throngs of red-hatted supporters to treat next week’s congressional elections as a referendum on Trumpism and the grass-roots movement that swept him to power. “You’re voting for me in 2018,” Trump told a raucous crowd in a late September appearance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election telethon aims to get youth to polls...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/cool-vote-hollywood-election-telethon-aims-young-polls-174914302--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a first-of-its-kind event, more than 50 actors, comedians and YouTube stars will join a two-hour, live-streamed telethon on Monday night aimed at firing up younger voters, the age group least likely to cast a ballot. Stars will not ask for money during the "Telethon for America." Instead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters are already streaming to polls in record numbers...</title>
      <link>http://www.courier-tribune.com/news/20181103/voters-are-already-streaming-to-polls-in-record-numbers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-tribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Voters across the country have been crowding into polling places and mailing in ballots in numbers rarely seen in an off-year election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite crackdown, 'junk news' still flourishes on social media...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/despite-crackdown-junk-news-still-flourishes-social-media-112309041.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite an aggressive crackdown by social media firms, so-called "junk news" is spreading at a greater rate than in 2016 on social media ahead of the US midterm elections, according to researchers. Oxford Internet Institute researchers concluded that Facebook and Twitter remain filled with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Edmondson threatens Republican dominance in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrat-edmondson-threatens-gop-dominance-oklahoma-144114597--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Oklahoma Republicans seized control of every statewide elected office in the 2010 midterm election, and they've maintained their dominance ever since.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho teachers suspended for border wall, Mexican Halloween costumes...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/idaho-teachers-suspended-border-wall-mexican-halloween-costumes-215414399.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of the group wearing stereotypical U.S. and Mexican costumes appeared this week on the Idaho school district's Facebook page, drawing complaints from parents, civil rights groups and members of the state's large Hispanic population. One photo showed seven staff from the Middleton Heights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibrant economy complicates decision...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b84b5f26ec5e4d5481c5882922c591d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXTON, Pennsylvania (AP) — For many voters in America's affluent suburbs, a flourishing economy is forcing a thorny dilemma for the midterm elections. Do they vote Democratic, in part to protest President Donald Trump for behavior some see as divisive and unpresidential? Or do they back Republicans in hopes that the economy will continue thriving under the majority party? A healthy economy has at least complicated their decision and blurred the outcome of the midterm elections . On Friday, the government reported that employers added a robust 250,000 jobs in October. And the unemployment rate stayed at a five-decade low of 3.7 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 MILLION ALREADY VOTED IN TX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8edc105f9e59479ab06981a9e409cd6f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump and Democrats are delivering competing closing arguments during the final weekend before Tuesday's elections, but their messages are complicated by a deadly shooting in a politically pivotal state. Trump aimed to drum up voter turnout with events Saturday in Belgrade, Montana, and Pensacola, Florida, about 200 miles west of Florida's capital, Tallahassee, where two people were shot to death and five others wounded at a yoga studio on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump presidency faces high stakes in Tuesday elections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6c4df5d8d6684e919b6431473684d895</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has been acting like a candidate on the ballot this week, staging daily double-header rallies and blasting out ads for Republicans up for election on Tuesday. Given the stakes for his presidency, he might as well be. A knot of investigations. Partisan gridlock. A warning shot for his re-election bid. Trump faces potentially debilitating fallout should Republicans lose control of one or both chambers in Congress, ending two years of GOP hegemony in Washington. A White House that has struggled to stay on course under favorable circumstances would be tested in dramatic ways. A president who often battles his own party, would face a far less forgiving opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party luminaries hit trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Party-luminaries-hit-campaign-trail-Saturday-to-13360291.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luminaries from both major political parties were set to hit the campaign trail Saturday in a late push to drive up turnout for Tuesday's midterm elections in key battlegrounds that will determine control of Congress and dozens of governorships. President Donald Trump has another pair of rallies planned, in Montana and Florida, two states with marquee Senate races. In Florida, Trump is also trying to bolster the fortunes of Republican gubernatorial hopeful Ron DeSantis, a candidate he endorsed during the GOP primary, who has been lagging in polls behind Democrat Andrew Gillum. If elected, Gillum would be the state's first black governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN worries about next 'America First' ambassador after Haley resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/un-worries-about-next-america-first-ambassador-after-haley-s/article_39070a72-673b-515b-a313-5d165c133d83.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK –– President Donald Trump’s “America First” rhetoric was never popular at the United Nations, but officials there are now worried they’re losing a critical ally as the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Area 52 UNCOVERED? Mysterious aircraft at secret US base 'intentionally BLURRED' by GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/1040448/Area-52-UFOs-aliens-mysterious-Google-Maps-top-secret-military-base</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPECULATION has erupted over a mysterious aircraft spotted at a top-secret US military base, amid claims that Google Maps has "refused" to update its satellite imagery of the area for more than eight years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Pentagon rejects request for troops to act as emergency law enforcement at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/11/02/politics/white-house-pentagon-troops-border/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Trump administration first asked the Pentagon to send troops to the southern border, the administration wanted the troops to take on duties that Department of Defense officials viewed as law enforcement functions, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make America mindful again: Meditation app offers 'politics pack' for election anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/02/headspace-app-offers-politics-pack-for-election-anxiety.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Headspace says it has seen an uptick in the use of its guided meditation sessions in times of high public stress, including after the 2016 presidential election that pitted Donald Trump against Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disabled veteran knocks MSNBC crew for blocking handicapped spots at polling site...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/414708-disabled-veteran-knocks-msnbc-crew-for-blocking-handicapped-spots-at-polling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A disabled Air Force veteran this week voiced frustration with an MSNBC news crew for blocking handicapped parking spots outside of a polling site in Houston.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaigns in high gear days before elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-campaign/u-s-campaigns-in-high-gear-three-days-before-congressional-elections-idUSKCN1N80II</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. congressional candidates hammered into the homestretch of a bruising campai...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embryo swapping is Wild West...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/03/embryo-swapping-is-the-wild-west/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a handful of states — including Florida, Louisiana, Oklahoma and Georgia — have passed legislation regarding embryo donation. (New York is not among them.) Georgia was the first to allow embry…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama builds in Mueller probe...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/414630-drama-builds-around-stone-in-mueller-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller continues to zero in on Roger Stone as speculation builds that the special counsel could take a major overt step in his Russia investigation following the midterm elections next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffet BERKSHIRE Bought Back Nearly $1 Billion of Own Stock...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/warren-buffetts-berkshire-hathaway-repurchases-more-than-900-million-of-stock-1541248428</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berkshire Hathaway repurchased $928 million of its stock in the third quarter, a rare move that indicates Chairman Warren Buffett sees a dearth of appealing investment options for his company’s large cash pile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech on Live Chats Tests YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hate-speech-on-live-super-chats-tests-youtube-1541205849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube’s Super Chat, which allows users to pay to have comments amplified during streaming videos, generates revenue but can contain racist comments and other hate speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Sex Worker Taking Hollywood by Storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-former-sex-worker-taking-hollywood-by-storm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The excellent new Netflix horror film ‘Cam’ captures the everyday fears of millions of cam girls, and was penned by ex-cam girl Isa Mazzei. Here, she opens up about her journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX culture of fear...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/805123/netflixs-culture-fear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Silicon Valley giant's workplace is reportedly ruthless. Is it worth it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida teen charged with strangling, burying mother...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-teenager-charged-strangling-burying-mother-135413575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAYTONA BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Authorities say a 15-year-old Florida boy was charged in his mother's strangulation death after her body was found buried at a nearby church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON new HQ in Virginia?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/03/amazon-reportedly-in-advanced-stages-of-naming-va-as-2nd-headquarters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon is in the advanced stages of placing its second headquarters in Northern Virginia, The Washington Post reported on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: THREE signs Biblical prophecies about end of world 'coming true'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/three-signs-biblical-prophecies-end-13526987</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trio of 'signs' have all emerged in the past few months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Generation Of Warfare: Genetically-Engineered Viruses...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-02/next-generation-warfare-genetically-engineered-viruses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Saudi crown prince crushed his rivals at the RITZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/mideast/how-saudi-royal-crushed-his-rivals-shakedown-ritz-carlton-n930396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Royals and others held at the luxury hotel after a Nov. 4, 2017, roundup were subjected to extortion, psychological abuse and torture, U.S. officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In France, spate of homophobic attacks on record just 'the tip of the iceberg'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181103-france-homophobic-attacks-record-lgbt-violence-gay-pride</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An increasing number of victims of anti-LGBT violence in France have spoken out over recent weeks, as rights groups have warned of a spike in attacks and the government has confirmed a 15 percent increase since the start of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Past midterms, some zero in on amending Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e84cdca5b568402398eabfcd2b6ada07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Whatever success Republicans have amassed in taking control of all three branches of U.S. government, and whatever fate awaits them as midterm elections near, some on the right are working to cement change by amending the Constitution. And to the mounting alarm of others on all parts of the spectrum, they want to bypass the usual process. They're pushing for an unprecedented Constitutional convention of the states. While opponents are afraid of what such a convention would do, supporters say it is the only way to deal with the federal government's overreach and ineptitude.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for chip implant?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/are-you-ready-for-a-chip-implant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You walk into a grocery store and pick up eggs. No smartphone? No problem. You swipe your hand across a reader, and the amount is deducted from your bank account. If that sounds far-fetched, you obviously haven’t been to Sweden recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: TRUMP ACCOMPLISHMENTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/here-it-is-complete-list-of-president-trumps-accomplishments-in-the-two-years-since-his-historic-2016-election-win/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paraplegic athlete 'forced' to drag himself through airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/paraplegic-athlete-justin-levene-forced-to-drag-himself-through-luton-airport-after-wheelchair-was-left-behind-on-flight/ar-BBPhf0x?li=AAaD62f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJ Guetta still spinning: Success is 70% hard work...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/news/dance/8483002/david-guetta-ap-interview-2018-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grammy-winning DJ-producer and hitmaker David Guetta says success is mostly down to hard work and luck -- not talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Dead In Building Collapse At AMAZON Fulfillment Center...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/11/02/partial-building-collapse-at-baltimore-amazon-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to our media partners the Baltimore Sun, officials say it was a partial building collapse and a search is underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia turns up uninvited to major NATO wargames...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181103-russia-turns-uninvited-major-nato-wargames</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite crackdown, 'junk news' still flourishes on social media...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2018-11-crackdown-junk-news-flourishes-social.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite an aggressive crackdown by social media firms, so-called "junk news" is spreading at a greater rate than in 2016 on social media ahead of the US midterm elections, according to researchers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Breakdancing Underdog at 60...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/a-breakdancing-underdog-at-60-1541242800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ad executive looking for a more fun way to lose weight discovers he can’t stop dancing against competitors half his age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 76: Mueller About to Roll Out the Barrels?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/03/robert-mueller-investigation-222184</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that the special prosecutor’s quiet period is nearly over, many Russia-scandal observers expect dramatic news from the long-silent investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of GOD? Claims humans will 'worship AI Messiah'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/740301/god-artificial-intelligence-ai-messiah-dan-rown-da-vinci-code</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
