<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Musk says TESLA has not signed contract with HERTZ. HERTZ says deliveries already started...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/hertz-says-teslas-already-started-delivering-cars-despite-musk-tweet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hertz declined to discuss details of the agreement but said the company remains "on plan" with its announcement to offer 100,000 Teslas by the end of 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has resettled fewest refugees in history of program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-has-resettled-the-fewest-refugees-in-the-history-of-the-us-program-what-could-change-that/ar-AAQdYsL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over time, refugees bring communities a net financial gain, research finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court looks to medieval England in gun rights case...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/supreme-court-looks-to-medieval-england-in-gun-rights-case/ar-AAQdZyY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court's originalists look to history to determine the meaning of the 2nd Amendment and the right to 'keep and bear arms.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tension Grows in East Ukraine With Report of Russia Army Buildup...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/tension-grows-in-east-ukraine-with-report-of-russia-army-buildup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tension Grows in East Ukraine With Report of Russia Army Buildup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools grapple with growing shortage of teachers...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/schools-grapple-growing-shortage-teachers-100000410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — South Florida’s schools are suffering under a pandemic double-whammy: Not enough teachers, and not enough substitutes to fill in for them. For substitutes, the stressful working conditions aren’t worth $15 an hour when they can make more at places like Walmart or Starbucks and also secure health care. Burnt-out teachers say the passion that keeps them coming back year ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERs swamped with seriously ill patients, although many don't have virus...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/hospital-emergency-rooms-swamped-seriously-ill-non-covid-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Certain patients who couldn’t get in to see a doctor earlier in the pandemic, or were avoiding the covid risks inside hospitals, have become too sick to stay away. Many ERs now struggle to co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring Wheat Prices Raising Bread Costs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/soaring-wheat-prices-raising-bread-124125570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wheat prices are surging from the U.S. to Russia, hitting a record in Europe and raising bread costs all over the world. And there may not be much relief soon.Most Read from BloombergSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’The Best New Restaurants in Washington, Chosen by Top ChefsBallot Initiatives to Watch, From Policing to the En</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missile Construction Progress...</title>
      <link>https://fas.org/blogs/security/2021/11/a-closer-look-at-chinas-missile-silo-construction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fas.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the discovery during the summer of what appears to be at least three vast missile silo fields under construction near Yumen, Hami, and Ordos in north-central China, new commercial satellite images show significant progress at the three sites as well as at the People’s Liberation Army Rocket Fo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Having Kids Make Happy?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/11/does-having-kids-make-you-happy/620576/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research has found that having children is terrible for quality of life—but the truth about what parenthood means for happiness is a lot more complicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX 'Jetpack Man' Just Balloon?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxla.com/news/lax-jet-pack-man-latest-new-video-may-finally-solve-viral-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New videos and photos released by LAPD may have finally revealed the true story behind the LAX “Jet Pack Man.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia official: Call to 'find' votes was threat...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-arts-and-entertainment-elections-georgia-2b27f4c92919556bf6548117648693b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Donald Trump was threatening Georgia Secretary of State Brad Raffensperger when he asked him to help “find” enough votes to overturn his loss in Georgia to Democratic President Joe Biden, Raffensperger writes in a new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping Naked Doubles Chances For Good Night's Rest?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sleeping-naked-good-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who prefer a warm room also reported better sleep than those who like sleeping in a cold room, survey results show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino to offer seven uncut scenes from 'PULP FICTION' as NFTs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/quentin-tarantino-to-offer-seven-uncut-scenes-from-pulp-fiction-as-nfts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The collectibles also include original handwritten scripts from the film and exclusive audio commentary from Tarantino himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster-spreading Delta variant spotted in 8 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-delta-plus-variant-ay-4-2-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data from the U.K. suggests vaccines remain effective against the coronavirus variant sometimes called "Delta plus."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughing or crying, Biden wears heart on sleeve...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/laughing-crying-biden-wears-heart-104258287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He laughs, he cries, he says sorry. For the most powerful man in the world, President Joe Biden sure shows his soft side a lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Pearl Harbor Coming?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/chinas-satellite-crusher-space-pearl-harbor-coming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race may hinge on debates about schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/opinion/article/Virginia-s-governor-s-race-may-hinge-on-debates-16584416.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Republican business executive Glenn Youngkin prevails over former Democratic governor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman convinced husband he had Alzheimer's. Police say she stole $600,000 from him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-woman-convinced-her-husband-that-he-had-alzheimer-e2-80-99s-police-say-she-stole-24600000-from-him-over-time/ar-AAQdEJv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To cover her tracks, she convinced the now-73-year-old man he had Alzheimer’s, according to police reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Hawley says attacks on manhood driving men to porn, video games...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Sen-Josh-Hawley-says-liberals-attacks-on-16584505.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri Republican Sen. Josh Hawley on Sunday night told fellow conservatives they must...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will broken supply chains stop Santa?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/international/579513-will-broken-supply-chains-stop-santa-claus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re speaking not just of stocking stuffers — but the success of U.S. technical industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulators Sound Alarm on Stablecoins...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/02/regulators-sound-the-alarm-on-stablecoins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seeking stability Financial regulators have urged lawmakers to act fast on legislation to address the rising risk of stablecoins. This</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YAHOO pulls out of China...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/yahoo-inc-leaving-china-f3b589754224bc663d5e83ec385eb49a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Yahoo Inc. said Tuesday it has pulled out of China, citing an “increasingly challenging business and legal environment.” Chinese authorities maintain a firm grip on internet censorship in the country and require companies operating in China to censor content and keywords deemed politically sensitive or inappropriate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govs and more: What to watch in elections...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-day-2021-what-to-watch-230b722f8fdf1f229ae043d1c1475a73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be an odd-numbered year but Tuesday's elections aren't sleepy, local contests. Voters in Virginia are weighing in on a governor's race that could rattle President Joe Biden and Democrats in Washington .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis voters weigh fate of police...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/death-of-george-floyd-police-minnesota-minneapolis-police-reform-cc108d1707d9cb8cbaa6135bb60e7fbd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Voters in Minneapolis were deciding Tuesday whether to replace the city’s police department with a new Department of Public Safety, more than a year after George Floyd’s death under the knee of a white police officer launched a movement to defund or abolish police across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mainers to decide on 'right to food' amendment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-maine-constitutions-referendums-605019e60df5b3e32bc70c86dcf957b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Maine voters will decide Tuesday whether to pass the nation’s first “right to food” constitutional amendment. A statewide referendum asked voters if they favored an amendment to the Maine Constitution “to declare that all individuals have a natural, inherent and unalienable right to grow, raise, harvest, produce and consume the food of their own choosing for their own nourishment, sustenance, bodily health and well-being.” It's an experiment not tried before by any state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists pushing emergency protections for gray wolves...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/579523-activists-pushing-interior-for-emergency-protections-for-gray</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indigenous activists are pushing Interior Secretary Deb Haaland to safeguard gray wolves after the expiration of federal protections allowed hunters to kill hundreds of the animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From BOEING to MERCEDES, worker rebellion swells over vax mandates...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211102105819-xsgq8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VACCINES-RESISTANCE (INSIGHT, PIX):INSIGHT-From Boeing to Mercedes, a U.S. worker rebellion swells over vaccine mandates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Peru's Amazon, 'forgotten' tribes discover COVID as vaccines arrive...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211102105819-sefxa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PERU-INDIGENOUS (PIX, TV):In Peru's Amazon, 'forgotten' tribes discover COVID-19 as vaccines arrive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing push on land justice for Black Americans...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211102085838-5ucry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Surging' public discussions on reparations to atone for the effects of slavery and structural racism in the U.S. are currently underway</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW to Offload 7,000 Homes After Flipping Fumble...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-seeks-sell-7-000-184559654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Zillow Group Inc. is looking to sell about 7,000 homes as it seeks to recover from a fumble in its high-tech home-flipping business.Most Read from BloombergSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’Can a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?In Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing Is at StakeThe company is seeking roughly $2.8 bill</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Car Shortages Putting Economy at Risk...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/02/how-car-shortages-are-putting-the-worlds-economy-at-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turmoil in the auto industry, a powerful engine of the global economy, is threatening growth and sending tremors through companies and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-conservative church on rise in Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/nov/02/christ-church-idaho-theocracy-us-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Increased influence of Christ Church, whose leader wants to create US ‘theocracy’, comes as social conservatives seek to gain wider foothold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi to cement authority in Communist Party resolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/china/chinas-xi-cement-authority-legacy-communist-party-resolution-2021-11-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping is expected to push through an historical resolution at a key Communist Party gathering next week, cementing his authority and legacy and strengthening his case for a precedent-breaking third term starting next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized after fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/02/us/jesse-jackson-hospitalized-howard-university/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil rights leader Rev. Jesse Jackson was hospitalized after falling and hitting his head while attending a meeting at Howard University in Washington, DC, Monday, according to his Rainbow PUSH Coalition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots hit streets as demand for food delivery grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-technology-science-business-europe-5b7dbb782f89ef3d586eefb9a33d5e1c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANN ARBOR, Mich. (AP) — Robot food delivery is no longer the stuff of science fiction. But you may not see it in your neighborhood anytime soon. Hundreds of little robots __ knee-high and able to hold around four large pizzas __ are now navigating college campuses and even some city sidewalks in the U.S., the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astronauts make 'space tacos' with green peppers successfully grown on ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/nasa-astronauts-make-space-tacos-25353836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA has announced that it has successfully cultivated chile peppers in space for the first time ever. It is the latest breakthrough in a project investigating which crops can be taken to Mars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle most anxious major city...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/data/stressed-out-in-seattle-were-the-most-anxious-major-metro-in-the-u-s-new-census-data-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Seattle metro area tops the nation for being stressed out during the pandemic, according to a new census survey. The feelings of anxiety are consistent across adult generations, too. FYI Guy explores who's on edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% of Republicans doubt their vote will be counted accurately...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/nbc-news-poll-50-percent-republicans-doubt-their-vote-will-n1282849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 22 percent of Republicans say President Biden was legitimately elected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOSTER NEEDED EVEN AFTER INFECTION?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-finds-immunity-from-vaccines-is-more-consistent-than-from-infection-but-both-last-at-least-six-months/ar-AAQcwyi?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naturally acquired immunity is at the center of a political fight over President Biden’s vaccine mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA orders rare medical delay in launch of SpaceX...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211101225720-xiqrz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-EXPLORATION/SPACEX (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-NASA orders rare medical delay in launch of SpaceX mission to space station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS SKIPS THE TRAIN...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boris-johnson-office-defends-pm-172008628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Boris Johnson’s office sought to defend the U.K. prime minister’s plans to fly to London rather than take the train after his attendance at the COP26 climate talks in Glasgow, Scotland.Most Read from BloombergInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideCan a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?Atlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’In Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing Is at StakeThe Terrifying Rise of Haunted Tourism“Both the fue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS:  Wants to build tunnel to flood-prone beach in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/elon-musk-wants-build-tunnel-185800304.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Inquiring minds want to know just how Elon Musk’s Boring Company will dig a pair of underground tunnels from downtown Fort Lauderdale to the beach in flood-prone South Florida on the cheap. The Boring Company’s 29-page pitch, submitted to the city in June but only recently made public, holds some clues to the ambitious plan. The tunnels would not be for your car or ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia prepares for long Election Day as polls show dead heat ...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/virginia-prepares-for-long-election-day-as-polls-show-dead-heat-between-mcauliffe-youngkin/ar-AAQcqwb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia voters are headed to the polls to pick a new governor in a neck-and-neck race that has drawn national attention for what it might reveal about the state of electoral politics in the first year of the Biden presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado Hits 80% Vaccine Rate With Hospitals STILL in Covid Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/colorado-hits-80-vaccine-rate-as-hospitals-in-covid-19-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado Hits 80% Vaccine Rate With Hospitals in Covid-19 Crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Now Three Times Richer Than Warren Buffett...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/elon-musk-now-three-times-205653968.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc.’s latest rally has blasted co-founder Elon Musk’s wealth past a new milestone: It now eclipses famed investor Warren Buffett’s fortune by a factor of three. Most Read from BloombergInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideCan a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?Atlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’In Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing Is at StakeThe Terrifying Rise of Haunted TourismMusk’s net worth rose by $24 b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's PAC offers 'iconic' Christmas wrapping paper for $35 donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/politics/trumps-pac-offers-iconic-christmas-wrapping-paper</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“President Trump asked us to personally reach out to you because he wants to make sure you get our NEW Trump Gift Wrapping Paper in time for Christmas,” an email sent to supporters Monday reads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon City Limiting How Often Church Feeds Homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4awyqw/oregon-brookings-ordinance-limits-churches-from-feeding-homeless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But a local reverend isn’t planning to follow the new rules. “We’re not going to stop feeding,” he said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man spreads to dog, cat in first-ever report of human to pet transmission in U.S...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10153637/Arizona-man-contracted-Covid-spread-dog-cat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first ever case of a person transmitting the virus to one of their pets was detected in Arizona in March. Pets are relatively safe from the virus, and are likely to have an asymptomatic case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Wants Congress to Crack Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/01/congress-should-regulate-stablecoins-biden-administration-report-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a long-awaited report, the President's Working Group on Financial Markets found, when regulated, stablecoins could transform payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodent-infested POPEYES shuts. Rats running around kitchen, climbing walls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/see-it-rodent-infested-popeyes-in-d-c-shuts-down-after-video-shows-rats-running-around-kitchen-climbing-up-walls/ar-AAQcAF8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You still love that chicken from Popeyes?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran's major image problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/san-francisco-major-image-problem-16575042.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One top PR expert thinks San Francisco’s image in the media 'is somewhere between 'The...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy concludes nuke sub hit uncharted seamount...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/11/01/investigation-concludes-uss-connecticut-grounded-on-uncharted-sea-mount-in-south-china-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators have determined USS Connecticut (SSN-22) hit an uncharted seamount that grounded the nuclear attack submarine on the underwater feature in the South China Sea Navy, USNI News has learned. The results of the command investigation into the Oct. 2 incident, completed last week, have now been passed up to U.S. 7th Fleet commander Vice …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Problems Lead To Limited Furnace Supply Ahead Of Winter...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/10/30/supply-chain-problems-lead-to-limited-furnace-supply/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like many industries, supply of furnaces and their parts is backed up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh may have upended ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.msnbc.com/craig-melvin/watch/how-justice-kavanaugh-may-have-upended-the-texas-abortion-ban-with-one-simple-question-125101637517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Monday is taking up two challenges to the Texas law that has all but stopped abortions in the state. Ken Dilanian, Joyce Vance, and Kim Wehle discuss how Justice Brett Kavanaugh displayed how the unique structure of the Texas abortion law could be used to bypass constitutional rights like freedom of religion and the 2nd amendment with one single question.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why celebrity chef is now making cat food...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/01/why-chef-bobby-flay-is-now-making-food-for-cats.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seeing a gap in quality cat food and inspired by his Maine Coon cat Nacho, chef and restaurateur Bobby Flay launched the cat food brand Made By Nacho.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid vanishes from campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/01/covid-campaign-trail-vanishing-act-517753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polls suggest the pandemic is fading as a voter priority. Covid-related political advertising has fallen off sharply as a result and strategists are advising candidates to shift their focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Teacher of the Year' arrested for hitting pupil who criticized award...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/01/florida-teacher-of-the-year-arrested-for-hitting-pupil-who-criticized-award/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High School English teacher Caroline Melanie Lee, 60, was proudly hailed for her achievement by the Duval County Public Schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge suspends deadline for Chicago cops to get jabbed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-police-chicago-illinois-83fa624fa859806f428eb228d3d3f86d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A judge on Monday suspended a Dec. 31 deadline for Chicago police officers to be vaccinated against COVID-19 but didn't interfere with a requirement that they be regularly tested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin won't back $1.75 trillion bill without 'greater clarity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/01/politics/joe-manchin-biden-agenda/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Joe Manchin said he won't support the $1.75 trillion reconciliation bill Democrats are negotiating until there is "greater clarity" about the impact it will have on the country's national debt and the economy, a warning sign for Democratic leaders trying to pass a pair of legislative packages key to President Joe Biden's agenda as soon as this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden appears to nod off...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/01/biden-nods-off-during-cop26-climate-conference/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden got little shut-eye Monday in a very high-profile place — appearing to fall asleep during opening remarks at the COP26 climate change conference in Scotland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syphilis resurging in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/11/01/1050568646/syphilis-std-public-health-funding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country nearly eradicated this treatable sexually transmitted disease twice, only to see it come roaring back. The failure shows the weakness of a cash-strapped public health system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Supreme Court Justices Voice Skepticism Over Texas Abortion Law...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/kavanaugh-barrett-signal-skepticism-in-texas-abortion-law-case/ar-AAQcb2n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key U.S. Supreme Court justices raised the prospect they might shift course and act to halt Texas’ far-reaching abortion ban, questioning the state’s contention that federal courts lack power to block the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False Promise of Psychedelic Utopia...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dypzxj/the-false-promise-of-psychedelic-utopia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some advocates claim that widespread psychedelic use will change the world for the better. But it’s not so simple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines who refuse will be booted...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2021/11/01/the-corps-covid-19-vaccination-deadline-is-soon-marines-who-refuse-will-be-booted/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Marine Corps has not approved any religious exemptions to the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big donors furious...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/01/democratic-donors-warn-they-may-hold-back-money-for-midterms.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Democratic donors have warned leaders that they may hold back on donations for next year's midterm elections unless the party can get some big wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J recipients 3.5 times more likely to develop rare blood clots...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10152723/Americans-received-one-dose-J-J-Covid-vaccine-3-5-times-likely-develop-blood-clots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Mayo Clinic of Minnesota found that people who receive the Johnson &amp; Johnson COVID-19 vaccine are 3.5 times as likely to develop rare blood clotting than others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church of England leader sorry for comparing 'climate change' to rise of Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211101170655-euhq3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-UN/BRITAIN-ARCHBISHOP-NAZIS (PIX):Church of England leader apologises for comparing climate change to rise of Nazis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TRAVEL HELL AFTER  AA CANCELS 2,000+ FLIGHTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/01/american-airlines-flight-cancellations-and-staffing-challenges-continue.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American cancelled hundreds of additional flights on Monday after more than 1,500 over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPUBLICAN RESET?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/virginia-governor-election-mcauliffe-youngkin-6af9b4e62d27bbc66042e819befe9c45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — As he explains it, part of why Glenn Youngkin decided to run for Virginia governor was a feeling that the state's beaten and battered Republican Party “could do so much better.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK EYES JAIL TIME FOR ONLINE TROLLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/online-safety-bill-jail-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bill would reportedly criminalize certain behavior that causes "emotional, psychological, or physical harm to the likely audience."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA sheriff warns 'mass exodus' among personnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/sheriff-warns-vaccine-mandate-causing-mass-exodus-among-personnel/ar-AAQ9XHX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County Sheriff Villanueva says the COVID vaccine mandate is causing personnel to leave, warning that as patrol services decline, crime will rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC begs for volunteer firefighters; One-third of FDNY remain unvaccinated... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10150073/NYC-issues-call-city-firefighters-Long-Island-Upstate-New-York.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC has issued a state-wide call for city firefighters in areas such as Long Island and Upstate New York as one-third of FDNY firefighters remain unvaccinated ahead of Nov. 1 deadline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: KISS Cancels Vegas Residency After Death Draws Criticism...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/music/news/kiss-cancels-las-vegas-residency-tour-guitar-tech-covid-death-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kiss canceled their planned Las Vegas residency suddenly late last week, amid questions about [...]</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
