<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Copper jumps to record...</title>
      <link>https://www.theedgemarkets.com/article/copper-jumps-record-growth-bets-supercharge-commodities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theedgemarkets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(May 7): Copper soared to an all-time high as optimism about a global rebound from the pandemic spurs a surge across commodities markets.The metal — an economic bellwether — is front and centre in a rally that’s driven raw materials from lumber to iron ore to multi-year highs or records. Stimulus measures and vaccine rollouts are fueling prospects for a resurgence in demand that’s set to strain supply, while copper’s crucial role in the green-energy transition is set to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bar owner charged with selling fake vax cards in one of first cases of its kind...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Bar-owner-charged-with-selling-fake-coronavirus-16159225.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Old Corner Saloon fashions itself as a small-town institution. Sitting on a historic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Capitol rioter had 'Foxitis,' his attorney says: He 'started believing what was fed to him'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/accused-capitol-rioter-had-foxitis-his-attorney-says-he-started-believing-what-was-being-fed-to-him/ar-BB1gsEBj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At at a hearing Thursday, Anthony Antonio’s attorney said he spent six months watching Fox News, which contributed to his decision to participate in the insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEC Dems blast decision to drop probe into hush-money payment to Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Democrats-on-FEC-blast-decision-to-drop-probe-16159195.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Federal Election Commission on Thursday dropped its inquiry to determine whether...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Americans hesitate to shed masks despite eased outdoor rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210507085304-dpx57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MASKS (TV, PIX):'You feel naked': Some Americans hesitate to shed masks despite eased outdoor rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Enough Chlorine, Propane...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/nationwide-shortage-of-chlorine-and-propane-tank-impacting-pools-right-before-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nationwide shortage of pool products is making chlorine tablets and propane tanks hard to come by and increasing prices right as the summer months approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Warns of Peril for Asset Prices as Investors Gorge on Risk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fed-says-asset-prices-may-201252345.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A rising appetite for risk across a variety of asset markets is stretching valuations and creating vulnerabilities in the U.S. financial system, the Federal Reserve said in its semi-annual financial stability report.“Vulnerabilities associated with elevated risk appetite are rising,” Fed Governor Lael Brainard, the head of the Board’s financial stability committee, said in a statement accompanying the report released Thursday. “The combination of stretched valuations with very high levels of corporate indebtedness bear watching because of the potential to amplify the effects of a re-pricing event.”In this environment, prices may be vulnerable to “significant declines” should risk appetite fall, the Fed report noted.Brainard and the report mentioned losses at banks stemming from dealings with Archegos Capital Management, and the governor called for “more granular, higher-frequency disclosures.”“The Archegos event illustrates the limited visibility into hedge-fund exposures and serves as a reminder that available measures of hedge-fund leverage may not be capturing important risks,” she said.The Managed Funds Association, which represents hedge funds, took issue with Brainard’s remarks.“It is unfortunate policy makers incorrectly conflate hedge funds with unregulated entities like individuals and family offices,” Association President Bryan Corbett said in a statement. “Hedge funds are well regulated” by the Securities and Exchange Commission.Near-zero interest rates and massive bond purchases, with the Fed buying $40 billion in mortgage-backed securities and $80 billion in Treasuries every month, have fueled a search for returns and helped buoy asset prices including those of risky investments such as speculative stocks, cryptocurrencies and high-yield debt. The Standard and Poor’s 500 stock index has risen 12% this year.“The real story here is the tension -- if not the glaring contradiction -- of the Fed’s pursuit of quantitative easing, the aim of which is to lower long-term rates and encourage reach for yield, and their concern that people are indeed reaching for yield,” said George Selgin, a senior fellow at the Cato Institute in Washington, referring to the bond buying. “The Fed could certainly taper its QE activities to counter this risk-taking as the recovery continues.”Spacs, Meme Stocks“Indicators pointing to elevated risk appetite in equity markets in early 2021 include the episodes of high trading volumes and price volatility for so-called meme stocks -- stocks that increased in trading volume after going viral on social media,” the report said. “Elevated equity issuance through SPACs also suggests a higher-than-typical appetite for risk among equity investors.”Low rates are also impacting the real economy. Home prices are up 12% year over year amid high demand for property and scarce supply, while a boom in home remodeling has helped push lumber futures to record highs. The Bloomberg Commodity Index, which tracks everything from grains to natural gas and nickel, is up 19%.The report said house-price increases have had a positive effect for borrowers by boosting equity. Still, it noted that borrowers in forbearance programs, who are likely to be employed in industries hard hit by the pandemic, could be vulnerable when they exit. “Even so, a large fraction of borrowers have already exited forbearance -- in general, these borrowers have loans that are either current or paid off,” the report said.The report also noted that low interest rates have reduced default expectations, and underwriting standards have weakened. “The share of newly issued loans to large corporations with high leverage -- defined as those with ratios of debt to earnings before interest, taxes, depreciation, and amortization greater than 6 -- has exceeded the historical highs reached in recent years,” it said.Hedge Fund LeverageThe report said that “available data suggest” that hedge funds are highly leveraged, and said there is a need for greater transparency on opaque risk exposures, echoing Brainard’s call for more transparency.“Some hedge funds with substantial short positions sustained losses during the meme stock episode in January 2021, when intense social media activity contributed to fluctuations in the prices of some specific stocks,” the report said, probably a reference to the short squeeze in shares of GameStop Corp., which soared to more than $300 a share from around $20 a share in a matter of days.Jon Caplis, chief executive officer at hedge fund consultant PivotalPath, said after the report’s release that one disclosure in particular could mitigate the risk of a future Archegos-like situation happening again.“Before you try and rewrite all the regulatory statutes, you can make one small change that would be effective,” he said. “If you merely treat total-return swaps in the same way hedge funds are already disclosing equity holdings, you would drastically mitigate an Archegos-like fallout from happening again.”(Updates with hedge fund reaction in sixth and seventh paragraphs.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.7 Mag Quake Rattles Lake Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/earthquakes/preliminary-4-7-magnitude-earthquake-strikes-near-the-california-nevada-state-line/2538658/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A preliminary 4.7 magnitude earthquake struck near the Truckee area, according to the United States Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Gets Ready for Elon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/07/saturday-night-live-gets-ready-for-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When “Saturday Night Live” announced last month that this weekend’s broadcast would be hosted by Elon Musk, the billionaire chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Not Quite Like Riding Bike': Pilots Get Ready to Fly Again...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/07/its-not-quite-like-riding-a-bike-pilots-get-ready-to-fly-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One returning pilot lost control of an aircraft during landing and skidded off the runway into a ditch. Another just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: Secret Papers of Lee Atwater, Political Mastermind...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-secret-papers-of-lee-atwater-who-invented-the-scurrilous-tactics-that-trump-normalized</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An infamous Republican political operative’s unpublished memoir shows how the Party came to embrace lies, racial fearmongering, and winning at any cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What lies ahead for Ruddy?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/chris-ruddy-and-newsmax-went-all-in-on-trump-now-they-might-pay-a-price-for-it/ar-BB1gptJq?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative media entrepreneur became Trump’s most quotable friend. His cable channel became one of the biggest promoters of Trump’s election-fraud fantasies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India 1 million covid deaths by August?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/covid-forecasters-warn-india-deaths-may-double-in-coming-weeks/ar-BB1gmvV9?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus wave that plunged India into the world’s biggest health crisis has the potential to worsen in the coming weeks, with some research models projecting that the death toll could more than double from current levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA PLANS ATLANTIC NAVAL BASE</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/may/6/general-chinas-africa-outreach-poses-threat-from-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is moving behind-the-scenes toward establishing a major naval port on the west coast of Africa that would host Chinese submarines and aircraft carriers capable of projecting Beijing’s military power directly into the Atlantic, a top U.S. military official warned on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bald men TWICE as likely to suffer severe Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2836376/bald-men-twice-likely-severe-covid-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALD men are up to twice as likely to suffer severe Covid, experts have warned. New research suggests they spend up to twice as long in hospital with Covid than those who still have a full head of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Robber Attempts Getaway On Bus...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/woman-arrested-in-sonoma-bank-robbery-attempted-getaway-on-local-bus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was arrested Wednesday following a bank robbery in Sonoma where police say the suspect tried to make her escape on a county transit bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORBES in talks to sell to venture firm for $650M...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/06/forbes-media-reportedly-in-talks-to-sell-to-venture-firm-for-650m/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forbes Media, owned by Asian investors since 2014, is in exclusive talks to sell itself for $650 million to an investment group led by Michael Moe, head of merchant bank GSV. Bloomberg on Thursday …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside NYPOST's Blowup Over Bogus Story at Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/05/inside-the-new-york-posts-blowup-over-a-bogus-story-at-the-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tabloid veteran Laura Italiano’s very public exit has rattled the newsroom, where staffers speak of intense pressure to drive clicks and stoke the culture wars. “The Post has always been a balancing act of catering to the masses and the elites,” says one. “Lately, it feels as if everything is now for the masses.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers investigating possibility of new mental health disorder...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/04/12/sluggish-cognitive-tempo-research-critics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many researchers say the study of sluggish cognitive tempo, which is still in its early stages, can’t yet support a formal diagnosis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI still after 'worst of the worst' as new arrests come at steady pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/fbi-still-after-worst-worst-capitol-riot-new-arrests-come-n1266580</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 440 people have been charged with taking part in the Capitol siege, coming from all but six states with the most coming from Texas, Pennsylvania, and Florida, in that order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>97-year-old killed in Atlanta home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/97-year-old-shot-to-death-in-dekalb-home-2-charged/WKBSELRY3BEVPJ6TRL5IQM6I2U/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people are behind bars after a 97-year-old man was found shot to death in his DeKalb County home this week, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Create Record-Breaking Laser With Mind Blowing Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3xxza/scientists-create-record-breaking-laser-with-mind-blowing-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The laser pulse's power is comparable to "focusing all the sunlight reaching Earth to a spot of 10 microns"—the size of a speck of dust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steel prices triple...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/06/investing/steel-shortage-stocks-bubble/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bubble could be brewing in steel stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Drivers Told to Drive Recklessly...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/xgxx54/amazon-drivers-are-instructed-to-drive-recklessly-to-meet-delivery-quotas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers say they’re being asked to quietly disable a driver safety system partway through their shifts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell 'likely to cut plea deal but may face same fate as Epstein'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2834589/ghislaine-maxwell-plea-deal-same-fate-as-epstein/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GHISLAINE Maxwell is likely to be negotiating a plea deal with prosecutors, which is why her trial has been delayed, a victims’ lawyer has claimed. Spencer Kuvin, who represents nine Epstein …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cox complains about 1,000-lb bear dominating coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/2021-05-John-Cox-bear-stunt-recall-Gavin-Newsom-CA-16154494.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'The coverage yesterday was all about the bear,' says the person who brought the bear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Florida's population growth slowed sharply...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/south-florida-s-population-growth-slowed-sharply-last-year-as-deaths-surged-and-people-moved-away-census-data-shows/ar-BB1gqOcg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Florida saw dramatic changes to its population trends in 2020 as COVID-19 led to more deaths than births and more people moved out of the area, according to annual data released by the U.S. Census Bureau. The swing was most stark in Miami-Dade County, which saw its population decrease for the first time in at least a decade. The figures come as part of the Census’s annual vintage ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise lines to seek volunteer passengers for trial voyages
...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/CDC-sets-rules-for-trial-cruises-with-volunteer-16154903.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruise lines can soon begin trial voyages in U.S. waters with volunteer passengers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGELS Release Slumping MLB Legend Pujols In Final Year Of $253M Contract...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/angels-to-release-albert-pujols-in-final-season-of-10-year-contract/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future Hall of Famer is in the final year of his 10-year contract</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark bites woman off Daytona Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2021/05/06/shark-bites-21-year-old-woman-off-daytona-beach-shores/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 21-year-old woman was bitten by a shark off Daytona Beach Shores.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ Republicans hunt for bamboo-laced China ballots in 2020 'audit' effort...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/06/arizona-republicans-bamboo-ballots-audit-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the conspiracy theories driving the exercise in Maricopa county is one that suggests 40,000 ballots were flown in from Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Months into Brexit, UK and France resort to gunboat diplomacy over fish...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/06/uk/britain-france-war-ships-jersey-cmd-intl-gbr/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take a glance at the British media and you'd be forgiven for thinking that the UK was preparing for war with France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago suburb set to pay reparations, but not all on board...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/national/2021/05/06/chicago-suburb-set-to-pay-reparations-but-not-all-on-board/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chicago suburb of Evanston is preparing to pay reparations in the form of housing grants to Black residents who experienced housing discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHERIFF: Army trainee arrested after hijacking school bus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/hijacking-arrests-983d15f70ebf3ad8129e1809ca558f47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — An Army trainee has been arrested after authorities say he boarded a South Carolina school bus with a gun Thursday and held the driver and elementary students hostage before letting them off the bus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS KEEP SOARING; MORE RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/05/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gains in the stock market came after a better-than-expected reading on jobless claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statue Of Jesus Beheaded Outside Church...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/05/st-charles-chapel-waltham-jesus-statue-beheaded/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So we’re hoping that if someone did this intentionally, they can come get help and they won’t do it again to another church."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC pitches free vaccines for tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/broadway-theaters-resume-ticket-sales-for-100-fall-return-but-how-many-will-fill/3039919/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City is getting creative when it comes to vaccinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli tech ensures you keep your distance; attached to clothing...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/this-israeli-tech-could-prevent-mass-quarantines-using-proximity-scanning-667411</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small enough to be attached to clothing, the Canario Pro buzzes to inform wearers that they are within two meters of someone – and tracks them to minimize the need to quarantine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis signs Florida election bill into law amid new controversy...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/gop-gov-desantis-signs-florida-election-bill-law/story?id=77530271</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis created new controversy around Florida's already controversial new election law Thursday, giving exclusive access to the signing ceremony to Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What lies ahead for Chris Ruddy?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/What-lies-ahead-for-Chris-Ruddy-16156348.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One night last month at Mar-a-Lago, Chris Ruddy positioned himself in a familiar spot:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Lapid faces daunting path to anti-Netanyahu govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210506-israel-s-lapid-faces-daunting-path-to-anti-netanyahu-govt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's Lapid faces daunting path to anti-Netanyahu govt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media shut out of DeSantis elections bill signing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/552085-media-shut-out-of-desantis-elections-bill-signing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Local reporters were barred on Thursday from witnessing Florida Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Musk Is Actually Going to Do This Mars Thing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/05/elon-musk-spacex-starship-launch/618781/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From his private Cape Canaveral, the billionaire is manifesting a world where interplanetary travel feels real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rage Coaches Helping Hollywood Take on Powerful Jerks...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-features/rage-coaches-are-helping-hollywood-take-on-powerful-jerks-1234947508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Coach Lacey Leone McLaughlin was advising a leader in the entertainment industry recently who had come up in the business working exhausting hours for relentless bosses. It had been an ag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Sequel Pave Way for Theater Return?</title>
      <link>https://www.cinemablend.com/news/2566965/a-quiet-place-part-ii-final-trailer-emily-blunt-john-krasinkis-movie-theater</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cinemablend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The saga of A Quiet Place continues in a fast and loud new trailer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Hunt for WASH POST Next Top Editor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inside-hunt-washington-post-next-084946890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily BeastThe Washington Post is in the closing stages of the hunt for its new top editor, and looks set to finalize a decision in the coming weeks.The Daily Beast spoke with seven knowledgeable people inside and outside the paper, including several with direct insight into the selection process. Over the past few weeks, these industry insiders said, a consensus has emerged that the internal favorite to replace long-time executive editor Marty Baron is Post national editor Steve Ginsberg, whose name has been floated as a potential successor in various outlets over the past year. Others believe the job could still go to New York Times assistant managing editor Marc Lacey, who insiders claimed is viewed as the strongest external candidate.Both of those candidates have strong credentials but come with some drawbacks.Ginsberg is broadly well-liked in the Washington Post newsroom, insiders said, at a time when there has been increasingly public tensions between many staffers and the paper’s management. But he is not seen as a major player in the broader media business and selecting Ginsberg, who is white, would buck the trend of powerful news outlets like CBS News, ABC News, MSNBC, and the Los Angeles Times making diverse hires for their top positions.Lacey is a prominent Black journalist held in very high regard at the Times. A member of two Pulitzer Prize-winning teams, the former Times national editor and foreign correspondent would represent the kind of splashy big-name (and diverse) hire that insiders said Post publisher Fred Ryan may be interested in. However, Lacey is further down the managerial line at the Times and, insiders suggested, his hire would potentially irk some editors at the Post who may be viewed as more qualified than him.Other names like interim editor Cameron Barr, National Geographic editor Susan Goldberg, and New York Times deputy managing editor Carolyn Ryan have been floated as potential successors in previous reporting. Media insiders have also noted that the paper’s process around this hiring has been unpredictable and intensely guarded.Neither Ginsberg nor Lacey responded to requests for comment. A Washington Post spokeswoman labeled this story “wild speculation” but declined to address specific parts of the reporting.Inside the Battle to Run CBS NewsSince Baron announced his departure early last year, the Post has cast a wide net in the hunt for his successor. At one point, the search included now-former ESPN executive Kevin Merida, who reportedly removed himself from the race and was named as the Los Angeles Times’ new top editor earlier this week. Multiple people familiar with the situation told The Daily Beast that Post staffers had privately expressed frustration that Merida, who is Black, was not courted more heavily for the job amid an industry-wide push for more diverse leadership.Another name that had been touted for the gig was New York Times media columnist and former BuzzFeed editor-in-chief Ben Smith, though sources said discussions never reached a serious level on either side. (Smith is currently writing a book about digital media in the blogging heyday of the late aughts, The Daily Beast has learned, including accounts from Gawker founder Nick Denton and BuzzFeed CEO Jonah Peretti.)To the chagrin of some staffers, much of the newsroom—including some relatively senior leaders—have been kept in the dark on the hiring process.Multiple people familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast that unlike other major news outlets like ABC News, which put together a group of staffers to find a new network president earlier this year, there has been no official search committee for Baron’s replacement. Insiders at the paper said that Ryan, the publisher, has largely conducted the search himself, with some assistance from Wayne Connell, the Post’s human resources vice president.Ultimately, Ryan’s decision could also have major implications for another newsroom that is also poised to begin its search for a new editor in the coming months. New York Times editor Dean Baquet is set to turn 65 later this year, the age when top Times masthead editors are typically expected to step down. Lacey, who is among the candidates primed to replace Baquet, would almost certainly increase his chances of getting the executive editor job should he turn down a possible offer to run the Post.Meanwhile, Baron has not been involved in his own succession. One person familiar with the matter told The Daily Beast that the former executive editor’s interest in the Post at this point is almost entirely limited to a book he is currently writing about his time at the newspaper’s helm.Earlier this year, the Post’s employee union sent a letter to the publisher seeking some input in the hiring process and noting that members hoped Ryan would hire a new top editor specifically committed to publishing work about underrepresented communities and the local D.C. area, fostering a more positive work environment, and tackling some lingering, thorny questions about social media policies.Ryan said in response that while some of the requests were “consistent with our vision for this position,” he would not agree to hold an employee town hall on the matter. “Given the confidential and sensitive nature of the executive editor search, however, we do not plan to broadly address the search process with employees,” he wrote in a reply email.Washington Post Braces for Top Editor Marty Baron’s RetirementThe next editor will have to gear up for contract negotiations with a larger, more emboldened staff union under the NewsGuild, which represents a number of media unions including ones at The New York Times and The Daily Beast. People with knowledge of the situation told The Daily Beast that the union—which, unlike other newsroom unions, is voluntary, but includes editorial and many non-editorial commercial staff—has increased membership substantially over the past several years from around 30 percent of staff to nearly 60 percent.Selecting Baron’s successor will prove to be one of the biggest decisions Ryan has made since becoming the Post’s publisher in 2014. People familiar with the situation said that Ryan was envious of Baron’s close relationship with the paper’s owner, Jeff Bezos, and tried to edge Baron out of some meetings with the Amazon founder. A Washington Post spokeswoman hit back, calling the allegations “categorically false.”In many ways, the next top editor will inherit an easier job than the one Baron stepped into. Bezos purchased the paper in 2013, providing a financial lifeline that allowed the paper to expand and invest in ambitious projects that have reversed the paper’s fortunes. The size of the newsroom nearly doubled under Baron, boosting web traffic and digital subscriptions, and opening up more diverse revenue streams including a successful content software licensing business.But the next newsroom leader will also have to contend with growing unrest in the newsroom’s ranks about the handling of sensitive newsroom issues. Staff were up in arms earlier this year after the paper’s leadership prohibited reporter Felicia Sonmez from covering stories related to sexual assault, essentially arguing that she was biased because of her own experience as a survivor (the paper reversed the decision after it became public and sparked outrage online).Others were upset about the recent decision to host Republican Sen. Josh Hawley for a live discussion, noting his key role in denying the legitimacy of the 2020 presidential election.That Tuesday afternoon chat became contentious when Hawley complained the paper was trying to “censor, cancel, and silence me here.” But in a now-viral moment, reporter Cat Zakrzewski fired back: “Senator, we’re hosting you here.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI raid exposes Giuliani and signals widening criminal search, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/06/rudy-giuliani-doj-raid-trump-prosecutors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-profile nature of search highlights inquiry’s seriousness and suggests officials may have new Ukraine-related leads to follow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER massive brawl breaks out at Miami Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9547293/Flight-Club-massive-brawl-breaks-Miami-International-Airport-face-mask.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos shared Wednesday shows a man fighting with two women - said to be from Chicago - after one of the women refused to wear a mask. The brawl is said to have begun after they were deplaned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did agents raid home of wrong woman over Jan. 6 riot? Maybe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/riots-technology-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-0a0f555f20c4d942fb9d3a515d391144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — “We’re looking for Nancy Pelosi’s laptop,” FBI agents told Marilyn Hueper after briefly handcuffing her. Hueper shot back: “That still doesn’t explain why you’re in my home...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Jenner, speaking from her plane hangar, says friends fleeing CA because of homeless people...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/caitlyn-jenner-speaking-from-her-plane-hangar-says-friends-are-fleeing-california-because-of-homeless-people/ar-BB1gq4lE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner’s attempt to court social conservatives in her recall-election campaign for California governor has sometimes put her in a tenuous spot, particularly as one of the most visible transgender women in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX series signals racial breakthrough in Italian TV...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/beyonce-knowles-europe-entertainment-race-and-ethnicity-business-638014ca4dcdcd4f8d84f5f33b26c71d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — The Netflix series “Zero,” which premiered globally last month, is the first Italian TV production to feature a predominantly Black cast, a bright spot in an otherwise bleak Italian television landscape where the persistent use of racist language and imagery is sparking new protests...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York's Luxury-Rent Rebound Leaves London Homes in Doldrums...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/new-york-s-luxury-rent-rebound-leaves-london-homes-in-doldrums/ar-BB1gpN8j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s luxury-home market is showing early signs of recovery, storming ahead of rival financial hub London and other global cities with a sudden rebound in rental growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand weightlifter set to be first trans Olympian...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210506-new-zealand-weightlifter-set-to-be-first-transgender-olympian</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand weightlifter set to be first transgender Olympian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Jet South to Caribbean Beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/where-can-you-fly-right-now-americans-jet-to-caribbean-with-other-places-shut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where Can You Fly Right Now? Americans Jet South to Caribbean Beaches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Vaccine Patent Shock Roils Pharma as Talks Move to WTO...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/u-back-waiver-vaccine-ip-194403661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S.’s sudden support for a waiver of patent protections for Covid-19 vaccines headed to the World Trade Organization, setting the stage for potentially thorny negotiations over sharing the proprietary know-how needed to boost global supplies of the life-saving shots.“In terms of how soon the WTO can deliver -- that literally depends on the WTO members, collectively, being able to deliver,” U.S. Trade Representative Katherine Tai said in an interview Wednesday. “I am the first one to admit that what we are leaning into is a process that is not going to be easy.”With the European Union and China signaling a willingness to take part in the debate after the Biden administration’s shock announcement, pharmaceutical executives reacted with anger and their stock prices tumbled worldwide.BioNTech SE’s depository receipts dropped as much as 19% in Germany while shares in Pfizer Inc. were down 2.5% in U.S. premarket trading as of 7:10 a.m. in New York, after closing little changed. Together, the companies sell the messenger RNA shot that was one of the first to win regulatory endorsement.“This change in longstanding American policy will not save lives,” said Stephen Ubl, the president and CEO of PhRMA, the biopharma industry’s lobbying group. “This decision does nothing to address the real challenges to getting more shots in arms, including last-mile distribution and limited availability of raw materials.”CureVac NV of Germany, which is developing another mRNA vaccine, fell as much as 17%, while Asian vaccine stocks including Shanghai Fosun Pharmaceutical Group Co. and CanSino Biologics Inc. also slumped.“The EU is ready to discuss any proposal that addresses the crisis in an effective and pragmatic manner,” European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen told a virtual conference in Florence, Italy on Thursday. “And that’s why we are ready to discuss how the U.S. proposal for a waiver on IP protection for Covid vaccines could help achieve that objective.”The U.S. and Europe have been strong supporters of IP protections at the WTO over the years, particularly as a way to enforce problems like Chinese patent infringement. As the pandemic leads to some of the world’s more monumental and lucrative scientific discoveries, defenders of IP rights are warming to exceptions on ethical grounds when it comes to vaccines even though the drug companies argue it’ll do more harm than good.The WTO’s General Council meets again on Thursday, though any final waiver of intellectual-property protections may take weeks to hammer out in the face of opposition from the pharmaceutical industry. Tai added that she sees momentum from WTO Director-General Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala “to take this opportunity and see what is the WTO capable of.”In a statement, Okonjo-Iweala called it the “moral and economic issue of our time.”The Biden administration will encourage other countries to join its position, Tai said. “We are for the waiver at the WTO, we are for what the proponents of the waiver are trying to accomplish, which is better access, more manufacturing capability, more shots in arms,” she said.Drugmakers argue that the plan is ineffective and that few countries have the capacity to produce more vaccines even if they knew the formulas. Also, there’s limited global supply of the materials needed, and building new factories with the necessary technology to produce the vaccines could take years, they say.Nathalie Moll, director general of the European Federation of Pharmaceutical Industries and Associations, said the Biden administration’s decision “puts the hard-won progress in fighting this terrible disease in jeopardy.”“While we wholeheartedly agree with the goal of protecting citizens around the world through vaccines, waiving patents will make winning the fight against the coronavirus even harder,” Moll said.India and South Africa, two nations struggling to contain fresh outbreaks of Covid-19, have been urging WTO members to temporarily suspend rules on IP rights, arguing that it would be the most efficient and equitable way to address vaccine shortages in poor countries.”We will be exercising our convening power at the WTO to bring members together to work towards resolving the different viewpoints to bridge the gap so that the WTO can be relevant, the WTO can be a force for good,” Tai said.The U.S. wasn’t the only country with initial reservations. The EU, U.K., Japan, Switzerland, Brazil and Norway have also resisted earlier proposals. However, supporters of the waiver argue that U.S. leadership on the issue could help sway other holdouts. The timing for approval of the waiver depends on how soon member states can find agreement.Norway’s foreign ministry on Thursday praised the U.S.’s decision to “commit itself to finding a solution that is less far-reaching than the proposal that was originally on the table, and on which there was great disagreement. This could be a limited and targeted measure to avoid patents being a possible bottleneck.”WTO chief Okonjo-Iweala said proponents of the waiver were planning to revise a proposal initially submitted in October 2020 and asked for a meeting open to all WTO members in the second half of May, before the next formal gathering on the issue slated for early June.As the U.S. inoculations advanced and outbreaks diminished in recent weeks, the White House came under pressure from progressive Democrats and public-health advocates to take a stance while India in particular suffers from surging deaths and infections.Tai also met with top executives of vaccine-producing companies and held calls with members of Congress and other stakeholders in civil society and public health. In April, she called on the pharma companies to make sacrifices.“The desperate needs that our people face in the current pandemic provide these companies with an opportunity to be the heroes they claim to be -- and can be,” she said at a virtual conference at the WTO.(Updates markets)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General: China's Africa outreach poses threat from Atlantic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-africa-china-business-government-and-politics-24f774a952eaabcb38d2b25380b61a62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The top U.S general for Africa is warning that a growing threat from China may come not just from the waters of the Pacific but from the Atlantic as well...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
