<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Fires Back With Photo From Khashoggi Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jeff-bezos-cryptically-responds-to-reports-of-saudi-hacking-with-image-from-jamal-khashoggi-memorial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos responded to Saudi Arabia today over reports that his phone was hacked through WhatsApp by crown prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA QUARANTINES WUHAN</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/china-quarantines-wuhan-coronavirus-outbreak-reports</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus has been linked to at least 17 deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Fast Track...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29b81fda30045ec649467abb7ee47d28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. Senate began hearing opening arguments Wednesday in President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial with proceedings now on a fast track. First up: Democratic House managers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flips out at reporter: 'Why why why why why why why?!?'   </title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/biden-flips-out-at-reporter-why-why-why-why-why-why-why/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This wasn’t a stutter — he just flipped out. After a campaign event in Mason City, Iowa on Wednesday, Joe Biden was being pursued by CBS reporter Ed O’Keefe, who wanted to know about Biden’s recent kerfuffle with Bernie Sanders. WATCH: After a campaign event in Mason City, Iowa, @joebiden reacts to @edokeefe's question about …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden cries on live TV, says 'Beau should be running for president, not me'...   </title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/295466/joe-biden-2020-election-beau-should-be-running-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden spoke emotionally today about his late son Beau — who he says “should be the one running for president, not me.” The former vice president described on MSNBC how much Beau, who died from …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico investigating possible case...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/americas/mexico-says-possible-case-of-coronavirus-under-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (REUTERS) - Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said on Wednesday (Jan 22) that authorities are investigating one potential case of coronavirus in the northern border state of Tamaulipas.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUIBI Whitman Ripped for Comparing Journalists to Sexual Predators...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/business-leaders/quibi-ceo-meg-whitman-journalists-sexual-predators</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whitman reportedly compared members of the media who cultivate sources within a company to sexual predators who “groom” underage victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry, Meghan could get $50 million book deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/abrambrown/2020/01/22/megxit-millions-how-harry-and-meghan-can-write-a-new-chapterand-get-royally-rich/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are our twopence on what the couple should do to earn an income: Take a page from the royal playbook—and write a book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA QUARANTINES WUHAN</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-china-quarantines-wuhan--21337907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Coronavirus has already claimed the lives of 17 people, with cases confirmed in China, Japan, Korea and the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds near banning emotional support animals from planes...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/policy/emotional-support-animals-banned-planes-dot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proposed rule would let airlines ban most "emotional support" animals in airplane cabins and board only trained service dogs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five questions scientists asking...</title>
      <link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-020-00166-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nature.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are racing to find out more about the epidemiology and genetic sequence of the coronavirus spreading in Asia and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468322-1/senate-impeachment-trial-day-3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate impeachment trial of President Trump continues with opening arguments from House managers and the President's defense team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What are they afraid of?'</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/479361-conway-says-senate-gop-knows-trump-is-guilty-what-are-they-afraid-of</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, a conservative lawyer and husband to White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, on Wednesday denounced Senate Republicans for blocking new witnesses and documents from the opening stage of the impeachment trial, claiming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAFT: 'We Plan To' Bring Brady Back To PATRIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/01/22/robert-kraft-tom-brady-new-england-patriots-nfl-free-agent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And now TMZ Sports Presents: Terrible Clip, Great Soundbite ... starring Robert Kraft!!!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous Oscar Voter: '1917 and 'JOKER' will win big, diversity issues overblown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/an-anonymous-oscar-voter-reveals-1917-and-joker-will-win-big-diversity-problems-overblown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anonymous Oscar voter reveals all to Michael Musto, including which film they believe will win Best Picture, why only one person of color was nominated, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Paint Picture of Serial Sex Predator... </title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/weinstein-prosecutors-paint-picture-serial-sexual-predator-opening-remarks-1272001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state revealed the identity of the second woman who is part of the case against the embattled mogul, an aspiring actress named Jessica Mann.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Attorneys To Use 'Loving' E-Mails To Challenge Accusers...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/harvey-weinstein-trial-opening-statements-defense-attorneys-loving-e-mails-challenge-accusers-1202836693/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with change of venue motion denied: In their opening statements at Harvey Weinstein’s criminal rape trial on Wednesday, Weinstein’s defense team will be able to refer to what they say are “…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eichner To Play Matt Drudge in 'AMERICAN CRIME STORY:  IMPEACHMENT'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/american-crime-story-impeachment-billy-eichner-matt-drudge-cast-drudge-report-1202837579/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Three-time Emmy nominee and American Horror Story alum Billy Eichner is joining FX’s Bill Clinton-Monica Lewinsky sex scandal limited series American Crime Story: Impeachment in th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing humiliating controls, Lebanese focus fury on banks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/92cd18d3cb9a756d2d436952aeda70f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Before picking up cash from a downtown bank in Lebanon's capital, Mey Al Sayegh mentally braces herself for what would have been a routine trip before the country's crippling cash...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW CASES RISE SHARPLY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/902c9f9f551d55b227b3d754f42aad50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Chinese health authorities urged people in the city of Wuhan to avoid crowds and public gatherings, after warning that a new viral illness that has infected more than 400 people and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD ON BRAZIL'S CHARGES AGAINST HIM...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/q-and-a/glenn-greenwald-on-brazils-charges-against-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“What a lot of people are not fully understanding about Brazil is that there are a lot of people in the government, beginning with the President himself, who explicitly want a resurrection of the military dictatorship,” Greenwald said. “They are not joking about it.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITNESS SWAP:  BIDEN FOR BOLTON?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-democrats-privately-mull-biden-for-bolton-trade-in-impeachment-trial/ar-BBZcdgW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Conway Rips 'Utterly Shameless' Lawyers...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/george-conway-rips-utterly-shameless-trump-lawyers-in-rare-tv-appearance-treating-the-senate-like-theyre-morons/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Trump's lawyers...were dissembling, distorting and even lying."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly restored 15th-century lamb leaves art world speechless...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/ghent-altarpiece-restoration-scli-intl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There are no words to express the result" was the beaming reaction of Belgium's Royal Institute for Cultural Heritage, after a 15th-century masterpiece -- painted over shortly after completion -- was restored to its former glory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE IN WASHINGTON STATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/21/health/wuhan-coronavirus-first-us-case-cdc-bn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has its first confirmed case of a new virus that appeared in Wuhan, China, last month, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention announced Tuesday. The coronavirus has already sickened hundreds and killed six people in Asia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Suspended GRAMMYS CEO alleges corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/grammys-ceo-deborah-dugan-discrimination-complaint-corruption-recording-academy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dugan alleges she was suspended for reporting misconduct within the Academy, detailing several explosive claims in the 46-page complaint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female sniper with 309 confirmed kills revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10792272/female-sniper-fascinating-pictures-lethal-world-war-two-sharpshooters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FEMALE sniper nicknamed “Lady Death” is revealed in these remarkable photos that show Second World War’s deadliest snipers in action. Credited with 309 kills, the Ukrainian-born…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,000 INFECTED?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2020/01/22/passengers-virus-hit-region-china-separated-heathrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 4,000 people in the city at the epicentre of an outbreak of a mystery new coronavirus could be infected with the disease, experts have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bench-clearing brawl erupts at end of college basketball game...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/sports/bench-clearing-brawl-erupts-end-kansas-kansas-state-basketball-game-n1119951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fight appeared to start after Silvio De Sousa of Kansas blocked a shot by a Kansas State freshman, sending the player to the floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEINSTEIN WITHOUT WALKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7916219/Harvey-Weinstein-arrives-opening-statements-landmark-rape-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers will make their opening statements to a jury of seven men and five women on Wednesday in the trial of Weinstein. He has pleaded not guilty to assaulting two women in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAUNTED OVER AFFAIR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7916121/Saudi-prince-sent-Bezos-sexist-joke-negotiating-women-planning-divorce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WhatsApp was message was sent to Bezos by Mohammed bin Salman in November 2018, two months before his affair with Lauren Sanchez was revealed by The National Enquirer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KINGDOM DENIES...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/22/saudi-arabia-calls-claims-that-crown-prince-hacked-jeff-bezos-phone-absurd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reports claim a malicious file was sent during a “seemingly friendly” WhatsApp chat between Bezos and Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial Begins...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/01/22/harvey-weinstein-trial-opening-statements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of women have accused of the disgraced movie producer of sexual misconduct, but his trial will focus on just two allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN CALLS FOR PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a490f73620f267ac3c96c6cd25348f6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The phone of Amazon billionaire and Washington Post owner Jeff Bezos was hacked after receiving a file sent from an account used by Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why PET SHOP BOYS still cleverest men in pop...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/culture/story/20200121-why-pet-shop-boys-are-still-the-cleverest-men-in-pop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For nearly 40 years, the duo have served up social commentary and infectious electro-pop. As they release their 14th album, they remain a unique musical force, writes Nick Levine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie joins Biden atop 2020 field...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/22/politics/cnn-poll-sanders-biden-january-national/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vermont Sen. Bernie Sanders has improved his standing in the national Democratic race for president, joining former Vice President Joe Biden in a two-person top tier above the rest of the field, according to a new CNN poll conducted by SSRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gabbard suing Clinton for defamation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479320-gabbard-suing-clinton-for-defamation-over-russian-asset-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Tulsi Gabbard (D-Hawaii) is suing Hillary Clinton for defamation over the former secretary of state's remarks on a podcast characterizing the Democratic presidential candidate as a Russian asset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary tears open wound with attack on Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/479268-hillary-clinton-tears-open-wound-with-her-attack-on-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton has torn open old wounds from her divisive 2016 battle with Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondhand screen time the new secondhand smoking?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/secondhand-screen-time-secondhand-smoking-133748940.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Environmental Protection Agency first warned of secondhand smoke in 1991, some 30 years after scientists determined that smoking cigarettes causes cancer. Today, a growing body of research points toward a new indirect health hazard.Just as frequently being around other people while they smoke can</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts admonishes both sides...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ddec6989614fea6b5421c130a4ee4efa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Chief Justice John Roberts drew little attention to himself in the beginning 12 hours of his first impeachment trial. But it was just before 1 a.m., as tempers on the floor had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-stunned iguanas falling from Florida trees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1ee59a008042351cbdf75540242ae4d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The National Weather Service routinely warns people about falling rain, snow and hail, but temperatures are dropping so low in South Florida the forecasters warned residents Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-senate-rejects-democrats-calls-for-early-witnesses-in-late-night-debate-2020-01-22/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first day of proceedings stretched into the early morning as Democrats pushed for but failed in their efforts to have subpoenas issued for witnesses and documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK VS THE SKEPTICS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-tesla-tslaq-skeptics-who-bet-against-elon-musk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tesla Skeptics Who Bet Against Elon Musk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorean military to discharge first trans soldier in landmark case...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/south-korean-military-discharge-first-115442241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A transgender South Korean soldier who enlisted as a man and underwent gender reassignment last year pleaded tearfully to be allowed to stay in uniform Wednesday after the military decided to discharge her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On menu at virus market: Rats and live wolf pups...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/menu-china-virus-market-rats-live-wolf-pups-111650959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The food market where China's deadly virus surfaced was a smorgasbord of exotic wildlife ranging from wolf pups to species linked to previous pandemics such as civets, according to vendor information and a Chinese media report. The Huanan Seafood Market in the central city of Wuhan came under greater</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fears grow...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200122090011-gpm8d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/ (WRAPUP 5, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 5-Pandemic fears grow as China virus toll rises to nine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods eyes record 83rd win...</title>
      <link>https://www.pgatour.com/news/2020/01/21/tiger-woods-torrey-pines-farmers-insurance-open-chases-83rd-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pgatour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LA JOLLA, Calif. – It is fitting that Tiger Woods’ first opportunity to set the PGA TOUR wins record comes at Torrey Pines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders rifts may help Trump, Dems fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Sanders-rifts-may-help-Trump-Democrats-fear-14993595.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMES, Iowa - On Tuesday, when Democrats had hoped to focus Americans squarely on President Donald Trump's impeachment trial, many in the party were instead watching in alarm and dismay as a fresh spat erupted between Hillary Clinton and the candidate she defeated in 2016, Sen. Bernie Sanders.  In comments published early Tuesday, Clinton left open the possibility that she might not support Sanders if he is the party's nominee. The remarks unleashed fresh angst less than two weeks before the Iowa caucuses amid a flurry of other attacks dividing the presidential candidates and their allies.  Sanders, I-Vt., has been engaged in battles with rivals on various fronts over the past week - squabbling with Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., over whether he once said a woman could not be president, attacking former vice president Joe Biden with an out-of-context video about Social Security and issuing a rare apology after a top surrogate called Biden corrupt.  The conflicts have reignited Democratic fears that, whoever becomes the nominee, the party will rupture as it did in 2016, when divisions between the Clinton and Sanders camps marred the primaries and the summer convention, and were blamed by many for contributing to her loss to Trump that November.  "Nobody wants to re-litigate 2016. I don't want Democrats focused on the last campaign; I want to focus on the next campaign," said Terry McAuliffe, the former Virginia governor and former head of the Democratic National Committee. "People have to check their attacks. We can't get in the mud pit where Donald Trump wants to be. Let's not be playing on his turf."  "If Bernie is the nominee," he added, "everyone has to rally."  Rebecca Katz, a liberal New York-based consultant, put the blame squarely on Clinton.  "This is bringing up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANGER:  TESLA stock rally 'extremely unusual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-rally-extremely-unusual-analyst-says-2020-01-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla shares resume their rally on Tuesday with the company pushing back against “unintended acceleration” safety allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX changes its view on 'views,' which will boost its numbers by 35%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/netflix-changes-its-view-on-views-which-will-boost-its-numbers-by-35-2020-01-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does it mean to “watch” a show on a streaming service? For Netflix Inc., it now means viewing at least two minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE US troops evacuated from Iraq for medical evaluation after Iran missile attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7913983/US-United-States-Iran-Missiles-Injuries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional U.S. troops have been flown out of Iraq for closer evaluation of potential concussion injuries from the Iranian missile attack of January 8, U.S. defense officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell in 1999: I support 'live witnesses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/21/politics/mcconnell-1999-impeachment-kfile/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell said in 1999 he believed the Senate was entitled to witnesses in President Bill Clinton's impeachment trial and added that he would have voted to give House impeachment managers "whatever" they wanted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collins and Romney hold keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Collins-and-Romney-hold-the-keys-in-the-14993295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyes will be glued to the Senate floor over the next two weeks as the Senate formally conducts its impeachment trial of President Donald Trump. The process got off the ground Tuesday as the two sides debated the rules.  But in actuality, much if it is window-dressing. The most significant stuff is what's happening off the Senate floor - particularly when it comes to potential GOP swing votes like Sens. Susan Collins of Maine and Mitt Romney of Utah. They hold the keys to new evidence that could actually change hardened views of Trump's actions with regard to Ukraine, and their words and actions are what matter most.  And a couple of significant things happened in that regard Tuesday.  One was a change to the rules that were initially proposed by Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky. The change brought the rules more in line with how they were during Bill Clinton's impeachment trial, and they were reportedly changed at the urging of Collins and others.  One rule change made it so evidence compiled by the House would automatically be included in the record, subject to objections by Trump's legal team, whereas before the Senate had to approve that. The other is that the 24 hours of opening arguments that have been allotted to each side will take place over three days each, rather than two each. Both of these are changes that Democrats wanted, and they apparently got some Republicans to side with them - enough to force McConnell to preemptively change the rules, just as the proceedings were beginning.  Democrats might be encouraged by that for a few reasons. One is that it reinforces the fact that McConnell wasn't actually going with the complete Clinton rules and erred in Trump's direction on a couple of things. It suggests that McConnell either wasn't aware of these objections or that they materialized later in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrific photos of starving lions at zoo prompt outcry...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/truly-horrific-photos-starving-lions-161725942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of malnourished and dying lions at a zoo in Sudan have sparked global backlash and a growing online campaign to save the animals.The five African lions were found in an emaciated state by activist Osman Salih in Khartoum’s Al-Qureshi Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg calls for Trump removal in new ad...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f73765998174ca6e9bd93350c26557d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democratic presidential candidate Michael Bloomberg launched a new impeachment-focused television ad Tuesday urging the Senate to remove President Donald Trump from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature checks, extra cleaning at airports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c27ec8b555c6a4fb0d8defab61618928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Many countries are checking the temperatures of arriving airline passengers and adopting precautionary quarantine procedures in response to a new virus that has sickened nearly 300...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29afb0d57286930a98a467a8a4523e89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Democratic presidential candidates have spent weeks reassuring voters they can unify the party, avoid the divisions that plagued the 2016 primary and defeat President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff: U.S. troops block Russian forces from capturing Syrian oil field...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/21/us-troops-block-russian-forces-capturing-syrian-oi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. troops last weekend reportedly found themselves in a standoff with Russian forces trying to gain access to key oil fields in northeastern Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JFK Mistress Gunned Down in Cold Blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-jfk-mistress-mary-pinchot-meyer-was-gunned-down-in-cold-blood-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among those haunted by the memory of President Kennedy’s murdered lover, Mary Meyer, were the most powerful reporters—and spies—in America. What secrets were in her lost diary?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC COMICS' first Asian American GREEN LANTERN Lantern is boy who fights racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/dc-comics-first-asian-american-green-lantern-boy-who-fights-n1119751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To be able to write a story that centers our community — where we're not just background characters or sidekicks but the actual heroes of the story — was really meaningful," author Minh Lê said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Antonio Brown Reportedly Facing Felony Battery Charges After Incident At FL Home...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/01/21/hollywood-police-antonio-brown-battery-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a heavy police presence at Antonio Brown’s residence Tuesday evening, and multiple reports believe it's linked to a battery on his property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: SAUDI PRINCE HACKED BEZOS' PHONE!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jan/21/amazon-boss-jeff-bezoss-phone-hacked-by-saudi-crown-prince</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: investigation suggests Washington Post owner was targeted five months before murder of Jamal Khashoggi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lose First Battle to Subpoena White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7912653/Donald-Trumps-Senate-trial-begins-senators-war-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats lost the first round in Donald Trump's impeachment trial when the Senate voted down an attempt by Chuck Schumer to subpoena documents from the White House on the Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service warns of falling iguanas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/21/weather/miami-freeze-falling-iguana-forecast-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday afternoon, the National Weather Service in Miami issued a rare forecast regarding cold temperatures but it was for iguanas. Yes, you read that correctly. Iguanas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Large Police Presence, 'Active Scene' In Front Of Antonio Brown's FL Home...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/01/21/police-at-antonio-browns-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is reportedly a large police presence and "active scene" in front of Antonio Brown's home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House weighs travel ban expansion in coming days...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/21/donald-trump-travel-ban-expansion-101581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is eyeing seven countries for new immigration restrictions three years after its original order, which created an uproar for targeting Muslim-majority nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says may seek 'new path' of weapons build-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/north-korea-says-may-seek-new-path-of-weapons-build-up/ar-BBZbE5Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror spies stationed across US...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-has-spies-across-u-s-officials-warn-after-tehran-posts-3m-bounty-on-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials and terrorism experts are warning that Iran has significantly expanded its terror capabilities in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators bend by wearing APPLE Watches...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/218484-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight senators had Apple watches to their wrists at the start of the impeachment trial Tuesday, despite a ban on electronics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell softens hard-line tactics...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/21/mcconnell-schumer-senate-impeachment-trial-101372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Senate Republicans are still preparing to steamroll Democrats on the rules to govern the impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-minute, handwritten changes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/mcconnell-makes-last-minute-changes-trump-impeachment-trial-rules-n1119511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sudden revision in the Senate's organizing resolution also ensures House Democrats' evidence will be admitted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa's richest woman under scrutiny after docs show she's exploiting country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/africas-richest-woman-is-barred-from-her-bank-and-under-investigation/ar-BBZa7XU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Player Making Anti-Abortion Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/patriots-benjamin-watson-producing-abortion-documentary-1270926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie, budgeted at less than $1 million, features former presidential candidate Ben Carson and Alveda King, the niece of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabs, kills pro-Trump boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2020/01/21/man-stabs-kills-pro-trump-boss-drapes-american-flag-over-him-deputies-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed to death by his coworker in an apparent argument over their views on the government and President Donald Trump, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100s in river 'no-man's land' after Mexico troops block way...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d685100193f6a2c521267fe614356df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Hundreds of Central American migrants were stranded in a sort of no-man’s land on the river border between Guatemala and Mexico after running up against lines of...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
