<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Cities see spike in cheating spouses...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/22/cities-most-ashley-madison-accounts-cheating-husbands/720864002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheating husbands and wives might be most common in Seattle, Washington, according to a report from infidelity website Ashley Madison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Positive Death Movement Comes to Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/22/nyregion/the-positive-death-movement-comes-to-life.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Death cafes, death doulas, ‘Ask a Mortician,’ DeathLab — once the province of goth subculture, death is having a moment in the sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKI publishes identities, info about ICE employees...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/WikiLeaks-publishes-identities-and-information-13016546.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks on Thursday published a database identifying more than 9,000 supposed current and former U.S. Immigration Customs Enforcement employees, saying it is important for "increasing accountability." The database contains the employees' publicly available personal information and job history scraped from LinkedIn, including deportation officers, IT workers, human resource interns and legal assistants, among others. The list includes their LinkedIn profile photos and information on educational background and the city and state where they're based.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, gender and social change: Cambodian blogger tackles taboos...</title>
      <link>http://www.freemalaysiatoday.com/category/world/2018/06/22/sex-gender-and-social-change-cambodian-blogger-tackles-taboos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freemalaysiatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hosted on Facebook, the show by a 23-year-old Cambodian woman tackles the finer points of sex education, women's health and gender imbalances in a country where the #MeToo movement has barely registered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vomiting, headaches: At least 33 children fall ill at Florida camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/health/33-children-examined-after-getting-sick-at-lake-placid-4-h-camp/67-566530714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtsp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Children at a summer camp in Highlands County are being monitored after falling ill, county officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Faces 'Unprecedented Threat' From China on Tech Takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-22/china-s-thousand-talents-called-key-in-seizing-u-s-expertise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s “Thousand Talents” program to tap into its citizens educated or employed in the U.S. is a key part of multi-pronged efforts to transfer, replicate and eventually overtake U.S. military and commercial technology, according to American intelligence officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thirty Years On, How Well Do 'Global Warming' Predictions Stand Up?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/thirty-years-on-how-well-do-global-warming-predictions-stand-up-1529623442 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Hansen issued dire warnings in the summer of 1988. Today earth is only modestly warmer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shari Redstone's Path to Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shari-redstones-path-to-power-1529659921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the heiress overcame a falling out with her father to become the most significant female media owner in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busted flush: Fans spark plumbing pinch in World Cup bathroom dash...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/sport/busted-flush--japan-fans-spark-plumbing-pinch-in-world-cup-loo-dash-10459732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armchair Japan fans following their team's 2-1 World Cup win over Colombia risked triggering a plumbing disaster of biblical proportions when ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAUTHAMMER DEAD...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2018/06/21/charles-krauthammer-conservative-commentator-and-pulitzer-prize-winner-dead-at-68.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Charles Krauthammer, a longtime Fox News contributor, Pulitzer Prize winner, Harvard-trained psychiatrist and best-selling author who came to be known as the dean of conservative commentators, has died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscientist Claims Majority Of Diseases Caused By Negative Thoughts...</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/as-loneliness-rises-among-americans-experts-warn-its-making-many-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health experts weigh in on how loneliness has become a major problem today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAD:  GIRL ON 'TIME' COVER WAS NEVER SEPARATED FROM MOTHER...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5869829/Father-two-year-old-face-child-separation-crisis-speaks-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Denis Javier Varela Hernandez said that he had not heard from his wife for a month until he saw the image of her and their daughter being apprehended in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROSEANNE' WITHOUT ROSEANNE GETS ABC GREENLIGHT...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/roseanne-spinoff-conners-officially-a-go-at-abc-1117397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After canceling the comedy following star Roseanne Barr's racist tweet, the Disney-owned network has found a way to move forward with the original cast, creators and likely crew as 'The Conners.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JARED MIDEAST PEACE PUSH IN EGYPT...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/kushner-egypts-sissi-discuss-israel-palestinian-peace-process/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Egyptian president calls for two-state solution, with East Jerusalem as Palestinian capital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venomous Caterpillar Sends Teen To Emergency Room...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/venomous-caterpillar-sends-teen-to-emergency-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A teenager in Florida experienced "the worst pain of his life" after coming in contact with a venomous caterpillar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sessions on the Bible and His Critics...</title>
      <link>http://www1.cbn.com/cbnnews/politics/2018/june/i-dont-think-it-was-an-extreme-position-i-took-jeff-sessions-on-the-bible-immigration-and-his-critics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www1.cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Jeff Sessions addressed some of the criticism he and the White House have received in recent weeks regarding the administration's immigration policy in an exclusive interview Thursday with CBN News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Majority Blame Illegal Parents For Crisis...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/rasmussen-parents-to-blame-border-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;54 percent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unaccompanied Alien Children Charged in Execution-Style Murder, Media Calls Them 'Baby-Faced Boys'...</title>
      <link>https://www.judicialwatch.org/blog/2016/02/unaccompanied-alien-children-charged-in-execution-style-murder-media-calls-them-baby-faced-boys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.judicialwatch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears that the recent execution-style murder of a Massachusetts man was committed by two Central American teens that came to the U.S. as Unaccompanied Alien Children (UAC) under President Obama’s open border free-for-all. Tens of thousands of illegal immigrant minors—mostly from El Salvador, Guatemala and Honduras—have entered the country through the Mexican border sinceRead the full post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA Moving All Its Data to Top Secret Cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/06/nsa-systematically-moving-all-its-data-cloud/149179/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Security Agency is all-in on cloud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: Canada uses massive US anti-terrorist database at borders...</title>
      <link>https://amp.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/21/canada-us-tuscan-anti-terrorist-database-at-borders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;amp.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuscan is separate from Canada’s official no-fly list and has more than 680,000 names provided to every border guard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST LADY FASHION FIREWORKS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf927d4412604313af8ac0d81b8c540f/Melania-Trump-dons-'I-really-don't-care,-do-u?%27-jacket</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Melania Trump went to Texas to show she cared about migrant children. Her fashion choice carried a baffling counter-message.        The first lady wore a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Already Made Record $2B At Box Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/disney-already-made-2-billion-domestic-box-office-this-year-black-panther-infinity-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Does West have will to survive?</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/has-the-west-the-will-to-survive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If you’re … pathetically weak, the country is going to be overrun with millions of people, and if you’re strong, then you don’t have any heart, that’s a tough dilemma. … I’d rather be strong.” So said President Donald Trump, on issuing his order halting the separation of children from parents caught breaking into the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST Won't Cover AMAZON Warehouse Conditions...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/democracy-dies-in-amazons-warehouses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why not?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Star NFL QB Suspension Looms Over UBER Groping Accusation...</title>
      <link>http://www.tampabay.com/blogs/bucs/2018/06/21/three-game-suspension-looms-for-bucs-qb-jameis-winston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAMPA — The Bucs will open the upcoming season without the face of their franchise, as quarterback Jameis Winston will be suspended three games by the NFL for violating the league's personal co</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist: WASH POST Killed Story Over Retweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/analysis/washington-post-twitter-apology.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacket Sends Message To Media...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-melanias-jacket-was-a-message-to-fake-news-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Military Aircraft Targeted By Lasers in Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-military-aircraft-targeted-by-lasers-in-pacific-ocean-u-s-officials-say-1529613999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials say pilots of American military aircraft operating in the Pacific Ocean have been targeted by lasers more than 20 times in recent months, incidents that follow a series of similar ones in which officials say Chinese personnel used lasers against American pilots in East Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Accuses NYT, WASH POST Of 'Irresponsible' Reporting...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/awkward/its-not-responsible-muellers-office-calls-out-new-york-times-for-incorrect-story-about-picking-manaforts-lock/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Electromagnetic Railgun War Ready By 2025...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/china-will-have-worlds-most-powerful-naval-gun-by-2025-us-intelligence-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The warship-mounted electromagnetic railgun is expected to enter China's arsenal by 2025, ahead of the U.S. and Russia, according to sources with direct knowledge of a U.S. intelligence report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Who  Wrote The Book On Corruption Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/crazy/judge-who-literally-wrote-the-book-on-corruption-indicted-on-fraud-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street slumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dow-drops-open-technology-stocks-boost-nasdaq-133905565--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) - U.S. stocks fell on Thursday, with the Dow marking an eighth straight decline, as industrials wobbled again on trade war concerns while Amazon and other online retailers weakened after a U.S. Supreme Court ruling on state sales tax collection. The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow extends 8 day losing streak...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/us-stock-futures-data-trade-oil-and-politics-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell on Thursday as fears of an impending trade war between the U.S. and China dragged investor sentiment lower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELANIA SURPRISE BORDER VISIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/21/politics/melania-trump-border-visit-immigration/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First lady Melania Trump touched down in McAllen, Texas, Thursday making a publicly unannounced and hastily planned trip to get a first-hand look at the crisis affecting immigrant families at the US border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viruses may play a role in Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8e4ebccd8f09446d982eb63b85aafa9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Viruses that sneak into the brain just might play a role in Alzheimer's, scientists reported Thursday in a provocative study that promises to re-ignite some long</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graydon Carter tried buying VANITY FAIR before leaving...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/graydon-carter-is-launching-his-own-media-company/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revenge may just be the sweetest victory for Graydon Carter. The legendary magazine editor, less than a year after stepping away from Vanity Fair, is close to launching his own media company, The P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 injured swerving to avoid kangaroo -- in Montana...</title>
      <link>http://www.kfbb.com/story/38478130/two-injured-in-montana-after-swerving-to-avoid-a-kangaroo-really</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kfbb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people were injured in Montana Wednesday morning after swerving to avoid a kangaroo on the road.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Billboard Telling 'Liberals' To 'Keep Driving' Out Of Texas Removed...</title>
      <link>http://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/liberals-keep-driving-billboard-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas billboard that sparked controversy and death threats online after going viral on social media this week has been removed.  That according to the company that manages the sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION IN CONGRESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/whats-the-difference-between-the-immigration-bills-and-how-will-this-play-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans' attempts at immigration reform aren't going as smoothly as hoped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seafood tied to more sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/seafood-tied-more-sex-faster-conception-191302101.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers followed 500 couples in Michigan and Texas for one year, asking them to log their seafood consumption and sexual activity in daily journals. "While an increase in sexual activity might be one behavioral mechanism linking seafood intake to higher fecundity, it is not the only mechanism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Alyssa Milano offers to foster children brought to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/alyssa-milano-offers-to-foster-migrant-children-brought-to-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actress Alyssa Milano wants to take in one of the hundreds of immigrant children housed in foster care facilities in Harlem, who were torn from their parents under President Trump’s “zero tolerance…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn industry awaits #MeToo moment...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-porn-metoo-misconduct-20180614-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The general public has a negative perception about a porn actor’s credibility because they’ve been paid to have sex in front of a camera – making it all the more difficult for performers to prove they’ve been sexually assaulted by a romantic partner or someone in the industry, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lion euthanized after escape from zoo...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/belgian-zoo-evacuated-lion-escapes-cage-095034130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MECHELEN, Belgium (AP) — A lion on the loose forced the evacuation of one Belgium's most famous zoos Thursday, and the animal had to be killed after several failed attempts to sedate it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorful 'Fire Rainbows' Seen In Skies Over Northeast...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/21/fire-rainbows-clouds-formed-circumhorizontal-arc-new-hampshire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was an unusual sight in the blue skies over New England this week – an apparent rainbow in the clouds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom bathes toddler in bleach to keep alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/21/mom-bathes-toddler-rare-skin-disorder-bleach-keep-him-alive/718328002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mom from Washington state bathes her 1-year-old son with harlequin ichthyosis in bleach twice a week, because she wants him to defy the odds. Alicia Barber is hopeful she won't need to use the toxic chemical forever. She's searching for other options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter Of DC Public Schools Teachers Unlicensed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Approximately-1000-DC-Public-Schools-Teachers-Are-Unlicensed-486076271.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 1,000 D.C. Public Schools teachers do not have a D.C. teaching license, according to a yearlong investigation by the News4 I-Team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rips Obama's 'Inhumane' Treatment Of Migrant Kids...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-calls-out-obama-for-inhumane-treatment-of-migrant-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'They were treating them terribly'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK: THE PHOTOS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/19/photos-obama-immigration-detention-facilities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negligent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury sneakers: High style and booming market...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/luxury-sneakers-high-style-booming-market-033449512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christian, aged 10, has 20 pairs of high-end sneakers in his closet at his home in the suburbs of New York. Maxance, who just turned 14, asked his parents for an $800 pair of Adidas shoes for his birthday. The world is also one in which luxury sneakers -- often limited-edition collaborations between</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas paid Gaza family to claim baby killed by Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/hamas-paid-family-to-say-baby-killed-by-tear-gas-says-gaza-terror-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mahmoud Omar, arrested by Israel for terror-related offenses, tells interrogators his relatives lied: 8-month-old Layla actually died from fatal blood condition that runs in family</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hispanics on pace to outnumber whites in Texas by 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/demographics/2018/06/21/texas-may-not-become-mostly-latino-soon-experts-thought</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas got a little older and a little more diverse last year, data released Thursday from the U.S. Census Bureau shows.The state’s median age...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLINE SHOPPERS FACE RECKONING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/21/supreme-court-rules-that-states-can-force-online-shoppers-to-pay-sales-tax.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court overturned a 1992 precedent barring states from requiring businesses with no "physical presence" in that state to collect sales taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE LOVED A KITTEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Koko-the-beloved-gorilla-who-knew-sign-language-13013823.php#photo-2701745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Koko, the beloved gorilla who shocked the world with her mastery of sign language and ability to communicate with humans, died in her sleep at the age of 46.         The western lowland gorilla, born on July 4, 1971 at the San Francisco Zoo, spent the bulk of her extraordinary life at the Gorilla Foundation in Woodside. Her full name, Hanabi-ko, is Japanese for "Fireworks Child."         When Koko was just a year old, her doctor, Francine "Penny" Patterson, decided to teach her a few basic signs including, food, drink and more. Patterson would speak the words as she signed them, according to the Gorilla Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famous gorilla Koko who could do sign language dead at 46...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/koko-gorilla-famed-for-using-sign-language-and-crying-over-pet-kitten-dead-at-46/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Koko, the thoughtful gorilla who captivated the world through her ability to use sign language and revealed an empathetic side to great apes, has died. She was 46. The western lowland gorilla passe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Media Face Class-Action Lawsuit over SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER labels?</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/47-groups-weighing-splc-lawsuit-warn-editors-ceos-you-are-complicit-in-hate-group-defamation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will journalists face a class-action lawsuit?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Pastor Shoots, Kills Gun-Wielding Carjacker In WALMART Parking Lot...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/20/pastor-kills-gun-wielding-carjacker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An armed off-duty paramedic is being hailed as a hero after he shot and killed a shooting suspect at a Washington state Walmart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALLOW INTERNET SALES TAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/norquist-statement-south-dakota-v-wayfair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES DEAL BLOW TO AMAZON EMPIRE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/332abb7455cb4b60b2effc0852ff3c89/High-Court:-Online-shoppers-can-be-forced-to-pay-sales-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court says states can force online shoppers to pay sales tax.        The 5-4 ruling Thursday is a win for states, who said they were losing ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smuggler abandons 6-year-old in Arizona desert...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/smuggler-abandons-6-year-old-in-blazing-desert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 6-year-old Costa Rican boy was rescued by U.S. Border Patrol agents after he was abandoned on a border road in Arizona on Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: People Freak Out On Trump's Detention Centers -- They're Actually Obama's!</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/21/trump-obama-detention-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheDC's Justin Caruso and Amber Athey are on it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC's crumbling subway system falling in on itself...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/subway-station-ceiling-tile-crumbles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Borough Hall subway station in Brooklyn is more than 100 years old and is known to have water problems. That issue led to a ceiling collapse on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI counterspies under fire after disclosures of politicization...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/issues/ig-report-highlights-fbi-counterspy-failings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disclosures by the Justice Department inspector general of political bias among FBI agents is focusing new attention on problems within the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked Internal Memo Reveals the ACLU Wavering on Free Speech...</title>
      <link>http://reason.com/blog/2018/06/21/aclu-leaked-memo-free-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Our defense of speech may have a greater or lesser harmful impact on the equality and justice work to which we are also committed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES DEAL BOW TO AMAZON</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/332abb7455cb4b60b2effc0852ff3c89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court says states can force online shoppers to pay sales tax.        The 5-4 ruling Thursday is a win for states, who said they were losing ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  New mosquito-borne virus jumps from animals to humans... </title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/health/first-human-case-of-virus-spread-by-mosquitoes-reported-in-north-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s mosquito season&amp;nbsp;and it’s almost impossible to avoid being bitten.&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pot users feel MORE pain...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5869259/Marijuana-users-feel-pain-study-debunks-theory-cannabis-numbs-discomfort.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Swedish Medical Center, Colorado, found that after an injury, cannabis users required higher painkiller doses than non-users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'blinding laser weapon' attacks on US pilots spread to Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/711099/china-news-laser-united-states-air-force-pacific-djibouti-africa-beijing-world-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND:  Erdogan seeks new term with greater powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/turkeys-erdogan-seeks-term-greater-powers-082436562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANKARA, Turkey (AP) — Since he took office in 2003, President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has given a name to each stage in his consolidation of power in Turkey. First he called himself the apprentice; then the journeyman; and latterly the master. Now, he says a new five-year term would elevate him to the role</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rats break into ATM, munch through $18,000 in cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rats-break-atm-munch-18-000-cash-132945441.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indian police on Thursday said rats nibbled through more than a million rupees of banknotes after busting into a cash machine in the country's northeast. The rodent heist in Assam state was only detected by bank officials after locals complained that the ATM was faulty and had stopped dispensing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Possible I'll be indicted...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/rising/393422-stone-its-possible-ill-be-indicted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone said Thursday that it's possible he'll be indicted by special counsel Robert Mueller. “I acknowledge it is a possibility," Stone said in an interview on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revenge-porn bill dies after 11th-hour campaign by GOOGLE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/21/new-yorks-revenge-porn-bill-dies-after-11th-hour-campaign-by-google/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York’s revenge-porn bill died early Thursday morning after the Senate adjourned for the year and took no action in the wake of an 11th-hour campaign by Google against the legislation. The propo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHT HELL: Terrified passengers vomit as cabin fills with mist...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/977606/viral-video-AirAsia-India-air-conditioning-passengers-vomit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALARMING footage has captured the moment airline passengers in India started vomiting as they were blasted with clouds of mist from the air conditioning in an attempt to force them out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Burger Built by Robot About to Hit Bay Area...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/21/the-world-s-first-robotic-burger-is-ready-to-hit-the-bay-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The First Burger Built by a Robot Is About to Hit the Bay Area</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTEL CEO resigns after consensual relationship with employee...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/intel-ceo-brian-krzanich-resigns-after-violating-company-policy-1529586884 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intel Corp. Chief Executive Brian Krzanich resigned Thursday after the company determined he violated company policies during a past, consensual relationship with an Intel employee. .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG HITS AGAIN...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5318229/donald-trump-border-separation-policy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gambit reflects a President uncomfortable with ideals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese worker punished for starting lunch three minutes early...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/21/japanese-worker-punished-for-starting-lunch-three-minutes-early</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Managers called TV news conference and bowed in apology at employee’s ‘deeply regrettable’ actions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jobless Claims Fall for Fourth Consecutive Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-jobless-claims-fall-for-fourth-consecutive-week-1529584802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans filing applications for new unemployment benefits fell for the fourth straight week in mid-June, signaling continued strength in the labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting suspect arrested in death of XXXTentacion...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/21/xxxtentacion-murder-arrest-cops-police-mom-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;XXXTentacion's alleged murderer is in police custody.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe hits road to boost Dem govs -- and self...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/21/mcauliffe-democratic-governors-2020-661140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Virginia governor has thrown himself into 2018 campaigning, gathering potential chits if he runs for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eureka! Giant Oil Find Set to Bring Guyana Startling Riches?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/eureka-giant-oil-find-set-to-bring-guyana-startling-riches-maybe-1529578800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Exxon Mobil-led consortium has begun offshore drilling after recently discovering at least 3.2 billion barrels of light crude in Guyanese waters. That makes the tiny South American nation a top global energy frontier, but not everyone is convinced of a bonanza.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash Is King: One-Month Treasury Bills Compete With S&amp;P Payouts...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/21/cash-is-king-one-month-treasury-bills-compete-with-s-p-payouts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now You Can Gorge Guilt-Free: 1-Month Bill Yield on Par With S&amp;P</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
