<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Delays Congressional Testimony;  'Safety Fears'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/23/michael-cohen-postpones-plan-to-testify-at-congress-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen's advisor Lanny Davis cited "ongoing threats" to Cohen's family from Trump and the president's current personal attorney, Rudy Giuliani, in the decision to postpone his Feb. 7 appearance before the House Oversight Committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private satellites open uncharted territory in data collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/privately-produced-satellites-open-uncharted-territory-in-data-collection-60-minutes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company has launched hundreds of small satellites capturing over a million photos of Earth each day for commercial use, offering unimagined possibilities and consequences. Sunday at 7 p.m. ET/PT on CBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated as Latin American nations back Guaido...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-latam/maduro-isolated-as-latin-american-nations-back-venezuela-opposition-leader-idUSKCN1PI01J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most Latin American nations recognized Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>600-million-year old creature earliest animal ever found...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/mg24132142-700-exclusive-600-million-year-old-blobs-are-earliest-animals-ever-found/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fossils in China suggest that that some of the first animals in existence may have been carnivorous comb jellies similar to some species that still exist today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tear gas, vehicles torched, civilians bloodied...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1076882/venezuela-riots-nicolas-maduro-juan-guaido-venezuela-presidential-crisis-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA has plunged into chaos as thousands of people have taken their rage to the streets demanding President Nicolas Maduro to resign while he clings to power and severs diplomatic ties with the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials rescue 80 cockatiels flying inside cramped apartment...</title>
      <link>https://fox5sandiego.com/2019/01/23/officials-rescue-83-birds-from-local-1-bedroom-apartment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5sandiego.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Humane Society helped rescue dozens of birds from their cramped quarters in a San Diego apartment Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED TO SLASH 15% OF WORKFORCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/buzzfeed-to-cut-15-of-its-workforce-11548286211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed is planning to lay off about 15% of its workforce, as the company seeks to reorient itself in a shifting digital-media landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across border from El Paso, violence surges....</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2019/01/23/Across-Mexico-border-from-safe-El-Paso-violence-surges-in-Jurez/2961548187558/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2018, 23 slayings occurred in El Paso, Texas, a low rate characteristic of U.S. border cities. But it's a different story just over the line in Juárez, Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANNETT cuts journalists across country...</title>
      <link>https://www.poynter.org/business-work/2019/gannett-lays-off-journalists-across-the-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.poynter.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Visit the post for more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congresswoman added to 'libel' list over deleted tweet...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/covington-catholic-lawyer-adds-rep-ilhan-omar-libel-get-sued-list</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Omar is latest public figure to catch attention of Covington Catholic students’ attorney, who is threatening to sue anyone he thinks libeled clients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 dead after gunman takes hostages in bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/florida/os-ne-sebring-bank-armed-person-investigation-20190123-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five people are dead after an armed man opened fire inside a SunTrust bank in Sebring, Florida, on Wednesday afternoon, prompting a standoff, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign staff demand progressive culture: Unionizing. Minimum wage. Time off...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article224923110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic strategists push presidential candidates to implement progressive working conditions on their campaigns, from unionizing and paying interns $15 an hour to ensuring time off and salary transparency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene-edited disease monkeys cloned...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2019-01-gene-edited-disease-monkeys-cloned-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first cohort of five gene-edited monkey clones made from fibroblasts of a monkey with disease phenotypes were born recently at the Institute of Neuroscience (ION) of the Chinese Academy of Sciences (CAS) in Shanghai. The expression of BMAL1, a core circadian regulatory transcription factor, was knocked out in the donor monkey using CRISPR/Cas9-mediated gene editing at the embryo stage, and the fibroblasts of the donor monkey were used to clone five monkeys using the method of somatic cell nuclear transfer, the same method that generated Zhong Zhong and Hua Hua, the first two cloned monkeys, last year. This major advance, reported in two articles in the journal National Science Review on January 24, demonstrates that a population of customized gene-edited macaque monkeys with uniform genetic background will soon be available for biomedical research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buried in Footnote, Manafort Suggests 'Unusual' Tactic Victim...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/buried-in-a-footnote-manaforts-attorneys-suggest-he-was-victimized-by-unusual-tactic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most expensive home EVER in USA sells for $238,000,000!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/billionaire-ken-griffin-buys-americas-most-expensive-home-for-238-million-11548271301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record-breaking purchase of a New York City penthouse is the latest in a string of multimillion-dollar real-estate deals by the hedge-fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JACK DORSEY: TWITTER NAZIS HERE TO STAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/01/jack-dorsey-twitter-nazis-are-here-to-stay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street, among others, wish the C.E.O. would stop talking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says Zuckerberg killed goat with 'laser gun, knife' then served cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-rolling-stone-interview-782298/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes 280 characters just aren’t enough. The social media mogul takes on his critics — and tries to explain who he really is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commission weighs requiring women to register for draft...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/01/23/proposal-could-require-women-register-draft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A commission is weighing whether women should be required to register for the Selective Service System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears China-funded centers at U.S. colleges harboring spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-na-pol-confucius-china-investigation-20190123-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials are taking aim at Confucius Institutes and other Chinese government-supported cultural programs, warning that universities have unwittingly exposed themselves to undue influence or even spies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi seeks criminal leak probe: 'Propaganda channels brain-washing viewers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Benjamin-Netanyahu/Netanyahus-lawyers-seek-to-open-criminal-probe-into-leaks-against-PM-578402</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A letter said that "propaganda television channels are brain-washing [viewers] with a constant stream of false and non-contextual leaks from the criminal probes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan forces fire tear gas at opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-violence/venezuelan-forces-fire-tear-gas-at-opposition-protesters-reuters-images-idUSKCN1PH2JF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan security forces fired tear gas at opposition demonstrators blocking a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro gives U.S. diplomats 72 hours to leave...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-usa-diplomacy/venezuelas-maduro-says-he-is-breaking-diplomatic-relations-with-u-s-idUSKCN1PH2NF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro said on Wednesday he was breaking diplomatic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elementary kids disciplined for butter knife at school...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/birmingham/2019/01/2-birmingham-first-graders-disciplined-after-butter-knife-found-at-school.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident happened Wednesday at Sun Valley Elementary School on 18th Avenue N.W. Birmingham City Schools spokeswoman Adrienne Mitchell confirmed that a teacher saw the knife and immediately confiscated it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher threatens to shoot up preschool...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/23/nj-teacher-threatens-to-shoot-up-preschool-investigators-seize-3-guns-in-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey preschool teacher allegedly threatened colleagues that she would shoot up the school, authorities and reports said Wednesday. “One day, I’m gonna come here and shoot it up,” Gina Schro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKILEAKS sues to unseal charges against founder...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1e7bf01f8c841aa8fdb35200207eb2b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — WikiLeaks says it is seeking to force the Trump administration to unseal any charges in the U.S. filed against founder Julian Assange. WikiLeaks says in a statement Wednesday that a legal challenge filed with the Inter-American Commission of Human Rights in Washington also asks Ecuador to protect Assange from extradition to the U.S. Assange has been staying in the Ecuadorian Embassy in London since 2012 under a grant of asylum and has long expressed fear of a U.S. prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE stars beg fans not to treat father's funeral as meet-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/youtube-stars-dolan-twins-ask-fans-not-treat-father-s-n961741</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The brothers made their requests after the hashtags #SeanDolanMeetUpParty and #seandolanfuneralparty appeared on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent 'conversion therapist' will now 'pursue life as a gay man'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/once-prominent-conversion-therapist-will-now-pursue-life-gay-man-n961766</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Described as the “intellectual godfather” of “ex-gay therapy,” David Matheson told NBC News he is now dating men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alligators renew freaky behavior...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article224946305.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alligators in one North Carolina swamp have proven it was no fluke last winter, when they survived a cold snap by freezing themselves in place with their noses above the ice. It has happened again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Emerges of Beto in Onesie, Sheep Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2019/01/heres-video-of-beto-orourke-singing-blitzkrieg-bop-in-a-sheep-mask-and-a-onesie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You're welcome, America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VERIZON MEDIA GROUP layoffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/23/verizon-media-group-plans-to-cut-7percent-of-its-staff-source.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Delivery Robots To Roam Seattle Sidewalks...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-23/amazon-starts-testing-scout-delivery-robots-near-seattle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man cites virginity as reason he planned to kill 'as many girls' as he could...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/man-cites-virginity-as-reason-he-planned-to-kill-as-many-girls-as-he-could-utah-police-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Wayne Cleary, 27, is also on probation in Jefferson County, Colorado, for stalking and threatening women, police said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Flight Attendants Hustle for Tips...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/now-flight-attendants-have-to-hustle-for-tips-11548252907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new policy at Frontier and credit-card peddling at other airlines raise questions about whether flight attendants should depend on passengers for income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo volunteer loses thumb after orangutan rips off...</title>
      <link>https://www.toledoblade.com/local/animals/2019/01/21/toledo-zoo-orangutan-bite-volunteer-loses-thumb/stories/20190121150</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Toledo Zoo orangutan seriously injured a volunteer this past weekend, detaching the victim’s thumb. Shayla Bell Moriarty, zoo vice president and chief ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to pass USA in retail sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190123-china-pass-us-retail-sales-year-forecast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China to pass US in retail sales this year: forecast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Predicts 'Global Warming' Will Increase iPhone Demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2019/01/23/apple-predicts-global-warming-will-increase-iphone-demand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple expects greater demand for iPhones as a result of global warming, according to a report assessing the impact of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After casino surge, a Mississippi county deals with a reversal of fortune...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/nation-world/la-na-tunica-casino-20190118-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its heyday, Tunica was one of the nation’s biggest gambling meccas, ranking third after Las Vegas and Atlantic City. But casino revenue has plummeted in the last decade as major casino markets have exploded across the nation. Tunica casinos now employ less than a third than at their peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical detection dogs 'best defense' against serious illnesses...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6622613/Medical-alert-dogs-detect-TEASPOON-sugar-two-Olympic-sized-swimming-pools.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research by the Milton Keynes-based charity Medical Detection Dogs claims the animals are our 'best defence' in early detection of diseases like cancer, malaria and Parkinson's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company sells used tissues to train immune system...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/company-sells-80-used-tissues-claims-to-help-prepare-people-for-flu-season</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A company is selling pre-infected tissues for $80 and they&amp;#39;re already sold out!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Economist Says Economy May Not Grow In First Quarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-economist-says-economy-may-not-grow-in-first-quarter-11548256042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration’s top economist said that the U.S. economy may not grow at all in the first quarter if the partial government shutdown continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Musk's secretive charitable foundation benefits own family...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/23/how-elon-musks-secretive-foundation-benefits-his-own-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the Musk Foundation’s largest grants have been given to his brother’s charity, his children’s school and his fight against LA traffic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAWKER 2.0 IMPLODES; ENTIRE WRITING STAFF QUITS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/gawker-writers-quit-over-editorial-director-carson-griffiths-offensive-tweets-workplace-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new site’s only two full-time writers exited Wednesday in protest of editorial director Carson Griffith’s offensive remarks about everything from race to penis size.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Predict Social Meida Behavior With 95% Accuracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/avoiding-social-media-privacy-still-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There's no place to hide in a social network," warns Lewis Mitchell, co-author of a new study which found that even if you don't have a Facebook or Twitter account, your behavior can still be predicted with the online behavior of people you know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film festival to screen thriller --  in coffins...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/entertainment/article224901355.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden’s Goteborg Film Festival will lock moviegoers inside coffins next week for special screenings of a dystopian sci-fi film called “Aniara.” The event is touted as “the world’s most claustrophobic cinema.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goes on TV after drinking?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6621863/Giulianis-media-blitz-draws-ire-Trump-allies.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) - Rudy Giuliani's latest media blitz, which was filled with a dizzying array of misstatements and hurried clarifications, agitated President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX Starship Blows Over in Wind...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/spacex-elon-musk-starship-test-hopper-rocket-ship-damaged-2019-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Mus said a stainless-steel prototype of SpaceX's Mars rocket was blown off its mooring blocks and knocked over by 50 mph winds overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Build a Wall &amp; Crime Will Fall!'</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/23/donald-trump-build-wall-crime-fall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump tested a new slogan Wednesday on Twitter, promoting his idea to build a wall on the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Subway Riders Fed Up As Homeless Take Over Train Cars...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/01/21/subways-homeless-taking-over-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As temperatures plunge, some subway riders say they're seeing more and more homeless people seeking shelter inside subway cars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Trump Disapproval Hits High...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/01/23/trumps-disapproval-hits-record-high-amid-government-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the partial government shutdown entered its second month Monday, the share of voters disapproving of President Donald Trump’s job performance reached its highest point of his first two years in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds ramping up probe against Assange...</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/u-s-ramping-probe-against-julian-assange-wikileaks-says-n961661</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors have formally approached people in the U.S., Germany and Iceland and pressed them to testify against Assange, according to WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Shocking pictures show dead horses at dried-up waterhole in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2019/jan/23/shocking-pictures-show-dead-horses-at-dried-up-waterhole-in-central-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deaths of about 40 horses discovered near Santa Teresa blamed on extreme weather conditions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hebrew Israelites See Divine Intervention in Confrontation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/23/us/black-hebrew-israelites-covington-catholic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaining attention is difficult for the Hebrew Israelites, who practice a fringe theology. By confronting a group of Kentucky high school students, they found the spotlight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walking? You're risking life in Florida, the deadliest state for pedestrians...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/article224923045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skyrocketing pedestrian death rates are highest in Florida, where streets are built for speed, and Orlando and Miami are among the deadliest cities for people on foot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance Poised for Dreamers-ICE Showdown at Doc Premiere...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/sundance-poised-dreamers-ice-showdown-at-doc-premiere-1178225 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I welcome any retaliation by the Trump Administration,” says Mohammad Abdollahi, an undocumented immigrant who will attend the world premiere of the film 'The Infiltrators,' in which he appears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incest fears over 'world's most popular sperm donor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6622467/Worlds-popular-sperm-donor-reveals-set-Facebook-group-parents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyle Gordy, 27, of Los Angeles, California, has helped father 18 children across the US over the last four years - and has five more on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Guthrie slammed by left, right over interview with student...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/426568-nbcs-guthrie-slammed-by-left-right-over-interview-with-covington-student</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC “Today Show” co-host Savannah Guthrie was criticized by the left and the right on Wednesday following her interview with Nick Sandmann, the Covington High School student at the center of a weekend controversy at the Lincoln Memorial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman: 'Give Trump money'...</title>
      <link>https://kfgo.com/news/articles/2019/jan/22/peterson-says-democrats-should-give-trump-the-money-for-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfgo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FARGO (KFGO) - Minnesota Democratic Congressman Collin Peterson is telling his Democratic colleagues to approve President Trump's request for funding a wall on the southern border.&amp;nbsp; On KFGO's "News &amp;amp; Views," Peterson said approving Trump's request could help bring an end to an "unnecessary" government shutdown. &amp;ldquo;Give Trump the m...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How He Could Win...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/pete-buttigieg-2020-democratic-nomination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’d be forgiven for not knowing, or at least not knowing how to pronounce, Pete Buttigieg’s last name (it’s boot-uh-judge). His political experience to date i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Baldwin pleads guilty in parking spot scuffle, will take anger management...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/entertainment/alec-baldwin-pleads-guilty-to-harassment-in-parking-spot-fight/5101965/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor Alec Baldwin was back in court Wednesday in a highly publicized scuffle over a parking spot, pleading guilty to second-degree harassment and agreeing to take anger management classes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange launches legal challenge against Trump administration...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/jan/23/julian-assange-launches-legal-challenge-against-trump-administration-extradition </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder’s lawyers file urgent application in attempt to prevent extradition to US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO-CORTEZ, THE MOVIE...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-social-media-warrior-goes-washington-1178063 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As AOC confounds both the right and the left, the self-described socialist and tweet-shaming agitator takes center stage in the documentary 'Knock Down the House' and invites The Hollywood Reporter to catch a few episodes in the life of the one Democrat Trump hasn't dared attack: "Maybe he thinks that he's met his match."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First nudist French farce hailed as naked success...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190123-first-nudist-french-farce-hailed-naked-success</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First nudist French farce hailed as naked success</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Offer? Green Cards on Table?</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/government-shutdown-daca-green-cards-jared-kushner-e438872b-af64-4675-81d5-6a8bdde6b62f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Republicans around D.C. are unenthused by the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDE NAST to Put All Titles Behind Paywalls...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/conde-nast-to-put-all-titles-behind-paywalls-by-year-end-11548244800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magazine publisher Condé Nast said it would put all its titles behind paywalls by the end of the year, a move that underscores how critical it has become for major publishers to generate revenue beyond advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryan Singer Hit With Fresh Allegations of Sex With Underage Boys...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/03/bryan-singers-accusers-speak-out/580462/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bohemian Rhapsody director Bryan Singer has been trailed by accusations of sexual misconduct for 20 years. Here, his alleged victims tell their stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland declares an emergency over measles outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/An-anti-vaccination-hotspot-near-Portland-13554351.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quickly escalating measles outbreak around Portland, Oregon, has led health officials in nearby Clark County, Washington, to declare a public health emergency as they warn that people infected with the highly contagious virus since the beginning of the year have visited schools and churches, a dentist's office, an Amazon locker pickup station, a Costco, and an Ikea. Someone with measles was at Concourse D of the Portland International Airport on Jan. 7, the county's public health department advised. An infected person attended a Portland Trail Blazers home game on Jan. 11. At the beginning of last week, there were only a handful of confirmed cases. On Friday, the day the emergency was declared, there were 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Worse: Torture or Starvation?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/what-s-worse-torture-or-starvation-venezuelans-to-answer-today#gs.cSoY9xfk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whatâ€™s Worse: Torture or Starvation? Venezuelans to Answer Today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Flying Car Takes Off...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/boeing-s-flying-car-takes-off-to-show-a-glimpse-of-the-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boeingâ€™s Flying Car prototype completed a controlled takeoff, hover and landing during the test conducted in Manassas, Virginia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag Cuts Ties With Reporter Over Suspect Stories...</title>
      <link>https://hosted.ap.org/bendbulletin/article/729b28eea2e54f0cb464db7be280da40/dutch-magazine-cuts-ties-reporter-over-suspect-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hosted.ap.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE HAGUE, Netherlands (AP) — A Dutch news magazine says it is withdrawing 27 articles written by a freelance reporter and cutting ties with him, saying that he cites sources in his stories that the magazine has been unable to trace.Nieuwe Revu magazine says on its website that it took the measures because it cannot vouch for every source quoted by the reporter, Peter Blasic. Belgian media also reported allegations that he made up sources and committed plagiarism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural net -- trains self...</title>
      <link>https://www.zdnet.com/article/chinas-ai-scientists-teach-a-neural-net-to-train-itself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zdnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at China's Sun Yat-Sen University, with help from Chinese startup SenseTime, improved upon their own attempt to get a computer to discern human poses in images by adding a bit of self-supervised training. The work suggests continued efforts to limit the reliance on human labels and "ground truth" in AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily dose of aspirin 'not worth risk'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/22/aspirin-self-medicating-boosts-risk-dangerous-bleeds-major-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aspirin should not be taken to prevent heart disease unless on doctors&amp;rsquo; orders, scientists have warned after a major study found the drug &amp;ldquo;substantially&amp;rdquo; increases the risk of dangerous bleeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats, protests, lives 'permanently altered': Kentucky town reels after DC face-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Death-threats-and-protests-beseige-Kentucky-town-13552921.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARK HILLS, Ky. - Residents of this affluent northern Kentucky town emerged from a turbulent holiday weekend with a question: How did a viral video showing local students interacting with a drumbeating Native American man on the steps of the Lincoln Memorial suck their community into the fractious national debates about politics and race? President Donald Trump was tweeting about them. Out-of-town protesters were showing up with signs, chanting in the street. And death threats had shut down Covington Catholic High School. No one knew when it would be safe to open again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son of Brazil president faces fresh question about Rio aides...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-politics-crime/son-of-brazil-president-faces-fresh-question-about-rio-aides-idUSKCN1PG2Q7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The son of Brazil's right-wing President Jair Bolsonaro said on Tuesday he ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADURO ON BRINK?</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Opposition-launches-protests-to-oust-Maduro-as-13554431.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, VENEZUELA - Amid sharply rising tensions between Washington and Caracas, the U.S.-backed opposition here sought on Wednesday to fill the streets with protesters and spark the beginning of a sustained uprising aimed at ousting President Nicolás Maduro from office. Overnight, the smaller-scale protests that began on Monday began to spread, with a throng of demonstrators in Bolivar state setting alight a statue of Hugo Chávez, the leftist firebrand who established Venezuela's socialist state and anointed Maduro as his successor before dying of cancer in 2013. By early Wednesday, at least one protester was reported dead. The actions against Maduro took place as U.S. officials sought to fan the flames against Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA to charge drivers by mile?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-pay-to-drive-20190122-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metropolitan Transportation Authority is pushing to study how what’s commonly referred to as congestion pricing could work in L.A., including converting carpool lanes to toll lanes, taxing drivers based on the miles they travel, or charging a fee to enter neighborhoods and business districts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: 86 million fear maxing out credit card...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/22/1-in-3-consumers-fear-maxing-out-a-credit-card.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the dangers of credit cards, many Americans are racking up enough debt to worry about overdrafting their account on a single big-ticket item.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Super Rich Americans Getting Younger and Multiplying...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/super-rich-americans-are-getting-younger-and-multiplying</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Super Rich Americans Are Getting Younger and Multiplying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISE OF THE UNKNOWNS? South Bend Mayor joins 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b6a09c1f2a0646a7b68b3091873279a5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — Democrat Pete Buttigieg, the 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, is forming an exploratory committee for a 2020 presidential bid, according to a video and email announcement obtained by The Associated Press. "The reality is there's no going back, and there's no such thing as 'again' in the real world. We can't look for greatness in the past," Buttigieg says in a video that includes before-and-after footage of South Bend, a Rust Belt city once described as "dying." "Right now our country needs a fresh start," he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCONNELL SCHEDULES DUELING SHUTDOWN VOTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/428ceac5274b485e8adda635f20b484f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate leaders agreed to hold votes this week on dueling proposals to reopen shuttered federal agencies, forcing a political reckoning for senators grappling with the longest shutdown in U.S. history: Side with President Donald Trump or vote to temporarily end the shutdown and keep negotiating. Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky., set up the two showdown votes for Thursday, a day before some 800,000 federal workers are due to miss a second paycheck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI MESS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1b3a0037c65941509653ca2a20cd366d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Rudy Giuliani's latest media blitz, which was filled with a dizzying array of misstatements and hurried clarifications, agitated President Donald Trump and some of his allies, who have raised the possibility that the outspoken presidential lawyer be at least temporarily sidelined from televised interviews. Trump was frustrated with Giuliani, according to three White House officials and Republicans close to the White House who were not authorized to speak publicly about private conversations. The president told advisers that he felt his lawyer had obscured what he believed was a public relations victory: the special counsel's rare public statement disputing portions of a BuzzFeed News story that Trump instructed his former attorney, Michael Cohen, to lie before Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 56% support Medicare for All...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/426418-poll-56-percent-of-public-supports-medicare-for-all</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But there are wide swings in support and opposition to the idea depending on how the question is asked, poll finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS Warns Absences May Delay Tax Refunds...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/426532-union-says-irs-worker-absences-expected-to-surge-amid-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Treasury Employees Union on Tuesday said Internal Revenue Service (IRS) worker absences are expected to surge amid the partial government shutdown,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paw patrol: Sony offers robocop dog at home...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2019-01-paw-patrol-sony-robocop-dog.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony's puppy-sized robot dog aibo, equipped with cameras, artificial intelligence and internet capability, can now remotely check up on family members, children or even pets, the Japanese electronics giant said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee Says On Run Over Crypto Crimes...</title>
      <link>https://cryptoiq.co/crypto-proponent-john-mcafee-fleeing-united-states-after-being-charged-with-felonies-by-irs-will-run-presidential-campaign-from-a-boat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cryptoiq.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crypto proponent John McAfee, who is running for President of the United States in order to advocate cryptocurrency, has been charged with felonies by the Internal Revenue Service (IRS) via a grand jury in Tennessee. According to McAfee, he has not paid his taxes in eight years, nor has he filed any returns, despite presumably… Read more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Caravan Grows as Mexico Eases Passage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/new-caravan-grows-as-mexico-eases-passage-11548191845</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A caravan of Central American migrants seeking to reach the U.S. is set to swell, as thousands gather at Mexico’s southern border waiting for humanitarian visas that are easier to get under Mexico’s new government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHOOL CLOSES OVER SECURITY CONCERNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/01/22/covington-catholic-high-school-backlash-protests/2642568002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vigil for peace and against racism was held after viral video showed some Covington Catholic students mocking a Native American activist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared plans peace push before heat of 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Jared-Kushner-plans-Trumps-peace-push-before-heat-of-2020-race-578296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Team has begun negotiation groundwork, sharing â€˜elementsâ€™ of plan to regional partners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVAL ACADEMY deteriorating; Mission to train midshipmen under threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldcourier.com/news/national/the-naval-academy-is-deteriorating-so-badly-its-mission-to/article_4729127e-af1c-5d70-ba0f-224d0f95ecb7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANNAPOLIS, Md. — Leaking pipes. Moldering walls. Condemned offices and balconies. Plumbing that can’t handle its load and a stormwater system dumping unfiltered rainwater into the Severn River.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS RACES BRANSON!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190122-blue-origin-make-10th-flight-test-space-tourist-rocket</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blue Origin to make 10th flight test of space tourist rocket</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rapid military escalation' between Iran and Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1076129/World-War-3-news-2019-latest-Iran-Israel-Syria-countries-date-Russia-military-warning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TENSIONS between Iran and Israel are "escalating and intensifying" after Israel struck Iranian targets this week, a former Pentagon official has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Phillips rally attempted to disrupt Basilica Mass...</title>
      <link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/nathan-phillips-rally-attempted-to-disrupt-mass-at-dcs-national-shrine-91038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.catholicnewsagency.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While chanting and playing ceremonial drums, a group of Native American rights activists reportedly led by Nathan Phillips attempted Jan. 19 to enter Washington, DC’s National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception during a Saturday evening Mass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's invigorated opposition take streets in key test...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7d3d2ed7d5ae45dcad96baf0286cbfa6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's re-invigorated opposition faces a crucial test Wednesday as it seeks to fill streets nationwide with protesters in an appeal to the military and the poor to shift loyalties that until recently looked solidly behind President Nicolas Maduro's socialist government. The protests have been called to coincide with a historic date for Venezuelans — the anniversary of the 1958 coup that overthrew military dictator Marcos Perez Jimenez. Government supporters are also expected to march in downtown Caracas in a rival show of strength.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
