<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SAfrica to change constitution to legalize taking away white farmers' land...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/434784-south-africa-amendemnt-land-expropriation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South African President Cyril Ramaphosa has said the ruling African National Congress must initiate a parliamentary process to enshrine in the constitution a proposed amendment, paving the way for land grabs without compensation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA EARNINGS: HIGH STAKES FOR MUSK...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/01/news/companies/tesla-earnings-walkup/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla will post its quarterly earnings Wednesday, and all eyes will be on the cash burn rate and clues about Model 3 demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem takeover could bring first black speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/01/house-speaker-african-american-democrats-753177</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upheaval in the Democratic caucus could pave the way for a historic House leader — and some potential names are already being discussed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: PRIVATE PAYROLLS BOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/01/adp-private-payrolls-increase-by-219000-vs-185000-estimate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls in the U.S. grew more than expected last month as companies get a boost from lower corporate taxes, ADP and Moody's Analytics said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden leads Trump in early match-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/01/biden-trump-2020-elections-752979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A plurality of registered voters, 44 percent, said they’d choose Biden in the 2020 presidential election, while 37 percent of voters said they would vote for Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Teen ripped out relative's eyes with his bare hands, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/08/01/teen-relatives-eyes-bare-hands/877266002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim was missing both eyes and multiple teeth when he was found by police. Mahad Aziz, an 18-year-old relative of the victim, is accused of using only his hands in the assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Minnesota, SDakota, Colorado Happiest States...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/minnesota-happiest-state-america-louisiana-least-happy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota may lack the glitzy allure of a New York or Los Angeles, but it beats out the rest of the nation when it comes to overall life satisfaction, a new study finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Slams 'Evangelist' USA as Pastor's Detention Roils Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/01/erdogan-slams-evangelist-u-s-as-pastor-s-detention-roils-ties#gs.yGf_Cvo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erdogan Slams ‘Evangelist’ U.S. as Pastor’s Detention Roils Ties</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bag rage' prompts backdown on plastic bag levy in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/australia-coles-supermarket-plastic-bag-levy-sparks-outrage-10579968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Dems try to catch some of Cortez lightning in a bottle...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/progressive-dems-try-catch-ocasio-cortezs-lightning-bottle-090017428.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston City Council member Ayanna Pressley, who is running for Congress,  on July 28 near Boston. SOMERVILLE, Mass. — On a sweltering July Saturday in this city a few miles west of Boston, Ayanna Pressley is making a pitch for change. Pressley, a member of the Boston City Council, is attempting to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope blasts supermarket of idols of money, drugs, vanity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/856e9f6923744957becec5efb840ddb7/Pope-blasts-%22supermarket-of-idols%22-of-money,-drugs,-vanity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Pope Francis has returned from a month's vacation, blasting the "idols" of money, drugs and vanity that he said distract people from God and render them blind</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation, gas prices, tariffs squeeze consumers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/78c2df3ec38449a493be1d467f2652aa/Inflation,-gas-prices,-tariffs-squeeze-consumers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The price of a can of Coca-Cola? Likely going up. A package of Pampers? That too. Plane tickets? They also may be more expensive. These items and more may cost more in the coming months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocaine use soars in richer households...</title>
      <link>http://www.itv.com/news/2018-08-01/cocaine-use-soars-in-richer-households/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burger on wheels: Saudis try once 'lowly' jobs as economy bites...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180801-burger-wheels-saudis-try-once-lowly-jobs-economy-bites</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Crew Killed in Africa Probed Mercenaries of 'Putin's Cook'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/08/01/tv-crew-killed-in-africa-probed-mercenaries-of-putin-s-cook#gs.6d3oZqU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV Crew Killed in Africa Probed Mercenaries of `Putin's Cook'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange May Be Ready to Take First Steps Into Different World...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/08/01/assange-may-be-ready-to-take-first-steps-into-a-different-world#gs.o4brozM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Assange May Be Ready to Take First Steps Into a Different World</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE to Launch Censored Search Engine in China?</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/08/01/google-china-search-engine-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search app that will "blacklist sensitive queries" could be launched in six to nine months, according to documents and people familiar with the plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson freed on bail after winning court battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6912226/tommy-robinson-freed-appeal-bail-contempt-of-court-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOMMY Robinson will today be freed from jail after winning his appeal for a contempt of court conviction. The English Defence League founder was sentenced to 13 months in prison after he broadcast …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders, Warren question whether Dem primary big enough for both of them...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/399795-sanders-warren-question-whether-dem-primary-is-big-enough-for-both-of-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Bernie Sanders debated whether or not to enter the 2016 presidential race, one of the first people he consulted was Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE FOR TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apple-quarterly-profit-leaps-nears-1-trillion-value-212721815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple said Tuesday that its profit had jumped more than 30 percent to $11.5 billion in the recently ended quarter, besting market expectations despite selling fewer iPhones than analysts projected. The news boosted shares in the tech giant in after-hours trading, putting it ever closer to a history-making</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Senior citizens fight in samples line at COSTCO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article215857825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cut in line at a Costco ended in a fight between two men, Greenville, South Carolina, police say. A 70-year-old man was hit in the head by a 72-year-old that he said cut in front of him for a free sample of cheese, cops say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist nation where nothing works anymore...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-juan-venezuelan-city-where-nothing-works-anymore-012518674.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Power blackouts are daily fare, running water comes only once a month, cash machines are empty and waiting for a bus can take hours. Welcome to San Juan de los Morros in Venezuela, where nothing works. The rest of the time we have to buy it," moaned Florimar Nieves, a 39-year-old primary school</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil rights groups, lawmakers express concerns about TSA tracking travelers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyrepublic.com/all-dr-news/wires/state-nation-world/civil-rights-groups-and-lawmakers-express-concerns-about-a-tsa-program-that-tracks-domestic-travelers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Civil rights groups and lawmakers are demanding that the Transportation Security Administration explain a program that tasks federal air marshals at airports and on domestic flights with monitoring Americans who have committed no crimes. The program, called Quiet Skies, was first reported by the Bos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget collusion, CONSPIRACY watchword in Mueller filings...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/07/31/forget-collusion-conspiracy-s-the-watchword-in-mueller-filings#gs.HcnkhPc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Collusion. Conspiracy’s the Watchword in Mueller’s Filings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE WARNS RUSSIA</title>
      <link>http://www.mcall.com/news/nationworld/ct-pence-condemns-russian-interference-20180731-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence on Tuesday affirmed the U.S. intelligence community's assessment that Russia sought to influence the 2016 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX FREAKS OVER FARRAKHAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/louis-farrakhan-documentary-will-not-stream-netflix/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix says there was a communication error that led to documentary being included on August release list</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End of Global Housing Boom? Prices Falling From Sydney to New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/07/31/are-house-prices-falling-from-sydney-to-new-york#gs.7cwIFts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cracks are showing in property markets from Sydney to New York .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT HAPPENED? </title>
      <link>https://www.airforcetimes.com/news/your-air-force/2018/07/31/unarmed-us-missile-test-flight-terminated-due-to-anomaly/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.airforcetimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unarmed U.S. Air Force Minuteman 3 intercontinental ballistic missile was intentionally destroyed in flight when an anomaly occurred during a test launch from California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noncitizens across USA find it easy to register to vote, cast ballots...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/31/noncitizens-find-it-easy-register-vote-cast-ballot/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian foreign national or any other noncitizen can easily influence a U.S. election by simply registering to vote in California — just ask Elizaveta Shuvalova.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUI by 'huffing'? Case spotlights potency of inhalants... </title>
      <link>https://www.mypalmbeachpost.com/news/crime--law/new-dui-huffing-delray-crash-case-spotlights-potency-inhalants/pew6ymwBaWZT6o6DbW60II/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mypalmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delray Beach police say a man driving at 107 mph a second before an April crash that killed four had a powerful spray-can chemical in his system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look at Mueller's scorched-earth prosecutor...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Manafort-on-trial-A-scorched-earth-prosecutor-13121415.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. - No one mentioned Donald Trump. Robert Mueller, either. The word "Russia" was not uttered. On the first day of the first trial to result from the special counsel's investigation of Russian interference in the 2016 presidential campaign, President Trump did not tweet about any "rigged witch hunt." He said nothing about "13 Angry Democrats," his biting shorthand for the prosecutors who are examining any potential ties between his campaign and Russian operatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive NASA space blanket proposed at 'Burning Man'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dezeen.com/2018/07/31/massive-nasa-space-blanket-proposed-billowing-burning-man-installation-alexander-schtanuk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dezeen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian artist Alexander Schtanuk has launched a crowdfunding campaign to turn NASA's metallic emergency blankets into an enormous artwork at this year's Burning Man festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repeat evacuations leave Californians weary...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/95576ed38b8045cb9a6c17039f218938 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPPER LAKE, Calif. (AP) — Jessyca Lytle fled a fast-moving Northern California wildfire in 2015 that spared her property but destroyed her mother's memorabilia-filled home in rura</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonves Destroyed CBS Evidence, Redstone Claims...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/les-moonves-cbs-evidence-destroying-shari-redstone-claim-tigertext-lawsuit-1202437320//</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with a statement from CBS Less than 24 hours after the CBS Board of Directors let Les Moonves stay in his job despite sexual misconduct allegations, the CEO and other executives were accuse…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC CRAZY: UBER driver hurls man into fountain outside HILTON hotel...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/ny-ent-uber-driver-fountain-20180731-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tourists in Midtown enjoyed free theater as a large man appearing to be an angry Uber driver picked up a smaller man and tossed him into a fountain outside the Hilton hotel just steps from Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's president admits economy has failed...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180731-venezuelas-president-admits-economy-has-failed </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Predicts Talks 'Soon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/iran-advisor-says-us-talks-must-return-nuclear-044038446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump suggested Tuesday that talks with arch foe Iran were imminent, despite silence from the Islamic republic's leaders to his offer for a meeting. The country's top leaders did not give an immediate response to Trump's statement a day earlier that he would meet them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer whale drags sailboat, crashes it into another vessel...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Odd_News/2018/07/31/Killer-whale-drags-sailboat-crashes-it-into-another-vessel/7081533061907/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A killer whale swimming in a Vancouver Island marina was recorded dragging a sailboat by its anchor line and crashing it into another vessel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe faces hottest ever day, Spain swelters at 118F!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6910780/heatwave-warning-southern-spain-europe-hottest-day-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITS across mainland Europe’s Mediterranean coast have been warned to take extra care as the continental heatwave threatens temperatures in the high 40s. Europe is set to experience its hottest da…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA: FIREFIGHTER FATIGUE SETS IN...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/california-wildfires/article/California-blazes-tax-budgets-firefighters-13121282.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — California’s firefighters are stretched as thin as they have ever been, state officials said Tuesday, with no indication that the wave of fires scorching the Golden State will ease in the coming months. It used to be that the fire season picked up at the end of August and ran through October. That changed with the state’s five-year drought, and this year’s outbreak in July has officials worried about firefighter fatigue. It was an unprecedented month for fires, both in the number of acres burned and the cost of fielding crews to douse the flames. The state spent $125 million in July fighting wildfires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opened 1884: Inked royalty to prostitutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6907239/tattoo-ole-copenhagen-worlds-oldest-parlour-closing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE world’s oldest tattoo shop is on the verge of closing after 134 years of trade. Tattoo Ole, in Copenhagen, Denmark, has inked members of the nation’s royal family in its colourful h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle to save world's oldest tattoo parlor from becoming kitchen...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/europe/denmark/copenhagen/articles/fight-to-save-tattoo-ole-oldest-parlour-copenhagen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM: Secret Vid of Ailing Mogul Felled Board Member...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cbs-alleges-videotape-of-ailing-mogul-sumner-redstone-felled-board-member-1533080957</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS Corp. alleged that its vice chairman, Shari Redstone, pushed to remove a board member earlier this year after he recorded a meeting with her father, CBS Chairman Emeritus Sumner Redstone, to document his medical condition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great White shadows unsuspecting Cape Cod paddleboarder!</title>
      <link>http://www.capecodtimes.com/news/20180730/great-white-shark-shadows-unsuspecting-paddleboarder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capecodtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drone footage captures close encounter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA, Mexico meet to talk NAFTA; Canada left out...</title>
      <link>https://globalnews.ca/news/4363615/u-s-mexico-meeting-in-washington-to-talk-about-nafta-but-canada-is-left-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;globalnews.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's continental partners are simply trying to work through difficult bilateral sticking points on NAFTA, federal insiders insist, even as the Canadian government appears to have been left out of ongoing talks between the United States and Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/jury-picked-for-trial-of-ex-trump-campaign-chairman-manafort-1533064117</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort’s lawyer told jurors that the former Trump campaign chairman was innocent of tax and bank-fraud charges but had made the mistake of trusting his associates, as the closely watched criminal trial got under way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crown jewels stolen in Sweden; Suspects chased on motorboat...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/997061/royal-family-crown-jewels-stolen-sweden-royal-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SWEDISH Royal Family’s priceless crown jewels have been stolen from a cathedral with police currently chasing the subjects by boat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Moves MORE Cases to NY Prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/31/politics/mueller-investigation-foreign-agent-referrals-new-york/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel has referred some cases to New York federal prosecutors concerning whether several high-profile American lobbyists and operatives failed to register their work as foreign agents, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>97 passengers miraculously survive as flight crashes after takeoff...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6012875/Aeromexico-plane-crashes-flames-near-airport-runway.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican airliner was taking off from Durango International Airport when it went down in an area of scrubland at the end of the runway after a failed attempt to abort take-off due to bad weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Slim Praises AMLO, Says No Threat To Biz...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/carlos-slim-sees-no-threat-to-mexican-business-from-leftist-s-election/4507913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slim says he has not met with Lopez Obrador, whose landslide victory put him on a path to take office on Dec. 1</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA: 666 MINS OF DAILY MEDIA CONSUMPTION!</title>
      <link>http://www.nielsen.com/us/en/insights/news/2018/time-flies-us-adults-now-spend-nearly-half-a-day-interacting-with-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nielsen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. audiences have never had as many options to access content as they do these days. In short, consumers in the U.S. seem like they can’t get enough of content and the possibilities for marketers to reach them, while fragmented, is an opportunity that is just too good to pass on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Consume 666 Minutes of Media Daily!</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1344501/americans-now-spend-11-hours-with-media-in-an-average-day-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular old radio is reaching the most people, Nielsen research shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California secession gets reboot: 'First ever autonomous Native American nation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/07/31/california-secede-america-effort-752491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposal is the latest in California’s decades-long series of flirtations with secession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bite from COBRA sparks multistate antivenom scramble...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2018/07/30/snake-bite-antivenom-quest/867915002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 26-year-old Bay County man is still recovering from the July 14 bite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anna Wintour To Remain With VOGUE 'Indefinitely'...</title>
      <link>https://wwd.com/business-news/media/anna-wintour-to-remain-with-vogue-conde-nast-indefinitely-1202768145/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wwd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement to WWD, Condé Nast chief executive officer Bob Sauerberg sought to put an end to months of speculation that she would relinquish at least one of her posts by yearend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Photo Shoots? Luxury Labels Bet On Culty Podcasts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/forget-photo-shoots-why-gq-and-gucci-are-betting-on-cutly-podcasts-1532966510</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an increasingly post-print world, fashion brands and publications are finding new audiences through podcasting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales jump 19% in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/business/apple-sales-jump-19-in-china-despite-trumps-trade-conflict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple, which garners more than half its revenue outside the U.S., continued to expand sales in China in the three months through June despite escalating trade tensions between the Trump administration and Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho troopers ticketing highway slowpokes...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahopress.com/news/local/small-number-of-slowpokes-cited-so-far-but-police-say/article_e8361476-a9a1-5e80-92ee-81751b33f108.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahopress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only two Idaho drivers have been cited for driving too slowly in the fast lane since the state’s new “slowpoke” law took effect July 1. Three other drivers got warnings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPITTING DISTANCE OF TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2018/07/31/aapl-gets-even-closer-to-1tn-market-cap-hits-new-all-time-high-in-after-hours-trading/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;9to5mac.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple stock is now within spitting distance of the $1 trillion market cap milestone. Although after-hours trading can be volatile, it is obvious that investors are pleased with Apple’s latest…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JAWS' Scene Key To Solving Decades-Old Murder Mystery?</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jaws-lady-dunes-joe-hill-stephen-king-steven-spielberg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Author Joe Hill, son of Stephen Spielberg, thinks Steven Spielberg's classic "Jaws" may include a woman later murdered and known as the Lady of the Dunes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fists fly, and so does megaphone, as refugee crisis inflames Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/fists-fly-and-so-does-a-megaphone-as-refugee-crisis-inflames-local-politics-in-toronto-area</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The protest was an illustration of the truism that all politics is local, and that even global crises can become ballot questions in municipal council races</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As sex misdeed rumors swirled, Cardinal became a powerful Vatican fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/As-rumors-of-sexual-misdeeds-swirled-Cardinal-13119614.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When Theodore McCarrick arrived in Washingon in 2001 to be the region's Catholic archbishop, it was clear right away that he was something very rare: a celebrity priest. The vivacious cleric reportedly had spent time with famous Americans such as Bing Crosby and the Hearst family. He was a prolific fundraiser for big-name Catholic groups from right to left, and valued for his connection to Pope John Paul II, who dispatched McCarrick to hot spots worldwide as his diplomat. President George W. Bush, also new in town that January, marked his first private dinner in Washington by going to the home of the new archbishop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Best-Ever June Quarter...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apples-revenue-earnings-top-estimates-1533069011</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple delivered its best-ever revenue for the June quarter, typically its weakest period, as demand for high-price iPhones remained resilient and services like app-store sales swelled to all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As China Woes Mount, Xi Faces Rare Rebuke...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/31/world/asia/xi-jinping-internal-dissent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As China confronts economic headwinds, a vaccine scandal and trade tensions, a legal scholar named Xu Zhangrun decided to speak out. It could be dangerous for him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers target Hollywood casting couch...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/31/hollywood-casting-couch-is-targeted-in-california-harassment-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Casting Couch Is Targeted in California Harassment Law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS, PBS MOST TRUSTED TV BRANDS...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/399701-bbc-fox-news-pbs-ranked-as-tvs-most-trusted-news-brands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC, Fox News and PBS are the most-trusted TV news brands in the U.S., according to an analysis rel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France bans smartphones, tablets from schools to counter 'addiction'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6011519/France-smartphone-ban-Mobiles-tablets-barred-schools-counter-screen-addiction.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ban on smartphones, tablets and other connected devices, which will apply to pupils up to the age of 15, fulfils a campaign promise by French President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY MOST-WATCHED IN JULY...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/399747-foxs-hannity-is-most-watched-cable-program-in-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News continued its command of the basic cable landscape in July by topping its competition in total viewers, with Sean Hannity leading the way in prime time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Air Force terminates ICBM test after 'anomaly'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-air-force-terminates-icbm-test-anomaly-193232823.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Air Force had to abort a test flight Tuesday of an unarmed intercontinental ballistic missile after it developed an "anomaly," officials said. The flight of the Minuteman III missile, which launched from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California, was safely terminated over the Pacific</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7th Worst In State History...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-wildfires/article/Carr-Fire-in-Redding-now-three-times-the-size-of-13119721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Redding and surrounding communities began returning home Tuesday morning, but the massive inferno that broke out more than a week ago continued to destroy homes as winds fueled the blaze to more than three times the size of San Francisco, officials said.         The Carr Fire grew only slightly from 103,772 acres Monday night to 110,154 acres Tuesday morning, according to the California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection, or Cal Fire. As of Tuesday, officials said, the Carr Fire has burned 172.11 square miles to become the seventh most destructive wildfire in California history. By comparison, San Francisco is 46.87 square miles.         The fire is 27 percent contained.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CO Residents Unnerved By Anonymous Highway Arson Threat...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/07/30/gilpin-county-anonymous-arson-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A warning written in chalk on a state highway last week threatened Gilpin County residents with intentionally set fires. This while investigators are still looking into the causes of two previous fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank robber gets cold feet, then tries to open account...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/hudson/index.ssf/2018/07/bank_robber_gets_cold_feet_then_try_to_open_an_acc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bank robber changed his mind about a heist in Bayonne Friday afternoon, but not before a teller saw the tell-tale note demanding cash, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Hiring Videogame Tutors for Children...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ready-aim-hire-a-fortnite-coach-parents-enlist-videogame-tutors-for-their-children-1533046708</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s not the violence or the addiction of the hit game that bothers mom and dad—it’s the losing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once oil wealthy, Venezuela's largest state struggles to keep lights on...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/once-oil-wealthy-venezuelas-largest-state-struggles-keep-121358902.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Mayela Armas MARACAIBO, Venezuela (Reuters) - Across Maracaibo, the capital of Venezuela's largest state, residents unplug refrigerators to guard against power surges. Many only buy food they will consume the same day. Others regularly sleep outside. The rolling power blackouts in the state of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-thousands-evacuated-area-hit-past-fires-181656885.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEPORT, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on fires in California (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have You Met This Cow? He's Delicious...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/have-you-met-this-cow-hes-delicious-1533044979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consumers are demanding to know more about their meat, but it’s a fine line between transparency and oversharing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YORK:  Republican midterm elections fear rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/columnists/byron-york-after-30-days-of-sh-t-gop-midterm-fear-rises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From time to time I've been catching up with a Republican strategist who is trying to help the GOP keep control of the House in this November's midterm elections. It's been an up-and-down ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Funeral Homes Posing Dead --  Like They're Still Alive!</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/9kmqy7/inside-new-orleans-extreme-embalming-funerals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We talked to the head of one of New Orleans's oldest funeral homes about why some families are drawn to "extreme embalmings."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As millennials embrace RVs, next wave of travel trailers go hip...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/07/30/millennial-interest-drives-wave-new-rvs/796785002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials aren't just buying any old RV. The young adults are purchasing connected campers equipped with hi-tech features.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi man arrested for kissing girlfriend during driving lesson...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6902723/saudi-man-arrested-after-he-dared-to-kiss-his-girlfriend-on-the-cheek-as-he-taught-her-to-drive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SAUDI Arabian couple have been arrested after a man filmed himself giving his girlfriend a peck on the cheek as he gave her a driving lesson. The clip was posted to Snapchat by the man who posted…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How legal pot actually made things worse for sick people in Oregon...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/jul/31/oregon-cannabis-medical-marijuana-problems-sick-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The medical marijuana market is in a downward spiral as businesses, lured by big money, shift to recreational</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dems Making Moves Behind Scenes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-2020-dem-class-is-already-frantically-making-moves-behind-the-scenes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are traveling the country, others are monopolizing the airwaves, and all of them are leaving the door open for a run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Office Worker Spends 1,700 Hours A Year In Front Of Screen...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/office-worker-1700-hours-computer-screen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds the average office worker spends 1,700 hours in front of a computer screen over the course of a year -- or about 6.5 hours per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows massive blazing cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/california-wildfires/article/mendocino-complex-ranch-river-fire-cloud-video-13117716.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Lake County resident Dylan Duarte gathered his belongings and rushed to evacuate, he took a minute to document the apocalyptic view in front of him. Videos Duarte shared show a massive mushroom cloud rising above the River Fire as he headed west through the town of Lakeport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grieving mother orca falling behind family as carries dead calf for 7th day...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/environment/grieving-mother-orca-falling-behind-family-as-she-carries-dead-calf-for-a-seventh-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers are keeping vigil over the orca mother for a seventh day. Now she's falling behind her pod. "I am so terrified for her well-being," said researcher Deborah Giles. "She is a 20-year-old breeding-age female and we need her."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Soviet echo, Putin gives army a political wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-military-politics/in-soviet-echo-putin-gives-russian-army-a-political-wing-idUSKBN1KL1VA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has created a new directorate inside the Russian army to promote patriotism, evoking memories of a Soviet practice that once saw soldiers taught the precepts of Marxism and Leninism by political commissars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones faces existential courtroom battle over limits of 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mystatesman.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/alex-jones-faces-existential-courtroom-battle-over-limits-fake-news/uzGiDhpaPz0c1OJ79fd6bJ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mystatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defamation lawsuits target Austin conspiracy theorist Alex Jones' portrayal of the Sandy Hook mass shooting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARNINGS WATCH: APPLE could become first TRILLION-dollar company...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/apple-could-become-worlds-first-13007852</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple could become the world's first trillion-dollar company if the technology giant reports better than expected financial results on Tuesday night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami prosecutors to review arrests in town accused of framing innocent people...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article215758485.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Miami-Dade State Attorney’s Office announced it will review all arrests that were made in Biscayne Park during the tenure of former Chief Raimundo Atesiano, who is accused of framing a black teenager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to be happier? Stop scheduling free time, study says...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Want-to-be-happier-Stop-scheduling-your-free-13119452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your social calendar might be sucking the joy out of activities that are supposed to be fun or relaxing, according to an upcoming paper co-written by a professor who studies time management. The paper argues that when a leisure activity is planned rather than spontaneous, we enjoy it less. That's because we tend to mentally lump all our scheduled activities in the same bucket - whether it's a dentist appointment or grabbing coffee with a friend. And that makes the pleasurable activities more of a chore. "It becomes a part of our to-do list," wrote Selin A. Malkoc, one of the study's authors, in an email to The Washington Post. "As an outcome, they become less enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Users share player tweets to expose 'toxic' baseball culture...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/Users-share-player-tweets-to-expose-toxic-13118708.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of Twitter users whose posts exposing offensive tweets by baseball players went viral over the weekend say their aim was not malicious but to give fans a fuller picture of who they're cheering for, and to expose the sport's "toxic" culture. In exclusive interviews with The Associated Press, both users said they weren't looking for the years-old tweets from Milwaukee Brewers reliever Josh Hader or Atlanta Braves pitcher Sean Newcomb , but when the posts came across their timelines, they felt obligated to share them. Kevin Jenkins wasn't looking through Hader's twitter feed as he watched the All-Star Game earlier this month. But then they began popping up on his Twitter feed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest punched, doused in wine, beaten with bottle in church...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/news/2018/07/30/priest-assaulted-pike-creek-parish/867390002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A priest was assaulted on Monday at the Resurrection Parish Catholic church in Pike Creek, said Robert Krebs, spokesman for the Diocese of Wilmington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stolen shark back at San Antonio aquarium; one charged...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/31/us/shark-stolen-san-antonio-aquarium-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What began with a quick grab-and-go theft of a shark at the San Antonio Aquarium ended with the safe return of "Miss Helen" to her tank at the aquarium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT BEGINS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/31/politics/manfort-trial-jury-selection/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trial of former Trump campaign chairman began shortly after 10 a.m. with jury selection as President continues to attack special counsel Robert Mueller</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAY, GO, MAYBE SO...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/31/john-kelly-agrees-to-stay-at-white-house-for-forseeable-future.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Chief of Staff John Kelly is expected to remain at his post for the foreseeable future, according to three Trump associates and two White House officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100+ call Ohio Dept. of Health to report illness from CHIPOTLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/31/chipotles-new-management-still-has-the-old-problem-food-safety.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While analysts have maintained their confidence in Chipotle, investors remain queasy after another round of food safety outbreak reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIMON CREDITS TRUMP FOR ECONOMIC BOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/30/dimon-says-the-presidents-tax-cut-and-other-efforts-have-accelerated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J.P. Morgan Chase CEO Jamie Dimon said President Donald Trump's tax cuts, along with some of his other efforts, have helped out the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOMBUST: More Americans forced to 'reside' in vehicles...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/more-americans-are-living-in-their-vehicles-amid-high-housing-prices/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lack of affordable housing is pushing more people around the U.S. to live out of their cars or campers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living Abroad Isn't So Idyllic for Expats Facing New Taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/31/living-abroad-isn-t-so-idyllic-for-u-s-expats-facing-new-taxes#gs.Q1sGx2M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. expatriates owning businesses abroad are concerned about a one-time repatriation levy and an annual levy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS to Begin Coffee Delivery With ALIBABA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/31/starbucks-is-said-to-begin-coffee-delivery-in-china-with-alibaba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ele.me, the meals delivery service owned by Alibaba, will handle the logistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking heat brings unprecedented destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/record-breaking-heat-brings-unprecedented-destruction-from-california-fires/article_8f00e187-cecd-565f-b07f-9155afa895c5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. — The northern Sacramento Valley was well on its way to recording the hottest July on record when the Carr fire swept into town last Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA on track to borrow most money since '08 financial crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.americanbanker.com/news/consumer-debt-is-at-an-all-time-high-should-banks-be-worried</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.americanbanker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As memories of the financial crisis fade, consumers are back to their old spending and saving habits — and that could be a big problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran currency continues plunge...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/iran-currency-drops-18-two-days-doc-1813vh2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC Puts Its Cagefighters in Suits...</title>
      <link>https://www.adweek.com/brand-marketing/ufc-fighters-show-just-how-stretchy-yet-professional-this-menswear-line-is-in-this-epic-ad/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Thompson and TJ Dillashaw duke it out for Van Heusen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHAT NEXT AT BLACKROCK?</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/tv/news/leslie-moonves-future-cbs-viacom-sexual-misconduct-1202889777/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having Leslie Moonves at the head of CBS Corp. was once a sign of stability and great promise. But now, the chairman and chief executive is sitting atop a faltering media company that faces an unce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters Battling Fatigue...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/07/30/as-california-wildfires-rage-firefighters-battling-fatigue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of them are so committed to serving, they don't ask for help when they're injured or near their breaking point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL FRANKEN:  Haven't ruled out running again!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/07/30/al-franken-1st-interview-since-senate-resignation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Franken resigned from the Senate in January after #MeToo allegations from more than half a dozen women alleging unwanted touching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says collusion is not a crime...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/trump-says-collusion-not-crime-first-russia-probe-121617573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Doina Chiacu WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Donald Trump again attacked Special Counsel Robert Mueller's probe into Russia and the 2016 U.S. election on Tuesday, reiterating that his campaign did not collude with Moscow and saying collusion is not a crime anyway. Trump commented hours before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town's Entire Police Force Quits, Citing Unsafe Conditions...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/07/31/blandford-police-department-quits-resigns-safety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The entire four-member police department of a small western Massachusetts town has resigned, citing poor equipment and unsafe working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires barrel toward California lake towns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c5b1b97ca92a40ce965c339922086208/Wildfires-barrel-toward-Northern-California-lake-towns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEPORT, Calif. (AP) — A pair of wildfires that prompted evacuation orders for nearly 20,000 people barreled Monday toward small lake towns in Northern California, and authoritie</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lovato's 'SOBER' reenters BILLBOARD chart...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c1d138cbe46648ab82544cea7dfd048d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Demi Lovato's song about relapsing has re-entered the Billboard chart a week after she was hospitalized for a reported overdose.        "Sober," released la</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threaten 10,000 homes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/95576ed38b8045cb9a6c17039f218938/Twin-wildfires-threatening-10,000-California-homes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAKEPORT, Calif. (AP) — Firefighters reported progress Tuesday in their battle against the wildfires that have ravaged some of Northern California's most scenic areas, including t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover video shows pig abuse but also common practices...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/20c8688f0d7647afbc574192aecc34d7/Undercover-video-shows-pig-abuse-but-also-common-practices</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Recently released undercover video showing pigs being kicked, hit and punched at a Kentucky supplier for the world's largest meat producer drew prompt condemnation f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackout during vote for Maduro as party head...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/13208ed7b5504053bf73ff535aea006a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — An annual gathering of Venezuelan socialists took an unexpected turn when the lights went out just as they were about to select President Nicolas Maduro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Secret-Spilling Site 'Dossier' Steps Into Spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/04151c1579724d46a2bda546cb37368d/Russian-secret-spilling-site-%22Dossier%22-steps-into-spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Over the past three months, a handful of highly placed Russians have discovered their secrets seeping onto the web.        It happened to a Russian Interior M</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay gains rise at fastest pace of decade...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/pay-gains-for-us-workers-slowed-in-second-quarter/489623991/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. workers saw their annual wages and benefits rise in the second quarter at the fastest pace in nearly a decade, a sign that the low unemployment rate is forcing employers to raise pay to attract and keep workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: PRESIDENT APPROVAL 48%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_jul31</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspaper employees down by 45%...</title>
      <link>http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/07/30/newsroom-employment-dropped-nearly-a-quarter-in-less-than-10-years-with-greatest-decline-at-newspapers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This decline in overall newsroom employment was driven primarily by one sector – newspapers, where newsroom jobs dropped 45% from 2008 to 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 300 passengers taken off plane after bomb comment, fight...</title>
      <link>http://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-orlando-international-airport-fight-20180730-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fight broke out on a plane at the Orlando International Airport before taking off for London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIPPIN' DOTS salesman's dry ice kills his 77-year-old mother...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-news-dry-ice-car-death-20180731-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tragic death of an elderly woman may have been caused by dry ice in a car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READY TO POUNCE:  Will Musk behave during conference call?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/autos/la-fi-hy-tesla-earnings-preview-20180731-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the first-quarter earnings call in May, Musk cut off questions from analysts who asked about competition from Porsche, capital expenditures and demand for the Model 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Arab sentenced to jail for 'incitement' with poems...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180731-israel-arab-sentenced-jail-incitement-with-poems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA signs MGM deal...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/chalk/story/_/id/24245142/nba-first-league-betting-sponsor-deal-mgm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NBA has signed a sponsorship deal with MGM, becoming the first major U.S. sports league to have an official relationship with a betting operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside home of loneliest man in world...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6010573/Amazon-Man-Hole-Inside-home-known-survivor-tribe-Brazil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, known as 'The Man in the Hole', has been surviving on his own in the remote state of Rondonia, Brazil, since the rest of his people were murdered by land-grabbing ranchers two decades ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Weather-Related Disaster Losses AT RECORD LOW?</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2018/07/31/2018-global-weather-related-disaster-losses-at-record-low-so-far/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map of flames...</title>
      <link>http://time.com/5353749/california-fire-map-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's only the beginning of California wildfire season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA defends 'Quiet Skies' monitoring program...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/transportation/399555-tsa-defends-quiet-skies-surveillance-program</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Transportation Security Administration (TSA) is defending its use of a previously secret program used to monitor potential security threats at airports and on planes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Media workforce down 23% in last decade...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/media/399641-analysis-media-workforce-down-23-percent-in-last-decade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of employees working in the media has dropped 23 percent in the last decade, according to a new analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump marks Kelly's one-year mark as departure rumors swirl...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/399589-trump-marks-kellys-one-year-mark-as-departure-rumors-swirl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday marked chief of staff John Kelly's one-year mark at the White House, which comes amid speculation he could soon leave his post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Takes Down Fraudulent 'Resistance' Pages...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/31/facebook-political-influence-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One page called on President Donald Trump to resign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PORTLAND POLICE REFUSED TO HELP ICE AGENTS WHO CALLED 911...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/30/portland-police-ice-911-calls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police refused to respond to at least two 911 emergency calls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Viciously Ambushed, Robbed Of Fried Chicken...</title>
      <link>http://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2018/07/30/aberdeen-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Aberdeen man is slowly recovering after being viciously attacked steps from his home this past weekend.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
