<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MILLER:  The president of the United States is the whistleblower!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/stephen-miller-says-trump-is-real-whistleblower</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House senior policy adviser Stephen Miller said on Sunday President Trump is the real “whistleblower” and slammed the whistleblower complaint that spurred the impeachment inquiry into Trump as a “Nancy Drew novel” and a “partisan hit job.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Majority approve of impeachment inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-impeachment-inquiry-poll-cbs-news-poll-finds-majority-of-americans-and-democrats-approve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Americans are divided on whether President Trump's actions deserve impeachment, while Republicans back him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants in Greece set fires at camp; at least 1 killed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/92a15950e8f948ef99ebdbcb5df2f966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Migrants protesting at an overcrowded camp on the Greek island of Lesbos set fires and clashed with police Sunday, killing at least one person, authorities said. A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Egyptian activist arrested as crackdown continues...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190929142452-7b4v7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EGYPT-POLITICS/:Prominent Egyptian activist arrested as crackdown continues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS WANT MORE CALL TRANSCRIPTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-whistleblower/democrats-want-access-to-trumps-phone-calls-with-russias-putin-others-schiff-idUSKBN1WE0GN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congress is determined to get access to Donald Trump's calls with Russian P...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters step on images of Xi Jinping's face...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/hong-kong-protesters-step-on-images-of-xi-jinpings-face-and-appeal-to-the-world/ar-AAI1IuW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former prosecutor says he saw no evidence of wrongdoing... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/former-ukraine-prosecutor-says-he-saw-no-evidence-of-wrongdoing-by-biden/ar-AAI1EFu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESURRECTION IN IMAX</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kanye-west-imax-reveal-movie-collaboration-1244115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The film, set for a Oct. 25 release, will include music from West's new album, 'Jesus Is King.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Premiere Falls 30%...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/saturday-night-live-premiere-ratings-fall-2018-1244145</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like most other shows in premiere week, NBC's late-night staple came in behind its opener from a year ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: 91-Year-Old Man Brutally Attacked, Robbed -- While Sitting At Wife's Grave!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/09/26/santa-clara-attack-elderly-man-cemetery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Clara police said Thursday they're looking for the suspect who violently attacked and robbed an elderly man who was sitting next to his wife's grave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE OF NAZARETH!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/27/why-christians-reject-kanye-wests-jesus-is-king-sunday-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This “exclusive” club isn’t for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower to testify 'very soon'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1041b44f79854c55bf075537ed2dfe69</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff said Sunday that he expects the whistleblower at the heart of impeachment proceedings against President Donald Trump to testify...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowstorm hits northern Rocky Mountains; Montana gets brunt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/018584920654411b8a44c9bf14ba4ecc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREAT FALLS, Mont. (AP) — Areas of the northern Rocky Mountains looked more like mid-winter rather than early fall on Sunday as a snowstorm dumped record amounts of wind-driven snow that caused...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's former national security advisor 'deeply disturbed' by Ukraine scandal...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/president-trumps-national-security-advisor-deeply-disturbed-ukraine/story?id=65925477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Bossert was Trump's homeland security adviser until April 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rollercoaster car derails, plunges to ground; 2 killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7516061/At-2-dead-Mexico-City-rollercoaster-goes-rails.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last carriage of the Quimera ride came loose and fell 33 feet at the La Feria amusement park in Mexico City. The decades-old ride was found to have a mechanical failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi state media say king's bodyguard shot in 'dispute'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/84208f062cb94324877a47e7b54531a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A prominent bodyguard to Saudi Arabia's King Salman was shot and killed in what authorities described as a personal dispute, state TV reported Sunday, offering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  MACY'S closing landmark Seattle store...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/macys-is-closing-its-landmark-downtown-seattle-store/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macy's landmark store at Third Avenue and Pine Street in downtown Seattle will close in February of next year, the company confirmed Saturday, ending a long history of retail and holiday tradition as its online rival Amazon has continued...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Did Republicans Lose Orange County for Good?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/09/29/republicans-orange-county-california-228110</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demographic changes and an unpopular president have remade Orange County’s electoral map. Is the transformation permanent?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas tycoon and VP's son: Story of Hunter Biden's foray into Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-gas-tycoon-and-the-vice-presidents-son-the-story-of-hunter-bidens-foray-into-ukraine/ar-AAHZFB6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Rudy ended up in the middle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/29/politics/giuliani-journey-trump-impeachment-ukraine-phone-call/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Rudy Giuliani, the final week of September could very well go down as the most consequential stretch of days in his long public career since he led New York City through the tragedy of 9/11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson apologizes to Queen after House of Commons suspension...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/28/boris-johnson-apologizes-to-queen-after-house-of-commons-suspension/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK Prime Minister Boris Johnson has personally apologized to the Queen for asking her to approve the unlawful suspension of the House of Commons, The Times of London reported Sunday. Johnson made h…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu to meet centrist rival in last-ditch bid to form unity government...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/netanyahu-meet-centrist-rival-last-125409196.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu will make a final effort this week to salvage a deal from talks to form a unity government with his centrist election rival, he said on Sunday. An inconclusive ballot on Sept. 17, the second this year, has created a political deadlock and left Israel's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Mulvaney on shaky ground...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/28/politics/mick-mulvaney-impeachment-inquiry-donald-trump/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney is on shaky ground in the wake of a bad week for President Trump, according to multiple sources with knowledge of discussions surrounding the whistleblower fallout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intense Hong Kong clashes ahead of China's 70th anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-leads-global-anti-china-rallies-ahead-090342060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fierce clashes broke out between protesters and riot police in Hong Kong on Sunday as thousands marched through the strife-torn city, during a day of global protests aimed at casting a shadow over communist China's upcoming 70th birthday. Beijing is preparing for huge, tightly-choreographed festivities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept. ramps up probe into Clinton email server...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/463525-state-dept-ramps-up-probe-into-clinton-email-server</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department reportedly intensified a probe into former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton's private email server, contacting dozens of former aides involved in email exchanges that passed through Clinton's server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lights Go Out on Mayor Pete...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/videos/politics/2019/09/29/pete-buttigieg-power-outage-campaign-event-vpx.cnn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg was left in the dark when a power outage at his campaign event in Sparks, Nevada, caused the lights to go out mid-speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese parade a glimpse into military ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca6f789c8b95493ba0a3327a042da596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — A parade Tuesday by China's secretive military will offer a rare look at its rapidly developing arsenal, including possibly a nuclear-armed missile that could reach the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi 'heartbroken, prayerful' as impeachment moves forward...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/pelosi-heartbroken-prayerful-dems-move-forward-impeachment-inquiry/story?id=65931464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi said that she is heartbroken and prayerful as House Democrats move forward with their impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Could Soon Say 'I Do' to Married Priests...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vatican-may-approve-married-priests-but-conservative-catholics-arent-celebrating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of hand-picked clerics meeting in Rome next week about the ecumenical needs of the Amazon could change the entire Catholic Church forever.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
