<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Kyrie Irving becomes NBA's anti-jab face...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/574927-nba-iconoclast-kyrie-irving-becomes-leagues-anti-vaccine-face</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brooklyn Nets star Kyrie Irving, an NBA champion and seven-time All-Star, has become the face of a vocal minority of prominent NBA stars voicing their hesitancy toward the COVID-19 vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>126,000 gallons leak from pipeline...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coast-guard-rushes-contain-13-232416528.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oil slick believed to have originated from a pipeline leak has hit Huntington Beach, closing a stretch of beach and raising grave wildlife and environmental concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small plane crashes into building in Italy; 8 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-milan-plane-crashes-sardinia-3f1faa3b84d5c5eaf80e7bd2ab0799b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — A small private plane carrying six passengers and a crew of two crashed Sunday into a vacant, two-story office building in a Milan suburb, and Italian news reports said all aboard perished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Missouri's Covid culture wars...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/oct/03/missouri-coronavirus-covid-culture-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With winter coming, health officials are now concerned that the arguments that have roiled Missouri will leave it vulnerable again when a next wave hits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA:  'VERY CONCERNED'</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/575054-us-very-concerned-about-chinas-provocative-military</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department said on Sunday that the U.S. is "very concerned" about China's "provocative military activity near Taiwan" following Beijing's most recent show of air power near the self-governing island.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead birds, fish wash ashore...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dead-birds-and-fish-wash-ashore-as-13-square-mile-oil-spill-reaches-southern-california-coast/ar-AAP5zz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local officials are warning of a possible ecological disaster, as the Coast Guard and state and local response teams rush to contain the spill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 'frustrated' as his agenda stalls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-congress-government-overhaul-public-works-9438a78ba7c7865d75428e746d1de04d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden on Saturday acknowledged frustrations as Democrats strain to rescue a scaled-back version of his $3.5 trillion government-overhaul plan and salvage a related public works bill after frantic negotiations failed to produce a deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinema plugged as iconoclast...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/sinema-plugged-iconoclast-arizona-she-threatens-biden-s-agenda-n1280600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back in her state, mailers boast about the infrastructure bill she co-wrote — even as her reticence on the president's priorities has sparked a liberal blockade of the measure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Savvy bolsters her political standing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/715140/sinemas-savvy-bolsters-her-political-standing-back-home/?unlock=U6AGY9K9ANN7I0R1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not only is she building a bipartisan coalition in a tough state for Democrats, she’s insulating other vulnerable Democrats from scrutiny.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blaze damages historic Rome bridge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-explosions-fires-rome-98a3dda107efe9af06499229e6e8c5de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — A blaze, possibly sparked by a gas canister explosion, destroyed part of an historic bridge spanning the Tiber River in Rome before firefighters extinguished the flames early Sunday. Firefighters said the fire erupted before midnight Saturday near the Ostiense neighborhood and by 4 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boogaloo Admits Posing as BLM Supporter While Shooting Up Cop Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/far-right-boogaloo-ivan-harrison-hunter-admits-posing-as-blm-supporter-during-minneapolis-george-floyd-riot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivan Hunter admitted he fired shots at the 3rd Precinct police station the night it went up in flames during the Minneapolis riot, then shouted “Justice for George Floyd!”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Woman Masquerading As KKK Member Terrorized Neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/black-woman-masquerading-klu-klux-klan-member-terrorized-neighbors-faces-charges-1635059</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terresha Lucas, 30, of Douglasville, Georgia, is charged with eight counts of making terroristic threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For years, voice behind ISIS propaganda was mystery. Now Canadian faces criminal charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/for-years-the-voice-behind-isis-propaganda-was-a-mystery-now-a-canadian-faces-criminal-charges/ar-AAP4kY3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohammed Khalifa was captured on the battlefield in Syria in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 injured in overnight fire at CIA HQ...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/fairfax-county/2021/10/two-people-injured-in-overnight-fire-at-cia-headquarters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two employees were injured after a fire broke out at the CIA headquarters in McLean, Virginia, early Saturday, according to Fairfax County Fire and Rescue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Electrician kills 3 coworkers after argument with boss...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/03/pennsylvania-electrician-shaun-runyon-kills-three-coworkers-after-argument-with-boss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shaun Runyon allegedly used a baseball bat and a knife to brutally attack his co-workers following a spat with his boss at a Florida job site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska allows hospitals to ration care...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-alaska-health-1500db35e56b688e9cf3e0eea1d2a114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — Alaska on Saturday activated emergency crisis protocols that allow 20 medical facilities to ration care if needed as the state recorded the nation’s worst COVID-19 diagnosis rates in recent days, straining the state’s limited health care system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive oil spill off Orange County coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/huntington-beach-air-show-canceled-due-to-massive-oil-spill-off-orange-county-coast/ar-AAP5xRg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final day of a popular air show in Huntington Beach was canceled after a massive spill brought oil onshore and threatened wildlife and wetlands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of pedophiles active in French Catholic Church since '50...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20211003-thousands-of-paedophiles-operated-in-french-catholic-church-since-1950-commission-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of paedophiles have operated inside the French Catholic Church since 1950, the head of an independent commission investigating the scandal told AFP, days ahead of the release of its report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing tightens political control of internet giants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-media-asia-social-media-6b7083e9bcaa5d093a10b1a40eeef89b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The ruling Communist Party is tightening political control over China’s internet giants and tapping their wealth to pay for its ambitions to reduce reliance on U.S. and European technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China sends 77 warplanes into Taiwan defense zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/02/asia/china-warplanes-taiwan-air-defense-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan has reported a record number of incursions by Chinese warplanes into its air defense identification zone (ADIZ) for the second day in a row, Taiwan's Ministry of National Defense said on Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel tightens 'green pass' rules, sparking protest...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-middle-east-health-jerusalem-israel-25ec5e9141c72080876bfe4f481bf50f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel restricted its COVID Green Pass on Sunday to allow only those who have received a vaccine booster dose or recently recuperated from coronavirus to enter indoor venues. Technical problems hamstrung the Health Ministry’s rollout of the updated green pass — a kind of digital vaccination passport — as millions of Israelis tried to reissue digital documentation that would allow entry to shops, restaurants, cultural events, gyms and other indoor venues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Day Atomic Bomb Was Dropped on South Carolina...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/when-the-us-air-force-accidentally-dropped-an-atomic-bomb-on-mars-bluff-south-carolina</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On March 11, 1958, the Gregg family was going about their business when a malfunction in a B-47 flying overhead caused the atomic bomb on board to drop on to their S.C. backyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRONK OUT</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/sports/bucs/2021/10/02/rob-gronkowski-wont-play-sunday-vs-patriots-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iconic former New England tight end has been nursing a rib injury sustained last weekend in the loss to the Rams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic health-care staff shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-mandates-hit-amid-historic-health-care-staff-shortage/ar-AAP4dew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one in four beds lies empty at TaraVista Behavioral Health Center in central Massachusetts -- not for lack of patients, but for lack of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio is one of most prolific migrant smugglers. He's about to turn 18, and has decision to make...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Antonio-is-one-of-the-most-prolific-migrant-16504435.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MATAMOROS, Mexico - The smuggler led a single-file line of migrants toward the border,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Throws In With Left...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/02/us/politics/biden-progressives-moderates-agenda.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives flexed, but remain empty-handed. Moderates feel betrayed. The outcome of their battle could determine Democrats’ fate in the midterms and the success of the Biden presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Megadrought Tests Hopi Tribe's Resilience...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebharatexpressnews.com/arizona-drought-ignites-tensions-threatens-hopi-traditions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebharatexpressnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOENKOPI, Arizona - On the barren plateau where the Hopi people have lived for over a thousand years, Robinson Honani pulled his truck over the side of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska's vanishing salmon push Yukon River tribes to brink...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-science-lifestyle-business-environment-and-nature-cb0c966f43e52fd9559857969f1203a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STEVENS VILLAGE, Alaska (AP) — In a normal year, the smokehouses and drying racks that Alaska Natives use to prepare salmon to tide them through the winter would be heavy with fish meat, the fruits of a summer spent fishing on the Yukon River like generations before them.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
