<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Lifting Weights For 30 Mins A Week Lowers Risk Of Death From ALL Causes...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/stronger-muscles-longer-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prior studies show that building muscle is linked to a lower risk of death, but scientists had not probed what the optimal "dose" might be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$10 toothpaste? Household goods makers face blowback on price hikes...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/consumerproducts-pricing-focus/10-toothpaste-u-s-household-goods-makers-face-blowback-on-price-hikes-idUSKBN2KY3FR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get ready for the $10 tube of toothpaste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nobody is Gonna Break Us! Zelensky Fearless Address to European Parliament...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/nobody-is-gonna-break-us-ukraines-zelensky-gives-emotional-fearless-address-to-european-parliament/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky delivered a passionate speech to the European Parliament in defiance of Russia's ongoing invasion of his country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invasion raises specter of conscription in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220301-ukraine-war-raises-spectre-of-conscription-in-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany scrapped compulsory military service just over 10 years ago, but the conflict in Ukraine has reignited the debate around whether young men and women should be required to fight for their coun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From banking to sports to vodka, isolation grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-sports-business-hockey-1af9762a9b6fbdc2854b5a01eb114095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a globalized world — a planet stitched together by intricate supply chains, banking, sports and countless other threads of deep connection. Until it isn’t. Exhibit A: Russia this week, abruptly cut off from the larger world on multiple fronts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate gears up for confirmation of first Black woman to Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/596226-senate-gears-up-for-confirmation-of-first-black-woman-to-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s Supreme Court pick, Ketanji Brown Jackson, is expected to be confirmed by the mid-April recess and stands a good chance of picking up bipartisan support to become the first Black woman to serve on the high court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As tanks rolled into, so did Malware; Then MICROSOFT entered war...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/world/as-the-tanks-rolled-into-ukraine-so-did-malware-then-microsoft-entered-the-war-7795622/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Wednesday, a few hours before Russian tanks began rolling into Ukraine, alarms went off inside Microsoft’s Threat Intelligence Center, warning of a never-before-seen piece of “wiper” malware that appeared aimed at the country’s government ministries and financial institutions. Within three hours, Microsoft threw itself into the middle of a ground war in Europe — […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COUNTDOWN: Mystery out-of-control rocket 'to crash into Moon in three days'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4794912/mystery-rocket-denied-china-elon-musk-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN OUT-OF-CONTROL rocket part the size of a school bus will smash into the Moon this week. The impending collision has sparked a war of words over who’s responsible – here’s what we kno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belarusian troops enter battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/belarus-invaded-ukraine-history-corrupt-26356308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Belarus has invaded Ukraine, meaning the latter is now fighting a war on two fronts. Belarus has close ties with Russia and the Kremlin, so the development is not entirely surprising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student who tracks Musk's private jet now targeting oligarchs!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/student-who-tracks-elon-musks-26354682</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teenager Jack Sweeney, who famously tracked Elon Musk's private jet on Twitter, has set up another account to keep tabs on Russian oligarchs like Roman Abramovich</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIP ON POWER SLIPPING</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-people-may-starting-think-092222195.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/The Daily Beast/GettyThere is a lot of talk in the West about Russian President Vladimir Putin being mentally unhinged. How could he not have known that his invasion of Ukraine would have serious consequences for his country? Or is he so obsessed with maintaining an image of greatness—especially ahead of Russia’s upcoming 2024 presidential elections—that he doesn’t care?Either way, Putin risks losing the confidence of his people, whose economic suffering wil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA exploring ways to keep ISS afloat without Russian help...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220228-nasa-exploring-ways-to-keep-iss-afloat-without-russian-help-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is exploring ways to keep the International Space Station in orbit without Russian help, but doesn't see any immediate signs Moscow is withdrawing from the collaboration following the invasion o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil jumps to 7-year high above $101 a barrel as war prompts supply fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/01/us-oil-jumps-to-7-year-high-above-101-a-barrel-as-russian-assault-prompts-supply-shortage-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices jumped Tuesday as Russia's invasion of Ukraine intensifies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural America shrinks for first time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/596189-rural-america-shrinks-over-decade-for-first-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Americans who live in rural areas declined in the last decade, the first time in history that the nation’s rural population dropped between one U.S. census and the next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Nostalgia Relieves Pain; Just Looking At Old Photos Cures Aches...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/nostalgia-pain-relief/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in China say taking a break to go down Memory Lane and enjoy nostalgia really does relieve general aches and pains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disillusioned and 'betrayed' -- Brazilians flock abroad...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220301-disillusioned-and-betrayed-brazilians-flock-abroad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's vibrant mix of business, beaches and carnival has long lured expats from around the world, but a reverse migration is also in effect, as each year thousands of citizens pack up and head for…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruble Now Worth Less Than 1 Cent...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/6152156/russian-ruble-plunges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian currency dropped nearly 26% to 105.27 per dollar, down from about 84 per dollar late Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis, Arabs, Iranians in harrowing exodus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israelis-arabs-iranians-harrowing-exodus-110345420.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli evacuees from Ukraine are reunited with their families after being flown home from neighbouring Romania following a harrowing escape overland through the war zone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden steps to State of the Union lectern at fraught moment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-voting-rights-state-of-the-union-address-ketanji-brown-jackson-4d6eb9fed9a46bb4efb63ea4e015725c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Facing disquiet at home and danger abroad, President Joe Biden will deliver his first State of the Union address at a precipitous moment for the nation, aiming to navigate the country out of a pandemic , reboot his stalled domestic agenda and confront Russia’s aggression .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNSTABLE?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-europe-moscow-nato-6abd03995b4d359ba194179d0b51b0de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For two decades, Vladimir Putin has struck rivals as reckless, impulsive. But his behavior in ordering an invasion of Ukraine — and now putting Russia's nuclear forces on high alert — has some in the West questioning whether the Russian president has become dangerously unstable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans hosts its 1st full-dress Mardi Gras since 2020...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-lifestyle-new-orleans-parades-57e161928d60c60f65252703ad4df375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS (AP) — People are out to party as New Orleans’ first full-dress Mardi Gras since 2020 dawns Tuesday, with a day of back-to-back parades through the city and masks against COVID-19 required only in indoor public spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election 2022: TX primary tests Republican rightward shift...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-austin-texas-donald-trump-election-2020-c4955491dbef028e2c702e276543da1e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — Voters in Texas will usher in the midterm campaign season with primaries that will test just how far to the right the Republican Party will shift in a state where many in the GOP have already tightened their embrace of former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster, Vaccum Bombs?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/ukraines-ambassador-us-says-russia-used-vacuum-bomb-monday-2022-02-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Human rights groups and Ukraine's ambassador to the United States on Monday accused Russia of attacking Ukrainians with cluster bombs and vacuum bombs, weapons that have been condemned by a variety of international organizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa requirements lifted for foreign fighters...</title>
      <link>https://www.republicworld.com/world-news/russia-ukraine-crisis/zelensky-lifts-entry-visa-requirements-for-foreigners-willing-to-join-fight-against-russia-articleshow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.republicworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zelensky signed a decree lifting the requirement for entry visas for any foreigner willing to join Ukraine’s Defence Legion and fight against Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls for wider sanctions, seizure of oligarchs' NYC real estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/new-york-elections-government/ny-nyc-russian-oligarchs-luxury-real-estate-sanctions-20220228-dz6244be3jf5pii4sahe46gwse-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Russian invasion of Ukraine enters its second week, Manhattan borough president Mark Levine demanded more brutal action to target cronies of strongman Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knocking teams off sports stage leaves him exposed to own people...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/winter-olympics/knocking-putin-e2-80-99s-teams-off-the-sports-stage-leaves-him-exposed-to-his-own-people/ar-AAUrhC7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid escalation fuels fear of confrontation with West...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/rapid-escalation-of-ukraine-crisis-fuels-fear-of-confrontation-between-russia-and-the-west/ar-AAUsnav</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In just 72 hours, Europe overhauled entire post-Cold War relationship with Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-just-72-hours-europe-overhauled-its-entire-post-cold-war-relationship-with-russia/ar-AAUrkjS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt building explodes in fireball...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/moment-russian-missile-smashes-ukrainian-26354342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian airstrike appears to hit a city council building in Kharkiv, Ukraine's second largest city, earlier this morning with videos showing a fireball outside its doors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Father shoots, kills his 3 children inside Sacramento church before killing self...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/law-enforcement-church-arden-sacramento-county/39271675#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sacramento County Sheriff's Office said the gunman shot and killed his three children before shooting and killing himself. There is also a fifth victim with unknown ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine accuses Putin of 'war crimes' for 'barbaric' blitz on Kharkiv...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60567162</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missiles hit the the cultural heart of the city, targeting an opera house, concert hall and offices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ill? 'Unhinged'? Or calculating?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ill-unhinged-calculating-russias-putin-000321682.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episodes of peculiar behavior by Russia's leader have marked the time frame surrounding the Ukraine assault. But what's behind them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia pummels No. 2 city and convoy nears Kyiv...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-united-nations-general-assembly-kyiv-business-europe-abc3e297725e57e6052529d844b5ee2f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Russian shelling pounded the central square in Ukraine's second-largest city and other civilian targets Tuesday and a 40-mile convoy of tanks and other vehicles threatened the capital — as Ukraine’s embattled president accused Moscow of resorting to terror tactics to press Europe’s largest ground war  in generations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even generals look stunned after 'alert'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10558599/Vladimir-Putins-military-chiefs-caught-headlights-issues-atomic-decree.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The expressions of army general Valery Gerasimov and defence minister Sergey Shoygu were caught on camera as the Russian president put his atomic arsenal on stand-by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AND IT'S 3 HOURS LONG!</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/the-batman-review-roundup-critics-1235191908/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The review embargo for Matt Reeves’ “The Batman” has lifted, bringing with it a handful of raves and several mixed takes on the director’s very long and very dark interpreta…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIAMI:  Knife-wielding man threatened to 'cut the gay out of' his brother...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/cut-the-gay-out-arrest-652930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 28--While threatening his brother with a knife, a Florida Man said that he was “going to cut the ‘gay’ out of” his sibling, according to police who arrested the suspect on multiple criminal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Zuckerberg plans to cure ALL diseases...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4790376/mark-zuckerberg-cure-all-diseases-meaning-of-life-thoughts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILLIONAIRE Mark Zuckerberg has revealed his thoughts on life and death in a recent podcast. The Facebook founder and Meta Platforms CEO has plans to cure all diseases this century but has no desir…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klitschko brothers on 'kill list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4790754/klitschko-brothers-russia-kill-list-ukraine-wagner-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE KLITSCHKO brothers have reportedly both been put on a Russian “kill list” of senior Ukrainians the Kremlin wants dead amid Vladimir Putin’s invasion. Hundreds of highly-traine…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE SEAN PENN'S TRIP...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4790823/inside-sean-penns-trip-to-war-torn-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEAN Penn’s trip to war-torn Ukraine to film a documentary about Russia’s invasion has been applauded by a presidential advisor who described him as “energetic and engaged” …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge explosions rock Kyiv; Kharkiv chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10559373/Ukraine-war-Kyiv-survives-night-Russians-suffer-losses.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has resorted to using banned cluster bombs against civilian areas in Ukraine' east that have successfully resisted Vladimir Putin's invasion, experts and activists have said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst is yet to come...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/28/politics/us-kyiv-fears/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian forces have so far managed to stave off Russian ground forces massed less than 20 miles north of the embattled capital Kyiv -- but though they've defied US intelligence predictions that the city would likely fall within one to four days of a full-scale Russian assault, US officials warn that Russian President Vladimir Putin could imminently increase the intensity of the attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YES, HE WOULD'</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/02/28/world-war-iii-already-there-00012340</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin is trying to take down the entire world order, the veteran Russia watcher said in an interview. But there are ways even ordinary Americans can fight back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech cracks down on state media content amid mounting pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/28/tech/big-tech-russia-ukraine/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Twitter and YouTube are all taking tougher stances on content from Russian state media amid intensifying pressure from European officials for the Big Tech platforms to act against pro-Russian propaganda and address the escalating information war in Ukraine and across the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani legal problems deepen as 'false electors' scheme investigated...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/feb/28/rudy-giuliani-legal-problems-false-electors-scheme</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ex-prosecutors say possible charges could include falsifying voting documents and even conspiracy to defraud the US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle O would put Republicans 'in very difficult position' if she ran for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10560673/Michelle-Obama-2024-bid-Republicans-difficult-position-ex-Trump-aide-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After tossing the popular Dem first lady's hat in the ring, Crowley explained how Obama would have been positioning herself to mount a White House bid after her husband left office in early 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says Americans should NOT be worried...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10560335/Biden-updates-nuclear-explosion-guidelines-include-SOCIAL-DISTANCING-Putin-readies-missiles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New guidance comes after Russian President Vladimir Putin escalated tensions with the West on Sunday by ordering Russian nuclear forces be put on high alert amid his invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Dutch embrace floating homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20220202-floating-homes-the-benefits-of-living-on-water</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faced with worsening floods and a shortage of housing, the Netherlands is seeing growing interest in floating homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Military radar facility' hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10561485/Huge-explosions-rock-Kyiv-hours-dozens-killed-Russian-CLUSTER-BOMBS-attack.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dramatic video filmed in the Ukrainian capital showed the moment that the night lit up with an enormous fire ball, which reportedly stemmed from a military radar communication center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada bans oil imports...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/politics/canada-preparing-third-shipment-of-lethal-equipment-for-ukraine-to-be-routed-through-poland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks yield no breakthrough...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-war-016cc6cbc65ae95286d825a4ebebd1c5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — The first talks aimed at stopping the fighting between Ukraine and Russia ended Monday with no agreement except to keep talking, while an increasingly isolated Moscow ran into unexpectedly fierce resistance on the ground and economic havoc at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face economic point of no return...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2022/feb/28/the-damage-is-done-russians-face-economic-point-of-no-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shoppers and business people express despair and disillusion as sanctions cause run on rouble</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strange left-right alliance making excuses for Vlad...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/28/strange-left-right-alliance-making-excuses-for-putin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several prominent figures from the Left and Right have formed a strange alliance saying that we should lay off Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sophisticated' new Chinese hacking tool found...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/world/united-states-canada/article/3168740/sophisticated-new-chinese-hacking-tool-found</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cybersecurity firm Symantec says the malware, which it calls Daxin, has been used to target high level, non-Western government agencies in Asia and Africa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oligarchs move yachts as USA looks to 'hunt down', freeze assets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/28/russian-oligarchs-move-yachts-as-us-moves-to-hunt-down-and-freeze-assets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian oligarchs are moving their yachts as the United States and its allies look to target personal property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US NETFLIX to be forced to broadcast Putin propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/us-streaming-giant-netflix-set-to-broadcast-putin-propaganda/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix comes under new rules in Russia on March 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Ambassador Calls for Putin to Kill Himself Like Hitler 'Did in Bunker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ukrainian-ambassador-to-un-calls-for-putin-to-kill-himself-like-hitler-did-in-a-bunker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine’s ambassador to the United Nations called on Russian President Vladimir Putin to kill himself like Adolf Hitler “did in a bunker.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Fighters Rushing to Join War...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akvyq4/russian-ukraine-invasion-foreign-fighters-battalion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of a volunteer unit told VICE World News hundreds of foreign fighters had signed up following a direct appeal by Ukraine's President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA faces new lawsuit over lucrative shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/moderna-faces-new-lawsuit-over-lucrative-coronavirus-vaccine/ar-AAUpsmL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN 'PROPAGANDA CHIEF' THREATENS WEST WITH '500 NUKES'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4789026/putins-propaganda-chief-threatens-west-with-nuclear-destruction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin’s “propaganda chief” has threatened the West with nuclear annihilation during a rambling broadcast on Russian TV. News anchor Dmitry Kiselyov told viewers across Ru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew could face more sex abuse lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4749540/prince-andrew-sexual-abuse-lawsuits-grope-royal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew could face more sex abuse lawsuits in the US due to a potential change in the law – including from a woman who claims she was groped by the disgraced royal.  The Duke of Yo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/02/28/review-the-batman-brings-david-fincher-like-darkness-to-a-young-goth-bruce-wayne-and-a-woke-catwoman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia thrown out of soccer World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/football/news/breaking-russia-banned-fifa-uefa-26350537</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FIFA and UEFA have moved to ban Russian clubs and its national teams from footballing competition following Russia's attacks on Ukraine ordered by president Vladimir Putin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-reviews/batman-robert-pattinson-1235100390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Caped Crusader is back on Gotham City’s crime-infested streets, exposing corruption at the highest levels in Matt Reeves’ reboot, also featuring Zoë Kravitz, Paul Dano and Colin Farrell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Woman attacked with human feces in NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/woman-attacked-with-feces-to-the-face/3574539/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are looking for a man who smeared human feces on the face and back of the head of a 43-year-old woman who was sitting on a subway station bench on a Bronx platform during the evening rush last week, authorities say. The woman was sitting on the bench on the southbound platform at the East 241st Street station around…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking scenes at Ukraine border sees thousands of kids separated from dads...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/inside-heartbreaking-evacuation-ukraine-many-26343744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mirror reporter Andy Lines is on the frontline of the evacuation efforts across Ukraine as thousands are faced with the devastating decision to run in a bid to save their lives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm staying for those jews who cannot flee, pledges Kyiv Chief Rabbi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/news/im-staying-for-those-who-cannot-flee-pledges-kyiv-chief-rabbi-2rTJXEnrM2aCK4B0uZJJ79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Trading Platform Founder Indicted in $2 Billion 'Global Ponzi Scheme'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/02/founder-crypto-trading-platform-bitconnect-indicted-global-ponzi-scheme/362512/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice charged Satish Kumbhani with conspiracy to commit fraud and misleading investors in the latest crypto crackdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Woman attacked with human feces in NYC subway...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-subway-feces-attack-investigated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in New York were investigating a very disturbing subway attack in which a woman was struck in the face and the back of her head with human feces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible drones, robot tanks and attack dogs?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/putin-unleash-nightmare-war-toys-26346047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin has a vast array of terrifying weapons at his disposal that he could use on Ukraine, including "invisible" T-14 robot super tanks and parachuting attack dog regiments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONLYFANS bans models...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/onlyfans-bans-russian-models-selling-26345036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult stars in Russia claim to have been banned from selling their X-rated content online as a result of sanctions imposed on Russia following Vladimir Putin's Ukraine invasion last week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>African Students Fleeing Ukraine Report Being Told 'No Blacks' Allowed on Buses...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2022/02/27/african-students-fleeing-ukraine-report-being-told-no-blacks-on-buses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boring to 'historic': The awakening of  Olaf Scholz...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220228-boring-to-historic-the-awakening-of-germany-s-olaf-scholz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often described as predictable and "robotic", Chancellor Olaf Scholz has become emboldened since Russia's invasion of Ukraine, smashing policy taboos to steer Germany into "a new era" that could resh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic fears fade...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-pandemics-public-health-only-on-ap-eaaf9967f97089f6e869b08573c292b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron is fading away, and so are Americans' worries about COVID-19. As coronavirus pandemic case numbers, hospitalizations and deaths continue to plummet, fewer people now than in January say they are concerned that they will be infected after the rise and fall of the wildly contagious virus variant, according to a new poll from The Associated Press-NORC Center for Public Affairs Research .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neutral Swiss adopt sanctions in break with past...</title>
      <link>https://www.deccanherald.com/international/world-news-politics/neutral-swiss-adopt-eu-sanctions-against-russia-in-break-with-past-1086204.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deccanherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neutral Switzerland will adopt European Union sanctions against Russians involved in Moscow's invasion of Ukraine and freeze their assets, the government said on Monday in a sharp deviation from the Alpine country's traditions. "In view of Russia’s continuing military intervention in Ukraine, the Federal Council took the decision on February 28 to adopt the packages of sanctions imposed by the EU on February 23 and 25," the government said in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: What Courage Says About the West...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2022/02/volodymyr-zelensky-courage-ukraine-russia/622948/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian leader’s refusal to back down is as inspiring as it is illuminating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Most Americans More Sensitive To Noise Since Pandemic Began...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/noise-sensitivity-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be time to get your ears checked. More than half of Americans say they’ve become more sensitive to noise since the pandemic started.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous takes down state run news services in major cyber attack...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/02/28/anonymous-hacks-russias-tass-news-service-with-latest-cyber-attack-16188295/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Websites belonging to TASS, Izvestia, Fontaka, RBC and Kommersant have been replaced with anti-Putin messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key interest rate doubles...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rouble-us-dollar-russia-interest-rates-101044165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's central bank has raised its key interest rate from 9.5% to 20% in an attempt to shore up the rouble after it plunged 30% to a record low against the dollar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON voice assistant Alexa to start seeking doctor help...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-health-lifestyle-dcc673a14cc14e1604a314f7df5fe46c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If there is no doctor in the house, Amazon’s Alexa will soon be able to summon one. Amazon and telemedicine provider Teladoc Health are starting a voice-activated virtual care program that lets customers get medical help without picking up their phones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians line up at banks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-japan-9fbeb1c66c523f4018abb8ebc6580839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Ordinary Russians faced the prospect of higher prices and crimped foreign travel as Western sanctions over the invasion of Ukraine sent the ruble plummeting, leading uneasy people to line up at banks and ATMs on Monday in a country that has seen more than one currency disaster in the post-Soviet era.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
