<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TEXT...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/12/4/18126388/mueller-michael-flynn-sentencing-memo-read</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s former national security adviser pleaded guilty to lying to the FBI about his contacts with the Russian ambassador.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Moonves Obstructed Investigation Into Misconduct Claims, Report Says...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/business/media/les-moonves-cbs-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leslie Moonves, the former CBS chief, destroyed evidence and misled investigators looking into his alleged misconduct, according to a draft of a report prepared for the company’s board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Hart to host OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/academy-eyes-kevin-hart-host-oscars-1155972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star and comedian is emceeing the event for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free tickets to NFL game fail to fill stadium...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/12/04/free-tickets-didnt-fill-up-tampa-bays-stadium/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Buccaneers, desperate to fill Raymond James Stadium, offered two free tickets to every season-ticket holder for last Sunday’s game against the Panthers. It didn’t work. As recently …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury developments come with sky ports for flying cars...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/04/luxury-miami-developments-now-come-with-sky-ports-for-flying-cars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami is now cleared for takeoff — launching its first three luxury residences with their own rooftop landing pads. The Paramount Miami Worldcenter — a 27-acre mixed-use super project that claims t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to disguise weapons as useless space junk to spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7901568/space-spy-satellites-weapons-junk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE United States may have come up with a novel way of concealing its spy satellites – by concealing them in ever-increasing amounts of space junk, according to reports. Jim Cantrell, who set up hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCARDMICROSOFT Plan For 'Universal Digital ID'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90276216/mastercard-and-microsoft-announce-frightening-universal-id-partnership</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two companies are creating “digital identity” solutions that will definitely alarm privacy activists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: GOOGLE gives different results for different users who search identical terms...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/googles-search-leaves-users-dark-duckduck-go-ceo-214438103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you use Google’s search engine, “There’s no way of knowing what you’re missing,” says Gabriel Weinberg, CEO and founder of search engine DuckDuckGo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Man handcuffs roommate to chair, hammers ICE PICK through genitals...</title>
      <link>https://fox13now.com/2018/12/04/police-utah-man-arrested-after-driving-tool-resembling-ice-pick-into-housemates-genitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox13now.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAYLORSVILLE, Utah -- Police say a man held another man at gunpoint, bound him to a chair and then told him he could choose between death in the desert or having a nail hammered through his genitals. According to charging documents filed September 5, the assault occurred on August 30 in Salt Lake County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Baby it's cold outside' returns to radio airwaves, listeners vote 'not offensive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/local-news/-baby-it-s-cold-outside-returns-to-denver-airwaves-after-feedback-from-kosi-1011-listeners</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A classic holiday song some say promotes a corrupt message of consent is back on the radio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK removes post accusing it of having 'black people problem'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/facebook-temporarily-pulls-down-post-by-ex-employee-who-accused-tech-firm-of-black-people-problem/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The author of the post says the removal proves his point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby born via uterus transplant from deceased donor...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/12/04/for-the-first-time-a-baby-is-born-via-a-uterus-transplant-from-a-deceased-donor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers said that if transplant teams can reliably use uteruses from deceased donors, it could expand the availability of organs for those in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ brings charges in first 'Panama Papers' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/04/panama-papers-investigation-four-men-charged-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say quartet went to ‘extraordinary lengths to circumvent US tax laws’ to boost the wealth of their clients</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO HUDDLES WITH OBAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/beto-orourke-met-with-barack-obama-as-he-ponders-a-2020-presidential-campaign/2018/12/04/fa895cc8-f7fb-11e8-8d64-4e79db33382f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meeting occurred as some Democrats, including former Obama aides, implored the Texas congressman to form his own hope-and-change candidacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAANG stocks shed $140,000,000,000 in market rout...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/04/faang-stocks-shed-140-billion-in-tuesdays-market-rout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The losses extend pain periods for Apple and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Maneuvers to Snag Top-Secret Satellite Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-maneuvers-to-snag-top-secret-boeing-satellite-technology-1543943490</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The founders of a small Los Angeles company, which ordered a satellite from Boeing, say the firm was financed and is now controlled by China, in violation of rules designed to keep such technology out of Beijing’s hands. Some worry China could use the technology for military purposes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ charges 4 in first 'Panama Papers' case...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/justice-department-charges-four-in-its-first-panama-papers-case-2018-12-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBATES: Lesser-knowns to share stage with front-runners?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/wary-of-repeating-2016-mistakes-democrats-prepare-to-shake-up-2020-presidential-debate-plan/2018/12/04/cd50e8c6-f741-11e8-8c9a-860ce2a8148f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party was chided last cycle as deferring to the needs of Hillary Clinton over other candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturers struggle to find workers, turn to high schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2018/12/04/US-manufacturers-struggling-to-find-workers-turning-to-high-schools/7841543589283/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Across America, manufacturing companies in desperate need of skilled labor are turning to a previously untapped pool -- high school students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>United Arab Emirates now world's most powerful passport...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/travel/news/article.cfm?c_id=7&amp;objectid=12170816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Arab Emirates now has access to the greatest number of countries visa-free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fate of WEEKLY STANDARD uncertain...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/media/weekly-standard-future-uncertain/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fate of The Weekly Standard, the conservative magazine that has staked out a position as a publication on the right still critical of President Donald Trump, is uncertain, Editor-in-Chief Stephen Hayes told staff in a series of phone calls Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR,  SLOWING ECONOMY</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stocks-extend-losses-as-investors-revise-initial-take-on-trade-truce-1543948467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average fell nearly 800 points and bond yields plummeted as investors’ doubts over the U.S.-China trade truce renewed anxieties about the pace of economic growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFI GIVES SPECIAL AWARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2018/12/04/afi-chooses-top-10-tv-film-roma-gets-a-special-prize-first-man-snubbed-this-is-us-only-network-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For what it’s worth, the American Film Institute chose its top 10 movies and TV shows of 2018. Alfonso Cuaron’s “Roma” not only won a spot in the top 10 but got a special pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first sex robot for women...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7899337/worlds-first-sex-robot-women-penis-brad-pitt-torso/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REALBOTIX, the company behind the RealDolls sex robots, is ready to start full production on its first male doll, called Henry. Henry might appear to be every heterosexual girl’s dream, with his ru…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020: Can Scandal Still Sink a Politician?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/04/us/politics/politics-scandal-2020-presidential-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has defied the old conventions around troublesome pasts and political careers. But it’s unclear whether the same rules apply to the Democrats running to unseat him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans contestant odds-on favorite to win Miss Universe...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/miss-universe-spain-transgender-gambling-angela-ponce/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage  quits UKIP over Tommy Robinson...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/7899373/nigel-farage-sensationally-quits-ukip-over-fears-party-is-turning-into-bnp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THREE time UKIP leader Nigel Farage has sensationally QUIT the party tonight. Ukip’s most famous face has torn up his membership card after 25 years in disgust at the party’s “obsession…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkest hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6458055/Attorney-General-SUSPENDED-MPs-hold-contempt-vote-Brexit-advice.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid a crucial test of strength between the House of Commons and the government, Labour's Keir Starmer warned that ministers are committing contempt of Parliament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEAR,  SLOWING ECONOMY</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-03/asian-stocks-set-for-muted-open-curve-flattens-markets-wrap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Mysterious Florida tunnels' secrets revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/mysterious-florida-tunnels-secrets-revealed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A newspaper article from almost 100 years ago has shed new light on the mysterious tunnel network beneath the historic neighborhood of Ybor City in Tampa, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS FEAR SLOWING ECONOMY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/04/stock-market-dow-futures-fall-amid-us-china-trade-deal-skepticism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell sharply on Tuesday in the biggest decline since the October rout as investors worried about a bond-market phenomenon signaling a possible economic slowdown. Lingering worries around U.S.-China trade also added to jitters down Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANK STOCKS FLASHING</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/04/bank-stocks-fall-the-most-in-more-than-a-year-enter-bear-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regional banks dipped into bear market territory Tuesday as long-term interest rates sank amid concerns of waning economic activity and falling inflation expectations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW -750</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/%5EDJI?p=^DJI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View the basic ^DJI stock chart on Yahoo Finance. Change the date range, chart type and compare Dow Jones Industrial Average against other companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Gets NHL Expansion Team...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/seattle-gets-nhl-expansion-team-1543954066</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NHL is expanding to Seattle, starting in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada desperately looking to fill 430,000 vacant jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181204-canada-desperately-looking-fill-430000-vacant-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada desperately looking to fill 430,000 vacant jobs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 attorneys general to subpoena Trump Org, IRS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8335d630f04248fe9175f893c6641729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The attorneys general of the District of Columbia and Maryland plan to file subpoenas Tuesday seeking records from the Trump Organization, the Internal Revenue Service and dozens of other entities as part of a lawsuit accusing Donald Trump of profiting off the presidency. The flurry of subpoenas came a day after U.S. District Court Judge Peter J. Messitte approved a brisk schedule for discovery in the case alleging that foreign and domestic government spending at Trump's Washington, D.C., hotel amounts to gifts to the president in violation of the Constitution's emoluments clause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX Workers In Violent Road Rage Incident Outside Funeral...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/03/fedex-workers-charged-with-assault-after-road-rage-incident-outside-funeral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident happened Monday afternoon as dozens of mourners were leaving a funeral at Bait El Maqdis Islamic Center on 63rd Street and Sixth Avenue in Sunset Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US general to Congress: War in Afghanistan at stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca8730a9b13f4eaba8b3de4cee35eb9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The fight in Afghanistan is at a stalemate, and the significant number of Afghan troop deaths in the war is not sustainable, the Marine officer nominated to command U.S. forces in the Middle East told lawmakers on Tuesday. Marine Lt. Gen. Kenneth McKenzie warned the Senate Armed Services Committee against an abrupt withdrawal of American forces or change in strategy despite frustration over the status of the 17-year conflict. He said he doesn't know how long it will take to develop an Afghan force capable of defending its own country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Dole Pays Respects in Stirring Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-bob-dole-pays-emotional-tribute-to-bush-at-capitol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85-Year-Old Man Attacked By Gator In FL Retirement Community...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/12/04/man-bitten-by-gator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 85-year-old man is hospitalized after he was bitten by an alligator at a retirement community in Lakeland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO DEAL? NO WAY! Theresa May suffers humiliating Commons defeat...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/brexit/7893804/theresa-may-brexit-deal-house-of-commons-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARLIAMENT is set to block a No Deal Brexit if Theresa May’s deal falls next week, it emerged tonight. In a massive blow for the Prime Minister, MPs voted to hijack Brexit if her withdrawal a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti to Skip 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/04/avenatti-announces-that-he-will-not-run-for-president-in-2020-1043388</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The celebrity lawyer says his family has requested that he not mount a presidential campaign against Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE: STEELERS Fan Chokes Pregnant CHARGERS Fan...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2018/12/04/steelers-fans-chokes-pregnant-chargers-fan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New video shows another violent fight during the Pittsburgh Steelers Sunday night game against the Los Angeles Charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorillas solve puzzle -- by cheating...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-science-gorilla-gaming/cheating-gorillas-show-clever-puzzle-solving-idUSKBN1O31CO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gorillas at a zoo in England have demonstrated a distinctly human trait while at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA recalls toxic dog food...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/dog-food-recall-8-brands-toxic-levels-of-vitamin-d-fda-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight brands of dry dog foods are being recalled after the FDA said the food could contain toxic levels of vitamin D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members 'Lining Up' for Impeachment Committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/video/2018/12/03/daily-beasts-woodruff-dems-lining-up-to-get-on-nadlers-committee-anticipating-impeachment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday on MSNBC's "Hardball," political reporter for the Daily Beast Betsy Woodruff said Democrats are "lining up" to get on the House Judiciary Committee | Video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More bodies found on TX ranches...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/12/04/three-migrants-found-dead-near-texas-border-in-as-many-days/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Border Patrol agents and local law enforcement recovered the bodies or remains of three deceased migrants in as many days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Children Dropped from Border Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/12/03/border-patrol-video-shows-migrant-children-being-dropped-from-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Yuma Sector Border Patrol camera operator observed a suspected human smuggler dropping two small children from the top of an 18-foot border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Overwhelming majority of adults so unhealthy lives at risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-46439892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey in England suggests nearly 9 in 10 have at least one unhealthy trait such as smoking or drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAGLIA: Hillary wants Trump to win again... </title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/camille-paglia-hillary-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 million pounds of beef recalled in salmonella scare...</title>
      <link>http://www.wtxl.com/million-pounds-of-beef-products-recalled-nationwide-due-to-salmonella/article_460e63b6-f79b-11e8-a461-973cb7ff7efd.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wtxl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(WTXL) - As the U.S. Department of Agriculture investigated an October recall on beef, officials realized some patients were falling ill from products not included in the initial recall, so</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD to deploy drone fleet...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/nypd-drone-program</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skies above New York City will be covered by a fleet drones piloted by police officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sicilian mafia smashed after arrest of 46 mobsters...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7ed7f3b3137641d9ae8a606b70bec28a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Italian authorities said Tuesday they had dismantled the rebuilt upper echelons of the Sicilian Mafia by arresting 46 people including the presumed new regional boss who took over after the death of the "boss of bosses" Salvatore "Toto" Riina. Interior Minister Matteo Salvini called the sweep an "extraordinary operation" in the Sicilian capital, Palermo. Based on wiretaps, police determined that during a May 29 meeting of clan leaders in Palermo, Settimo Mineo had been elected head of the "cupola," the mob leadership. It was the first time clan leaders had gathered in such a forum for years, and followed the November 2017 death of Riina, prosecutors said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Russia just put weapon in orbit? Mysterious launch prompts concerns...</title>
      <link>https://thenewsrep.com/111080/did-russia-just-put-a-new-weapon-in-orbit-mysterious-launch-prompts-new-concerns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenewsrep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER REDSKINS QB Breaks Leg...</title>
      <link>https://thefandc.radio.com/articles/news/colt-mccoy-played-through-broken-leg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefandc.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN Climate Chief: We require deep transformations of  economies, societies...</title>
      <link>http://www.climatedepot.com/2018/12/03/un-climate-chief-has-solution-to-urgent-climate-threat-we-require-deep-transformations-of-our-economies-and-societies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.climatedepot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Attacker chases injured victims to hospital, shoots man at doorway, kills self...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/local/crime/article222591820.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kansas City, Kan., police are investigating a shooting at the University of Kansas Medical Center. A suspect left one victim in critical condition and another injured before killing himself, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sicilian mafia smashed after arrest of 46 mobsters...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/sicilian-mafia-smashed-after-arrest-13685504</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State prosecutors say the arrests are the "one of the biggest blows ever inflicted" on the mafia come after the first gathering of mob families for more than 25 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattooed Maestro Aims to Take Met Opera Into New Era...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tattooed-maestro-aims-to-take-met-opera-into-new-era-1543936023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Metropolitan Opera’s new music director, Yannick Nézet-Séguin, debuts Tuesday with ‘La Traviata’ as he grasps the challenge to reverse audience declines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARBON TAX REVOLT!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/france-to-delay-fuel-tax-increase-after-violent-protests-1543925246</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron delayed a planned tax increase on fuel, handing a victory to a grass-roots protest movement that has massed across France to challenge his agenda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LBGT Writer Gets Death Threats After Calling Ariana Grande Video 'Anti-Queer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/lgbt-site-writer-calls-ariana-grandes-new-video-anti-queer-removes-byline-after-death-threats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When a writer’s own life could potentially be at stake, we must take necessary steps to ensure their safety," INTO says in a statement added to the piece</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Trump touts trade war truce, China holds its tongue...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trade-china-differences/as-trump-touts-trade-war-truce-china-holds-its-tongue-idUSKBN1O31NB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As White House officials fanned out to talk up what U.S. President Donald Trump ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tired of waiting for asylum, migrants from caravan breach U.S. border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-caravan/tired-of-waiting-for-asylum-migrants-from-caravan-breach-u-s-border-idUSKBN1O30D5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central American migrants stuck on the threshold of the United States in Mexico ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS to cut workforce...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-thomsonreuters-jobs/thomson-reuters-to-cut-workforce-by-3200-or-12-percent-by-2020-idUSKBN1O31OL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomson Reuters Corp said on Tuesday that it will cut its workforce by 12 percen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France suspends fuel tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests/macron-makes-u-turn-on-fuel-tax-increases-in-face-of-yellow-vest-protests-idUSKBN1O30MX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's prime minister on Tuesday suspended planned increases to fuel taxe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos, or keep calm and carry on? What happens if May loses Brexit vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-vote-explainer/explainer-chaos-or-keep-calm-and-carry-on-what-happens-if-uks-may-loses-brexit-vote-idUSKBN1O31SJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May needs to win approval for her Brexit deal in ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Born in USA, Florida man says ICE requested deportation to Jamaica...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/12/04/in-fla-us-citizen-says-ice-requested-he-be-held-for-deportation-to-jamaica/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This case tests the relationship between federal immigration operations and local law enforcement, exposing the flip side of the Trump administration’s row with so-called sanctuary cities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOBODY Wants to Host OSCARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/why-oscar-host-is-worst-job-town-1165880</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the 91st Academy Awards less than three months away, producer Donna Gigliotti has yet to line up an emcee, but don’t blame her —  it's a gig that almost no one should want.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: World's best restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6446521/The-worlds-best-restaurants-named-TripAdvisor.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They have been handed the accolades as part of TripAdvisor's 2018 Travellers' Choice Restaurants Awards. The restaurants coming second and third are both in Spain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series of disclosures...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/04/politics/robert-mueller-donald-trump-michael-flynn-paul-manafort-russia-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America may get its most intimate look yet inside Robert Mueller's secretive Russia investigation in the next four days, with a series of disclosures that have the potential to be greatly damaging for President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men booted from leadership positions...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/women-in-democratic-leadership-116th-congress-dcf34228-a42b-4436-bffb-e753b8bd6c88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a recognition of the importance of women in the Democratic coalition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US embassy closed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/africa/419583-us-embassy-closes-over-isis-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Embassy in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) was closed after U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>300 pound woman guilty of crushing boyfriend to death...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/300-pound-woman-guilty-of-crushing-boyfriend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman has pleaded guilty to killing her boyfriend by stabbing him, hitting him with a table leg and crushing him under the weight of her roughly 300 pounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE CHANGES ON MACRON</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181204135718-mg8jt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-PROTESTS/STUDENTS (TV, PIX):French student unrest gathers momentum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Xi agreement buys time in trade war...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-xi-agreement-buys-time-063308061.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The dinner table diplomacy that Presidents Donald Trump and Xi Jinping of China conducted over the weekend produced something as vague as it was valuable: an agreement to keep talking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIKOFF:  MUELLER PREPS END OF RUSSIA PROBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mueller-preparing-end-game-russia-investigation-225720798.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The office of the special counsel investigating ties between the Trump campaign and Russia in the 2016 election says it is "tying up loose ends."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico's new 'common man' president hits ground running...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexicos-common-man-president-hits-ground-running-140213915.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexico's newly inaugurated president kicked off his first Monday in office with something not seen in recent history — a news conference and a pledge to hold one every working day of his six-year term to keep the people informed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Global Carbon Tax Revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-global-carbon-tax-revolt-1543880507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French are the latest to refuse to sacrifice growth for green piety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DJs Get Into Streaming Revenue Mix...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/djs-get-into-streaming-revenue-mix-1543924803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DJs are about to get a cut of streaming revenue, a new source of funds for artists who typically make a living performing in front of live audiences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Dumps $1 BILLION More of U.S. Real Estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-dumped-1-billion-of-u-s-real-estate-in-third-quarter-extending-recent-retreat-1543924802 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising corporate debt levels, concern over currency stability led Beijing to tighten capital outflows and curb overseas acquisitions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Markets Wobble, Cash is King...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/as-markets-wobble-cash-is-king-1543921730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. cash and cash equivalents are on track to be some of the best-performing assets in 2018, enticing money managers amid a rare synchronized downturn in stocks, commodities and bond markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A site says data breach may affect 100 million users...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/news/2018/12/04/quora-says-data-breach-may-affect-100-million-its-q-site/2200175002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quora, a question-and-answer website with 300 million users, says a data breach may have compromised 100 million users' data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNISM:  Havana collapsing, building by building...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/12/02/havana-cuba-collapsing-buildings-housing-unesco/1998606002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Building collapses worsened an already severe housing shortage. Havana alone had a deficit of 206,000 homes in 2016, official figures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise? Just have a long, hot bath...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/dont-go-for-a-long-hot-run-try-running-a-long-hot-bath-c9f5x5cp3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the choice of a bath or a shower, my overwhelming preference is to spend time in a tub. I am, it must be said, something of a serial soaker, luxuriating in a warm, scented bath at least five...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANET OF THE APES:  ISLAND OF 'MONSTER' CHIMPS RELEASED FROM LABS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7893314/monkey-island-liberia-lab-tested-chimpanzees-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the secret African island inhabited by super aggressive “monster'” chimps all freed from a US testing laboratory. The apes -who are infected with contagious diseases- were aband…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University hosts critical look at 'whiteness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/university-hosts-critical-look-at-whiteness-forum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual event at Cal State San Marcos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA drove 7 miles using Autopilot as driver allegedly slept drunk behind wheel...</title>
      <link>https://www.techspot.com/news/77672-tesla-drove-7-miles-using-autopilot-diver-allegedly.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.techspot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police spotted the gray Model S belonging to Alexander Samek, the chair of the Los Altos Planning Commission, doing 70 mph on Highway 101 early Friday. As this was above the speed limit, officers pulled up alongside the car and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Millennial Men Ditching 'Masculine' Values...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/millennial-men-ditching-masculine-values-embracing-altruism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the famous Village People song declares, "Every man wants to be a macho macho man / To have the kind of body, always in demand." But are "macho macho" mindsets becoming a thing of the past? A new study finds that male millennials are drifting away from stereotypical masculine values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500-year-old skeleton found in River Thames -- still wearing boots...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/london/500yearold-skeleton-found-in-river-thames-wearing-remarkably-wellpreserved-boots-a4007416.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 500-year-old skeleton has been found in the River Thames wearing remarkably well-preserved knee-high leather boots. The mysterious male skeleton was found face down in the Thames mud by archaeologists working on one of the sites used to build London’s sewers in Bermondsey. Incredibly, the man’s tough leather boots have survived centuries and are in good enough nick for examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: MANAFORT TRIED TO BROKER ASSANGE DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/03/us/politics/manafort-assange-wikileaks-ecuador.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is no evidence that Paul Manafort was working with President Trump or other administration officials on the talks, which stemmed from 2017 discussions on Chinese investment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is visiting robot brothel ok? Most say yes -- if single...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2187075-is-visiting-a-robot-brothel-ok-most-people-say-yes-if-you-are-single/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When people in Finland were asked about the morality of visiting a robot brothel most thought it was OK for singles to do it, but not people who were married</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital-media bubble bursting?</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/opinion/article/Digital-media-bubble-is-bursting-That-s-hurting-13439600.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About five years ago, I was asked to visit the newsroom at Mic, a digital-media start-up backed by venture capital and focused on news for the millennial audience. As the public editor of The New York Times, I suppose I was seen as an expert in traditional journalism ethics - especially through the eyes of Mic's reporters and editors, mostly in their 20s, and many in their first jobs out of school. And because I was active on Twitter and writing a frequent blog, perhaps I looked like I knew how to build a bridge from old-school newspapering to the digital-first present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Investigations Will the Dems Launch First?</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2018/12/which-investigations-will-the-dems-launch-first/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They will have plenty of targets to choose from come January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California charges trio who made millions via 'recycling fraud'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercedsunstar.com/news/state/california/article222572040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercedsunstar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona trucking company allegedly smuggled millions of dollars worth of recyclable beverage containers into California, according to the California Attorney General Xavier Becerra’s office. Three men are charged with recycling fraud.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study reveals actors in worst-reviewed movies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcall.com/ct-ent-actors-worst-movies-1205-20181203-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study revealed the actors in the worst-reviewed movies of the past 20 years — and many were Oscar winners.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge under investigation for illegal's escape from ICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/news/index.ssf/2018/12/massachusetts_judge_under_scru.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Massachusetts district court judge who is reportedly under federal investigation should not be handling criminal cases while a review is underway, Gov. Charlie Baker said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump begins courting Democrats...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-begins-courting-Democrats-13440639.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, facing a Congress that will become dramatically more antagonistic toward him in January, has begun courting Democrats who could determine whether his next two years are spent scoring legislative deals or staving off an onslaught of congressional investigations. Trump's charm offensive was on display Monday when he hosted Sen. Joe Manchin, D-W.Va., at the White House for a meeting that the two men had spent days trying to schedule. Over a lunch of chicken, green beans and mashed potatoes, Manchin preached bipartisanship - urging the president to work with lawmakers on ending a pension crisis affecting tens of thousands of coal miners nationwide, said Jonathan Kott, Manchin's spokesman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' JOLTS HOLLYWOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/hollywood/la-fi-ct-netflix-roma-20181203-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing rising competition from Disney and other media giants entering into the streaming business, Netflix is increasingly eager to lure filmmakers who want their movies to be shown on a big screen and get awards recognition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog sniffs out owner's cancer THREE times...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/columnists/jim-stingl/2018/11/30/womans-dog-detects-her-ovarian-cancer-three-times/2154700002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sierra madeÂ her diagnosis, which she tried to communicate by freaking out and rolling up in a ball in the back of a closet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garlic holds promise in treating lingering Lyme...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/garlic-holds-promise-in-treating-lingering-lyme-disease-research-finds/article_c87fe1ca-3b2a-5d5d-a5be-d1c6b155b48d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oils from garlic and other common herbs and medicinal plants are showing promise in the lab for treating the bacteria that causes Lyme disease, and may prove especially useful in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel launches operation to destroy Hezbollah infiltration tunnels...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181204-israel-lebanon-netanyahu-operation-hezbollah-pompeo-tunnels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel’s army said on Tuesday it had detected Hezbollah tunnels infiltrating its territory from Lebanon and launched an operation to destroy them, a move likely to raise tensions with the Iran-backed group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy to populate sea with genetically engineered marine life forms... </title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2018/12/us-military-genetically-engineering-new-life-forms-detect-enemy-subs/153200/?oref=d-river</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon is also looking at living camouflage, self-healing paint, and a variety of other applications of engineered organisms, but the basic science remains a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARIS REMAINS TENSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6454033/Riot-police-beat-lone-protester-shocking-video-Paris.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video footage shows teenagers fleeing from police tear gas in Orleans during a demonstration against President Macron's university education reforms earlier today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAKE OR BREAK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/03/trump-china-trade-talks-and-nafta-fight-in-congress-set-up-key-stretch.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commitment to talks throws Trump into his most high-stakes period yet in his yearslong effort to crack down on what he calls unfair trade practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress to delay border wall fight until Friday before Christmas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/03/congress-to-delay-government-shutdown-date-trump-border-wall-fight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both chambers aim to approve a funding extension by voice vote before Friday's government shutdown deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert claims GOOGLE search irregularities in 2018 election...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/12/03/dr-robert-epstein-moderate-republicans-most-vulnerable-to-google-influence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychologist Dr. Robert Epstein appeared on SiriusXM Patriot's Breitbart News Sunday to discuss Google's power and influence over public opinion and voting patterns with Breitbart News Deputy political editor Amanda House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not enough?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2018/12/04/not-enough-yellow-vests-reject-temporary-suspension-fuel-tax-rises-france/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representatives from the Yellow Vest movement have said that a temporary suspension of a further tax increase does not go far enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Money? Swiss Can't Raise Enough Funds to Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/free-money-swiss-village-can-t-raise-enough-funds-to-experiment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crowdfunding campaign yielded just 151,836 francs, a fraction of the 6.1 million francs required for the experiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World becoming more allergic to food...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-46302780</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Food allergy rates among children are on the rise, and Western lifestyles may be to blame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller breadcrumbs suggest he has the goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/mueller-investigation-report-details-court-filings-2511dd33-1928-4431-a9bb-09488ee216ef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his major court filings so far, Mueller has already written more than 290 pages of the "Mueller Report."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaires with eye on White House to visit key states...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bacce76099b24348a64d9859f2aac1b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Two deep-pocketed Democrats are set to travel to early presidential primary states, stoking further speculation about whether they will soon launch bids for the White House. Michael Bloomberg, the billionaire former New York mayor, is set to visit three towns in Iowa on Tuesday, while billionaire investor and activist Tom Steyer will host a town hall in Charleston, South Carolina. Both men have been noncommittal about whether they will run for president in 2020. But with as many as two dozen Democrats considering a campaign, they'll likely have to decide whether to run early in the new year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,400 aftershocks since Alaska quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2018/12/03/nearly-1400-aftershocks-have-been-measured-since-fridays-70-earthquake-in-alaska/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most have been small, but at least 18 have measured 4.0 or greater. They should decrease in size and number.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE COOK:  'Hate and division' have no place on tech platforms...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/419541-tim-cook-hateful-views-have-no-place-on-tech-platforms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple CEO Tim Cook on Monday said he believes it is "right" and "moral" for technology companies to block hate speech and violent conspiracy theories from their platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: I am most qualified...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/419577-biden-i-think-i-am-the-most-qualified-person-in-the-country-to-be-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden fueled speculation he might make a 2020 bid for the White House, saying Monday night that he believes he is the “most qualified” person to take on President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Murphy announces initiative to vote out anti-LGBTQ lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/419504-tv-producer-ryan-murphy-announces-multi-million-dollar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Television producer Ryan Murphy is announcing a multimillion-dollar initiative to help elect pro-LGBTQ candidates and vote out anti-LGBTQ incumbents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kellyanne husband suggests Trump tampering with witnesses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/419454-conways-husband-suggests-trump-is-tampering-with-witnesses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, suggested on Monday that President Trump obstructed justice and tampered with a witness when he praised Roger Stone for vowing never to testify against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TUMBLR to delete all porn...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2018/12/03/tumblr-no-more-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tumblr, a microblogging service that’s impact on internet culture has been massive and unique, is preparing for a massive change that’s sure to upset many of its millions of users. On December 17, Tumblr will be banning porn, errr “adult content,” from its site and encouragi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents using GPS ankle monitors to track teens...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1482833/parents-are-putting-gps-ankle-monitors-on-their-teenage-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No court order necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS Threatens NYC with Sniper Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/isis-groups-nyc-new-years-threat-harvest-them-with-silencers-and-snipers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest threat circulated online follows other message from jihadists that have specifically cited Jan. 1 in calling for attacks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR IS SCORNED:  Madonna goes after Lady Gaga... </title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/12/03/madonna-goes-after-lady-gaga-in-latest-instagram/?_ga=2.35297441.1051984005.1543890915-1073313886.1542905213</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If there are 100 people in a room and 99 say they liked it, I only remember the one person who didn’t,” Madonna said back in the ’80s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIBERTY MEDIA angling to snag post-bankruptcy iHEARTMEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/03/liberty-media-angling-to-snag-post-bankruptcy-iheartmedia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radio giant iHeartMedia just took a major step toward emerging from bankruptcy — and falling into the clutches of John Malone. The Denver-based media tycoon is angling to take control of the broadc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nigerian President denies dying, replaced by clone...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/nigerian-president-muhammadu-buhari-denies-he-died-and-was-replaced-by-clone-11570542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rumours, spread on social media, alleged that the Nigerian leader was replaced by a Sudanese impostor named "Jubril".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Zucker: I'm Interested in Running For Office...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/cnns-zucker-im-interested-in-running-for-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN President Jeff Zucker said in a newly released interview he is "very interested in politics" and is considering running for office someday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RESPECT FOR BUSH</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2b97b9b238ad4aeda3f58ef906b333a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The nation's capital embraced George H.W. Bush in death Monday with solemn ceremony and high tributes to his service and decency, as the remains of the 41st president took their place in the Capitol rotunda for three days of mourning and praise by the political elite and everyday citizens alike. With Bush's casket atop the Lincoln Catafalque, first used for Abraham Lincoln's 1865 funeral, dignitaries came forward to honor the Texan whose efforts for his country extended three quarters of a century from World War II through his final years as an advocate for volunteerism and relief for people displaced by natural disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft visitor on ancient asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/144355e6b43a4202936456caacc80775</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — After a two-year chase, a NASA spacecraft arrived Monday at the ancient asteroid Bennu, its first visitor in billions of years. The robotic explorer Osiris-Rex pulled within 12 miles (19 kilometers) of the diamond-shaped space rock. It will get even closer in the days ahead and go into orbit around Bennu on Dec. 31. No spacecraft has ever orbited such a small cosmic body. It is the first U.S. attempt to gather asteroid samples for return to Earth, something only Japan has accomplished so far.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New court filings could offer 'road map'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/court-filings-due-week-offer-road-map-mueller/story?id=59591976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of court filings due this week that could shed new light on the way high-profile witnesses have been behaving behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TheBlaze</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And President Donald Trump handles George H.W. Bush’s death with abnormal normality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official Website of The Sean Hannity Show. Sean Hannity is a multimedia superstar, spending four hours a day every day reaching out to millions of Americans on radio, television and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state funeral will take place Wednesday morning at the Washington National Cathedral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, womenâ€™s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel to recommend sentencing for Flynn...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181204105556-lc7gd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/RUSSIA-FLYNN:Mueller's office to recommend sentencing for ex-Trump aide Flynn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain can end Brexit unilaterally says top EU court adviser...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181204081741-7ca88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ARTICLE50 (URGENT):Britain can end Brexit unilaterally says top EU court adviser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston news, sports, politics, opinion, entertainment, weather and obituaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
