<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Humans Born Kind? Researchers Prove Altruistic Behavior Begins In Infancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/benevolent-babies-infants-quick-to-share-food-help-others-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers studied nearly 100 infants, and discovered they were quick to share their food, even when they themselves were undoubtedly hungry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES 'BEST IS YET TO COME'</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/02/04/trump_at_state_of_the_union_the_best_is_yet_to_come.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump promised "the best is yet to come" at the 2020 State of the Union address. PRESIDENT DONALD J. TRUMP: This is our glorious and magnificent inheritance. We are Americans, we are pioneers, we are the pathfinders, we settled the new world, we built the modern world and we changed history forever by embracing the eternal truth that everyone is made equal by the almighty hand of God. America is the place where anything can happen. America is the place where anyone can rise. Here, on this land, on this soil, on this continent, the most incredible dreams come true. This nation is our canvas and this country is our masterpiece. We look at tomorrow and see a limited frontiers just waiting to be explored. Our brightest discoveries are not yet known. Our most thrilling stories are not yet told. Our grandest journeys are not yet made. The American age, the American epic, the American adventure has only just begun. Our spirit is still young. The sun is still rising. God's grace is still shining. My fellow Americans, the best is yet to come. Thank you. Thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkland father removed from speech after protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article239976003.html?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI RIPS UP SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/watch-nancy-pelosi-rips-up-trumps-sotu-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi tore up a copy of President Donald Trump's speech at the conclusion of his State of the Union address on Tuesday night. The event was marked by concurrent spectacles. T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotions run high...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200205030741-tofp0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/SPEECH (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Trump snubs Pelosi, she tears up his speech as impeachment trial nears end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP AWARDS LIMBAUGH MEDAL OF FREEDOM AT STATE OF UNION</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2020/02/04/melania_trump_awards_rush_limbaugh_presidential_medal_of_freedom_at_trump_state_of_the_union_address.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch: First lady Melania Trump presents Rush Limbaugh with Presidential Medal of Freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF UNION: President confronts impeachment foes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/314d6d298427151dc580f81a3ebece78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Addressing the nation in extraordinary times, President Donald Trump declared America “stronger than ever before” Tuesday night as he delivered his State of the Union address on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence photos of naked Harvey passed around jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-harvey-weinstein-trial-20200204-voz53d3oxvfwrhw3vjydczl2q4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jessica Mann, returning to a Manhattan courtroom one day after a witness stand meltdown, also testified that her access to the Oscar-winning movie maker could be a positive thing when asked by defense attorney Donna Rotunno about reaching out to Weinstein for help with a 2016 business venture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD scandal opens window into California's secret gang database as reforms debated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/lapd-scandal-opens-window-into-californias-secret-gang-database-as-reforms-debated/ar-BBZDnOD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless camp the size of 3 football fields catches fire in Austin...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/officials-consider-next-steps-after-large-homeless-camp-fire-in-ne-austin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fire broke out at a large homeless camp below the eastbound frontage road of Anderson Lane, between IH-35 and Cameron Road Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?468549-1/2020-state-union-address&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump delivers the State of the Union address to a joint session of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg Seeks to Capitalize With New Ad Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloomberg-seeks-capitalize-iowa-chaos-213026309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Michael Bloomberg is doubling his already unprecedented television advertising budget and expanding his field staff in an effort to capitalize on the chaos in the Iowa caucus.Bloomberg, who is skipping the first four contests in February, is immediately increasing spending on ads in markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snubs Pelosi handshake...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-snubs-pelosi-handshake-attempt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCARS Voter Reveals Ballot: 'MARRIAGE STORY' Was Fake, 'IRISHMAN' Boring...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/brutally-honest-oscar-ballot-irishman-was-boring-tarantino-amazing-1275576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As voting ends, a female member of the Academy's actors branch, granted anonymity to speak freely, shares which films earn her precious vote (and — gulp — why).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madness or visionary investing?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b98dbef7b86e27b98698cddf9567d778</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — Eight months after it seemed headed for the corporate junkyard, Tesla is now worth more than General Motors, Ford and Fiat Chrysler combined, even though the Big Three together sell...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's poor showing shakes establishment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a6ea236b5abcb43b40f79cfbf3f8c20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Joe Biden's third presidential bid enters a critical stretch after a disappointing finish in the Iowa caucuses sent the former vice president on to New Hampshire with a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newport Beach Swinging Surgeon Cleared of Rape...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/grant-robicheaux-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Newport Beach surgeon and girlfriend Cerissa Riley were charged with rape by drugs, oral copulation by anesthesia, and assault with intent to commit sexual offenses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Administration Proposes Government Licenses for News Websites...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2020/02/03/trudeau-minister-proposes-forcing-news-websites-government-license/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Heritage Minister Steven Guilbeault has stated that news websites could be forced to obtain government licenses to operate in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIZA OPENS UP  IN RARE INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/features/liza-minnelli-judy-garland-bob-fosse-rehab-1203490846/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liza Minnelli is getting ready to be photographed for the cover of Variety. She’s wearing an off-the-shoulder black beaded shirtdress and perched on a director’s chair. As she adjusts herself, tryi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Attorney Questions Accuser's Psychiatric History; 'Private' Photos Of Harvey Shown To Jury...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/harvey-weinstein-rape-trial-jessica-mann-psychiatric-history-private-photos-shown-to-jury-1202851381/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defense team for accused rapist Harvey Weinstein on Tuesday questioned accuser Jessica Mann about her psychiatric and emotional history, eliciting responses indicating that Mann had been diagno…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Unveils Electronic Trackers for Suspected Virus Carriers...</title>
      <link>https://coconuts.co/hongkong/news/govt-unveils-new-electronic-tags-for-people-under-wuhan-coronavirus-home-quarantine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;coconuts.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has Top TV News Anchors Over for Lunch; Eats Them Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-had-americas-top-tv-news-anchors-over-for-lunch-and-ate-them-alive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Beast learned that Trump’s off-record Tuesday lunch with prominent news anchors was surprisingly “chill,” with the president mocking his chuckling guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAUCUS CONFUSION:  DEMS RELEASE PARTIAL RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2020/02/04/iowa-democratic-party-delayed-caucus-results-should-soon-published/4659581002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We hit a stumbling block," Iowa Democratic Party chair Troy Price said Tuesday, "but we know this data is accurate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TO AWARD LIMBAUGH MEDAL OF FREEDOM</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/rush-limbaugh-donald-trump-medal-of-freedom/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump told network anchors during a private lunch Tuesday that he will award Rush Limbaugh with the Medal of Freedom, one day after the prominent political radio host announced he has advanced lung cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Media Hyped Digital Startup Behind 'Shadow'...</title>
      <link>https://theoutline.com/post/8636/acronym-shadow-iowa-caucus-results-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theoutline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shadow, a branch of the glossy digital strategy startup, was a mess from the start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Dolls Experience raises eyebrows in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-las-vegas/sex-dolls-experience-raises-eyebrows-in-las-vegas-neighborhood-1950537/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Neighbors and county officials are concerned about the existence of an alleged sex doll brothel and sex club operating in a central Las Vegas neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm not bitter'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/04/trump-on-impeachment-not-bitter-110720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president told television anchors ahead of his State of the Union address that he’ll defer comments about impeachment until his acquittal a day later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN 15%</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/2020-election/results/iowa/?2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Explore POLITICO's real-time 2020 Iowa election results and live maps by county and district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Collins will vote to acquit...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/maine-gop-sen-susan-collins-key-swing-vote-senator-announces-she-will-acquit-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine Republican Sen. Susan Collins, a key swing vote in President Trump's impeachment trial, announced she would vote to acquit on both articles of impeachment -- noting that Democrats' "abuse of power" charge "did not even attempt" to allege that Trump had committed a crime, and instead constituted a "difficult-to-define, non-criminal act."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates snipe at each other...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/04/buttigieg-narrative-iowa-caucus-official-results-110663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The blame game kicked into high gear as the Iowa Democratic Party prepares to release a portion of the caucus results at 5 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House excludes CNN from session, with no protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.ny1.com/nyc/all-boroughs/ap-top-news/2020/02/04/white-house-excludes-cnn-from-trump-session-with-no-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ny1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House excluded CNN from its annual off-the-record briefing with television news personalities prior to the State of the Union address</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic 'black goo' base used by U.S. had enriched uranium. Vets report cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/national/national-security/article239856133.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S to close 125 stores...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/macys-to-close-125-stores-sees-480-million-in-restructuring-costs-to-2000-corporate-jobs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macy's stock, which is valued at more than $5 billion, has fallen 36% over the past 12 months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez skipping...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/AOC/status/1224794340272242689</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“After much deliberation, I have decided that I will not use my presence at a state ceremony to normalize Trump’s lawless conduct &amp;amp; subversion of the Constitution. None of this is normal, and I will not legitimize it. Consequently, I will not be attending the State of the Union.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macau casinos told to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-health/china-virus-claims-second-life-off-mainland-macau-casinos-told-to-close-idUSKBN1ZY05A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus outbreak claimed its first life in Hong Kong on Tuesday, compoun...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even middle class having trouble paying rent now...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-rent-is-too-damn-high-even-for-middle-income-americans-2020-02-04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in four renters now spend more than half their incomes on housing, a new study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE 'accidentally' sends users' private videos to strangers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/google-accidentally-sent-some-users-private-videos-to-strangers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google apologized on Tuesday for accidentally sending users' private videos to strangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why vegans inspire hatred...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200203-the-hidden-biases-that-drive-anti-vegan-hatred</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People love to moan about vegans: research shows only drug addicts inspire the same loathing. Now psychologists may understand why – and the reasoning isn't entirely rational.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors Rush to Downplay Ties...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/investors-rush-to-downplay-ties-to-shadow-the-firm-behind-iowa-caucus-clusterfuck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frantic cleanup put a microscope on one of Democratic Party’s fastest-rising digital stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE FURIOUS...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/elections/presidential/caucus/2020/02/04/bernie-sanders-disappointed-iowa-democrats-havent-released-caucus-results/4656451002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before heading to New Hampshire, the senator said that results should not take this much time to release in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tries to reassure donors; Guarantees Nevada, SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/biden-reassures-donors-he-will-win-nevada-south-carolina-after-iowa-caucus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a conference call with some of Biden's top donors hours after the Iowa contest concluded, campaign officials said they were confident they can win the two votes at the end of the month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Wilson Urges Fans To Boycott BEACH BOYS Over  Trump Jr. Hunting Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/brian-wilson-beach-boys-boycott-urges-fans-over-donald-trump-jr-hunting-event-safari-club/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wilson shared a petition that urges fans to stop buying or downloading the band's music, going to their concerts and purchasing merchandise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand names 'whistleblower' in Senate...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200204173901-7ij95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT-PAUL:Republican Rand Paul names purported 'whistleblower' in the Senate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV drugs touted as weapon in war...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hiv-drugs-touted-weapon-war-coronavirus-134745541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As doctors scramble to contain the fast-spreading coronavirus, a potent brew of anti-retroviral and flu drugs has emerged as a possible defence against the disease that has killed hundreds. Used together, lopinavir and ritonavir decrease the amount of HIV cells in a patient's blood, stripping back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 earthquakes rattle Tennessee in month...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article239943558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus hoax forces flight back to airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/article239945633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre moment two disc-shaped objects appear in sky  -- before 'multiplying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/bizarre-moment-two-disc-shaped-21428429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two ring-shaped flying objects appeared above the city of Irkutsk before a third ring emerged from behind as citizens sparked dicussion online of the mysterious phenomenon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg Shrugs Off Criticism After Claiming Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iowa-caucus-buttigieg-responds-to-election-chaos-shrugs-off-mayorcheat-twitter-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Looking at all of the data that we've got, it was an extraordinary night and we are absolutely victorious coming into New Hampshire," Buttigieg told "CBS This Morning."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oprah on Defense in Two Separate Controversies...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/film/features/oprah-winfrey-american-dirt-russell-simmons-documentary-1203491393/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before signing an open letter asking Oprah Winfrey to rescind her endorsement of Jeanine Cummins’ “American Dirt,” her latest book club pick, Jose Antonio Vargas spent the day digging around on You…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY NOT BE FIRST IN NATION EVER AGAIN!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481391-iowa-meltdown-threatens-future-of-states-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa — Iowa political experts and observers are worried their state’s first-in-the-nation status in presidential nominating contests is in jeopardy after technical issues marred Democratic caucuses on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Woman, 68, repeatedly tased husband, 73, after he asked for separation...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/taser-separation-anxiety-908351</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 4--Pamela Carr’s husband delivered some stunning news Sunday morning: He wanted a separation after nine years of marriage. The 68-year-old Carr’s response was equally shocking: She pulled ou</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warned About Problems Last Week...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/iowa-democrats-were-warned-about-app-problems-last-week-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The app—which was designed to report Iowa Democrats’ results to party officials—has been partially blamed for a deeply embarrassing night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of poisoned babies deepens after probe blunder...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/europe/mystery-of-poisoned-babies-deepens-after-german-probe-blunder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT AM MAIN (AFP) - Fresh questions emerged on Tuesday (Feb 4) in the mysterious case of five newborn babies who were drugged with morphine at a German hospital, after police said they made "a mistake" when they arrested a nurse on suspicion of attempted manslaughter.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT MESS IOWA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/iowa-democratic-party-blames-app-coding-issue-delay-caucus-results-n1129701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some precinct captains and organizers had expressed doubt about the app in the days leading up to the vote on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter Freaks Out on Buttigieg Precinct Capt. After Finding Out Pete Gay...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-iowa-voter-freaks-out-on-buttigieg-precinct-capt-after-finding-out-mayor-pete-is-gay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nikki van den Heever, a caucus precinct captain for former South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg, tried to talk down an Iowa woman who was incensed to find out — in real time during a caucus, after she'd signed a card supporting him — that the candidate is openly gay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He says mass shooting threat was joke. Case may answer whether such posts are crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/he-says-his-mass-shooting-threat-was-a-joke-his/article_62696a4b-8a5d-5618-9373-b472320e79e6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — David Puy headed out to meet friends for dinner in West Boca. “On my way! School shooter,” he wrote in a Snapchat post with his photo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor was one of first to warn about virus. He got detained -- and infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-Chinese-doctor-was-one-of-the-first-to-warn-15028767.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As word of a mysterious virus mounted, Li Wenliang shared suspicions in a private chat with his fellow medical school alumni.  The doctor said that seven people seemed to have contracted SARS - the respiratory illness that spread from China to more than two dozen countries and left hundreds dead in the early 2000s. One patient was quarantined at his hospital in Wuhan, Li said. He urged people to be careful.  Li and seven other doctors were quickly summoned by Chinese authorities for propagating "rumors" about SARS-like cases in the area - but their warnings were prescient. Soon, health officials around the world would be scrambling to combat a novel virus with a striking genetic resemblance to SARS. The outbreak in Wuhan has exploded to more than 20,000 confirmed cases just in China.  Among the ill: the ophthalmologist who was censured for sounding an early alarm.  "The diagnosis is finally confirmed," Li posted Jan. 31 on the social media platform Weibo.  Li's situation has drawn rare acknowledgment of official missteps in China, where a bureaucratic culture that prioritizes political stability over all else probably allowed the new coronavirus to spread farther and faster. Late last month, China's highest court admonished the Wuhan police for the detentions.  "If society had at the time believed those 'rumors,' and wore masks, used disinfectant and avoided going to the wildlife market as if there were a SARS outbreak, perhaps it would've meant we could better control the coronavirus today," the court said. "Rumors end when there is openness."  Li, an ophthalmologist at Wuhan Central Hospital, had shared his concerns the same day that Chinese authorities confirmed they were investigating 27 cases of viral pneumonia. Officials at the epicenter in Wuhan - the capital of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prank forces Jamaica-bound flight back to Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200204-coronavirus-prank-forces-jamaica-bound-flight-back-to-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus prank forces Jamaica-bound flight back to Canada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Also set to be used in Nevada!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/iowa-caucus-app-issues/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mobile app that has apparently caused issues during the Iowa caucuses is due to be used in the Nevada Democratic caucuses later this month, a person familiar with the app told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  TRUMP POPS TO 49% APPROVAL</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/284156/trump-job-approval-personal-best.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's job approval has climbed to 49%, his highest to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER: Might Have Screwed Up Whole Nomination Process...</title>
      <link>https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/iowa-might-have-screwed-up-the-whole-nomination-process/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In trying to build a forecast model of the Democratic primaries, we literally had to think about the entire process from start (Iowa) to finish (the Virgin Isla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Due back on stand...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dd97b161a67d367421c9b516d20023cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A key accuser in the New York City rape trial of Harvey Weinstein is due back on the witness stand for a third day of testimony after she broke down in tears Monday, halting an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems have no caucus results, blame 'coding issue'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65327a2b9acbc9c903ef7f906bfce1f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Democratic party officials in Iowa worked furiously Tuesday to deliver the delayed results of their first-in-the-nation caucus, as frustrated presidential candidates...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painting showing Hitler as Cain displayed in Berlin museum...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5b71d0b6ae5e9ce0364d26f444e4dded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A 1944 painting by German artist George Grosz that depicts Nazi leader Adolf Hitler as the Bible's fratricidal Cain went on display at the German Historical Museum in Berlin on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BESTS OBAMA </title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2020/02/04/politics/donald-trump-gallup-poll/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump has never made it to the 50% approval mark in Gallup polling, which makes him the first president never to rise above the halfway mark in the poll. But he's pretty damn close right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Forcibly Taken Away After Refusing Quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/residents-hauled-away-after-refusing-be-quarantined-new-accounts-china-detail-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS head claims Dems refused to let department test app...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/dhs-head-claims-iowa-democrats-refused-to-let-department-test-failed-caucus-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Party in Iowa declined an offer from the Department of Homeland Security to vet the app that failed during the state's caucuses on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is China Doing on Dark Side of Moon?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/what-the-hell-is-china-doing-on-the-dark-side-of-the-moon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite Trump’s ambitions to put man back on the moon, experts believe that Beijing might be preparing to make a giant leap of its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddle adds new urgency to NH, as candidates flock there...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/iowa-muddle-adds-new-urgency-to-new-hampshire-as-2020-candidates-flock-there/ar-BBZDSzs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baboon grooms little lion cub in South Africa's Kruger park...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/018e5fd57ceb38d25669329c8e05f870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — A male baboon carrying and grooming a lion cub is an unusual sight, yet it happened over the weekend in South Africa's Kruger National Park. The baboon took the cub up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross drives her to tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/key-weinstein-accuser-driven-to-tears-is-due-back-on-stand/2277523/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key accuser in the New York City rape trial of Harvey Weinstein is due back on the stand for a third day of testimony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech firm started by Clinton campaign vets linked to debacle...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/technology/story/2020-02-04/clinton-campaign-vets-behind-2020-iowa-caucus-app-snafu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shadow, a developer of campaign tools started by veterans of Hillary Clinton’s 2016 run, built the app being blamed for delayed results from the Iowa Democratic caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem convention host committee under investigation over 'work environment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/investigations/daniel-bice/2020/02/03/dnc-host-committee-leaders-sidelined-amid-probe-toxic-work-culture/4645443002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee tasked withÂ raising $70 million for the Milwaukee-hostedÂ 2020 Democratic National Convention this summer is in turmoil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami sees return to Cold War cultural hard line on Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-sees-return-cold-war-050212122.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Platinum-selling reggaeton act Gente de Zona were barred from a New Year’s Eve concert in a Miami park. The mayor of Miami declared another Cuban singer persona non grata and her concert in a private club was cancelled. Fellow artists Jacob Forever y El Micha were shut out of a July 4 concert the neighboring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA adds 'low yield' nuke to sub arsenal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b910d5f4f2076d558416ae021b511517</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. military has deployed a new addition to its nuclear arsenal — a long-range missile armed with a nuclear warhead of reduced destructive power. The so-called low-yield...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Russia stalking American spy satellite in orbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/615129/a-russian-satellite-is-probably-stalking-a-us-spy-satellite-in-orbit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This isn’t the first time Russia has engaged in such maneuvers. It’s very unclear how the US will respond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gap Between Haves and Have-Nots Widens...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/technology/big-techs-runaway-growth-widens-the-gap-tween-the-haves-and-have-nots-of-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite regulatory scrutiny and pressure from lawmakers, the industry’s wealthiest are continuing to grow at remarkable speeds for big companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Stock Skyrockets As Bulls Think It Will Keep Climbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/02/04/tesla-stock-surging-yet-again-tsla-jumps-past-800-in-early-trading.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surge on Tuesday comes after Tesla on Monday climbed nearly 20%, its biggest one-day gain in six years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Party Hangs Up On Precinct Captain On Live TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/iowa-caucus-results-chaos-is-the-big-winner-in-the-iowa-democratic-caucuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Monday turned to Tuesday, there was no victor. There weren't even officially reported votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rivals Barrel Towards New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/turning-to-new-hampshire-democratic-rivals-jostle-for-advantage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES — With a glaring question mark hanging over the Iowa caucuses, a frustrated pack of Democratic presidential candidates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii Is Paradise, but Whose?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/hawaii-is-a-paradise-but-whose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Locals in Oahu know that the best way to get from Waikiki’s crowded beaches to the cool North Shore is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to Execute 'CIA Spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/iran-sentences-alleged-cia-spy-to-death/a-52249837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman for Iran's judiciary has said one man was to be executed as a US spy. Two other suspects were given jail sentences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Death' smog over Wuhan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/fears-thick-death-smog-over-21426098</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Chinese nationals have shared their concern over a fog which has engulfed Wuhan, fuelling fears the death toll inside coronavirus-hit China is higher than what has been reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE INTERNALS SHOW THEM WINNING...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2020/02/04/sanders-campaign-release-caucus-numbers-iowa-buttigieg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The internal numbers, with 40 percent of precincts, put Sanders at 29.7 percent of the vote, closely followed by former South Bend Mayor Pete Buttigieg at 24.6 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acquittal may have profound impact on presidential power...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/481290-trumps-acquittal-may-have-profound-impact-on-presidential-power</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s acquittal at the end of his Senate trial could set a new bar for future impeachment trials, according to experts and historians interviewed by The Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to confront his impeachment foes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/481291-trump-set-to-confront-his-impeachment-foes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After sitting impatiently on the sidelines for months, President Trump on Tuesday night will finally get a chance to address — face to face — the House Democrats who impeached him and the senators who will soon vote on whether to end his presidenc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTOR: Locust Invasion, Rain Not Normal. Repent...</title>
      <link>https://nairobiwire.com/2020/02/locust-invasion-january-rain-not-normal-repent-pastor-nganga-urges.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nairobiwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial city preacher James Ng’ang’a was in Kajiado last week to pray for the country and ask for God’s forgiveness following the locust invasion in parts of the country. Speaking last Friday after spending five days praying for the country, the Neno Evangelism church leader urged Kenyans to repent. “It is not normal that the country …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Systemwide Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/04/a-systemwide-disaster-how-the-iowa-caucuses-melted-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES — Sean Bagniewski had seen the problems coming. It wasn’t so much that the new app that the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QUALITY CONTROL' OF VOTES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69dd698aed24770b925add5fb69b501f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Problems with a mobile app appeared to force a delay in reporting the results of the Iowa caucuses Monday, leaving the campaigns, voters and the media in election limbo and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT MESS 2020...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/04/iowa-caucus-biden-campaign-blasts-democratic-party-over-reporting-meltdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, IOWA — Joe Biden’s campaign lawyer sent an excoriating late-night letter to the chair of Iowa’s Democratic Party over Monday’s caucus meltdown demanding an explanation…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS DOOMED?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/02/03/iowa-caucus-2020-election-110600</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa caucus results appear to be indefinitely delayed, leaving the Democratic candidates in a lurch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APP FAILURE</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/news/iowa-results-delayed-as-precincts-struggle-with-caucus-phone-app/ar-BBZCKFe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> CAUCUS CONSPIRACY AGAINST SANDERS?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/iowa-caucuses-results-reporting-delays-revive-bernie-sanders-supporters-concerns-and-conspiracy-theories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Des Moines, Iowa — Workers on Bernie Sanders’s presidential campaign already had suspicions about the logistics and fairness of the Iowa caucuses. Counting delays by the Iowa Democratic Party are stirring those concerns anew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delegates decided by coin flips...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/893489/iowa-officially-first-caucusdeciding-coin-flips-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some cases, Iowa is leaving the Democratic caucuses up to chance. In the case of a tie during Monday night's caucuses, the state is resorting to an old-fashioned coin flip to decide which candidates win delegates. A couple have already occurred. Buttigieg and Warren tie. Coin toss about to happen pic.twitter.com/fJVqDDN5pS â€” John Pemble (@johnpemble) February 4, 2020 Final count: Pete - 44Biden - 31Bernie - 31Amy - 29 Pete picks up most people from 1st to 2nd round. Amy back from the dead. Biden and Bernie now settling tie through ancient democratic practice of a coin flip. pic.twitter.com/Nwz2feXF4t â€” Eric Lach (@ericlach) February 4, 2020 This is nothing new â€” in 2016, Hillary Clinton won all six of her Iowa caucus coin tosses. The current candidates are surely hoping they have that kind of luck. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustration, questions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/481310-frustration-questions-as-delays-hamper-iowa-caucuses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrations mounted late Monday night after the Iowa Democratic Party said it found “inconsistencies” in the reporting of the caucus results and delayed releasing any precinct vote tallies to ensure the integrity of the</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
