<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>12-MILE-WIDE RESERVOIR?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2018/07/news-lake-found-mars-water-polar-cap-life-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 12-mile-wide reservoir could solve a Martian mystery—and offer a new target in the hunt for extraterrestrial life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR DETECTS LAKE ON MARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/25/world/mars-subsurface-water-lake-evidence/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lake of liquid water has been detected by radar beneath the southern polar ice cap of Mars, according to a new study by Italian researchers from the Italian Space Agency, published Wednesday in the journal Science.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish student stops plane deporting Afghan man from leaving...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/25/swedish-student-elin-ersson-stops-plane-deporting-afghan-man-leaving/832071002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elin Ersson has been applauded by many for her courage, but critics have called her selfish for singlehandedly making a decision on the country's deportation stance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golf carts torched at site proposed for Beckham's soccer stadium...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/07/25/miami-golf-course-carts-go-up-in-flames/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An explosive night at Miami's Melreese Golf Course as dozens of golf carts went up in flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of anti-Putin feminist group found dead...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/398727-feminist-protest-movement-founder-found-dead-in-apartment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A co-founder of the international feminist group Femen was found dead Monday in her Paris apartment, according to The Gu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power prices all-time highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/u-west-power-prices-soar-time-highs-again-122922575--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters) - Power prices for Wednesday in some U.S. Western markets rose to all-time highs for a second day in a row as consumers kept their air conditioners cranked up to escape a brutal heat wave blanketing much of the region. In California, the state's power grid operator urged customers to conserve</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV infects one teen girl every 3 minutes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hiv-infects-one-teenaged-girl-every-3-minutes-130140250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every three minutes, a girl between the ages of 15 and 19 is infected with the virus that causes AIDS, said a UN report Wednesday that warned of a "crisis" fuelled by gender inequality. Girls and young women made up two-thirds of 15- to 19-year-olds infected with HIV in 2017, according to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superbugs in air: People breathing in antibiotic resistant genes around world...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5990223/People-breathing-antibiotic-resistant-genes-major-cities-world.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research by the American Chemical Society has revealed there are antibiotic resistant genes floating in the air of at least 19 major cities around the world, adding to the global failure of antibiotics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He Slept With Cary Grant and Spencer Tracy -- And Changed Hollywood History...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/he-slept-with-cary-grant-and-spencer-tracyand-changed-hollywood-history </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scotty Bowers ran a brothel out of a gas station and slept with dozens of Hollywood’s biggest stars. Inside his ‘Secret History of Hollywood’ and why we should believe his stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE WATERS: I've been sent by God to get Trump!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/maxine-waters-preaches-on-mission-against-trump-god-sends-you-to-do-something-you-just-do-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move over Jake and Elwood, Maxine Waters is on a mission from God. After acknowledging the children in the audience, the California Congresswoman ripped into President Trump during a Sunday appearance at First AME Church in Los Angeles. ﻿ Wanting to address what people are reading on the “social internet,” she said, “We never dreamed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tick-borne disease soaring...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/living/article215348200.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tick-borne diseases such as Lyme disease and Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever are increasing in North Carolina. Here are tips to avoid getting bit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10-foot 'cliff' forms on popular Outer Banks beach, prompting warnings to tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article215442510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Gray Eagle beach on the Outer Banks has been closed as town officials try to figure out how get rid of an 10-foot escarpment that formed. Many people refused to believe the photos on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key West mayoral candidate takes call from God during debate...</title>
      <link>http://www.flkeysnews.com/news/local/article215418680.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.flkeysnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Key West, Florida, mayoral race has seven candidates, including one who says God wants him to run. The biggest money-raiser by far, though, is former city commissioner Teri Johnston, who told a questioner that climate change is real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not seeking pardon...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/GMA/status/1022080700839677955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“FULL INTERVIEW: Michael Cohen's attorney, Lanny Davis, one-on-one with @GStephanopoulos; says there are "certainly" more tapes, and that Michael Cohen is not seeking a pardon from the President: https://t.co/m55qCWk199 https://t.co/UXZPHIad1X”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Star on Hollywood Walk of Fame Destroyed With Pickaxe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-star-on-hollywood-walk-of-fame-destroyed-with-pickaxe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President’s star smashed to bits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Rate Hits New Low...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/237908/smoking-rate-hits-new-low.aspx </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The percentage of U.S. adults who smoke cigarettes fell to 16% this year, the lowest rate since Gallup first asked this question in 1944.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weaponized drones. Machines that attack on own. 'Day is going to come'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/20/ai-cyberattacks-artificial-intelligence-threatens-cybersecurity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of artificial intelligence has experts worried.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Airlines Bow to China on Taiwan References...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-airlines-bows-to-beijing-on-taiwan-issue-1532490608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American, Delta and United joined other carriers in bowing to Chinese pressure to change the way they describe Taiwan—but stopped short of expressly referring to the self-governing island as part of China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds: ICE protesters spewed racist insults...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/expo/news/erry-2018/07/3c121acf878231/feds-portland-ice-protesters-s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officers policing the ICE building in Portland say they were subjected to hateful and racially-charged comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Armageddon' fire in Greece kills at least 80, many missing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180725103746-in1a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country has declared three days of national mourning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA CLAIMS A SCALP: Lawmaker resigns after dropping pants, using slur on show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/georgia-lawmaker-resigns-after-dropping-his-pants-saying-n-word-n894346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. Jason Spencer came under fire for his appearance on Sacha Baron Cohen's 'Who Is America.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under pressure from China, AMERICAN AIRLINES removes references to Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-44948599</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many already bowed to pressure to list Taiwan as part of China, but until now US carriers held out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ailing US newspapers feel new pain from tariffs...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180725-ailing-us-newspapers-feel-new-pain-newsprint-tariffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Top cardinal demands Vatican get tough with bishops on sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vatican-abuse-cardinal/top-cardinal-demands-vatican-get-tough-with-bishops-on-sex-abuse-idUSKBN1KF191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading Roman Catholic cardinal and key adviser to Pope Francis called on Tuesday for the Vatican to "swiftly and decisively" adopt strict policies for cases of sexual abuse involving bishops and top clergy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wannabe ninjas plague Japan town after viral mix-up...</title>
      <link>http://www.asiaone.com/asia/wannabe-ninjas-plague-japan-town-after-viral-mix</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiaone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - A Japanese city has been left fighting off wannabe ninjas after a news report on local labour shortages that suggested it wanted to hire the traditional assassins went viral. The western city of Iga was featured in a report by American radio station NPR this month about Japan's depopulation and labour shortage problems. The report said Iga was trying to capitalise on its history as home to ninjas by building a new museum focused on the warriors, but was struggling to hire staff, including ninja performers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 dark horse candidates for Speaker of the House...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/398701-10-dark-horse-candidates-for-speaker-of-the-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What happens if neither Majority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) nor Majority Whip Steve Scalise (R-La.) can secure the 218 votes needed to become the next Speaker?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollster: Anti-establishment phenomenon 'here to stay'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/hilltv/what-americas-thinking/398648-pollster-anti-establishment-phenomenon-is-here-to-stay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pollster and HarrisX CEO Dritan Nesho said on Tuesday that the anti-establishment movement within American politics will be a long-term phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOTS, BYE: TWITTER curbs access for 143,000 apps in new crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/twitter-curbs-access-143-000-apps-crackdown-223639678.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter said Tuesday it had removed more than 143,000 apps from the messaging service since April in a fresh crackdown on "malicious" activity from automated accounts. The San Francisco-based social network said it was tightening access to its application programming interfaces (APIs) that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  THE FIRES OF ATHENS...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/sweden-faces-extreme-fire-risk-coming-days-142738368.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fires, which broke out on Monday afternoon, devoured homes and forests, forcing terrified residents to flea into the sea for safety, while pine forests were reduced to ash and charred cars lined the smoke-filled streets of seaside towns near Athens. "Today, Greece is in mourning," said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 85, Yoko Ono plans new album for peace...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/85-yoko-ono-plans-album-peace-184555991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yoko Ono on Tuesday announced that she is releasing a new album at age 85, saying that her lifelong message of peace was sorely needed in 2018. "Warzone," which will come out on October 19, will revisit songs penned by Ono since 1970, concluding with "Imagine," her seminal pacifist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA FASHION FORWARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ivanka-trump-closing-her-namesake-fashion-brand-1532452229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s daughter and adviser is closing the company more than a year after separating from it. She has grown frustrated by restrictions required to avoid conflicts of interest while serving in the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Lawyer Rips Trump After Tape Airs on CNN: 'Only People Who Use Cash Are Drug Dealers and Mobsters'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-cohen-lawyer-rips-trump-after-tape-airs-on-cnn-only-people-who-use-cash-are-drug-dealers-and-mobsters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Biblical disaster'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180724190137-614nm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREECE-WILDFIRE/ (UPDATE 17, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 17-Wildfires kill at least 74 in Greece's</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO aims to stem customer churn...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/HBO-aims-to-stem-customer-churn-13102086.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's never been easier to sit down on the couch, pay for a month of HBO and then power through an entire season's worth of "Westworld" or "Game of Thrones" before canceling the service in hopes of avoiding further credit card charges. But while that clever approach might be saving consumers money in an age of ubiquitous cord-cutting and online streaming, it doesn't work out so well for HBO, which has to deal with inconsistent subscription rates. In the coming months, HBO will try to stem that constant customer churn by enticing more viewers to stick with the premium channel year-round, according to John Stankey, the head of HBO's parent company, WarnerMedia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans ready new cuts... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/business/article/House-Republicans-ready-new-tax-cut-package-aim-13101752.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Republicans unveiled the broad outlines of a new tax package Tuesday that would make individual rate cuts permanent under the nation's revised tax code, instead of allowing them to expire in 2025.  The proposal stands little chance in the Senate. Nonetheless House Republicans intend to bring it to a vote ahead of the November midterm elections, with the aim of refocusing attention on what they say are positive impacts from a new tax law that has not proven particularly popular with voters. Some also hope that the vote will put Democrats on the spot, by forcing them to vote for or against extending tax cuts for individuals after months of railing against the tax law as a giveaway for corporations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency tycoon: 'I will be world's first trillionaire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/718647/cryptocurrency-trillionaire-list-jeff-bezos-mark-zuckerberg-elon-musk-chris-kelsey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots threaten to turn population into 'endangered species'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/718599/sex-robots-dolls-japan-endangered-species-documentary-video-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran on edge after third BART murder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/24/san-fran-straphangers-on-edge-after-third-bart-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco-area straphangers are on edge Tuesday following the third homicide on Bay Area Rapid Transit in less than a week. “Maybe I should start driving to school, because I don’t think …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will 'MISSION' Be Summer's Last Big Box Office Blockbuster?</title>
      <link>https://movieweb.com/mission-impossible-fallout-box-office-predictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;movieweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Cruise's Mission: Impossible - Fallout opens against Teen Titans Go! to the Movies this weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious package labeled 'anthrax' left at office of Rep. Maxine Waters...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/suspicious-package-labeled-anthrax-left-office-rep-maxine/story?id=56796906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hazmat crew determined that no hazard existed after an investigation, the Los Angeles Fire Department said on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley 124&amp;#176;... </title>
      <link>http://www.azfamily.com/story/38712575/death-valley-high-of-124-degrees-forecast-in-southwest-heat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azfamily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scorching heat radiated across the U.S. Southwest on Tuesday, with the highest temperatures expected in California's Death Valley during a week that forecasters say could prove to be the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN PLAYS COHEN TAPE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/24/politics/michael-cohen-donald-trump-tape/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential candidate Donald Trump is heard on tape discussing with his attorney Michael Cohen how they would buy the rights to a Playboy model's story about an alleged affair Trump had with her years earlier, according to the audio recording of the conversation aired exclusively on CNN's "Cuomo Prime Time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern California home sales crash, warning sign to nation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/24/southern-california-home-sales-crash-a-warning-sign-to-the-nation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of both new and existing houses and condominiums in Southern California dropped 11.8 percent year over year, as prices shot up to a record high, according to CoreLogic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisp Neptune shot shows Hubble has new rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/spectacular-neptune-photo-shows-hubble-space-telescope-has-new-rival-ncna893996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Earth, the outermost planet has never looked so good.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK quietly sets up China hub despite hardening censorship...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-china-facebook-subsidiary/facebook-plans-innovation-hub-in-china-despite-tightening-censorship-idUSKBN1KE1JF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has set up a subsidiary in China and plans to create an "innovation hub" to support local start-ups and developers, the social media company said on Tuesday, ramping up its presence in the restrictive market where its social media sites remain blocked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scooter companies ride high on hope, hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-scooters-ninebot/scooter-companies-ride-high-on-hope-and-hype-idUSKBN1KE2QR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Segway-Ninebot Group, a Beijing-based manufacturer of electric scooters, rolled into Los Angeles this week hoping to bolster its position as the main supplier for a new wave of well-funded scooter-rental startups and offer a peek at new battery-powered transit products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Occasion of sin', Bishop's sign-off tweet rips TWITTER...</title>
      <link>http://www.providencejournal.com/news/20180724/an-occasion-of-sin-ris-bishop-tobin-quits-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. — Following a Tuesday evening farewell tweet, Bishop Thomas J. Tobin of the Diocese of Providence has deleted his Twitter account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen suspended for 'Wall Construction' shirt gets $25k from school...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/washingtoncounty/index.ssf/2018/07/student_with_banned_trump_shir.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addison Barnes, an 18-year-old senior at Hillsboro's Liberty High School, was suspended for wearing the shirt backing Trump's immigration and Homeland Security policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as Russia sky turns black during day...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6856742/sky-turns-black-middle-day-remote-russian-towns-weapons-test-aliens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REMOTE Russian towns were plunged into total darkness for several hours last week — sparking rumours of a secret Kremlin weapons test, UFOs or even the devil’s work. Mystery surrounds the sud…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE triples work place investigations...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5988465/ICE-TRIPLED-U-S-work-place-investigations-2018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ICE has investigated 6,093 U.S. workplaces so far this year - up dramatically from 1,716 in all of 2017, according to new data. Immigration opponents are hailing the numbers as a victory under Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG BETS ON CHINA 'BIG BROTHER'</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/big-investors-are-placing-bets-on-china-s-facial-recognition-start-ups/17719704/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s facial recognition startups are attracting big investments at a time when Silicon Valley’s giants are facing a backlash over their use of the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rattled by violence, Toronto wonders if city unraveling...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jul/24/toronto-attacks-greektown-shooting-is-city-unraveling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As residents grapple with the latest attack to hit the city in recent months, some are asking whether it was becoming less safe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisp Neptune shot shows Hubble has new rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/spectacular-neptune-photo-shows-hubble-space-telescope-has-new-rival-ncna893996.</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey puts marijuana prosecutions on hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/marijuana/2018/07/nj_just_effectively_decriminalized_weed_possession.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marijuana possession's been decriminalized in New Jersey's municipalities -- at least until September, when an adult use legalization bill is expected to hit the state Senate, sources said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War against scooters on LA streets: Torched, Smashed, Hurled From Roofs...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxla.com/news/local-news/electric-scooters-accused-of-being-a-nuisance-on-la-streets-are-now-being-destroyed-in-creative-ways</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Instagram account is documenting all of the creative ways people are destroying electric scooters they come across, and most of the videos are being filmed in LA&amp;rsquo;s west side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 hopefuls quoting Bible to oppose Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/24/liberal-2020-hopefuls-quote-bible-call-reject-bret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal 2020 presidential hopefuls quoted from the Bible Tuesday, saying the responsibility of the Senate to fill the vacancy on the Supreme Court is a moral choice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD: TRADER JOE'S worker killed in shootout by cop's bullet...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Trader-Joes-Standoff-Hostage-Shooting-Silver-Lake-LAPD-488992231.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bullet that killed a Trader Joe's store manager in an exchange of gunfire with a homicide suspect following a pursuit crash Saturday was fired by a Los Angeles Police Department officer, police said Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inquisitive UBER Driver Spooks Security Summit Attendees...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/spy-or-uber-driver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, as America's top national security experts convened in Aspen, a strangely inquisitive Uber driver showed up, too—and caused a minor freak-out. Was the mystery woman some kind of covert agent—or simply a figment of these hyper-paranoid times?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMI LOVATO HOSPITALIZED FOR HEROIN OVERDOSE...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/07/24/demi-lovato-heroin-overdose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demi Lovato suffers apparent heroin overdose and is rushed to a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman driving over 140 mph arrested moments after receiving ticket for going 92...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/crime/council-bluffs-woman-driving-over-mph-arrested-moments-after-receiving/article_8d764368-e26f-5310-be02-ca852a574e77.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman was arrested on suspicion of willful reckless driving. Later, deputies conducting an inventory in her car found what they suspected was marijuana in the vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGING WILDFIRE CLOSES YOSEMITE...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article215400735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yosemite Valley will shut down July 24, 2018 as fire crews try to stop the Ferguson Fire from spreading into the national park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist murdered near Cancun...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/journalist-murdered-southeast-mexico-near-tourist-hotspot-192819890.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A journalist has been murdered in southeast Mexico, not far from tourist hotspot Cancun, the government said on Tuesday -- the seventh such killing in the country this year. "Ruben Pat, editor in chief at the Playa News weekly, was shot dead this morning" in the Playa del Carmen area, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sextortion Scammers Threaten to Release Hacked Webcam Video of You Watching...</title>
      <link>https://krebsonsecurity.com/2018/07/sextortion-scam-uses-recipients-hacked-passwords/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;krebsonsecurity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common painkillers linked to dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/world/common-painkillers-triple-side-effects-dementia-study-says/PLjrRq6hGXfTeGKpTRaalO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Common painkillers have previously been linked to heart risks. Now scientists believe the medication could also triple the side effects of dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY: Longest blood moon of century...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/fridays-total-lunar-eclipse-will-be-longest-blood-moon-visible-this-century-until-2123/70005578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DENVER POST Runs Letter to Editor Suggesting Trump Should Be Executed...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/denver-post-runs-letter-editor-suggesting-trump-executed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Denver Post published a letter to the editor suggesting President Donald Trump should be executed for treason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens Of KKK Fliers Found In Yards Across Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/07/23/kkk-fliers-found-tinley-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bags with messages of hate were discovered over the weekend in Tinley Park.  CBS 2’s Jeremy Ross reports KKK flyers were found in a nearby community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELIZABETH WARREN: RAISE TAX RATE TO 50%...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/fake-indian-elizabeth-warren-suggests-50-democrat-tax-rates-calls-trump-tax-bonuses-crumbs-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tempers Iran rhetoric, says ready for new deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/eb9376eb3b264b5f9fbe48d774a9ad99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANSAS CITY, Mo. (AP) — President Donald Trump tempered his threatening rhetoric toward Iran Tuesday, two days after he sent an all-caps warning of future conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Secret to Protect From Hacking: Physical Keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/security/a22530218/google-yubikey-fishing-krebs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google says phishing incidents among its employees dropped to zero after adopting Security Keys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SERIES OF QUAKES OFF OREGON SPARK FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/index.ssf/2018/07/43_earthquake_recorded_off_sou.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No tsunami warnings were issued. One earthquake expert says these quakes are nothing to worry about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAGRAM'S Heiress Among 4 More Arrested In Connection To Sex Cult...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/07/24/seagrams-nxivm-bronfman-russell-salzman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four more people have been arrested in connection to the alleged sex cult NXIVM, including group leaders with such titles "The Prefect" serving "The Vanguard."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIGHT-WING GROUP FACES BRUTAL BEATING IN OAKLAND...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/24/shock-video-proud-boy-beaten/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shocking violence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS threatens to BEHEAD Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/718630/isis-terror-threat-facebook-mark-zuckerberg-behead-propaganda-united-cyber-caliphate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Push Federal Jobs Guarantee Bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/house-democrats-to-introduce-federal-jobs-guarantee-bill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Freshman Rep. Ro Khanna wants to provide an opportunity for federally subsidized employment as the ascendant left wing of the Democratic Party gains footing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House preps $12 billion emergency aid for farmers hurt by tariffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/24/trump-plans-to-give-billions-in-aid-to-farmers-hurt-by-tariffs-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration plans to offer billions in aid to farmers hit by tariffs on their goods, a move that aimed at easing the pain caused by Trump's escalating trade war in key electoral states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Porn Booming...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/blakemontgomery/porn-pornhub-mindgeek-girlfriend-experience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“You can’t pirate someone saying your name.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Faces Backlash From Its Stars for Firing 'GUARDIANS' Director...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/07/23/disney-hit-by-backlash-over-gunn-firing-as-stars-seek-his-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney Faces a Backlash From Its Stars for Firing ‘Guardians’ Director</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22% of US population does not speak English at home...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/22-of-us-population-does-not-speak-english-at-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 13.5 percent of the U.S. population -- 44 million -- is foreign born, the highest level ever, and many are not proficient in English, choosing to speak Spanish at home instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de France Hits Cloud of Tear Gas and Comes to Stop... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/cycling/6851556/tour-de-france-strike-farmers-tear-gas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERAINT THOMAS was one of over 100 Tour de France riders stopped after drifting into a cloud of TEAR GAS. A farmers’ strike just ahead of the race forced police to spray protesters — and it g…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Airline CEOs Try the Cheap Seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/when-airline-ceos-try-the-cheap-seats-1532441990</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leaders of Delta and American defend the tightest sections of their planes while sitting in them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOMBUST:  Chinese Real-Estate Investors Retreat From U.S. as Political Pressure Mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-real-estate-investors-retreat-from-u-s-as-political-pressure-mounts-1532437934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese investors have become net sellers of U.S. commercial property for the first time in a decade, reflecting China’s crackdown on foreign investment and growing tensions between the U.S. and Chinese governments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferno rages; 70+ DEAD...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5984481/At-seven-dead-huge-forest-fires-destroy-homes-vehicles-Greek-holiday-resorts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The worst Greek forest fires in a decade have killed at least 74 people and left 70 injured as people attempted to flee the wildfires in their cars or on foot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary wearing 'Life Alert' emergency device?</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/mystery-was-hillary-wearing-life-alert-emergency-device-during-nyc-appearance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s fallen before and she’s needed help getting up. Maybe that’s why Hillary Clinton appeared to be wearing a Life Alert emergency button necklace during her recent appearance in New York City. Twitter user @ComfortablySmug posted a photo of Clinton posing with a fan while she was in Central Park for the Ozy Fest: Look …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRID COULD BUCKLE...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/24/california-heat-wave-electricity-use/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Natural gas limitations and pipeline outages'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find your passion? That's bad advice, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Find-your-passion-That-s-bad-advice-scientists-13100194.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Find your passion" is a mantra dictated to everyone from college students to retirees to pretty much anyone seeking happiness. But according to a forthcoming study from Stanford and Yale-NUS College in Singapore, it's actually bad advice - and may actually make it harder for people to figure out what they love to do. Why? The idea of "finding" one's passion implies that people have built-in interests just waiting to be discovered, and if you can simply figure out what they are you will magically be able to embrace them, says the study, which will be published in the journal Psychological Science. But people with that mind-set are more likely to give up on their newfound interest when they hit the inevitable roadblock, the study found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA claims largest dinosaur foot ever discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/2265/us-claims-largest-dinosaur-foot-ever-discovered-doc-17v8h23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elton John blasts Russia, eastern Europe for bigotry against gays...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/205/elton-john-blasts-russia-eastern-europe-bigotry-against-gays-doc-17w3d74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAY INDOORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2018/07/23/you-should-stay-indoors-due-to-record-breaking-heat-in-southern-california-officials-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meteorologists with the National Weather Service said temperatures in many locations could reach around 110 degrees on Wednesday, expected to be the hottest day of the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: More and More of What Do Depends on Govt Permission...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/archives/2018/07/24/permitted-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The granting or withholding of that approval is a powerful lever over our lives.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
