<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE CONTINUES:  Trump supporters clash with ANTIFA outside Trump Tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9332069/Trump-supporters-clash-ANTIFA-Trump-Tower-MAGA-fans-unfurl-huge-flag-Pelosi-demon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump supporters paraded down Fifth Avenue in New York City on Friday afternoon. They carried with them massive Trump 2024 banners which they unfurled outside Trump Tower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: There Was NO 'Mass Exodus' From California In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/03/05/california-exodus-did-not-happen-uc-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular notion that there was a mass exodus from California last year is wrong, according to research from a nonpartisan think tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOB GROWTH SURGES</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210305201433-c1e6v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Beach Mayor Worried About Super Spreader Events...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/05/miami-beach-mayor-dan-gelber-spring-concerned-spring-break-covid-super-spreader-events/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sun and sand of South Beach is synonymous with Spring Break and as travelers from across the country begin flocking to Florida for Spring Break, there are fears that there may be an uptick in coronavirus cases again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge scolds 'QAnon Shaman' for appearing on '60 MINS' without permission...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Judge-scolds-QAnon-Shaman-for-appearing-on-60-16004848.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A federal judge chided the self-identified</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperinflation Pushes Venezuela to Print 1,000,000-Bolivar Bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/hyperinflation-pushes-venezuela-to-print-1000000-bolivar-bills/ar-BB1ei8Dj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela said it will introduce new large-denomination bolivar notes as hyperinflation renders most bills worthless, forcing citizens to turn to the U.S. dollar for everyday transactions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk's Historic Wealth Gains Unravel With $27 Billion Loss!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/elon-musk-loses-27-billion-as-historic-wealth-gains-unravel/ar-BB1ei4am</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk set records last year for one of the fastest streaks of wealth accumulation in history. The reversal is underway, and it’s steep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cronkite signed off 40 years ago; Seems like an eon in news standards...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/technology/541882-cronkite-signed-off-40-years-ago-it-seems-like-an-eon-in-news-standards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The journalism world could use more of the Cronkite method today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Funerals, Zen Apps Keep Buddhist Temples Afloat...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/online-funerals-zen-apps-keep-230000463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Memorial services held online. Zen meditation apps. Buddhist temple-led match-making services.As the coronavirus pandemic forces institutions around the world to change the way they do things, those new endeavors are some of the ways that Buddhist groups in Japan are trying to survive. Their temples are part of the landscape: there are about 77,000, more than the number of Japan’s ubiquitous convenience stores.Covid-19 has caused further pain for Buddhist organizations already struggling in recent years due to Japan’s shrinking population and sagging interest in religion among the young. One estimate is that temples’ total income has halved in the five years to 2020. And now the virus has kept believers at home, reducing donations they make for services such as memorials for the deceased.Buddhist temples have thrived in Japan for more than a millennium. But they need money to operate, and the pandemic has prompted some priests and monks to think of new ways to generate income. It’s a reflection of the way that industries worldwide from travel to dining and retail are having to improvise as Covid-19 restrictions batter their usual business.‘Cloud-Sitting’Ryosokuin, a Zen temple with more than 660 years of history in Kyoto, is one such innovator. Faced with a drop-off in services such as memorials and a plunge in tourism, the organization boosted its online operations. It developed a meditation app that’s been downloaded more than 15,000 times that it expects to eventually monetize, and it’s organized an online zen meditation community called UnXe, meaning ‘cloud-sitting.’“When we lost visitors and donations fell, we realized that our conventional way of supporting our operations no longer works,” said Toryo Ito, deputy chief priest at the temple. “We need to adapt to a management style which meets with the times.”Read about some Buddhist monks snapping up ESG debtBuddhism has a history stretching back to the 6th century in Japan, but few periods have brought such challenges. Over a third of temples may disappear by 2040 as the population grows old, according to Kenji Ishii, a religious studies professor at Kokugakuin University in Tokyo.Temple income is falling too. The total figure likely dropped about 51% since 2015 to 263 billion yen ($2.4 billion) in 2020, according to estimates by Hidenori Ukai, the chief priest at the Shokakuji temple in Kyoto and a freelance journalist.The pandemic is adding to financial troubles across a broad swath of Japanese society. While the economy is recovering, a state of emergency in major cities has continued to weigh on consumer spending. And businesses that serve customers face-to-face such as retailers have been hit especially hard, resulting in a spate of bankruptcies for restaurants and hotels.Tsukiji Hongwanji, a four-century-old temple near Tokyo’s old fish market, is another organization trying to make the best of the virus period. It started online memorial services last May for families that don’t want gatherings for the deceased, and has done about 70 such events, according to Yugen Yasunaga, a representative director and priest at the temple.The organization is also venturing into areas that staid temples aren’t traditionally known for, such as match-making services, a cafe and yoga classes, said Yasunaga, who worked in a major Japanese bank for more than two decades before starting his career at Tsukiji Hongwanji.“Just like Amazon.com responds to the various needs of customers online, a temple can do the same,” he said.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iPhone feature reveals if someone  stalking you...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/14241996/iphone-feature-prevents-find-my-app-stalking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPLE is working on a new feature for its Find My app that could let you know if someone is stalking you. The setting is called “Item Safety Alerts” and tells a user if an unknown device travelling…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring break crowd storms Fort Lauderdale beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/vaccines/fl-ne-spring-break-crowd-covid-20210305-xkzs2tppxnhznellmgtyhc5uve-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Universities across the country canceled Spring Break to discourage college coeds from spreading the coronavirus. But judging from the crowds hitting the beach — just days into the celebration — the kids are here in full force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Digital Devices 'Rewire' Minds Of Young Children, Alter Way They See World...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/alpha-generation-rewiring-way-children-see-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not only does this change how kids view their surroundings, researchers say it affects their cognitive, emotional, and social development too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines changing their destinations after devastating year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/05/airlines-changing-business-to-answer-post-pandemic-demand-for-holidays.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines in Europe are looking at sunshine and beaches as their route to making money again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>69% of U.S. adults intend to become vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-embraces-covid-19-vaccines-223658707.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are warming up to COVID-19 vaccines, with 19% saying they've already received at least one dose and 49% intending to do so when they get the chance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope arrives in Iraq, where beleaguered Christians are struggling to hold on...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-francis-arrives-iraq-where-130508210.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Francis becomes the first pontiff to visit Iraq, where he hopes to shore up the fast-dwindling Christian community and promote religious harmony.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School under fire for 'chivalry day' that had girls obey boys...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/05/texas-school-under-fire-for-chivalry-day-that-had-girls-obey-boys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas school is under fire after it organized a “Rules of Chivalry Day” and encouraged female students to “obey” any “reasonable” demands made of them by male …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems draw on civil rights history to push AMAZON union vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amazoncom-inc-alabama-birmingham-voting-rights-84450dd14ace9d747a4bd56fbe5282d5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BESSEMER, Alabama (AP) — Some Democratic members of Congress and national union leaders on Friday sought to rustle up support for unionizing a massive Amazon facility outside Birmingham, comparing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant boosting production has repeat quality offenses...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pfizer-plant-boosting-vaccines-has-repeat-quality-16003061.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The factory that Pfizer Inc. plans to use to boost production of its covid-19 vaccine for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glimpse of normalcy: Hundreds attend Tel Aviv concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20210305-glimpse-of-normalcy-hundreds-of-vaccinated-israelis-attend-tel-aviv-concert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of people vaccinated against Covid-19 packed a Tel Aviv football stadium Friday for the first of four concerts organised by the municipality, as Israel eases virus restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA's new Mars rover hits dusty red road, 1st trip 21 feet...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-us-news-planets-mars-a01ac6bab9ccba414737d884222e1ba2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA’s newest Mars rover hit the dusty red road this week, putting 21 feet on the odometer in its first test drive. The Perseverance rover ventured from its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Reception centers': Biden eyes friendlier name for new facilities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/exclusive-%E2%80%94-reception-centers-biden-eyes-friendlier-name-for-new-migrant-facilities/ar-BB1ehFVC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is weighing a new name for the facilities it is setting up to manage the influx of migrant children and families at the southern border, hoping to limit the criticism and emphasize that the buildings will hold people only temporarily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC lets child shelters fill 100% despite Covid concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cdc-child-migrant-shelter-full-capacity-coronavirus-41d1ae80-1ecf-4815-a755-7b01fac5850b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"CDC advises that ORR facilities may temporarily increase capacity to full licensed capacity," a memo, obtained by Axios, states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists shut down Bay Area site...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Golden-Gate-Fields-vaccine-shut-down-horse-protest-16001618.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two hundred vaccine appointments were canceled as activists protested horse deaths at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC 'Golf Channel' accused of sexism, misogyny and harassment...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9327129/NBCs-Golf-Channel-accused-hostile-workplace-sexism-misogyny-harassment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sixteen women who previously worked at Golf Channel and two more current female employees are echoing claims of sexism, misogyny and harassment against the NBC-owned network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA detained 100,000 migrants at border in February...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/u-detained-nearly-100-000-210746376.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. border agents detained nearly 100,000 migrants at the U.S.-Mexico border in February, according to two people familiar with preliminary figures, the highest arrest total for the month of February since 2006. The figures, which have not been previously reported, show the scope of a growing surge of migrants arriving at the southwest border as U.S. President Joe Biden, a Democrat, seeks to roll back some of the restrictive policies of former President Donald Trump, a Republican. In particular, an increasing number of children arriving at the border without a parent or legal guardian has forced U.S. officials in recent weeks to scramble for housing options and take steps to speed up their release to sponsors in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro: 'Enough fussing and whining'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-brazil-bolsonaro-fussing-whining/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro has continuously downplayed the pandemic in Brazil, which has the second-largest COVID-19 death toll after the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More staffers bail as scandals spiral...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/05/cuomo-staffers-bail-as-nursing-home-sex-harass-scandals-spiral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo’s staff was hit with more resignations Friday as the embattled three-term executive struggles to hang onto his powerful post amid growing calls for his ouster over allegatio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Barkley fears hora at daughter's Jewish wedding...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/charles-barkley-fears-dancing-hora-at-daughters-jewish-wedding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basketball star tells Jimmy Kimmel he's been trying to lose weight 'because apparently they’ve got to pick me up in a chair. Listen, I need all Jewish people on deck'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER CEO has NOT gotten shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/pfizer-ceos-israel-visit-cancelled-because-he-is-unvaccinated-report-661100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bourla said in December that he has not yet received the vaccine yet because he does not want to "cut in line."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allergy season about to collide with virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/health-wellness/accuweathers-2021-spring-allergy-forecast/904590</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year into the pandemic, and after a rough winter for much of the U.S., people may be itching to escape the confines of their homes -- and as allergy season rolls in, here's how you can be prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto criss-crossing TX again, igniting Dem hopes he'll run for governor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/05/politics/beto-orourke-texas-governor/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beto O'Rourke is on the road again, criss-crossing Texas and broadcasting his stops in small towns live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officers maced, trampled: Docs expose depth of chaos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/docs-expose-depth-january-6-capitol-siege-chaos-fd3204574c11e453be8fb4e3c81258c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two firefighters loaned to Washington for the day were the only medics on the Capitol steps Jan. 6, trying to triage injured officers as they watched the angry mob swell and attack police working...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating ship off English coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-england-cornwall-56286719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An illusion called "superior mirage" caused the vessel to look like it was hovering above the sea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man robbed of $500K watch in Beverly Hills recalls terrifying ordeal...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/05/man-robbed-of-500k-watch-in-beverly-hills-recalls-ordeal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The target of a brazen daylight robbery outside a Beverly Hills eatery that netted a $500,000 watch — and left an innocent bystander shot — recounted the terrifying ambush to The Post o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Anti-Price Gouging Laws Make It Worse?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/03/05/did-anti-price-gouging-laws-lead-to-more-covid-19-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new paper finds that the shortages produced by emergency price controls led to more social interactions as people searched for scarce goods. Additional COVID-19 deaths weren't far behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses suit over 'slave ancestor' photos at HARVARD...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-56297390</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tamara Lanier argued Harvard University profited from images of her family's enslaved "patriarch".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee charged over TWITTER 'pump-and-dump crypto schemes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2456745/john-mcafee-anti-virus-software-charged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-virus pioneer John McAfee has been charged over a $13million cryptocurrency “scam” after allegedly luring victims on Twitter. The McAfee Associates founder was hit with a slew of c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Elections: Can Bennett go from kingmaker to prime minister?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-elections/israel-elections-can-bennett-go-from-kingmaker-to-prime-minister-660988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICAL AFFAIRS: Two weeks before the election, Naftali Bennett thinks that not only can he coronate the next prime minister, but that it could very well be him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: Military members who opt out of vaccine are 'part of the problem'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/04/fauci-troops-who-opt-out-of-covid-vaccine-are-part-of-the-problem.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military has tasked thousands of service members to help vaccinate communities across the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Liberating'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/meghan-markle-interview-liberating-oprah-prince-harry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, spoke with Oprah Winfrey in an exclusive interview airing on CBS on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California law would ban boys and girls sections at retailers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article249695008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is California ready to go gender free?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Danger zone: Creator behind viral Tom Cruise deepfakes says they're a warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/creator-viral-tom-cruise-deepfakes-speaks-rcna356</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The creator of a series of deepfake Tom Cruise videos that garnered more than 11 million views on TikTok said he never wanted to trick people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT'S ON:  MEGHAN TAKES ON THE FIRM... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-oprah-winfrey-prince-philip-coronavirus-pandemic-4639b55ce87cf8ee6b7a696eed3148ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The timing couldn’t be worse for Harry and Meghan. The Duke and Duchess of Sussex will finally get the chance to tell the story behind their departure from royal duties...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN HONEYMOON 60%</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ap-norc-poll-americans-largely-back-biden-virus-response-d365bff571c24f9d3575bcbd051780aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden is enjoying an early presidential honeymoon, with 60% of Americans approving of his job performance thus far and even more backing his handling of the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Rich Got Richer as Pandemic Unfolded, Pew Study Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rich-americans-got-richer-as-pandemic-unfolded-pew-study-shows/ar-BB1ehlif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial effect split along socioeconomic and racial lines, exacerbating wealth gap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL names first Black female referee...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/nfl-news-maia-chaka-first-black-female-nfl-referee-joins-sarah-thomas-150137000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maia Chaka was named to the NFL Officiating Development Program in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least seven injured as vehicle plows through outdoor dining area in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/05/six-injured-as-vehicle-plows-through-nyc-outdoor-dining-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The crash happened just after 8:30 a.m. at the intersection of E. 50th Street and Second Avenue, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiger Woods doesn't remember crash that hospitalized him, but SUV does...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tiger-woods-doesnt-remember-crash-130018605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods doesn't remember the crash, but the SUV he was driving does. It may know his every move</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Worst Covid Crisis Unfolding in Brazil, Where No Fix Seems to Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/worlds-worst-covid-crisis-is-unfolding-in-brazil-where-no-fix-seems-to-work/ar-BB1ehgXT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three adjacent cities with three different approaches illustrate the despair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims she was stopped by Palace from talking to Winfrey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9330173/Meghan-claims-stopped-Palace-aides-talking-Oprah-Winfrey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duchess of Sussex said she was not allowed to have a personal conversation with Oprah Winfrey two months before her wedding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Unemployment Rate Rises Despite Declines for All Other Groups...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/black-unemployment-rate-rises-despite-143209839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Black unemployment rate climbed in February even as most other Americans saw a decline in joblessness, underscoring that the labor-market recovery remains uneven one year after the pandemic began.The unemployment rate for Black Americans rose to 9.9%, the highest among all race groups tracked, the Labor Department said Friday. The overall U.S. jobless rate fell to 6.2% and White, Hispanic and Asian-American workers saw declines, the data show.Pandemic job losses have disproportionately impacted minorities, which is something policy makers are watching closely as the economy recovers. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell on Thursday said that it will take more than a low jobless rate to get to so-called maximum unemployment and that the central bank will be looking at a variety of indicators when assessing the labor market’s health.In February, the Asian-American unemployment rate fell to 5.1% and joblessness also improved for women, who made up the bulk of payroll gains. Hispanic unemployment fell to 8.5%.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA flight to Cabo diverted after passenger dies suddenly on board...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/ny-delta-flight-diverted-passenger-dead-20210305-lmalphsyd5badm6v52gajt5jtu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger died suddenly aboard a Delta flight bound for the Mexican resort city of Cabo, forcing the plane to divert to Sacramento International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swalwell sues Donald over attack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/541770-trump-sued-by-democrats-over-mob-attack-on-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump, his eldest son and several of his allies were sued on Friday by Rep. Eric Swalwell (D-Calif.) over their role in the run-up to the Jan. 6 breach of the U.S. Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NY officials altered count of nursing home deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-new-york-andrew-cuomo-coronavirus-pandemic-nursing-homes-58b0f62d0f88328e911d0d5c65bbf7fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Some New York lawmakers are calling for Gov. Andrew Cuomo's impeachment after reports late Thursday that his top aides altered a state Health Department report to omit the true...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOB GROWTH SURGES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/05/jobs-report-february-2021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nonfarm payrolls were expected to increase by 210,000 in February, while the unemployment rate held steady at 6.3%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP: Americans largely back Biden response...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-ap-top-news-coronavirus-pandemic-only-on-ap-honeymoons-d365bff571c24f9d3575bcbd051780aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Joe Biden is enjoying an early presidential honeymoon, with 60% of Americans approving of his job performance thus far and even more backing his handling of the coronavirus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss mull 'burqa ban' in vote centering on security, rights...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-voting-rights-coronavirus-pandemic-switzerland-europe-e79c272e5827ad543b7f890d48194a4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — At a time when seemingly everyone in Europe is wearing masks to battle COVID-19, the Swiss go to the polls Sunday to vote on a long-laid proposal to ban face-coverings, both the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: For first time, majority says COVID situation getting better...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/331832/optimism-covid-situation-reaches-new-high.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after the pandemic took hold of the U.S., a majority of Americans say the situation is improving. Half expect the disruption to persist into 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading Critic of Big Tech Expected to Join White House...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/05/a-leading-critic-of-big-tech-is-expected-to-join-the-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden is expected to name Tim Wu, a Columbia University law professor, to the National Economic Council</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Biden Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/03/04/reagan-democrats-biden-republicans-politics-stan-greenberg-473330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pollster who identified “Reagan Democrats” in the 1980s sees the emergence of a mirror image voting bloc. And it spells trouble for a GOP dominated by Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sand shortage? World running out of crucial commodity...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/05/sand-shortage-the-world-is-running-out-of-a-crucial-commodity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world is facing a shortage of sand — and climate scientists say it constitutes one of the greatest sustainability challenges of the 21st century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangers await humans on Mars as Elon Musk sets sights on colonization...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/03/04/dangers-await-humans-on-mars-as-elon-musk-eyes-colonization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Science journalist Shannon Stirone explains why SpaceX founder Elon Musk “is absolutely out into space” when it comes to the “unrealistic” colonization of Mars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 fatalities in northern Italy staggering. Did pollution play role?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-19s-death-toll-northern-100009103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air quality has been terrible for decades in Bergamo, in northern Italy, which last year suffered many COVID-19 deaths. Researchers see a connection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During tough times, dogs save the Queen...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/during-tough-times-dogs-save-114438587.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II has acquired two new corgi puppies after the last of her succession of the dogs died several years ago, The Sun reported on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Storm Brewing Over Anti-Money Laundering Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bitcoin-storm-brewing-over-trump-e2-80-99s-anti-money-laundering-push/ar-BB1egBqj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration will soon have to settle a Bitcoin fight it didn’t even start, and its decision could have far-reaching implications for the virtual currency industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berlin: 'BAD LUCK BANGING OR LOONY PORN' Wins Golden Bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/berlin-film-festival-2021-awards-winners-golden-bear</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The winners of the Gold and Silver Bears at the 2021 Berlin International Film Festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unstoppable revenge of the mullet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unstoppable-revenge-mullet-045415125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Business in front, party in the back": a hairstyle considered so obnoxious that for years it verged on being an arrestable offence, the mullet has made the unlikeliest comeback of the century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not your bitch: Campaign against 'sexist' dictionaries moves to Italy...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210305095546-jxvsy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women's rights campaigner Maria Beatrice Giovanardi launches petition to change Italy's Treccani dictionary after successful push to amend Oxford Dictionaries' definition of 'woman'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope lands in Baghdad, beginning  first-ever papal trip to Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/islamic-state-group-ali-al-sistani-coronavirus-pandemic-baghdad-pope-francis-ca6f3bcfe979bbaf399e15d9d614b25a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — Pope Francis arrived in Iraq on Friday to urge the country’s dwindling number of Christians to stay put and help rebuild the country after years of war and persecution, brushing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US new daily Covid cases at five-month low as nations try to hold off surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-new-daily-covid-cases-at-five-month-low-as-nations-try-to-hold-off-surge/ar-BB1ecXdS?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States recorded fewer than 40,000 new daily cases of Covid-19 for the first time in five months on Thursday, a piece of promising news as countries across the globe struggle to hold off another infection surge before inoculations become widespread. With frustration over restrictions having long weighed on populations worldwide, leaders were seeking to balance demands for easing rules while not unleashing another explosion in cases. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercomputer shows doubling masks offers little help preventing viral spread...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210305030525-fscog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-SUPERCOMPUTER (PIX, TV):Japan supercomputer shows doubling masks offers little help preventing viral spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO of CNN Owner Says Pandemic 'Really Good For Ratings'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/warnermedia-ceo-says-coronavirus-really-good-for-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WarnerMedia CEO Jason Kilar apologized Thursday after he let slip that the coronavirus pandemic will continue to dominate the news cycle on CNN because it's "really good for ratings."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police chief appeals for National Guard to stay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/law-enforcement-on-alert-warning-capitol-siege-plot-07a1a03fcdb14e40ac0b182fbed39d6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Worried about continuing threats, the acting chief of the U.S. Capitol Police appealed to congressional leaders Thursday to use their influence to keep National Guard troops at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fever scanners can be wildly inaccurate, researchers find...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Those-fever-scanners-that-everyone-is-using-to-16002043.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Temperature-scanning devices that check for fevers in schools, workplaces...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
