<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Meet man Pope sends in when facing major sex scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/world/europe/vatican-s-sex-crimes-specialist-weeps-as-victims-share-horror-stories-20190513-p51mmt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo crashes EU diplomat meeting -- but changes few minds...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Pompeo-crashes-Brussels-meeting-of-EU-diplomats-13840292.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS - Secretary of State Mike Pompeo crashed a meeting of European foreign ministers in Brussels on Monday to push for a united transatlantic front against Tehran and its nuclear program. But he failed to bend attitudes among leaders who fear the United States and Iran are inching toward war.  Pompeo's last-minute decision to visit the European Union capital, announced as he boarded a plane from the United States, set up a confrontation between the top U.S. diplomat and his European counterparts, who have been scrambling to save the 2015 Iran nuclear deal in the wake of the U.S. withdrawal last year. At least one, British Foreign Secretary Jeremy Hunt, said he feared that unintentional escalation from the United States and Iran could spark a conflict - an unusually bold statement that appeared to assign equal culpability to Washington and Tehran.  The visit came on a day that the Saudi Foreign Ministry said two of its oil tankers and a Norwegian ship were damaged near the Persian Gulf, in what it claimed was an "act of sabotage."  A statement from Thome Ship Management, the owners of the Norwegian-flagged vessel, said an "unknown object" had created a hole in the hull of one of its ships, the MT Andrea Victory. Photographs of the ship show a hole just above the waterline.  Neither Saudi Arabia nor the UAE produced photographs to support claims that Saudi tankers had incurred "significant damage." The incidents did not cause casualties or oil spills, according to a statement by Saudi Energy Minister Khalid al-Falih.  The countries stopped short of assigning blame, but the incidents occurred at the same time and in the same place off the coast of the United Arab Emirates only days after the United States dispatched warships and bombers to the area to deter alleged...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clergy abuse victims sue Vatican, seek thousands of abuser names...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/443485-victims-of-clergy-abuse-sue-vatican-seek-names-of-abusers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five victims of clergy sexual abuse are suing the Vatican for the disclosure of thousands of predatory Catholic priests’ names, according to the Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks massage tape evidence in Kraft case...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/05/13/robert-kraft-prostitution-case-massage-spa-video-blocked-suppressed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Patriots win ... again, and this time it's their owner, Robert Kraft, who gets to spike the football.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAJOR BLOW FOR PROSECUTORS...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-robert-kraft-court-ruling-20190513-2ro766zxrzahxigoyhvoqfl2vi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Robert Kraft got a major court victory Monday when a judge ordered prosecutors are forbidden from using sex videos secretly recorded by police during a massage parlor prostitution sting. The ruling by Palm Beach County Judge Leonard Hanser effectively ends the prosecution of two misdemeanor counts pending since late February, barring a successful appeal by prosecutors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter recovers from surgery after breaking hip...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/05/13/jimmy-carter-recovers-surgery-after-breaking-hip/1192641001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carter fell prior to turkey hunting trip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers 'supercitizens'? Constitutional question for congressman's trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/lawmakers-supercitizens-constitutional-question-delay-case-rep-chris-collins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Collins raises "speech or debate" clause of Constitution to block prosecutors' use of emails sent on private account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents set up cameras in bedroom, bathroom to stop son from masturbating...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/irl/reddit-teen-cameras-masturbating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy prosecutor accused of trying to spy on SEAL defense attorneys...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/navy-spy-seals-attorneys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They did a warrantless search of a defense attorney's email less than three weeks before trial is supposed to start."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter recovers from surgery after breaking hip...</title>
      <link>https://www.kolotv.com/content/news/Former-President-Jimmy-Carter-recovers-from-surgery-after-breaking-hip-509860781.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kolotv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carter Center says former President Jimmy Carter is recovering from surgery after breaking a hip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space stunner: Moon shrinking, study reveals...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/moon-shrinking-study-reveals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Somebody alert Jeff Bezos: the Moon is shrinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>62% of Millennials live paycheck to paycheck...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7024883/Almost-two-thirds-Millennials-live-paycheck-paycheck-just-38-feel-financially-stable.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, 59 percent of Americans report living paycheck to paycheck, a new survey reveals. However Millennials struggle the most in between paydays, at 62 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False rumor on WHATSAPP started run on London bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/whatsapp-rumour-started-run-on-metro-bank-2019-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metro Bank's stock dropped 9% this morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Pesticides Suspected In Deaths Of Bald Eagles Across MD...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/05/12/banned-pesticides-bald-eagles-maryland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carbofuran was banned in the US in 2009, but some farmers have continued to use it illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Pampered World of DC's VIP Diners...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2019/05/12/inside-the-pampered-personalized-world-dcs-vip-diners/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The big restaurant lie: Everyone is treated the same.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of the Sober Bar...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/capital/story/20190510-can-you-have-any-fun-at-a-bar-with-no-booze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pub without alcohol is something of an oxymoron – but here's why they’re growing in popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio holds press conference at Trump Tower -- gets heckled...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/13/de-blasio-holds-press-conference-at-trump-tower-and-gets-heckled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of Donald Trump disrupted Mayor Bill de Blasio’s press conference in Trump Tower Monday while he announced a potential $2 million in fines facing the president’s real estate company if i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed gang pose as women on TINDER to lure men...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/13/armed-gang-posed-as-single-women-on-tinder-to-lure-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swipe right with caution. Police in San Jose, California, arrested five people for allegedly staging a series of armed robberies, assaults and carjackings by asking unsuspecting men to meet “Victor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles Cases In US Reach 839...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/05/13/more-than-800-cases-of-measles-reported-in-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of measles cases in the US is now at 839 for the year, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's weekly measles update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Most Expensive Coffee -- $75 A Cup...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/05/13/worlds-most-expensive-coffee-elida-natural-geisha-klatch-coffee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s most expensive coffee may leave some Southern Californians with the jitters – but not from the caffeine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weed smuggling arrests at LAX skyrocket following legalization...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/weed-smuggling-arrests-at-lax-surge-following-legalization/5297621/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities at Los Angeles International Airport say they are seeing more airline passengers trying to carry marijuana on flights, both in personal items and checked bags.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmentalists want charge on restaurant bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/food-drink/restaurants/article229820899.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepest ocean dive by any human in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/business/business/2019/05/13/unprecedented-dallas-businessman-victor-vescovo-completes-deepest-ocean-dive-human-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas businessman Victor Vescovo became the deepest diving human in history when his Five Deeps Expedition reached the bottom of the Challenger...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shia LaBeouf, Mel Gibson Star In New York Super Rich Comedy 'ROTHCHILD'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/global/shia-labeouf-mel-gibson-starring-in-rothchild-film-1203212936/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shia LaBeouf and Mel Gibson will star in “Rothchild,” a dark comedy about New York’s super rich helmed by “Stan &amp; Ollie” director Jon S. Baird. HanWay Films has boarded the project and will kic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA denies visa to senior Palestinian official...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b9c27d20b334bd290d8a65079948cab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — A senior Palestinian official says the U.S. has denied her application for a visa to travel to the United States. Hanan Ashrawi, a top official in the Palestine Liberation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: FBI Finds Child Remains, 'Obstacle Course' at Suspected Alabama Jihad Camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2019/05/13/report-fbi-finds-child-remains-obstacle-course-at-suspected-jihad-camp-in-alabama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI reportedly discovered a "makeshift military-style obstacle course" and the remains of a child on a plot of land in Alabama.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Shuts Down Populist Pages Before EU Elections...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/europe/2019/05/13/facebook-shuts-down-pro-populist-italian-pages-before-eu-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook has shut down 23 major populist Italian pages with 2.5 million followers just two weeks before the European elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their caliphate gone, hidden militants wage nighttime war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/12be07c521a343aea188004b028657e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BADOUSH, Iraq (AP) — It was a chilly January evening, and Khadija Abd and her family had just finished supper at their farm when the two men with guns burst into the room. One wore civilian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Anger Worse For Physical Health Than Sadness...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/anger-more-harmful-than-sadness-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that anger appears to be much more harmful to our health, with the potential to increase one's risk for ailments like heart disease, arthritis, and even cancer in old age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge approves unusual transportation plan for 900-pound man...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/local/crime/judge-approves-unusual-court-transportation-plan-for-defendant-who-weighs/article_ec5e923d-ddbe-549c-aebd-4caea18556be.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who weighs more than 900 pounds is set to be brought to federal court in Richmond on Monday, after the approval of a plan involving the FBI, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels 'kicking our butts' in New Mexico, as state left without checkpoints...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/cartels-kicking-butts-new-mexico-state-left-without-checkpoints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The cartel is winning and winning big."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco may ban police, city use of facial recognition...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-may-ban-police-city-facial-recognition-050021962--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco is on track to become the first U.S. city to ban the use of facial recognition by police and other city agencies, reflecting a growing backlash against a technology that's creeping into airports, motor vehicle departments, stores, stadiums and home security cameras</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL 'NEVER SURRENDER' </title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/china-defiant-toward-u-trade-kudlow-urges-strong-003402716--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON/BEIJING (Reuters) - China said on Monday it would impose higher tariffs on a range of U.S. goods, striking back in its trade war with Washington shortly after U.S. President Donald Trump warned it not to retaliate. China's finance ministry said it plans to set import tariffs ranging from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds: Immigration top crime; One-third all sentencings...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/feds-immigration-top-us-crime-one-third-of-all-sentencings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immigration crime, virtually all involving illegal male, Hispanic immigrants, was the top offense in federal courts last year, according to the United States Sentencing Commission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And then there was light: Cardinal breaks law to restore power for homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-homeless-cardinal/and-then-there-was-light-cardinal-breaks-law-to-restore-power-for-homeless-idUSKCN1SJ1C5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A close aide to Pope Francis has drawn the ire of Italy's anti-immigrant In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUMP TREASURIES?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/dow-futures-drop-over-200-points-as-u-s-china-trade-talks-appear-stalled-2019-05-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stockst fall Monday as investors focus on stalled U.S. -China trade talks and new retaliatory measures announced by China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm predicts who will die, have heart attack with 90% accuracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7022667/Netflix-style-algorithm-detect-DIE-heart-attack-90-cent-accuracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 1,000 patients complaining of chest pain were assessed and treated at Turku PET Centre, Finland and their data used to train the LogitBoost algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules against APPLE in App Store antitrust case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/13/supreme-court-rules-against-apple-in-app-store-antitrust-case.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade after recession, 40% of families still struggling...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/a-decade-after-the-recession-40-of-us-families-still-struggling/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steady economic growth hasn't lifted the fortunes of millions of Americans amid mounting housing and medical costs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage surges on Brexit discontent...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britains-trump-farage-surges-brexit-discontent-002810606.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polls show his Brexit Party easily winning next week's European Parliament polls and edging ahead of Theresa May's Conservatives in a UK general election. Nigel Farage is channelling Donald Trump's brand of angry populism to help turn British politics on its head. "You are in denial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORIS DAY DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9064342/doris-day-dead-at-97-legendary-actress-passes-away-after-80-year-career-as-a-hollywood-icon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACTRESS Doris Day has died at the age of 97 after a career of more than 80 years. The death of the Hollywood icon, who was best known for her work in the late 50s and 60s, was announced by her foun…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUMP TREASURIES?</title>
      <link>https://www.forexlive.com/news/!/china-says-to-raise-tariffs-on-some-us-goods-from-june-1-20190513</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forexlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China hits back China to raise tariffs on US goods. They plan to set import tariffs on $60 billion worth of US goods. The tariffs will range from 5%-25%. Reports also say China may stop purchasing US agricultural products and energy, cut Boeing orders and restrict US service trade with China. The Global Times reports that Chinese scholars are discussing the possibility of dumping US Treasuries and how to do it specifically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAVENDER OIL TO TREAT ANXIETY?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6761759/Leading-expert-claims-doctors-dish-LAVENDER-OIL-line-treatment-anxiety.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Professor Peter Hans-Volz, from Germany, said millions are hooked to anti-anxiety drugs benzodiazepines. Experts have disagreed, but are trying to cut back on prescriptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SHOOK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/13/us-markets-react-to-china-trade-war-news-and-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stock futures point to sharp losses as China raises tariffs on $60 billion worth of U.S. goods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese newspapers take hard line on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-china-trade-war-chinese-newspapers-reaction-9beec3df-f91b-4ff0-9499-021a55494a44.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war of words is getting heated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER gets hit again; shares below $40...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/5dad6f17faa54898bf3e35d7c57131b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Uber shares are down 7% and trading below $40 before the opening bell. Monday will be the ride-hailing company's first full day of trading after its rough initial public...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GULF TENSIONS FLARE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-oil-tankers-hit-sabotage-attacks-gulf-tensions-072309087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia said Monday two of its oil tankers were damaged in "sabotage attacks" in the Gulf as tensions soared in a region already shaken by a standoff between the United States and Iran. It came as US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo scrapped a planned visit to Moscow to head to Brussels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' OVER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/05/empire-canceled-jussie-smollett-scandal-fox-upfronts-lee-daniels-1202613350/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reign of Empire on Fox is coming to an end next year. Just two weeks after the Charlie Collier-run Fox Entertainment renewed Lee Daniels and Danny Strong’s hip hop drama for a sixth seaso…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain warns conflict could break out 'by accident'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-5508304,00.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ynetnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain warned Monday that conflict might break out "by accident" between the United States and Iran amid rising tensions, as European Union powers gathered to thrash out ways to keep afloat the nuclear deal with the Islamic Republic.  The warning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam intensifies crackdown on online dissent: Amnesty report...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-vietnam-security-rights/vietnam-intensifies-crackdown-on-online-dissent-amnesty-report-idUSKCN1SJ0EA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vietnam has stepped up its imprisonment of political activists, Amnesty Internat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sri Lanka blocks social media after anti-Muslim riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190513-sri-lanka-blocks-social-media-after-anti-muslim-riots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sri Lanka blocks social media after anti-Muslim riots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones in Aisle 5? Grocery stores hotbeds of innovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/12/grocery-stores-innovation-robots-drones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a grocery store somewhere in North America, a small drone floats from aisle to aisle, hovering like a hummingbird that has traded its nimble wings for tiny propellers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Ma urges ALIBABA employees to 'have sex marathons every day'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7022665/Jack-Ma-urges-Alibaba-employees-partners-sex-marathons-day-group-wedding.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Ma, also China's richest man, was offering marital advice at Alibaba's mass wedding which takes place every year on 'Ali Day' on May 10 at the company's headquarters in Hangzhou, east China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY: Snow set for Northeast?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/05/13/us/may-snow-northeast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be May, but winter is apparently not finished with parts of the Northeast, which coulc see yet more snow this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Half man, half god' Maradona is king of Cannes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/half-man-half-god-maradona-king-cannes-103024621.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diego Maradona is sure to cause a stir when he turns up next week at the Cannes film festival for a new documentary about his jaw-dropping life by the Oscar-winning maker of "Amy". It is only one of a wave of new works about the flawed Argentine football genius that include a just-wrapped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami of pop stars make film festival splash...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannes-rocks-tsunami-pop-stars-film-festival-splash-043646444.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bono, Elton John, Iggy Pop, Tom Waits... The red carpet at Cannes is shaping up to look like a dream rock festival line-up. Not to mention Rihanna and a couple of the surviving members of Led Zeppelin, who may yet put in an appearance at the world's biggest film festival, which starts Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTRE DAME: First look inside fire-ravaged cathedral...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/notre-dame-abc-news-exclusive-inside-fire-ravaged/story?id=62992558</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s been nearly a month since the flames leaping from Notre Dame cathedral in Paris left the world aghast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI TANKERS 'SABOTAGED'</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9060525/saudi-oil-tanker-sabotage-us-iran/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO Saudi oil tankers were hit by a “sabotage attack” off the United Arab Emirates, it was announced this morning – as tensions flare between the US and Iran. The ships were struc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto: Incredible disappearing candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/may/12/beto-o-rourke-2020-disappearing-act-what-happened-popularity-texas-politician</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;#Betomania became #Betofatigue in six short months – can the Texas Democrat rise again and show voters what type of president he’d be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON rolls out machines that pack orders, replace jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-amazon-com-automation-exclusive-idUSKCN1SJ0X1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc is rolling out machines to automate a job held by thousands of it...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Justices, With Much in Common, Take Different Paths...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/trumps-justices-with-much-in-common-take-different-paths/ar-AABgn8k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden to reopen rape case against Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4d496b0cfcaa49398609c2a136c8c42c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM (AP) — Swedish prosecutors said Monday they are reopening a rape case against WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange and will seek his extradition after he has served his 50-week prison term...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarms of A.I. Drones May Soon Patrol European Borders...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/05/11/drones-artificial-intelligence-europe-roborder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The EU is funding the development of AI-powered drones that would autonomously patrol Europe’s borders. The project's potential for military use can't be ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden learns not to take the bait...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/443125-a-more-disciplined-biden-learns-not-to-take-the-bait</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a woman screamed “You can hug and kiss me anytime!” to Joe Biden at a campaign rally in Las Vegas this week, the candidate looked like had more to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Time to rise up!' Venezuelan general tells military...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-venezuela-politics-military/its-time-to-rise-up-venezuelan-general-tells-military-officers-in-video-idUKKCN1SJ03S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Venezuelan general called on the country's armed forces on Sunday to rise...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBERT GATES: President in 70s 'problematic'; Acuity issues...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/robert-gates-on-face-the-nation-age-of-biden-sanders-and-trump-is-problematic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm not sure you have the intellectual acuity that you might have had in your 60s," the former defense secretary said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside epic TX cockfighting bust: 100 officers, choppers, drone, flash-bangs, dogs, horses, ATVs...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/local/article/Bust-of-Karnes-County-cockfight-yields-weapons-13838554.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The well-orchestrated bust of the cockfight, an hour southeast of San Antonio, was one of the largest in South Texas in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golfer hits wife in head with errant shot at PGA event...</title>
      <link>https://www.golfchannel.com/news/tyler-duncan-accidentally-hits-wife-head-errant-approach-att-byron-nelson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golfchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second-year Tour member dropped just one shot in his second-round 66, but he really made two mistakes at the par-4 13th.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handful of 'left leaning sources' dominate GOOGLE 'Top Stories'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/12/google-top-stories-dominated-left-leaning-sources-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from the Computational Journalism Lab at Northwestern found that many of Google’s top hits for news searches came from just a handful of left-leaning sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taunts, Threatens Assault on Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/iran-says-us-doesnt-dare-attack-for-fear-of-provoking-assault-on-israel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian Guards chiefs dismiss US 'psychological war,' say aircraft carrier deployed to region not a threat, but a target; 'If they make a move, we will hit them in the head'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bedroom' cinemas entice viewers away from NETFLIX?</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.ch/20190510/introducing-the-new-swiss-vip-bedroom-cinema</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switzerland’s first new concept ‘VIP bedroom’ cinema has opened in Cinema Pathé in Spreitenbach - but operators are not concerned that any inappropriate activity will take place during film screenings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran orders men not to look at women during Ramadan as hardliners tighten control...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/05/11/men-ordered-not-look-women-ramadan-iran-hardliners-tighten-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men in Iran have been ordered not to look at women during Ramadan as part of a round of draconian restrictions imposed by the increasingly isolated regime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador to Give US Assange Personal Devices, Docs...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/201905121074944323-ecuador-assange-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (Sputnik) - The Ecuadorian government will pass to Washington documents of WikiLeaks founder Assange that are currently kept in the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, where Assange was residing from 2012 and until his arrest in April, according to El Pais newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applause for Warren in heart of MAGA country...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/11/warren-west-virginia-2020-1317611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The liberal firebrand draws nods and even a few cheers on a trip through rural West Virginia.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
