<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Says he's the 'new Moses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8733347/Kanye-NOT-new-music-contact-Sony-Universal-expires.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West took to Twitter on Monday night to share a string of tweets, beginning by announcing he's 'not putting no more music out till I'm done with my contract with Sony and Universal.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/weather/radar/interactive/l/e508e61a6fb719e0d7a0fdadf8a18292b177e6bbbad4f715d42ba4fe7f1a95fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Interactive weather map allows you to pan and zoom to get unmatched weather details in your local neighbourhood or half a world away from The Weather Channel and Weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Defends Indoor Rally, but Aides Express Concern...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/14/trump-defends-indoor-rally-but-aides-express-concern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Trump and his campaign are defending his right to rally indoors, despite the private unease of aides</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he's the 'new Moses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1473561/kanye-west-new-moses-drake-kim-kardashian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE WEST said he’s the “new moses” and demanded an apology from Drake in a wild new Twitter rant as his marriage to Kim Kardashian remains in crisis. The controversial star took…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ad asks people to support troops. But it uses picture of Russian jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/14/trump-ad-asks-people-to-support-the-troops-but-it-uses-a-picture-of-russian-jets-414883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump Make America Great Again Committee is run by both the Republican National Committee and the campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QAnon Website Shuts Down After Man Identified as Operator...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/qanon-website-shuts-down-after-nj-man-identified-as-operator/ar-BB18WFHV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNSTEIN:   'Homicidal President Convening Homicidal Assembly'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/carl-bernstein-nukes-trump-for-restarting-maskless-indoor-campaign-rallies-homicidal-president-convening-a-homicidal-assembly-to-help-him-get-re-elected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carl Bernstein nukes Trump for restarting maskless, indoor campaign rallies: 'Homicidal president, convening… a homicidal assembly to help him get re-elected'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists create gene-edited animals to boost food production...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200914180913-2iwk8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENCE-GENEEDITING/LIVESTOCK (PIX):Scientists create gene-edited animals as 'surrogate sires' to boost food production</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5daY0lh8XRw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ You can support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Follow my Twitter for more f...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA Hoaxster stages 'FBI raid,' fools media...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jacob-wohl-staged-fake-fbi-raid-on-business-partner-actor-hired-for-production-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Virginia man who responded to a Craigslist ad seeking actors to play FBI agents quickly discovered he’d been roped into yet another Wohl/Burkman hoax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye West builds giant wall around ranch and church...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/1471937/kanye-west-builds-giant-wall-around-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West built a white wall around the Los Angeles home he shares with wife Kim Kardashian and their four children. The 43-year-old rapper made the decision to erect the walls around the ranch ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Wohl Drama... </title>
      <link>https://www.newstimes.com/news/article/A-fake-FBI-raid-orchestrated-by-right-wing-15567141.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fake FBI raid staged Monday by a notorious right-wing activist and conspiracist turned into an embarrassment for The Washington Post, which briefly reported the faux-event as if it were the real deal.  The "raid" on a house in Arlington, Va., actually involved actors recruited by Jacob Wohl, who has a history of making false accusations and has orchestrated dubious events in an effort to smear perceived opponents of President Donald Trump.  This time, Wohl recruited actors to pose as FBI agents, telling them they would be participating in a scene for a "TV pilot," one of the actors involved told the Daily Beast. The actors donned FBI-style windbreakers and pretended they were raiding a house during early-morning hours.  It appears Wohl used photos of the event to trick a reporter into believing that Wohl's longtime associate, Jack Burkman, was being targeted by law enforcement officials. The intended purpose of the deception was not clear.  In a story written by Metro reporter Rachel Weiner, The Post briefly reported Monday that a real FBI raid had taken place. The story was updated about two hours later to note that the raid was a fabrication.  The story unfolded as a confluence of outright falsehoods by Burkman and Wohl coupled with lapses by Post journalists.  A purported neighbor of Burkman emailed a tip to the Post on Monday morning to report "a bunch of commotion" outside Burkman's house. "His house was being raided by the FBI," said the email, which included a link to photos and video of the alleged raid.  Burkman and Wohl later corroborated this version of events to The Post; Wohl said agents had taken computers, papers and cellphones.  Burkman is longtime conservative lobbyist and recent conspiracist. Together with Wohl, a 22-year-old former hedge fund manager...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters scramble again ahead of winds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/as-california-fire-death-toll-hits-24-firefighters-scramble-ahead-of-winds/ar-BB191X0z?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suggests tear-gassing reporters... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/top-trump-health-spokesman-deletes-twitter-account-after-rant/ar-BB191SLV?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO delivers Europe warning as infections hit new high ...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/who-delivers-europe-death-warning-infections-hit-new-high-3045564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO delivers Europe death warning as infections hit new high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot can detect people not wearing masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/robot-can-detect-if-people-are-wearing-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A human-like robot called Pepper can now detect whether people are wearing a mask to help stop the spread of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in cases, deaths close to election could be disastrous...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-s-latest-indoor-rally-defies-state-health-15567097.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's first indoor rally in months was staged as a rebuke to Democrats he accuses of using coronavirus restrictions against him, but the campaign event in Nevada also prompted sharp denunciations from critics on Monday as a symbol of the president's handling of the covid-19 pandemic.  The Sunday-night gathering came as the pandemic has caused at least 190,000 deaths in the United States, with the number expected to pass 200,000 before Trump holds his next official campaign events on Friday. The Nov. 3 election had already become a referendum on the president's often dismissive approach to the pandemic before revelations last week that he had told Washington Post journalist Bob Woodward that he knew the severity of the virus but preferred to play it down in public.  "We are already making the turn. We're making that round, beautiful, last turn" to a post-pandemic economic recovery, Trump said during the rally in Henderson, Nev., although the nation has recovered only about half of the jobs lost since spring and 13.6 million workers remain unemployed.  On Monday, Trump held another indoor campaign event at a luxury hotel in Phoenix that was billed as a roundtable with Latino supporters. The White House pool reporter traveling with Trump described the scene as looking much like a rally, with more than 100 people crowded closely together in a ballroom. Television footage showed mask-free supporters waving campaign signs.  "I know this was supposed to be, you know the fake news, they said that this is supposed to be a roundtable, but it looks like a rally," Trump said. "But it is a rally because we love each other." He then added that "it is a roundtable."  Democratic nominee Joe Biden has made adherence to coronavirus rules a defining feature of his mostly virtual campaign. Although Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health and Human Services spokesman warns of armed insurrection after election...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Health-and-Human-Services-spokesman-warns-of-15567068.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A top communications official for the administration's coronavirus response urged President Donald Trump's supporters to prepare for an armed insurrection after a contested election and accused government scientists of "sedition" in a Facebook Live chat that he described in detail to The Washington Post on Monday.  Michael Caputo, assistant secretary for public affairs at the Department of Health and Human Services, which is overseeing the coronavirus response, leveled the accusations and promoted other conspiracy theories in a Facebook Live event first reported by The New York Times. Caputo confirmed the authenticity of the video in comments he made to The Post.  "Since joining the administration my family and I have been continually threatened and in and out of criminal court dealing with harassment prosecutions," Caputo said in a statement. "This weighs heavily on us and we deeply appreciate the friendship and support of President Trump as we address these matters and keep our children safe."  Caputo's comments come as Trump administration officials say they are seeking to build public support for a coronavirus vaccine but have faced setbacks, most recently the release of audio in which the president admitted that he deliberately downplayed the virus when he knew it was "deadly."  Trump installed Caputo in April after considering whether to fire Health and Human Services Secretary Alex Azar over a series of damaging stories about Trump's handling of the pandemic, according to three current and former White House officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe behind-the-scenes discussions. Allies persuaded Trump to not make such a change amid a pandemic, but instead to bring in Caputo, the officials said. (Trump denied reports that he was considering firing Azar at the time.)  Almost...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis Angered By Nationwide Lockdown Days Before Rosh Hashanah...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-israel-nationwide-lockdown-reaction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shutdown will be implemented hours before the start of the Jewish New Year and the High Holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Turn Up Heat on Postmaster DeJoy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scrutiny-of-postmaster-general-louis-de-joy-intensifies-230112268.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scrutiny of Postmaster General Louis DeJoy intensified on Monday amid new reports alleging improper business dealings and persistent charges that the longtime Republican donor is subverting postal operations in order to make mail-in voting difficult in November’s presidential election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's antagonistic relationship CA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-testy-relationship-trump-overshadows-185013659.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump deflected questions about whether climate change was a driving force behind California&amp;#39;s historic wildfires this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump health aide alleges broad conspiracies and warns of armed revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/trump-health-aide-alleges-broad-conspiracies-and-warns-of-armed-revolt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Caputo, assistant secretary of public affairs at the Department of Health and Human Services, went on Facebook live with numerous far-fetched accusations, warnings and the statement that has own "mental health has definitely failed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine maker got $1 billion from taxpayers. Now it's boosting drug prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/news/vaccine-maker-got-241-billion-from-taxpayers-now-its-boosting-drug-prices/ar-BB190Nbt?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smutty' secrets on bin Laden's hard drives uncovered in new documentary...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/smutty-secrets-osama-bin-ladens-22682812</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Osama bin Laden was shot dead in a US Navy Seal strike in 2011. Hard drives, USBs, DVDs and other storage devices were seized from his hideout – uncovering huge porn stashes and hundreds of articles about the man himself</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulations Have Made Worse...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/09/14/western-wildfires-can-be-prevented-if-burdens-on-forest-management-are-eased</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controlled, prescribed burns can stop wildfires from spreading. Too bad they are effectively prohibited by rules like the Clean Air Act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum comes out as Bi...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/politics/andrew-gillum-says-heis-bisexual-in-his-first-interview-since-hotel-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His wife said "love and sexuality exist on a spectrum” and that all she cares about “is what’s between us and what agreement do we make to be in a relationship with each other”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Confronts Trump About CA Wildfires: 57% Of The Land In This State Is Federal!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/california-governor-gavin-newsom-confronts-donald-trump-california-wildfires-1234576479/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California Governor Gavin Newsom started his Monday meeting with President Donald Trump by thanking the Commander-in-Chief for his help with the California wildfires. Newsom said the president had …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BICOASTAL BURN: Smoke from West Coast fires reaches DC...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/937474/smoke-from-west-coast-fires-reached-all-way-washington-dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You've seen the harrowing images of West Coast skies this past week, as wildfires continue to rage across California, Oregon, and Washington. Now, the smoke that created that apocalyptic orange glow has moved across the country, though the air quality and appearance is nowhere near as drastic as in the Pacific states. The National Weather Service office in Sterling, Virginia, confirmed that the 'hazy appearance to the sky' in the Washington, D.C. area on Monday is a result of smoke from the western fires getting caught in the jet stream and floating swiftly toward the Atlantic. Wow-- smoke from the West Coast fires has reached DC https://t.co/gqGSN7qfoB — Jennifer Haberkorn (@jenhab) September 14, 2020 Indeed, both NASA and AirNow — which monitors U.S. air quality — predict the smoke plume area will stretch far and wide this week. Tim O'Donnell Here's a map from https://t.co/OB2UM7gO3H which approximates smoke plume area in gray... it's covering much of Lower 48, including DC area: pic.twitter.com/hIfBTRzLzT — Capital Weather Gang (@capitalweather) September 14, 2020 this smoke is coming for the east coast. https://t.co/uWCD9vyXpo — Tim Dickinson (@7im) September 14, 2020</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navalny, Awake and Alert, Plans Return to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/14/navalny-awake-and-alert-plans-to-return-to-russia-german-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — Laboratories in France and Sweden have confirmed that the substance used to poison the Russian opposition leader Aleksei</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthens to Cat 2...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ea2a4cd36cceefad876d9e878cb5bc3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAVELAND, Miss. (AP) — Hurricane Sally, one of a record-tying five storms churning simultaneously in the Atlantic, closed in on the Gulf Coast on Monday with rapidly strengthening winds of at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ watchdog investigating Roger Stone sentencing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/justice-department-internal-watchdog-investigating-roger-stone-s-sentencing-say-n1240033</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutor Aaron Zelinsky told Congress the U.S. Attorney's office in D.C. told him to recommend a lighter sentence because of Stone's ties to Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive breakthrough: Howitzer artillery destroys incoming cruise missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/massive-breakthrough-155-mm-howitzer-artillery-destroys-attacking-cruise-missile</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an amazing first, an artillery cannon took out a cruise missile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower Says FACEBOOK Ignored Global Political Manipulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/craigsilverman/facebook-ignore-political-manipulation-whitstleblower-memo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 6,600-word internal memo from a fired Facebook data scientist details how the social network knew about specific examples of global political manipulation — and failed to act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Judge Rules PA Shutdown Orders Unconstitutional...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/09/14/gov-tom-wolf-coronavirus-shutdown-orders-unconstitutional/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Wolf administration will try to appeal a federal judge's ruling saying the governor's shutdown orders were unconstitutional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON workforce to hit 1 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/amazon-workforce-hit-one-million-173447157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon is hiring another 100,000 permanent workers in the United States and Canada to meet soaring demand for online shopping, almost certainly taking its overall headcount over 1m. The online shopping titan said it would open 100 new operations buildings this month as it prepares for a logistical double</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Area Of Brain That Controls Sexual Desire In Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/scientists-discover-brain-area-sexual-desire-in-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this specific area of the brain, the gene aromatase converts testosterone to estrogen and helps the male sex drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star arrested 'for filming' in sacred forest...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-54152233</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nigerian Tobiloba Jolaosho was detained for recording at his country's revered Osun-Osogbo grove.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL warns coaches about coverings or 'risk' season...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/atlanta-falcons/nfl-warns-coaches-about-face-coverings-or-risk-season/TGPZIQ4SKBDORIZBSAJB2OJ2TQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL on Monday reminded team personnel on the sidelines about the COVID-19 requirements for wearing face coverings, saying such carelessness or disregard could put the season “at risk.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACY'S Thanksgiving Parade Goes 'TV-Only'...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/09/14/macys-announces-changes-for-thanksgiving-day-parade-for-first-time-ever-it-will-be-tv-only/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The traditional giant balloon inflation public event the night before Thanksgiving is also canceled this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Dakota AG thought he hit deer. Instead he killed pedestrian with car...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/09/14/jason-ravnsborg-told-authorities-he-thought-he-hit-deer-south-dakota-ag/5794312002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Dakota Attorney General Jason Ravnsborg told authorities he thought he hit a deer on Saturday night when he struck and killed a pedestrian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama Warning: 'Potentially historic' flooding...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/hurricane/2020/09/tropical-storm-sally-could-bring-dangerous-potentially-historic-flooding-to-alabama.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sally could bring up to 16 inches of rain to parts of the state, along with damaging winds, storm surge and tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Florida Gov candidate comes out as bisexual...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/516336-ex-florida-gubernatorial-candidate-andrew-gillum-says-he-identifies-as</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Florida gubernatorial candidate Andrew Gillum (D) on Monday told daytime talk show host Tamron Hall that he identifies as bisexual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anthony Weiner piecing together shattered life as CEO of broken glass factory...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/14/disgraced-pol-anthony-weiner-is-ceo-at-a-broken-glass-factory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weiner, 56, revealed his new gig in a promotional email that shows a product sample containing colorful flecks of orange and blue glass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flush Biden boosts battleground buys...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c8c65ca2021d4c7ec5542c5b9335600c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s massive campaign war chest was supposed to finance an onslaught of attacks that would destroy Joe Biden’s chance of winning in November. But after...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon man freed after using Molotov cocktail to start fire set 6 more...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/14/oregon-man-freed-after-starting-brush-fire-set-six-more-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oregon man was charged with using a Molotov cocktail to start a brush blaze in the wildfire-devastated state — then busted again just hours later for allegedly going back and starting six …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Official Alleges Broad Conspiracies, Warns of Armed Revolt...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/09/14/trump-health-aide-alleges-broad-conspiracies-and-warns-of-armed-revolt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The top communications official at the powerful cabinet department in charge of combating the coronavirus accused career government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrest in place better known for Amish...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d7cb1109c72ef5dc5fe314ef44785569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LANCASTER, Pa. (AP) — A police officer fatally shot a man during a domestic disturbance call, leading to street protests and vandalism in what the mayor of the small Pennsylvania city of Lancaster...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France tightens screws on public activities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7936f82ccce2dbbea19223593f2a27ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Two of France’s biggest cities with COVID-19 infection rates gathering speed even faster than the national surge in new cases are tightening limits on public activities as the French...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEPSICO, Longtime Purveyor of Caffeine, Now Aims to Make You Sleepy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/companies/pepsico-longtime-purveyor-of-caffeine-aims-to-make-you-sleepy/ar-BB191nhj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corona can infect brain cells, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/brain-invasion-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Sign of life' on Venus discovered with Hawaii telescope...</title>
      <link>https://www.hawaii.edu/news/2020/09/14/hints-of-life-on-venus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaii.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of international astronomers detected what may be extra-terrestrial life in Venus' upper clouds using the JCMT telescope on Maunakea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALLY EYES NEW ORLEANS...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2020-09-14-hurricane-sally-forecast-gulf-coast-storm-surge-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest on the dangerous storm surge and flooding rain threats Sally will bring to the Gulf Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd aims 'lock him up' chant at Obama...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/516252-crowd-aims-lock-him-up-chant-at-obama-during-trump-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd at President Trump's rally Sunday evening chanted "lock him up" after the president accused his predecessor, former President Obama, of being caught "spying" on the 2016 Trump campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York City's Day of Reckoning Is at Hand...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/york-city-day-reckoning-hand-103054768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- A large group of New York business leaders, all with pedigrees and some of them well-known, sent up a flare over City Hall late last week.“Despite New York’s success in containing the coronavirus, unprecedented numbers of New Yorkers are unemployed, facing homelessness, or otherwise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASK OFF!  In defiance of Nevada governor, Trump holds indoor rally...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5d306f8176972692ce700b569b01cd73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — In open defiance of state regulations and his own administration’s pandemic health guidelines, President Donald Trump hosted his first indoor rally since June, telling a packed,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Slashes Ad Spending in Key States...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-campaign-slashes-ad-spending-in-key-states-in-cash-crunch/ar-BB190HgD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIS: Biggest Crisis Test Still to Come With Insolvencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/biggest-crisis-test-is-still-to-come-with-insolvencies-bis-says/ar-BB191337?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviction Filings by Big Landlords Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2020/09/14/eviction-filings-by-big-landlords-surged-after-trump-issued-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Institutional landlords filed more than 900 eviction cases across eight metropolitan areas from Sept. 2 to Sept. 8, according to data compiled by Private Equity Stakeholder Project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Tropical Cyclones In Atlantic Simultaneously...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-atlantic-churns-out-another-record-setting-storm-with-formation-of-vicky/812199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNF' RATINGS SLIDE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/09/rams-nfl-sunday-night-football-ratings-down-cowboys-nbc-60-minutes-1234576202/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SoFi Stadium was devoid of fans on last night’s Sunday Night Football due to the coronavirus pandemic, but full of victory for hometown heroes the Los Angeles Rams. Sadly that winning feeling wasn&amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST plane returns to gate because 2-year-old not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/09/13/southwest-airlines-escorts-mother-2-year-old-flight-over-mask/5789143002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago woman said she was humiliated when she and her 2-year-old son were escorted from their flight Saturday because her child was having a snack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Industry Headed for Major Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-porn-industry-is-headed-for-a-major-coronavirus-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adult star Cherie DeVille writes about how the testing system—and contact tracing—employed by porn is woefully inadequate and even dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviction Filings by Big Landlords Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-09-14/eviction-filings-by-big-landlords-surged-after-trump-issued-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan's Newest Skyscraper Opens Up to Dead Midtown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/manhattan-newest-skyscraper-opening-dead-103000949.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- SL Green Realty Corp. is opening its new $3.3 billion office skyscraper Monday, in a neighborhood that’s among Manhattan’s busiest -- but is now still unusually quiet.The first tenants at One Vanderbilt, across from Grand Central Terminal, will start moving in by year’s end, SL Green Chief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign of life on Venus discovered with Hawaii telescope...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/09/14/hawaii-news/sign-of-life-on-venus-discovered-with-hawaii-telescope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ROCKET TO MARS? SPACEX LAUNCH TO 60,000 FEET... </title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2020-09-spacex-sn8-feet-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk, head of SpaceX, has announced via Twitter that the company's SN8 rocket will take a test flight sometime next week. The plan is for the rocket is to soar up to 60,000 feet (18,300 meters) and then return to Earth in a controlled landing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Tropical Cyclones In Atlantic Basin Simultaneously...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/marshallshepherd/2020/09/14/5-tropical-cyclones-in-the-atlantic-basin-simultaneouslyis-this-a-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 tropical cyclones were in the Atlantic Basin on Monday morning. Is that a record?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans raiding retirement savings...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/14/americans-are-forced-to-raid-retirement-savings-during-the-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The economic fallout from the coronavirus pandemic is pushing retirement savers to pull thousands of dollars from their nest eggs to make ends meet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIS: Biggest Crisis Test Still to Come With Insolvencies...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/biggest-crisis-test-is-still-to-come-with-insolvencies-bis-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biggest Crisis Test Is Still to Come With Insolvencies, BIS Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumber's Staggering Rally Has New Homes Selling for $16,148 More...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-09-14/lumber-s-staggering-rally-has-new-homes-selling-for-16-148-more?srnd=prognosis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK SPORTS CLUB Bankrupt After Gym Shutdown...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/york-sports-clubs-owner-files-045126109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The owner of the New York Sports Clubs chain sought bankruptcy protection from its creditors, unable to keep up with debt payments after the pandemic shut its gyms for months.Town Sports International LLC filed a Chapter 11 petition in Delaware that estimates liabilities and assets of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20-INCHES OF RAIN?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/tropical-storm-sally-forecast-hit-gulf-coast-slow/story?id=72980671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Sally is forecast to strengthen into a hurricane as it approaches the Gulf Coast Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 DAYS OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2020/09/14/election-2020-50-day-mark-voters-anxious-trump-and-biden/5720729002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just 8% of voters agreed with the statement that choosing would be difficult "because either one would make a good president," a Pew poll said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Tehran considering assassinating US ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/13/iran-south-africa-ambassador-assassination-plot-413831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Islamic Republic is still looking to avenge the death of Qassem Soleimani, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign Slashes Ad Spending in Key States...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-campaign-slashes-ad-spending-in-key-states-in-cash-crunch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Campaign Slashes Ad Spending in Key States in Cash Crunch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marrakesh 'Suffocates' Without Tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/morocco-s-marrakesh-suffocates-without-tourists-01600079407</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snake charmers, storytellers and crowds of tourists; the legendary Jamaa El Fna square of Morocco's Marrakesh is almost as famous for the number of visitors as its colourful performers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Maskers Forced to Dig Graves For Victims In Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/anti-maskers-forced-to-dig-graves-for-covid-19-victims-1845046526</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight people who have refused to wear masks during the coronavirus pandemic have been forced to dig graves for people who died from covid-19 in the province of East Java, Indonesia, according to a report from the Jakarta Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Calling Shots in Europe and Merkel Isn't Sorry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/germany-is-calling-the-shots-in-europe-and-merkel-isnt-sorry/ar-BB18ZTBs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
