<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Thousands, Without Masks, Party At Wuhan Water Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/china-coronavirus-thousands-without-masks-party-at-wuhan-water-park-in-china-2280793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of partygoers packed out a water park over the weekend in the central Chinese city of Wuhan, where the coronavirus first emerged late last year, keen to party as the city edges back to normal life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters in NC receive ballot forms with Trump face on them...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/16/politics/postal-service-trump-absentee-ballot-request-mail-usps/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the crisis facing the United States Postal Service before a presidential election, the last thing John Herter expected to receive in the mail Saturday was an absentee ballot request form with President Donald Trump's face on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems kick off convention unified...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/unlike-2016-democrats-kick-off-090000757.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden enters the virtual 2020 Democratic National Convention with a much more unified party behind him compared to four years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dems demand DeJoy testify, protesters picket his homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/As-the-House-demands-an-interview-with-Postal-15488875.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of hundreds blasted sirens outside Louis DeJoy's Washington apartment building early on Saturday morning, sliding mock blank ballots behind the iron gates. The next day in Greensboro, N.C., dozens more protesters blocked the leafy street to the postmaster general's mansion, clapping to the tune of a banjo and carrying signs that read "Stay out of our boxes."  Hours later, as fears escalated that DeJoy's cost-cutting changes could delay ballots in November, Democratic lawmakers summoned him to testify at an emergency hearing.  DeJoy, who was named to head the U.S. Postal Service in May, and his wife, Aldona Wos, have for decades worked behind the scenes to raise millions for candidates like President Donald Trump and former Gov. Pat McCrory, R-N.C. But over the weekend, the GOP power couple found themselves at the nexus of public anger over fears that Trump is interfering with the November election by crippling the Postal Service.  "We're in the middle of a historic pandemic and as many as 40% of Americans plan on casting their ballot by mail," Patrick Young, an organizer with the group Shut Down D.C. told WUSA. "If we can't rely on those ballots getting to where they need to go, we've got a serious problem with democracy."  It is unclear if DeJoy or Wos were at either residence during the demonstrations this weekend; a spokesperson for the Postal Service did not immediately respond to a request for comment.  As The Washington Post has reported, DeJoy has upended the mail system months before it is expected to serve as the main conduit for millions of mail-in ballots, as voters seek to avoid polling places during the coronavirus pandemic. In the past week alone, he fired or reassigned several agency leaders and ordered the removal of hundreds of high-speed mail-sorting machines critical to maintain processing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US intelligence indicates Iran paid bounties to Taliban for targeting American troops in Afghanistan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/17/politics/iran-taliban-bounties-us-intelligence/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US intelligence agencies assessed that Iran offered bounties to Taliban fighters for targeting American and coalition troops in Afghanistan, identifying payments linked to at least six attacks carried out by the militant group just last year alone, including a suicide bombing at a US air base in December, CNN has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Spars With Oz Watchdog After News Row Deepens...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/google-spars-with-australian-watchdog-after-news-row-deepens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Spars With Australian Watchdog After News Row Deepens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warp Speed Vax Push Lacks Key Ingredient: Trust...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/gadfly/warp-speed-s-covid-19-vaccine-push-lacks-a-key-ingredient-trust</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 Vaccine Push Lacks a Key Ingredient: Trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Faces Well-Armed Enemy in Battle With FORTNITE Owner...</title>
      <link>https://www.aviationanalysis.net/apple-faces-a-nicely-armed-enemy-in-fortnite-struggle-royale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aviationanalysis.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- When Apple Inc. opened the Application Store in July 2008, it was a $155 billion organization promoting 12 million iPhones a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing video shows BLM mob beat white man unconscious...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/17/blm-mob-beat-white-man-unconscious-after-making-him-crash-truck/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mob of Portland Black Lives Matter and Antifa militants forced a white man to crash his truck, and then punched and kicked him unconscious, disturbing footage shows. A series of clips on social m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to Flee City for Suburbia? Think Again...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/17/want-to-flee-the-city-for-suburbia-think-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walking the streets of San Francisco during these coronavirus days, you’ll see a sight rarer than Bigfoot: “for sale” and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President motivates party to rally behind ticket...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd2e087f20fc144cd065550ea0b837f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — For the second time in four years, the Democratic presidential primary pitted the expanding progressive movement against an eventually victorious establishment. But as the party...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Returning vacationers face new constraints as virus spikes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5301598bd1bd569d5e4b72d937eddca5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Countries that had seen a summer respite from coronavirus outbreaks tracked swiftly rising numbers of new confirmed cases Monday, prompting fears among government leaders and health...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharon Stone blames non-mask wearers as sister hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/aug/17/sharon-stone-blames-mask-refuseniks-sister-covid-hospital</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor blames ‘non-mask wearers’ for sister Kelly Stone’s condition and calls on viewers to support Joe Biden and Kamala Harris in US presidential run</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holds clear lead in polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/17/biden-trump-polling-democratic-convention-396275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 things you need to know as the Democratic National Convention kicks off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exotic dancer, nuclear engineer, QAnon enthusiast, Laura Loomer: GOP race to represent Trump's Palm Beach district...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/An-exotic-dancer-a-nuclear-engineer-a-QAnon-15488787.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PALM BEACH, Fla. - In a congressional race where an acolyte of Roger Stone who's been banned by Twitter and Facebook may not even be the most unconventional candidate, voters in the Republican primary for Florida's 21st Congressional District have a rich array of choices.  The six people competing in the Aug. 18 primary include a former burlesque dancer and wild animal exhibitor who did business in the same circles as "Tiger King" Joe Exotic; a Palm Beach neighbor of Mar-a-Lago who is supported by QAnon believers; and Laura Loomer, a far-right commentator and anti-Islam activist who calls herself "the most banned woman on the Internet" and who once handcuffed herself to the front door of Twitter's office in New York.  There's also an ex-cop, a nuclear engineer-turned college professor and a retired investigator for the IRS.  Among the constituents they hope to represent: the president and first lady. The Trumps registered as Republicans in Palm Beach County in October when President Trump changed his official domicile from Manhattan to his Mar-a-Lago Club in Palm Beach. They both voted by mail in the March presidential primary.  All six candidates are political newcomers running in a heavily Democratic district that covers Palm Beach, West Palm Beach and parts of Broward County. One of them will face Lois Frankel, a Democrat who ran unopposed two years ago, or her primary opponent, Guido Weiss, a former legislative assistant for Rep. Tulsi Gabbard, D-Hawaii.  Regardless of their long shot chances of winning the congressional seat in the fall, the GOP candidates are being scrutinized due to Trump's decision last year to call the district home.  Loomer's campaign manager is Karen Giorno, who was a senior political adviser to the Trump campaign in 2016. She said the president's team wants the congressional seat - which...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Moon drifting away from Earth?</title>
      <link>https://www.business-standard.com/article/current-affairs/is-the-moon-drifting-away-from-earth-laser-beams-unravel-a-new-mystery-120081600252_1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.business-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By measuring how long it takes laser light to return to Earth - about 2.5 seconds on average - researchers calculate the distance between Earth laser stations and Moon reflectors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Rage Moms' Dems Counting On...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/17/the-rage-moms-democrats-are-counting-on/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Bill Clinton introduced America to the “soccer mom,” anxiously shuttling her children across swing state suburbs in her minivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Grow in Thailand, Where Speaking Out Can Be Perilous...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/16/protests-grow-in-thailand-where-speaking-out-can-be-perilous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK — They gathered at a monument celebrating Thai democracy. They raised their hands in defiance below a giant image</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATH VALLEY HITS 130 DEGREES</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/death-valley-hits-130-degrees-053931284.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the reading is shown to be valid, it would also be among the top-three highest temperatures to have ever been measured in Death Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College students raise alarm by packing bars, avoiding masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/College-students-raise-alarm-by-packing-bars-15488745.php </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims of plot to undermine election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/postal-slowdown-sparks-claims-plot-023525958.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Postal Service is popularly known for delivering mail despite snow, rain or heat, but it faces a new foe in President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING BLACKOUTS IN CALI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-power-grid-manager-urges-000110208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The heat &amp;quot;is causing a strain on supplies, and consumers should be prepared for likely rolling outages during the late afternoons and early evenings through Wednesday,&amp;quot; the California Independent System Operator said in its statewide flex alert Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi calls House back to deal with Postal Service crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8cd319f66ae12bc23f4cadd38cc21f5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Speaker Nancy Pelosi says she is calling the House back into session over the crisis at the U.S. Postal Service, setting up a political showdown amid growing concerns that the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libertarian candidate Jo Jorgensen advocates end to big govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article244996385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY corralled virus. What's California's excuse for surge?</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/new-york-corralled-coronavirus-whats-californias-excuse-for-case-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts and those with ties to both states say New Yorkers gained a healthy respect for the virus’ deadly potential after it hammered the state in the spring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convention season set to begin, with [virtual] spotlight on Biden...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-convention-season-set-begin-201227357.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Democrats on Monday open an unprecedented virtual convention, the party&amp;#39;s disparate factions are projecting a united front behind Joe Biden, brought together by their common determination to defeat Donald Trump in November&amp;#39;s election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First major Mediterranean cruise liner sets sail since pandemic... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/first-major-cruise-line-set-082146808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first major cruise ship to resume tours of the Mediterranean since the coronavirus pandemic hit Europe set sail from the Italian city of Genoa on Sunday, as the industry tries to regain ground after a bruising hiatus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2ND NIGHT OF ROLLING BLACKOUTS IN CALI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-worst-power-shortage-years-130019359.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People staying home with air conditioners blasting, plus a dearth of power from other states results in the worst statewide energy shortage in nearly 20 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy closes nightclubs as cases rise among young...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816173142-jjf0d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ITALY-NIGHTCLUBS (PIX):Italy closes nightclubs as coronavirus cases rise among young</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival rallies face off in Warsaw over gay rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200816160439-m28p6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nationalists burnt a rainbow flag, while the LGBT activists painted one on the street</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey in a Stir Over Old Biden Remarks Backing Erdogan Ouster...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/turkey-stir-over-old-biden-133025340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- An old video of Democratic presidential hopeful Joe Biden calling for the removal of Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan has set off a furor in Turkey while earning U.S. President Donald Trump a shout-out.In a Dec. 16 meeting with New York Times editors, Biden called Erdogan an “autocrat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst heatwave in 70 years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/california-faces-second-night-blackouts-020525955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- First, it was the prospect of wildfires that took down large swaths of California’s power grid. Now, it’s the worst heat wave in 70 years.Climate change is contributing to increasingly extreme weather in California. Less than a year ago, millions of people were plunged into darkness in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New White House virus doc has no expertise in public health or infectious diseases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/886b59d445a3d20739e2f77600976ea0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has found a new doctor for his coronavirus task force — and this time there's no daylight between them. Trump last week announced that Dr. Scott...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
