<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Watch how I run up ramps while Trump 'stumbles down'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/sep/8/joe-biden-watch-how-i-run-ramps-while-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential nominee Joseph R. Biden this week disputed the Trump campaign’s contention that the 77-year-old Mr. Biden has lost a step or two by touting his ability to run up ramps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 8 states where 2020 will be won or lost...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/09/08/swing-states-2020-presidential-election-409000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within each of these swing states, the roadmap ahead for President Donald Trump and Joe Biden is clear. Polling, however, is not.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL COHEN: President should resign; 'Let Pence pardon you'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/515408-cohen-compares-trump-to-cult-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s former personal attorney, Michael Cohen, compared the president to a cult leader in an interview with NBC set to air Tuesday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army vet fatally shoots self in FACEBOOK livestream...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/08/army-veteran-kills-himself-in-facebook-livestream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 33-year-old Army veteran from Mississippi who served in Iraq shot himself in the head live on Facebook — and social media sites are still scrambling to remove the harrowing footage, which went vi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grisly series of horse mutilations mystifies France...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/grisly-series-horse-mutilations-mystifies-102908638.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Didier Fruchet, owner of a horse club with some 80 animals outside Paris, looks with concern at his stables. &amp;quot;It&amp;#39;s stressful to be thinking, &amp;#39;what happened tonight?&amp;#39; When we arrive in the morning we don&amp;#39;t know what we are going to find.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P7mqaE07RQU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired on India-China border first time in decades as tensions flare...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Shots-fired-on-the-India-China-border-for-the-15549227.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI - India and China accused each other on Tuesday of firing warning shots during a confrontation the day before at their disputed border in a marked escalation of tensions between the two nuclear-armed neighbors.  It was the first time in decades that shots were fired at the shared frontier, where longstanding protocols observed by both countries forbid the use of firearms.  Such protocols did not prevent the two countries from engaging in their deadliest violence in nearly 50 years in June, when soldiers armed with clubs studded with nails and metal rods clashed in a remote area of the western Himalayas.  Twenty Indian soldiers were killed. The number of Chinese casualties remains unknown.  Both countries moved thousands of troops as well as tanks, artillery and fighter jets to areas close to the disputed and unmarked border, which is known as the Line of Actual Control. Despite numerous rounds of talks, tension remain high.  Col. Zhang Shuli, the spokesman for the People's Liberation Army western theater command, said in a statement early Tuesday that Indian troops "blatantly fired upon Chinese border patrols with threatening shots" near the southern bank of Pangong Tso Lake in Ladakh. Chinese troops took unspecified "countermeasures" to stabilize the situation, he said.  "These are serious military provocations of a terrible nature," Zhang said. China demanded that India restrain its troops and punish the soldiers who fired their weapons.  India denied that its troops had used firearms. The Ministry of Defense released a statement saying that PLA soldiers were trying to "close-in" on a forward position on the border and "fired a few rounds in the air in an attempt to intimidate" Indian troops.  An Indian official with knowledge of the incident who spoke on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force Tests 'Robot Dogs' For Base Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/36229/the-air-force-just-tested-robot-dogs-for-use-in-base-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The quadrupedal robots secured the perimeter of a base during a recent test of the USAF's Advanced Battle Management System.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'blue shift' in mail ballots might set off Election Week chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-delay/how-a-blue-shift-in-u-s-mail-ballots-might-set-off-election-week-chaos-idUSKBN25Z1I1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When polls closed in Arizona's U.S. Senate race in November 2018, initial results from in-person voting showed Republican Martha McSally in the lead. Her advantage evaporated in the days that followed with the tallying of postal ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY TAP OWN FUNDS</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-weighs-putting-up-to-24100-million-of-his-cash-into-race/ar-BB18OmRN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious leader who blamed gay marriage for virus now infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/religious-leader-who-blamed-gay-22646310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriarch Filaret, 91, head of the Ukrainian Orthodox Church of Kyiv, also faced legal action after blameing 'sinful' humanity and 'same-sex' marriage for the coronavirus pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORBES: Richest Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbespr/2020/09/08/forbes-releases-39th-annual-forbes-400-ranking-of-the-richest-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;September 8, 2020 – Forbes today released the 39th annual Forbes 400 list, the definitive ranking of the wealthiest Americans—including a comprehensive report of not only what these billionaires are worth, but how they are using their money to drive change and make an impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens More Mystery Drone Incursions Over Nuke Power Plants Revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidhambling/2020/09/07/dozens-more-drone-incursions-over-us-nuclear-power-plants-revealed/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salmon May Harbor Covid For Week, Study Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-09-08/salmon-may-harbor-infectious-coronavirus-for-a-week-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue operation to airlift over 60 trapped people 'unsuccessful...</title>
      <link>https://abc30.com/creek-fire-rescue-operation-to-airlift-over-60-trapped-at-lake-edison-china-peak-unsuccessful/6413342/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc30.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen people were rescued by helicopter early Tuesday morning after being trapped by the raging Creek Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel will investigate reports DeJoy pressured employees to make campaign donations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/House-panel-will-investigate-reports-that-DeJoy-15548940.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats are launching an investigation of Postmaster General Louis DeJoy and called for his immediate suspension after reports that he reimbursed former employees for campaign contributions they made to his preferred GOP politicians, an arrangement that would be unlawful.  Rep. Carolyn Maloney, D-N.Y., said in a statement late Monday that the House Committee on Oversight and Reform, which she chairs, would begin an investigation, saying that DeJoy may have lied to her committee under oath.  Maloney also urged the U.S. Postal Service Board of Governors to immediately suspend DeJoy, who, she said, "they never should have hired in the first place."  A spokesman for the Postal Service did not immediately respond to a request for comment.  Maloney's announcement came a day after The Washington Post reported allegations that DeJoy and his aides urged employees at his former North Carolina-based logistics company to write checks and attend fundraisers on behalf of Republican candidates.  DeJoy then defrayed the cost of those political contributions by boosting employee bonuses, two employees told The Post.  Although it can be permissible to encourage employees to make donations, reimbursing them for those contributions is a violation of North Carolina and federal election laws.  Such federal violations carry a five-year statute of limitations. There is no statute of limitations in North Carolina for felonies, including campaign finance violations.  Maloney said DeJoy faces "criminal exposure" not only if the allegations are true "but also for lying to our committee under oath."  Maloney was referring to DeJoy's testimony to the House Oversight and Reform Committee last month, when he forcefully denied that he had repaid executives for contributions they had made...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Under Fire for Filming 'MULAN' in Chinese City Running 'Concentration Camps'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/disney-under-fire-for-filming-mulan-in-chinas-xinjiang-province</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>121&amp;#8457;:  Weather service records hottest temperature on record in LA County!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailybulletin.com/2020/09/06/record-heat-sends-more-waves-of-people-to-la-countys-beaches-parks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailybulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic heatwave fueled multiple wildfires, triggered waves of power outages and threatened to return for another searing day on Labor Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As California burns, winds arrive and lights go out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c0aa17fff978e9c4768ee32679b8555c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAVER LAKE, Calif. (AP) — New wildfires ravaged bone-dry California during a scorching Labor Day weekend that saw a dramatic airlift of more than 200 people trapped by flames and ended with the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE:  Cardi B tells Candace Owens she's being 'pimped out by white men'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8707237/Cardi-B-hits-Candace-Owens-calling-embarrassment-Biden-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feud began on Sunday when Owens, 31, shared a clip of her on The Ben Shapiro Show, in which she said slammed Democratic nominee Joe Biden for taking part in an interview with Cardi B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has 71.1% Chance of Winning Election...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2020-election-forecast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Latest forecast of the 2020 presidential election between President Donald Trump and Joe Biden by Nate Silver’s FiveThirtyEight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France makes first arrest over horse mutilations...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/france-man-arrested-after-horses-killed-in-mysterious-ritual-like-mutilations-12066266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horses have been found with ears cut off, eyes gouged out and genitals mutilated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ Whale Theory for Tech Stock Surge Is Stirring Doubts...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-whale-theory-tech-stock-150545049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A report that SoftBank Group Corp. is making billions by using options to bet on technology stocks has stirred speculation the Japanese conglomerate could have been a driving force behind the rally -- but not everyone is convinced.Evidence suggests the kind of strategies pursued by institutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Summer of covid ends with health officials worried...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7940955a3288f661110bfb5d30a84b39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lost Summer of 2020 drew to a close Monday with many big Labor Day gatherings canceled across the U.S. and health authorities pleading with people to keep their distance from others so as not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot companions improve mental health and loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1436520/robots-loneliness-mental-health-older-people/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Calls Cops on 12-Year-Old Holding Toy Gun During ZOOM Class...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/09/07/zoom-nerf-gun-school-cops-kid-isaiah-elliott/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Isaiah Elliott also received a five-day suspension, but plans to transfer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mighty Mice' Stay Musclebound in Space, Boon for Astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/news/articles/2020-09-07/mighty-mice-stay-musclebound-in-space-boon-for-astronauts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Final Stretch, Biden Defends Lead Against Onslaught...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-final-stretch-biden-defends-lead-against-trumps-onslaught/ar-BB18KPHj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece to boost military amid tensions with neighbor Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e2451f1547136c0a75ebcd417e7b7fb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece will bolster its military with new arms, more personnel and by developing the country’s defense industry, the government said Monday, as a tense standoff with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hints at Vaccine 'Surprise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-hints-at-vaccine-surprise-as-biden-demands-transparency/ar-BB18NqWu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA reviews BOEING Dreamliner quality-control lapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/07/faa-reviews-boeing-dreamliner-quality-control-lapses-wsj-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The review could require enhanced or accelerated inspections for as many as about 900 Dreamliners delivered since 2011, the report said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record 2M acres burned so far this year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a168491f2cb25810c9e2a40316fe43a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHAVER LAKE, Calif. (AP) — Wildfires have burned more than 2 million acres in California this year, setting a state record even as crews battled dozens of growing blazes in sweltering temperatures...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters light fire near Portland police precinct...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Portland-Oregon-has-quiet-night-after-100-days-15547353.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) - A fire started outside a police precinct on Portland's north side resulted in about 15 arrests during protests Sunday night into Monday morning, police said.  Demonstrators protesting police brutality began marching at about 9 p.m. Sunday and stopped at the North Precinct Community Policing Center, the site of several volatile protests in recent months.  Officials warned demonstrators against entering the precinct property, saying they would be trespassing and subject to arrest.  Shortly after arriving, the crowd began chanting, among other things, "burn it down," police said in a statement. Some in the group lit a mattress on fire just after 10 p.m.  "Because it was not an immediate threat to life safety or structures, officers remained far back and did not engage," police said. "Another mattress was added to the fire, as was some yard debris. The larger fire began to send lit embers into the air."  Since Multnomah County has a burn ban in effect due to extremely dry conditions, firefighters came in to extinguish the blaze.  Demonstrators moved to another side of the building and blocked some streets until dispersed by police. Most protesters were gone by about 1 a.m. Monday.  "Officers discovered one arrestee was in possession of a glass jar filled with flammable liquid," police said. "Another had a bottle containing an accelerant and a slugging weapon known as a slung shot. Still another had an electronic control weapon ("stun gun") and a baton. Two arrestees had ballistic vests, including one, marked with the word "press," with rifle plates."  Most of those arrested were from Portland. Others were from San Francisco; Sacramento, California; Mesa, Arizona; and two from Vancouver, Washington.  Charges included interfering...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer's not over yet: Remote workers extend their vacation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/travel/summer-s-not-over-yet-remote-workers-extend-their-vacation-n1239474</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotels in summer hotspots usually go into hibernation once Labor Day rolls around. But this is 2020, and rules no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says Pentagon brass doesn't 'love' him...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-troops-love-him-even-if-pentagon-brass-doesn-t/ar-BB18NjeF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President goes on the attack in Labor Day speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-is-a-stupid-person-trump-goes-on-the-attack-in-labor-day-speech/ar-BB18NvOe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Respect for troops, military sacrifice becomes election friction point...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/pentagon-congress/2020/09/05/respect-for-troops-military-sacrifice-becomes-an-election-friction-point/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accusations that Trump insulted troops and wounded veterans will be a frequent talking point for election rivals this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postmaster General Accused of Pressuring Employees to Make Political Donations, Then Reimbursing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/06/politics/dejoy-gop-fundraiser-contributions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former employees of the company that US Postmaster General Louis DeJoy previously ran told The Washington Post they were pressured to donate to GOP candidates and then reimbursed through bonuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA moves on vaccines spark political worries...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/515210-fda-moves-on-vaccines-spark-political-worries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Public health officials are taking aim at the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), warning it should not bow to political pressure and clear a COVID-19 vaccine before one is ready.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divers pull human remains from Central Park pond...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/09/07/divers-pull-human-remains-from-central-park-pond/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Divers pulled a body out of a pond in Central Park on Labor Day afternoon, FDNY officials said. The human remains were taken out of The Pond around 12:30 p.m. near the park entrance at 59th Street …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Turns Into Furnace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/california-wildfires-extreme-heat-turns-state-into-a-furnace/ar-BB18NlFZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi killers have death sentences overturned in Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706159/Saudi-Arabia-convicts-eight-people-killing-Jamal-Khashoggi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia has convicted eight people of killing Jamal Khashoggi and has jailed them for up to 20 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy opens competition probe into APPLEGOOGLE cloud...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/09/07/italy-opens-competition-probe-into-apple-google-and-dropbox.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Competition and Market Authority said it launched six total investigations into the Google Drive service, Apple's iCloud and DropBox.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban Journalist Jailed for Christian Persecution Coverage: 'They're Going to Have to Kill Me'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/faith/2020/09/07/cuban-journalist-jailed-christian-persecution-coverage-theyre-going-have-kill-me/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo welcomed the release of Cuban journalist Roberto de Jesús Quiñones Haces from a year in prison on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Soviet Triple Agent Recruited New Spies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/leaked-kgb-manual-reveals-how-soviet-spies-recruited-in-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A KGB manual, published in English for the first time, reveals how Soviet spies infiltrated Western governments in an elaborate game of cat-and-mouse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran shatters 1904 heat record by 8 degrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/Some-spots-in-San-Francisco-could-break-100-15546642.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a light ocean breeze fails to develop along the Northern California coast on Sunday,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black families put trust in Black doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/During-pandemic-Black-families-put-trust-in-15547723.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Dr. Janice Bacon was exactly the person Kay McField hoped to talk...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange faces 18 new charges as he appears in court to fight US extradition...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/julian-assange-wikileaks-founder-arrested-over-18-new-allegations-as-he-appears-in-court-to-fight-us-extradition-12065979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new US indictment, filed in June, contains 18 charges and was handed to Assange moments before he appeared at the Old Bailey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bold hopes for antibody tests still unfulfilled...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd6b3e37ed51fe770b60c2ec5f8bc293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — At the height of the coronavirus lockdown, President Donald Trump and his top health advisers trumpeted a new test that would help Americans reclaim their lives — one that would...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line judge bombarded with death threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/tennis/article-8706299/US-Open-line-judge-struck-ball-hit-Novak-Djokovic-bombarded-death-threats-trolls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Open line judge hit in the throat with a ball by Novak Djokovic has been subjected to vile online abuse after fans of the world No 1 discovered her Instagram account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP IN SURPRISE CASH CRUNCH</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-election-campaign-fundraising-cash-eb9915fc-bbab-410f-8e99-fcca14a68024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of states Trump has to worry about has actually grown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President looms large over campaigns for control of Congress...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7ede31313f4988e76dc220bc5302afca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The battle for control of Congress is solidifying into a race about President Donald Trump, as Republicans hitch their fortunes to their party’s leader and Democrats position...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin critic Navalny out of coma, Berlin hospital says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-navalny-hospital/putin-critic-navalny-has-come-out-of-coma-berlin-hospital-says-idUSKBN25Y1E0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny has been removed from a medically induced coma and is responding to speech, Berlin's Charite hospital said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How NETFLIX Reed Hastings Rewrote The Hollywood Script...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/dawnchmielewski/2020/09/07/how-netflixs-reed-hastings-rewrote-the-hollywood-script/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant had upended show business long before the pandemic hit. But with a highly unusual management style, its billionaire founder has now positioned his entertainment juggernaut to prosper like few companies in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'kidnaps' five Indian citizens in disputed border territory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8706069/China-KIDNAPS-five-Indian-citizens-disputed-border-territory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The five missing men are from the Indian state of Arunachal Pradesh, which China claims as South Tibet, and the Indian Army said it had made representations to the People's Liberation Army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest trend in RV'ing: Getting way off the grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/09/07/success/boondocking-rvs-dry-camping/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recreational vehicle makers often boast how their RVs and trailers can feel just like home. Besides their cleverly packaged bathrooms and kitchenettes, when you park your rig at a campground you can find something else that will make you feel you never left home: neighbors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organized labor staging political resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/515345-organized-labor-staging-political-resurgence-for-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unions, with only a few exceptions, are going all out for Joe Biden this fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCHESTER: Naked protesters demand action after Daniel Prude's killing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e04d590aa95eb033a7e5a50dad3df4e6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROCHESTER, N.Y. (AP) — Naked except for “spit hoods” in a reference to the killing of Daniel Prude, several protesters sat outside Rochester's police headquarters Monday morning to push for police...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Claim DISNEY Covering Up Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/workers-reveal-disney-is-covering-up-its-covid-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers and their worried spouses reveal to The Daily Beast that Disney is not only underreporting its COVID cases but clearing COVID-positive employees to return to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte Pardons U.S. Marine Who Killed Trans...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200907-philippines-president-pardons-us-marine-in-transgender-killing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines president pardons US marine in transgender killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third-party voters imperil Trump margins in battlegrounds...</title>
      <link>https://justthenews.com/politics-policy/elections/third-party-voters-were-major-factor-trumps-2016-victory-how-could-they</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;justthenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a warning sign" for the Trump campaign, said pollster Scott Rasmussen. "Maybe it's a yellow flag as opposed to a red flag. And it is one of many things that could change in the three states that shocked everybody: Pennsylvania Michigan and Wisconsin."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
