<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: ISIS militants break out of prisonafter bombing by Turkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/isis-turkey-syria-prison-bombing-kurds-sdf-a9152536.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stinging Blow...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-accountant-told-appeals-court-142207180.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump, under siege from House Democrats weighing impeachment, suffered a stinging blow as a federal appeals court upheld a subpoena ordering his accountants to provide Congress with his financial records.The ruling, by a divided three-judge panel of the U.S. Court of Appeals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEADED TO THE SUPREME COURT?</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7563373/Federal-appeals-court-turns-Trumps-attempt-block-Democrats-getting-tax-returns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An administration official with knowledge of the case said Friday that Trump will 'in all likelihood be headed to the Supreme Court for [legal] relief.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Police Response at Capitol Metro After Stabbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.popville.com/2019/10/huge-police-emergency-response-at-capitol-south-metro-confirmed-stabbing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popville.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo by Max Max writes at 1:01pm "What's going on??" From Metro Transit Police: "Confirmed stabbing. Police, medics o/s.  Capitol South Station: MTPD, MPD, USCP &amp; DC EMS o/s responding to a confirmed stabbing. Details will follow. The station is CLOSED at this time. Trains on Blue/Orang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incarcerated Felons Could Be Allowed To Vote In DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/local/305/2019/10/10/769086866/incarcerated-felons-could-be-allowed-to-vote-in-bill-moving-through-d-c-council</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maine, Vermont and Puerto Rico currently allow residents in prison for having committed felonies to vote in elections. And D.C. may not be far behind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprising benefits of trash talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20191010-the-surprising-benefits-and-risks-of-trash-talk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Channelling your inner Muhammad Ali might not always be as reckless as it sounds. Zaria Gorvett explains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter Of US Companies Now Allowing Employees To Work 4-Day Work Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/10/10/4-day-work-week-new-employees/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With unemployment at historic lows, many companies around the country are attracting employees with all kinds of perks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanism At US Naval Academy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theamericanconservative.com/dreher/satanism-at-the-us-naval-academy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanconservative.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One Christian midshipman calls for 'civil dialogue' in response. A USNA source says, 'Dialogue with Satanism? Seriously?'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Walking slowly is sign of aging fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7563395/People-walk-slowly-45-higher-risks-dementia-study-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duke University researchers found that the same people who were already walking slowly at age 45 looked older, had early signs of dementia, and had scored lower on mental tests at age three.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon deploying 3,000 troops, advanced equipment to Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/11/us-deploying-3000-troops-advanced-equipment-saudi-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. military is significantly increasing troop deployments to Saudi Arabia, the Pentagon said Friday, announcing that 3,000 American personnel — including two fighter squadrons and an air expeditionary wing — will be sent to the Persian Gulf nation, as well as advanced missile defense systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE 'WHISTLEBLOWERS' CONTACTING CONGRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/more-potential-whistleblowers-are-contacting-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first two officials who came forward about the president’s pressure campaign on Ukraine seem to be just the beginning, according to Hill sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Slow walkers more likely to get sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/walking-slowly-aging-brain-body-sick-later-study-a9151976.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fonda arrested in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/jane-fonda-arrested-protesting-dc-1247035</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress was demonstrating on the Capitol with the group Oil Change International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 83&amp;#176; To 13&amp;#176;: Extreme Temp Drop In Denver Second Largest On Record!</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/10/11/denver-weather-largest-day-change-on-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The official temperature in Denver dropped 70 degrees from Wednesday to Thursday. That change just missed the record for the largest 2 day temperature drop in Denver's history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine envoy shows up for depo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/470b8da7d0da439686342904906c5f43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former U.S. Ambassador to Ukraine Marie Yovanovitch told lawmakers Friday that President Donald Trump pressured the State Department to oust her from her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100,000 evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0bca0959ed7a45939b7c922608c3dcc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A wildfire raged out of control along the northern edge of Los Angeles early Friday, forcing thousands of people from their homes as firefighters battled flames from the air and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Giuliani's relationship with arrested men subject of investigation...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/rudy-giulianis-relationship-arrested-men-subject-criminal-investigation/story?id=66212654</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The business relationship between Rudy Giuliani and men charged in a campaign finance scheme is a subject of the ongoing criminal investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen girls cry tears of joy at Trump rally --  that looks more like a Justin Bieber concert!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10112113/donald-trump-rally-minneapolis-minnesota-us-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s rally in Minneapolis has turned heads after people pointed out that it looked more like a Justin Bieber concert rather than a political meeting. Teenage girls and boys were see…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR IN RED SEA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10111909/iranian-oil-tanker-hit-by-explosion-near-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Iranian oil tanker was today hit by two rockets in a suspected terrorist act, according to reports. The huge blast struck the vessel belonging to the National Iranian Oil Company 60 miles from t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda moving to DC with plans to get arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/10/11/jane-fonda-steps-up-political-activism-moves-to-dc-for-four-months-to-stage-civil-obedience-rallies-fire-drill-fridays-at-the-capitol-over-climate-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two time Oscar winner Jane Fonda is once again trail-blazing with her legendary political activism. She’s moved to Washington, DC for the next four months to help stage civil disobedience ral…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU ambassador to testify in impeachment inquiry, defying State Dept...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/e-u-ambassador-sondland-testify-impeachment-inquiry-defying-state-department-n1064966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorneys for Gordon Sondland said he would speak to House Democrats, but that he would not turn over documents viewed as property of the State Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says oil tanker struck by missiles off Saudi Arabia...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/55f68b50763c40eeb25ee19027573d86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Iran said Friday two missiles struck one of its oil tankers traveling through the Red Sea off the coast of Saudi Arabia, a mysterious assault not immediately corroborated that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELLEN LIKES BUSH!</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/10/11/why-ellen-degeneres-friendship-with-george-w-bush-is-so-controversial/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s a list of stars DeGeneres has banned from her show because they had different beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forces push deeper into Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2beb641ae63a4a4fb07e77cfa962d68f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AKCAKALE, Turkey (AP) — Turkish forces pushed deeper into northeastern Syria on Friday, the third day of Ankara's offensive against U.S.-allied Syrian Kurdish fighters, as casualties mounted,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan State University bans 'racially, culturally, or ethnically based' costumes for Halloween...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/michigan-state-u-bans-mustaches-sombreros-aliens-in-orange-suits-mexicans-japanese-hypersexualized-racism-for-halloween/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students at Michigan State University are getting an education in how they can avoid offending people with culturally inappropriate Halloween costumes in what’s becoming a new tradition that undermines the university’s own identity. The unsolicited advice on what to wear on fright night appeared on message boards in campus residences this week to help students …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witches Having Resurgence...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/10/11/style/pam-grossman-witch-feminism.html?emc=rss&amp;partner=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pam Grossman, author and host of the popular “The Witch Wave” podcast, said witches are having a resurgence among feminists who want authority over their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Not Weinstein Incident That May Bring Down NBC Execs. It's Everything Else...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/opinion/its-not-the-weinstein-incident-that-may-bring-down-nbc-execs-its-everything-else/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current unfolding of NBC News (mis)handling of sexual misconduct within its ranks is, without question, the biggest media story of the year (at least one that doesn't involve President Donald</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clock ticks as SPACEX builds craft for NASA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/news/clock-ticks-as-spacex-builds-craft-for-nasa/article_91b21da7-8fa4-577a-9efc-18f0d2c4f615.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two weeks ago, the head of NASA seemed sick of waiting for SpaceX and Boeing Co. to finish developing the capsules that are supposed to carry U.S. astronauts to and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest of Giuliani associates ensnares 'Congressman 1'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bd7b2b04b101440e9a5559b9501e24b4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Businessmen with ties to Rudy Giuliani lobbied a U.S. congressman in 2018 for help ousting the American ambassador to Ukraine around the same time they committed to raising money...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: Will Smith 'GEMINI MAN' Ossified Bore...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/10/gemini-man-review-will-smith-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Save your money and wait for it any minute now on late night cable TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will America Catch 'PARASITE' Fever?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2019/10/parasite-movie-bong-joon-ho</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bong Joon-Ho’s brilliant genre mash-up has already generated Oscar buzz and been a hit around the world. It’s not what you’re expecting, no matter what you’re expecting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Harry Styles 'LIGHTS UP' soulful, enigmatic return...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2019/oct/11/harry-styles-lights-up-review-soulful-enigmatic-return</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former One Direction member’s second solo single is laced with surprises and sounds refreshingly like nothing his British male pop peers are doing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURN OUT: 4 In 10 Close To 'Breaking Point' At Work...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/perpetual-stress-four-in-ten-adults-close-to-breaking-point-at-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 2,000 adults finds that the modern employee is more stressed than ever, and a significant portion feel like they just can't take it anymore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM appeals direct to employees as strike losses pile up...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-autos-labor/gm-appeals-direct-to-employees-as-strike-losses-pile-up-idUSKBN1WQ1O1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Motors Co took the unusual step of appealing directly to employees in a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA WILDFIRES RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7562033/Terrifying-footage-shows-drivers-rushing-escape-huge-wildfires-burning-California.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shocking videos show residents driving along the freeway as the massive flames rise up on both sides of them in Saddleridge, Sylmar near Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court rejects president's appeal of House subpoena for his tax returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/11/appeals-court-rejects-trump-appeal-of-subpoena-for-tax-returns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subpoena was issued earlier this year to Trump's accountants at Mazars USA by the House Committee on Oversight and Reform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Turkish invasion raises fears of Islamic State prison break...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f366e0aeaa1349769cbc0a73bbe02c26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — In the sprawling al-Hol camp in northeastern Syria, Islamic State wives and widows have set up special courts, stabbed to death at least two people accused of apostasy and wielded...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why John Roberts is sweating...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/870886/why-john-roberts-sweating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If legal battles crucial to Trump's survival reach the the Supreme Court, the chief justice may cast the deciding vote</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANCHESTER: Five knifed in shopping center stabbing rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10114078/anti-terror-cops-arndale-centre-evacuated-stabbing-manchester/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three people have been stabbed in a knife rampage at a shopping centre in Manchester today. Anti-terror cops are investigating after terrified families described a knifeman “running and lungi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds space fireballs that crashed into Earth; Experts rule out meteor shower...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/470690-mysterious-unexplained-fireballs-chile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a barrage of fireballs recently rained down on Chile, many assumed it was a meteor shower and moved on. However, analysis has since dismissed that theory and experts are struggling to explain the unidentified falling objects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda moving to DC for four months with plan to get arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-10-10/jane-fonda-climate-change-protest-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Fonda is moving to Washington to protest the lack of U.S. action on global warming. She talks about climate change, activism and being 81 in Hollywood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beverly Hills Billion-Dollar Fire Sale: Inside Implosion of Historic Real Estate Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-greed-derailed-a-billion-dollar-real-estate-deal-mountain-1246029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How did the expansive property, known as The Mountain, list for 10 figures and end up selling for $100,000 in a Pomona courtroom? Infighting, a Hollywood wannabe and a big bluff caused America's all-time trophy property to end up in legal chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First pilotless Black Hawk helicopter capable of 172mph speeds to launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/first-pilotless-black-hawk-helicopter-20556519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S-70 has already gone through 54.5 hours of flight testing without a pilot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside world's most elite sex club...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/inside-theworlds-most-elitesexclubwhere-hollywood-20554496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sntcm is dubbed the 'world's most elite sex club' because of the A-listers and super-rich members it attracts. Take a look inside the notorious nightclub here</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfires break out overnight in Los Angeles area... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/11/us/gallery/california-wildfires-oct-2019/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Saddleridge Fire, which started Thursday and exploded to 4,600 acres by early Friday, has destroyed an undetermined number of homes and led to mandatory evacuations in and near Los Angeles' Porter Ranch neighborhood, the Los Angeles Fire Department said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greta Snubbed for Peace Prize...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10113003/nobel-peace-prize-greta-thunberg-snubbed-ethiopian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GRETA Thunberg has been snubbed for the Nobel Peace Prize which has instead been awarded to Ethiopia’s Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed for ending the 20-year Eritrea conflict. Bookies had suggested…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stalking suspect studied pop idol's pupil images online to find her location...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/stalking-suspect-allegedly-studied-pop-idol-s-pupil-images-online-n1064916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man allegedly studied reflections of the woman's pupils in photos on social media and using Google Street View to find where she lived and what train stations she used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Senate likelier to remove than think...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-Senate-is-likelier-to-remove-Trump-after-14514050.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the House of Representatives builds momentum to impeach President Donald Trump, conventional wisdom holds that the constitutionally required two-thirds vote in the Senate to remove him would be impossible.  This conventional wisdom is wrong.  While getting rid of the president this way remains far from certain, it's more likely than most observers will admit. And it's becoming a stronger possibility day by day as Trump's foreign policy stumbles remind GOP senators that speaking out against the president doesn't have to be political suicide.  Historically inclined naysayers cite the acquittals of our only two impeached presidents as support for the argument that Trump won't be removed. Those examples, both of which ended with the commander in chief beating the charges against him and serving out his full term, on first blush do appear to bolster that case.  Andrew Johnson's experience in particular astounds to this day. After that president's egregious behavior and manifest unfitness for office got him impeached by the Republican-dominated House in 1868, the Senate failed to remove him from office - by one vote. That result came despite the GOP holding a greater-than-two-thirds majority in the Senate.  The wrong lesson, however, can be taken from Johnson's nonconviction. Senators allowed the president to remain in place partly because they suspected the law that the president had violated to prompt his impeachment, the Tenure of Office Act, itself stood on particularly shaky ground. (It was, in fact, later ruled unconstitutional.) Other articles of impeachment against Johnson included "crimes" like speaking ill of Congress in public - which may very well have contravened a lingering norm from the early days of the republic but fell very well short of warranting immediate ejection from the presidency.  It's hard to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers kept refusing to let him have sex with their animals. So he sought revenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Farmers-kept-refusing-to-let-him-have-sex-with-14514093.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For well over a year, two mysteries consumed a peaceful New Jersey community. There were the strange letters that showed up in the mailboxes of local barns, asking about the possibility of forming a "sexual relationship" with horses, cows or other large animals. And then, there were the homemade tire-slashing devices that farmers kept finding in their driveways, or near the entrances to rural farm roads.  Now, authorities in Sussex County, New Jersey, are saying that both were the work of the same man, Richard Decker, who lashed out by harassing people who refused to let him have sex with their farm animals.  The 31-year-old was arrested Oct. 3, according to the New Jersey Herald. Prosecutors said at a Wednesday detention hearing that since August 2018, he had been sending letters and emails detailing his request to farms, stables and horse boarding facilities throughout Sussex County, located in the northernmost point of the state. Unsurprisingly, many of the recipients were not thrilled to learn than an adult man was interested in having a sexual relationship with their livestock.  Decker didn't take the rejection well, authorities said on Wednesday. He left messages harassing the property owners who had turned him down - in one instance threatening to beat a man's wife with a wooden stick - and wrote negative online reviews of their businesses. The 31-year-old also allegedly kept a stash of homemade metal tire deflation spikes in his bedroom, and would plant them in the driveways of farmers who angered him.  In January, police in Decker's hometown of Vernon Township, New Jersey, issued a warning to "anyone who has farm-like property" after several residents found that their tires had been destroyed by homemade spikes, which are also known as caltrops. The department's Facebook post was deluged with comments from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Satanic Temple HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/10/10/inside-the-satanic-temples-salem-headquarters/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Satanic Temple may make headlines across the country for their highly confrontational political displays, but it calls Salem home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With less to lose, will retiring Republicans desert Trump?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a4848dc015e547d0b9db1adeee3735c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Retiring congressional Republicans are a natural group to watch for defectors as Democrats' impeachment inquiry of President Donald Trump builds steam. But they're not crumbling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns jailed militants may escape amid Turkey's Syria operation...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191011085352-l92f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-PUTIN (URGENT):Putin warns jailed militants may escape amid Turkey's Syria operation - Ifax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terminally-ill scientist to 'transform' into world's first full cyborg...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/terminally-ill-scientist-transform-worlds-20559021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Peter Scott-Morgan, 61, was diagnosed with motor neurone disease two years ago, but instead of accepting his fate he decided to challenge what it meant to be human</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Cancels All Media Appearances for Rest of China Trip...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/11/nba-nixes-media-availability-for-rest-of-china-trip/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHANGHAI, China – Apparently the NBA is going to go 0-for-China in terms of media availability on this trip that has gone from highly anticipated to highly controversial. Both the Brooklyn Nets and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Shops, Spotty Phones, Rotting Fish...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/dark-shops-spotty-phones-rotting-224608892.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The first thing you notice is clearly the darkness.I was showering late Wednesday, shampoo in my eyes and American Horror Story playing on my phone so loud that my husband couldn’t hear my shouts for a light. I had just become one of the millions of people to have lost power in the biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela gas shortages stall ambulances in their tracks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8c1402829d8943c89aadb72d95758cdf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN CRISTOBAL, Venezuela (AP) — Ambulances have become the latest casualty of Venezuela's unraveling political and economic crisis, struggling to fuel up and speed away to emergencies as gasoline...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALI NIGHTMARE:  Winds move south, may force new power outages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5fe83d4daed64b5daa67ef5e5d81a936</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Hot, dry winds sweeping into Southern California raised concerns that the region's largest utility could widen power shut-offs Friday to prevent its equipment from sparking...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpatriotic? Whistleblowers have been speaking up, and suffering consequences, from the beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/unpatriotic-whistleblowers-have-been-speaking-up-and-suffering-the-consequences-from-the-beginning/ar-AAItELA?li=AA4Zoy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighting foam leaves toxic legacy in drinking water near military bases...</title>
      <link>https://www.richmond.com/news/national-world/ap/firefighting-foam-leaves-toxic-legacy-in-drinking-water-near-military/article_d16e4a2b-0ffa-5942-951f-49e14860eb49.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.richmond.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. — It was a Sunday tradition at Bethany Slavic Missionary Church. After morning services, Florin Ciuriuc joined the line of worshippers waiting to fill their jugs with gallons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Pompeo aide steps down...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/all/senior-pompeo-aide-steps-down-amid-impeachment-inquiry-n1064866</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Career diplomat P. Michael McKinley, who served as ambassador to Afghanistan, Colombia, Brazil and Peru, has told his colleagues he is resigning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence, economy worry many Mexicans, but they try to keep faith in populist president...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/violence-economy-worry-many-mexicans-but-they-try-to-keep/article_34c55951-04f2-504e-9ef6-0254b5af13df.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUAN ALDAMA, Mexico — The human exodus here reached new heights over the summer as entire families hightailed it out of this once booming agricultural valley. They headed north in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As abortion opposition rallies, some activists taking aim at in vitro fertilization, frozen embryos...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-abortion-ivf-frozen-embryos-naperville-20191008-sw2dpa4cozey7fquf6fq4nxx3i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some call embryos the latest frontier of the anti-abortion movement, a crusade that’s growing momentum as fertility technology progresses and some of its consequences become more understood. To those who are fervently against abortion, these embryos are its tiniest victims -- just as worthy of preservation as a fetus of any gestational age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham dishes on Trump in hoax calls with Russians...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/10/lindsey-graham-trump-hoax-call-043991</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO-like helicopter dubbed 'Super Great White Shark' unleashed by China...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ufo-like-helicopter-dubbed-super-20556409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rotorcraft garnered huge attention online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS SCRUTINIZE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/10/10/politics/giuliani-fruman-parnas-finances/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani's financial dealings with two associates indicted on campaign finance-related charges are under scrutiny by investigators overseeing the case, law enforcement officials briefed on the matter said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Impeachment now inevitable?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/10/impeachment-now-inevitable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russiagate consumed the first three years of Trump's presidency. "Ukrainegate" and impeachment give promise of dominating the fourth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  BIDEN WORKED WITH WHISTLEBLOWER</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/joe-biden-worked-with-whistleblower-when-he-was-vice-president-officials-reveal  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2020 Democratic candidate with whom the CIA whistleblower had a "professional" tie is Joe Biden, according to intelligence officers and former White House officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO IS PAYING RUDY?</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/We-have-no-idea-who-is-paying-Rudy-Giuliani-14506916.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani is not the secretary of state. In fact, he has no official position in President Donald Trump's Cabinet or administration. Yet he is traveling the world holding himself out as a U.S. government operative, engaging in some unknown amount of "unofficial" diplomacy and insisting his work is not only officially sanctioned by the president but also assisted by the State Department. The president's "private lawyer" is not charging Trump for his services, but he and his law firm are known to have dozens of clients - including foreign entities - who are paying for whatever services they think Giuliani can provide for them.  That is a very convenient setup for Giuliani - but it leaves the public in the dark about the wealthy special interests who might be subsidizing his gratis work for Trump - or for whom he might actually be working while invoking Trump's name and that of the State Department. Because Giuliani is not officially a federal employee, he can sidestep ethics obligations that would require transparency behind the foreign or domestic interests who are paying him.  Giuliani appears to have spearheaded Trump's efforts to convince the Ukrainian president to open an investigation into Trump's political rivals. Text messages released by Congress also show he was steering U.S. policy in Ukraine in a direction that alarmed career State Department officials, who thought it harmed U.S. interests there. Giuliani himself has boasted that he effectively had official imprimatur for what might appear to have been freelance diplomacy with Kiev: Appearing on CBS's "Face the Nation" on Sept. 29, Giuliani said about his outreach to Ukraine: "I did not do this on my own. I did it at the request of the State Department, and I have all of the text messages to prove it."  Despite playing such an important role in U.S....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National security officials raised alarms about Ukraine policy before and after Trump call... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Several-national-security-officials-raised-alarms-14510135.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - At least four national security officials were so alarmed by the Trump administration's attempts to pressure Ukraine for political purposes that they raised concerns with a White House lawyer both before and immediately after President Donald Trump's July 25 call with that country's president, according to U.S. officials and other people familiar with the matter.  The nature and timing of the previously undisclosed discussions with National Security Council legal adviser John Eisenberg indicate that officials were delivering warnings through official White House channels earlier than previously understood - including before the call that precipitated a whistleblower complaint and the impeachment inquiry of the president.  At the time, the officials were unnerved by the removal in May of the U.S. ambassador to Ukraine; subsequent efforts by Trump's lawyer Rudy Giuliani to promote Ukraine-related conspiracies; as well as signals in meetings at the White House that Trump wanted the new government in Kiev to deliver material that might be politically damaging to Democratic presidential candidate Joe Biden.  Those concerns soared in the call's aftermath, officials said. Within minutes, senior officials including national security adviser John Bolton were being pinged by subordinates about problems with what the president had said to his Ukrainian counterpart, Volodymyr Zelensky. Bolton and others scrambled to obtain a rough transcript that was already being "locked down" on a highly classified computer network.  "When people were listening to this in real time there were significant concerns about what was going on - alarm bells were kind of ringing," said one person familiar with the sequence of events inside the White House, who, like others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive matter....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rick Perry subpoenaed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/10/democrats-subpoena-rick-perry-for-documents-in-impeachment-inquiry-000280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton For Congress?!</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-nita-lowey-reelection-2020-20191010-cpu4x77l2vbgdb2oxpihxrpd3i-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Westchester Democrats want the Clinton machine back in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV Study Tracks 'Attentiveness' of Viewers via In-Home Data Collection...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/carols-second-act-has-attentive-viewing-new-series-1246901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS comedy's audience had its eyes on the screen more than any other series premiere, according to a company that tracks viewing habits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POSE' Star Billy Porter to Play Fairy Godmother in 'CINDERELLA' Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/billy-porter-talks-join-sonys-cinderella-1244953</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Emmy winner and 'Pose' star will join Camila Cabello, who is tackling the titular princess role.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders' heart attack puts his campaign in uncharted territory...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sanders-heart-attack-puts-campaign-080000425.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders has so far muscled past questions about his age by keeping a grueling campaign schedule, bouncing between ice cream socials, private meetings, rallies or town halls in a single day -- with aides decades his junior struggling to keep up.But the 78-year-old’s heart attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi confronts decision on vote... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pelosi-confronts-decision-impeachment-vote-080000147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump is pushing House Speaker Nancy Pelosi to hold a formal vote on impeachment, a move that would change the politics of the probe more than its legal standing.Trump this week escalated his fight against the Democratic-led investigation of his dealings with Ukraine with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charged with federal campaign finance violations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9125e9ccd894965bbf2860100366779</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Two Florida businessmen tied to President Donald Trump's lawyer and the Ukraine impeachment investigation were charged Thursday with federal campaign finance...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Low IQ Linked To Greater Risk Of Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/low-iq-associated-with-greater-risk-of-suicide-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have found a connection between low IQ scores in adolescence and a greater risk of suicide or attempted suicide during adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire's comments about 'getting into a girl's pants' spark backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fisher-investments-ken-fisher-billionaires-sexist-comments-spark-outrage-getting-into-a-girls-pants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is why we haven't had our #MeToo moment," said one female wealth manager who heard Ken Fisher's remarks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUTAGE OUTRAGE: PG&amp;E Egged By Frustrated Resident...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/10/10/pge-office-in-oroville-gets-egged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PG&amp;E is taking a lot of heat as frustration mounts over the Public Safety Power Shutoffs that have hit a good swath of Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  How the NBA censored me on American soil...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/10/how-the-nba-censored-me-on-american-soil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I’ve been an NBA fanatic as long as I can remember. Growing up, I rooted for the Minnesota Timberwolves. I was there for the ups — who can forget that almost magical 2004 season? — and all of the d…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities Banning New Fast-Food Drive-Throughs...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2019/10/10/765789694/why-u-s-cities-are-banning-new-fast-food-drive-throughs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the bans aim to curb emissions and protect pedestrians. The bans are also sometimes touted as a way to help fight obesity, but past studies suggest they don't have that effect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for Chelsea?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/10/nita-lowey-congresswoman-people-think-chelsea-clinton-groomed-replace-retire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Democratic Rep. Nita Lowey announced she will not seek reelection in 2020 in a district where Chelsea Clinton is reportedly considering a run.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
