<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau Faces Growing Doubts Over Refugee Policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trudeau-faces-growing-doubts-over-canadas-refugee-policy-1533288601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau’s open-arms policy on refugees is facing pushback at home, according to a new poll published Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Potential Kobach Candidacy, Kansas Faces Another Lurch to Right...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/in-potential-kobach-candidacy-kansas-faces-another-lurch-to-the-right/17744686/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOPEKA, Kan. — The evolution of the Kansas Republican Party mirrors that of the national party, a rightward shift from the moderation of Dwight D. Eisenhower to the mainstream conservatism of Bob Dole to the small-government absolutism of former Gov. Sam Brownback and Wichita-based Koch Industries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JULY JOBS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/02/july-jobs-seen-strong-but-wage-growth-could-again-disappoint.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;July's employment report is expected to show solid job growth of 190,000, but wage growth is expected to remain on the tepid side, at about the same pace as last quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENSIONS REACH NEW HEIGHTS...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/400161-trump-takes-us-versus-them-media-war-to-new-heights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When CNN’s Jim Acosta was booed and cursed at a campaign rally for President Trump this week, many political observers said it exemplified how much the media environment has changed under the current administration — and that is a sign of what’s t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump: Entire family has received 'white powder' in mail...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/400213-eric-trump-several-members-of-my-family-have-received-white</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's son Eric Trump on Thursday said that all the members of his family have had "white powder" mailed to their house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports agents scrutinizing clients' old tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Sports-agents-are-scrutinizing-their-clients-old-13127851.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As old social media posts have resurfaced and prominent athletes have been forced into public soul-baring in recent weeks, sports agents have undertaken emergency Twitter work, carefully excavating, scrutinizing and, if need be, deleting youthful indiscretions and ignorance. Agents across multiple sports say recent headlines have prompted athletes to delve into their Twitter histories, searching for anything offensive or controversial that might have been sitting forgotten and unnoticed. One NBA team even reached out to representatives of all its players this week, according to an agent, urging them "to do a deep dive" through social media histories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump staffs up Mideast team for peace plan rollout...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/099069cecd5244b8b766fa77e264b58b/Trump-staffs-up-Mideast-team-for-peace-plan-rollout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. officials say the Trump administration is staffing up a Middle East policy team at the White House in anticipation of unveiling its long awaited but largely</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Tweets A Sword Against Short Sellers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/for-teslas-elon-musk-twitter-is-sword-against-short-sellers-1533216249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk’s extraordinary use of Twitter to battle short sellers has often been followed by a jump in Tesla’s stock price, hurting shorts in the process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freed From Gilded Cage, Famed Saudi Investor Returns to Markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/freed-from-a-gilded-cage-a-famed-saudi-investor-returns-to-the-markets/17743666/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia’s best-known investor is back in the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living near busy road can seriously harm heart...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/living-near-a-busy-road-can-seriously-harm-your-heart-3pc5rvph6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People living near busy roads have dangerously swollen hearts, similar to those seen in the early stages of heart failure, in the clearest physical sign of the risk of air pollution. People with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweaty T-shirt turn on? At pheromone party, singles match using only noses...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Does-my-sweaty-T-shirt-turn-you-on-At-a-13127553.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As I walked into a party on a recent Thursday night, I was self-conscious in a way I'd never been before: What if no one likes the way I smell? It's summer in Washington, D.C., so no one smells all that great. But this night was different from your average gathering of sweaty bodies. I was about to enter a pheromone party, where strangers would be inhaling my scent via a T-shirt I'd been wearing. It's a fun if strange experiment. Singles are meeting in lots of odd ways these days. Perhaps sampling each other's DNA the way you might go wine-tasting makes more sense than swiping through photos on a dating app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot timebomb: Human extinction...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/720731/sex-robot-doll-japan-extinct-birth-rate-web-clock-endangered-species</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmland Values Hit Record Despite Trade Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/02/u-s-farmland-values-hit-record-as-trade-fears-get-shrugged-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Farmland Values Hit a Record Despite Trade Fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence on streets of Iran as police use tear gas on protesters; 'Death to dictator!'</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6022673/Violence-streets-Iran-police-use-tear-gas-furious-protesters.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests have broken out in a number of Iranian cities this week over the dramatic drop of the country's currency and other economic problems ahead of the imposition of renewed US sanctions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKE PHONES FROM CHILDREN UNDER 11...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6021463/Parents-NOT-children-mobile-phones-secondary-school-psychiatrist-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice chairman of the Royal College of Psychologists said UK government guidance on when to give smartphones to children would help parents stand their ground.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Age author Marianne Williamson 'looking into' presidential run...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/02/marianne-williamson-new-age-author-looking-into-presidential-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Williamson’s interest in a potential presidential bid is a sign of how broad the Democratic field in 2020 might be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON LOWEST TAX BILL IN YEARS -- AS PROFITS SOAR!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/amazon-now-pay-even-less-13023482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The online retailer paid £4.6million last year – or just over 6% on profits of £72million – despite the firm’s UK sales soaring by a quarter to £8.8billion in 2017</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson compares jail to Guantanamo Bay claiming inmates threw 'excrement' at him...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/720883/tommy-robinson-fox-news-tucker-carlson-news-appeal-free-prison-guantanamo-bay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELL ON EARTH: Europe heatwave turns killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/720801/weather-forecast-uk-heatwave-london-spain-portugal-bbc-met-office-warning-neqa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused of crippling business...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6021101/Theyre-taking-fools-Amazon-nearly-halved-corporation-tax-bill-just-4-5million.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite soaring sales of close to £2 billion, Amazon yesterday revealed it had paid just £4.5 million in corporation tax last year - down from £7.4 million the previous year – when its sales were actually lower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethnic cleansing makes comeback; Muslims vanish...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/ethnic-cleansing-makes-a-comeback--in-china/2018/08/02/55f73fa2-9691-11e8-810c-5fa705927d54_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijng’s crackdown on its Uighur minority is setting a new standard for oppression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Jr. compares Democratic platform to Nazis...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/02/donald-trump-jr-democrats-nazis-platform-760569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's oldest son made the comments at an event for conservative commentator Dinesh D'Souza's new film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATMs go cardless...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/chase-atms-go-cardless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bank now offers phone-based withdrawals at “nearly all” of its ATMs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Gets Approval to Disclose Accuser Emails...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/weinstein-rape-accuser-emails-1202893662/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bankruptcy judge gave permission on Thursday for Harvey Weinstein’s attorneys to include 40 emails from an anonymous rape accuser in a motion to dismiss his criminal case. Judge Mary Walrat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper blasts NFL for censoring like curse word...</title>
      <link>https://uproxx.com/sports/big-sean-colin-kaepernick-madden-19-yg-big-bank-response/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uproxx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Sean claims his Colin Kaepernick line in ’Madden 19’ was removed without his consent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Forces All Religious Buildings to Fly Communist Flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/08/02/china-forces-all-religious-buildings-to-fly-communist-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Global Times derided critics in the West for condemning a new initiative forcing all religious buildings to fly China's red flag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MADDEN' game scrubs Kaepernick from song lyrics...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/08/02/new-madden-game-scrubs-colin-kaepernick-from-song-lyrics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new Madden video game has one very curious omission. The soundtrack contains the song Big Bank from YG. The lyrics include a variety of words that were scrubbed from the song, including profani…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birds learn 'languages' by eavesdropping...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/birds-learn-another-language-eavesdropping-neighbors-180707881.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — For birds, understanding neighborhood gossip about an approaching hawk or brown snake can mean the difference between life or death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for threatening to 'feed lead' to Scalise...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/article_20e24a6a-9695-11e8-86e0-037f5f86d9a1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities arrested an upstate New York man accused of leaving menacing voicemails on the office phones of House Majority Whip Steve Scalise, R-Jefferson, and another congressman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#METOO HITS MONASTERY: High-ranking monk 'coerced nuns into sex'...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/society/article/2158046/china-investigates-high-ranking-buddhist-monk-accused-coercing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abbot of the Longquan Temple on the outskirts of Beijing denies allegations, saying they stemmed from ‘fabricated material’ and ‘distorted facts’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War on Sharks: Rogue fleets plunder top predator...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/environment/article215598705.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What you didn’t see on Discovery Channel’s Shark Week: A new investigation shows poachers might be winning in the battle to keep shark fishing alive. Despite regulations in places like the Central American Pacific, shark fin exports have increased and some species face extinction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Russian spy' working at US embassy in Moscow had 'full access' to secrets...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/aug/02/suspected-russian-spy-us-embassy-moscow-secret-service</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: Russian is understood to have had full access to secret data during decade at embassy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of phone call? Conversations lose ground to chat apps...</title>
      <link>http://www.theweek.co.uk/95553/phone-calls-losing-ground-to-chat-apps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theweek.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of minutes Brits spend talking on mobiles drops by 2.5 billion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modified mosquitoes eliminate city-wide virus for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2175827-modified-mosquitoes-wipe-out-whole-citys-dengue-for-the-first-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-dengue mosquitoes have eliminated the virus from Townsville, Australia - the first successful large-scale use of modified mosquitoes to wipe out disease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rape claim against BACKSTREET BOY Nick Carter under review by LA prosecutors...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/ny-news-nick-carter-rape-case-under-review-20180802-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles prosecutors are reviewing a rape claim against Backstreet Boys singer Nick Carter for possible charges, a DA spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest-ever Jerusalem Pride Parade under heavy security...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/thousands-march-in-largest-ever-jerusalem-pride-parade-under-heavy-security/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid anger over gay parental surrogacy rights, nation-state law, large crowds gather in the capital, with many saying they are marching 'for those who still can't'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donor Agreed to Pay Cohen $10M to Push Project...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/top-trump-donor-agreed-to-pay-michael-cohen-10-million-for-nuclear-project-push-sources-say-1533245330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major donor to President Trump agreed to pay $10 million to the president’s then-personal attorney if he successfully helped obtain funding for a nuclear-power project, including a $5 billion loan from the U.S. government, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man convicted of attempted homicide for spiking girlfriend's drink with abortion pill...</title>
      <link>https://www.postcrescent.com/story/news/crime/2018/08/02/man-convicted-spiking-girlfriends-drink-abortion-pill/878158002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postcrescent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manishkumar Patel was charged in 2007 but forfeited a $750,000 cash bond and went on the run for nearly a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen arrested in cockpit trying to STEAL JET to fly to rap concert...</title>
      <link>http://www.texarkanagazette.com/news/texarkana/story/2018/aug/01/police-man-tried-steal-plane-concert/736990/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.texarkanagazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man arrested at the Texarkana Regional Airport on July 4th allegedly told investigators he intended to fly a stolen plane to a rap music concert in another state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Allen on Roseanne firing: 'Who makes up these rules?'</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/08/02/tim-allen-roseanne-firing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Allen is opening up about the other conservative sitcom star whose show was canceled by ABC -- Roseanne Barr. Asked…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOPE DRAWN FROM 'ANGEL' IN TX SKY...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article215968750.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montgomery, Texas resident Danny Ferraro and his wife were traveling west down Texas 105 when they saw a reassuring sign in the sky — a cloud that closely resembled an angel — on their one-month wedding anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Indonesian Isle, Shrinking Bodies Puzzle Scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/02/science/pygmies-flores-evolution.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Indonesian island of Flores has given rise to smaller hominins, humans and even elephants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death row journo describes searing memories of 400+ executions...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/finance/work/at-work/texas-death-row-reporter-reveals-what-its-really-like-to-watch-criminals-take-their-last-breaths/news-story/67c36baede5d6dc5bf08dd2c95b89b76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOR 34 years, Michael Graczyk has made a living watching people die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO reporter sorry for 'garbage people' tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2018/08/02/politico-reporter-apologizes-for-calling-trump-supporters-garbage-people-with-bad-teeth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Hate begets hate,” Politico reporter Marc Caputo said as he apologized for mocking Trump supporters at a Tampa rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired-up liberals raise $1,000,000,000+ on 'ActBlue'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/08/02/liberals-donations-through-actblue-top-1-billion-ahead-midterms/884400002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record fundraising on ActBlue's online platform offers one sign that the liberal activism fueled by President Trump's election isn't slowing down.The group predicts donations will top $1.5 billion by year’s end, double the amount the fundraising clearinghouse processed in the 2016 election cycle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden's highest peak no longer tallest point...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.se/20180802/arctic-heat-melts-away-swedens-highest-peak-kebnekaise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.se&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sweden's highest peak, a glacier on the southern tip of the Kebnekaise mountain, is melting due to record hot Arctic temperatures and is no longer the nation's tallest point, scientists said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORTEZ STORMS LA; TOO FAR LEFT FOR HOLLYWOOD?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/is-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-far-left-hollywood-1131514</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The newly minted Democratic star makes her first appearance in Los Angeles on Thursday — but she isn't meeting with traditional Hollywood power brokers for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man Dumps Human Waste Bucket In 7-ELEVEN...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/vile-slurry-arrest-710532</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 2--In one of the more vile episodes to recently transpire inside a 7-Eleven, a Florida man yesterday dumped a bucket containing human feces and urine inside a convenience store in St. Petersbu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDP TO 5%?</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/trump-gdp-growth-q3-third-quarter-strong-2018-8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump celebrated the 4.1% GDP growth in the second quarter as a sign his policies were working. Based on early estimates for third quarter GDP, there may be more to celebrate on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FULL INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?449294-1/ivanka-trump-remarks-education-workforce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump, daughter of and adviser to the president, discusses workforce issues at an event hosted by Axios in Washington, D.C.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAROSA'S REVENGE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6019907/Omarosa-tells-President-Trumps-mental-decline-not-denied.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omarosa Manigualt Newman's blockbuster book Unhinged: An Insider’s Account of the Trump White House  is set to be published August 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severed leg leads cops to cult's 'apostle'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-severed-leg-led-police-to-a-Connecticut-cult-s-13125710.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic Shuttle Meadow Country Club in Kensington, Connecticut, sprawls over nearly 400 acres of land. Surrounded by dense forests and rolling hills, the club's picturesque 18-hole course is a golfer's dream. About 14 years ago, New Britain police made a grim discovery there. Responding to a report of human remains on Aug. 27, 2004, police arrived to find part of a leg, severed so cleanly that they could only come to one conclusion: someone had been killed. The source of the leg would remain a mystery until 2016, according to a recently released arrest warrant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squirrels take over Maine neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://bangordailynews.com/2018/08/02/homestead/nuisance-squirrels-digging-up-gardens-invading-houses-in-bangor-neighborhood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bangordailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Crises Herald 'Fall' Of NYC... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/02/new-york-city-problems-subways-mayor-deblasio-bloomberg/777568002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After some golden years, slow subways, deteriorating public housing and creaky rent protections add up to a crisis of confidence in New York City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Co Sends NAACP Volunteer Racial Slur Password Reset...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/pse-sends-racial-slur-to-black-woman/803894220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PSE sends racial slur to black woman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran naval drills underway amid tensions with USA...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org//item/20180802193531-lbdcm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/MILITARY:Iran naval drills underway amid tensions with U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW IT'S PERSONAL!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/watch-sarah-sanders-refuses-to-say-press-isnt-enemy-of-the-people-in-jawdropping-clash-with-jim-acosta/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS CLASH AT WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6020573/I-attacked-restaurant-mocked-looks-medias-fault-says-Sarah-Sanders.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House press secretary visbly upset some journalists when she complained about physical dangers she faces in her job and blamed reporters in the room for causing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-clear given at OH Air Force Base after active shooter report...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/police-activity-reported-wpafb-near-medical-center/zbwqtemrZ2Vb1tasmndpyN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are reports of an active shooter at Wright-Patterson Air Force Base at the base hospital, according to an alert sent to base personnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acosta Calls For Press Protest At White House...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/acosta-journalists-should-chant-were-not-the-enemy-of-the-people-in-front-of-the-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN correspondent Jim Acosta went on a lengthy rant against White House attacks on the media on Thursday, suggesting he and his fellow reporters chant on Pennsylvania Avenue "we're not the enemy of the people" in protest against President Donald Trump's claims that they are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago highway closure latest US protest targeting affluent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cd1bb17c68764a4eb16e8da3a243be0f/Chicago-highway-closure-latest-US-protest-targeting-affluent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — A planned march Thursday along Chicago's picturesque roadway bordering Lake Michigan to one of the most historic baseball stadiums is the latest chapter in the nati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands March in Jerusalem Gay Pride Amid Surrogacy Uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2018-08-02/thousands-march-in-jerusalem-gay-pride-amid-surrogacy-uproar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duck Boat Collides With Car In Boston...</title>
      <link>http://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/08/02/boston-duck-boat-crash-state-congress-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Police have closed off the intersection of State and Congress streets after a duck boat and a car collided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James O'Keefe Targets Elite College Football Coach...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/2018/08/02/an-unfair-game-urban-meyer-a-history-of-abuse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROBLEMS MOUNT AT OHIO STATE...</title>
      <link>http://www.dispatch.com/sports/20180801/ohio-state-urban-meyer-placed-on-administrative-leave</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-wife of Zach Smith said she informed Urban Meyer's wife, Shelley, in 2015 that the former Ohio State assistant football coach had abused her and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel Officials Back Shutting Out Brennan, Clapper...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearinvestigations.com/articles/2018/08/01/intel_officials_back_revoking_clearances_for_brennan_clapper.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearinvestigations.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has been criticized for politicizing the intelligence community by threatening to strip the security clearances of former top officials including John Brennan and James Clapper. But...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller wants to interview Russian pop star...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/investigations/mueller-wants-interview-russian-pop-star-emin-agalarov-lawyer-says-n896951</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The son of a Russian oligarch helped set up the now infamous 2016 Trump Tower meeting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA goes ahead with tax on Canadian newsprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/2018/08/02/united-states-tariffs-canadian-newsprint/37264097/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.detroitnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tax on Canadian newsprint is a threat to the already-struggling American newspaper industry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prospective member locks puppy in locker at LA FITNESS...</title>
      <link>http://www.cbs46.com/story/38793841/man-facing-charges-after-locking-puppy-inside-gym-locker-at-la-fitness</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbs46.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trip to the gym in Midtown ends with a man facing criminal charges for locking his puppy in a gym locker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paper stands by...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/08/02/new-york-times-stands-by-new-tech-writer-sarah-jeong-after-racist-tweets-surface.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times is under fire for adding Sarah Jeong to its editorial board as derogatory tweets sent from her Twitter account have been unearthed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm donor secrets emerge as Australia law erases anonymity...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d24e6ecc38ea49e39bba937af361ff2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia (AP) — For Peter Peacock, fate arrived in the form of a registered letter.        The letter, at least initially, looked to be a bit of a letdown. Peac</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Detroit cop beats naked woman inside hospital...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox2detroit.com/news/local-news/live-police-chief-speaks-about-officer-punching-naked-woman-at-detroit-receiving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox2detroit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit Police Chief James Craig said on Thursday that he is concerned by video that shows an officer punching a naked woman at Detroit Receiving Hospital, specifically because the woman's back is turned and the officer continued to punch her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service locks down White House after suspicious vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://wjla.com/news/local/secret-service-vehicle-white-house-check-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wjla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Secret Service says they're investigating a vehicle at a checkpoint near the White House.As a result of the investigation, the North Fence along Pennsylvania Avenue as well as Lafayette Park are shut down. D.C. police are also responding to the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with firearm in car arrested near Capitol...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/400086-man-with-firearm-in-car-arrested-near-capitol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested a man on Thursday who had a weapon and ammunition in his vehicle parked near the Capitol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dentists accused of raping woman at Las Vegas Strip hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/sex-crimes/4-dentists-accused-of-raping-woman-at-las-vegas-strip-hotel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four California dentists, including three brothers, are facing sexual assault charges after a woman accused them of raping her at a Strip hotel last weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIOLENT FIGHT OVER WIG ROBBERY AT STORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/Video-Wigs-Whip-Fists-Fly-During-Robbery-at-Silver-Spring-Shop-489802991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video shows three suspects, punching, kicking and pepper-spraying employees while trying to steal wigs from a store in Silver Spring, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE HITS A TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/02/apple-hits-1-trillion-in-market-value.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon had also been fast approaching the record market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu threatens...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/434898-netanyahu-warns-iran-yemen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu has lashed out at Israel's arch-foe Iran, vowing that any attempt by Tehran to block the key waterway off Yemen’s coast would be met by force from the “international coalition” and Israel in particular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THIS IS IVANKA</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tag/ivanka-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual reality porn booths take Japan by storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6926107/vr-porn-booths-tokyo-japan-virtual-reality-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN is home to seedy virtual reality porn booths where randy locals get off to hi-tech smut. Horned-up Tokyo residents – and tourists, too – can pay ¥1,500 (around £10) for an hour-long XXX sessi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept. Lauds FACEBOOK for Removing Pages Doing 'Coordinated Inauthentic Behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/state-dept-lauds-facebook-aggressive-approach-to-remove-insidiuous-pages-doing-coordinated-inauthentic-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"These efforts are part of a broader external campaign aimed at weakening America and threatening our way of life by pitting citizens against each other and sowing discord in general."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campus Socialist Chapters Increase 280%...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/01/democratic-socialists-of-america-campuses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'57 chapters registered on college campuses.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE embraces evil with CENSORED search engine for oppressive China...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/6921397/google-evil-china-censored-search-engine-android/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOGLE’s “evil” plan to gain a foothold in China with a censored search engine that scrubs results about human rights and religion has been exposed. In the next few months, the te…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vagina beer made with 'essence of hot underwear models'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/weird-news/vagina-beer-made-essence-hot-13021963</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customers can now buy the beer and taste the 'essence' of good looking models at various pubs after its debut on July 28 in the city of Katowice, Poland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 POINTS HIGHER THAN OBAMA at Same Point in Presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/08/boom-trump-approval-at-50-5-points-higher-than-obama-at-same-point-in-his-presidency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media not enemy of  people...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ivanka-trump-breaks-from-president-the-media-is-not-the-enemy-of-the-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hispanics boosting numbers...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/31/good-news-for-the-gop-hispanics-are-boosting-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are Hispanics shifting their allegiances to President Trump?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newest NYT Editorial Board Member: 'White Men Are Bullshit'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/02/new-york-times-sarah-jeong-racist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As fires burn faster, emergency alerts fail to keep pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-fires-burn-faster-emergency-alerts-fail-to-keep-pace/article_a88986a2-cc77-5d33-9615-09a3226181f0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. — It was a week ago when the Carr fire barreled out of the foothills and took aim at this city, with hot winds launching embers well ahead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: APPLE HITS TRILLION!</title>
      <link>https://9to5mac.com/2018/08/02/apple-becomes-first-company-to-hit-1-trillion-market-cap-according-to-apples-own-stocks-app/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;9to5mac.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has succeeded in becoming the first public company to hit a trillion dollars … although it depends who you ask. Due to a discrepancy in the count of total available shares, Yahoo is rep…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Activist Was Challenging Xi on Live TV. Police Came to Stop Him...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/media/400049-chinese-professor-removed-by-police-during-live-interview-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese police officers removed a professor who has been critical of Beijing's policies from his home during a live interview on Wednesday night, according to Voice of America (VOA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA: Family separations at border 'low point'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6019537/Ivanka-breaks-fathers-immigration-policy-family-separations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump, the president's daughter and senior adviser, said seeing the aftermath of family separations – desperate mothers and distraught children – was 'a low point for me.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family separations at border 'low point'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/ivanka-trump-calls-family-separations-at-border-a-low-point</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s daughter and White House adviser Ivanka Trump called the administration’s separation of immigrant families at the U.S.-Mexico border “a low point” for the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA: Media not enemy of the people...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ivanka-trump-media-enemy-of-the-people-3ac579de-fb03-4edd-9cf2-b526d0f7dc0a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This breaks with her father</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: TRUMP APPROVAL 50%</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/current_events/politics/prez_track_aug02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgium begins charging journalists a fee to cover EU meetings...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/400033-china-calls-on-us-to-correct-its-attitude-after-threat-to-raise-tariffs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Belgian government this week began charging its journalists a fee to cover European Union (EU) meetings, according to The Ne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEATWAVE FREAKOUT: Droughts led to assassinations!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/beware-heatwave-droughts-roman-empire-122352552.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beware of the heatwave - droughts in Roman Empire led to more emperors being assassinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire smoke: Experts warn of 'serious health effects' across western USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/02/wildfire-events-air-quality-health-issues-in-western-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smoke from fires has been linked to asthma attacks and heart problems and has contributed to a decline in air quality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican fears mount over Ohio special election...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article215938730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A special election next week in Ohio’s 12th Congressional District is the last big electoral test before November’s election, a showdown in a once deep-red suburban House seat that Donald Trump won by 11 points.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm Totally Freaked Out'; Brazilians Weigh Farewell to Paradise...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/im-totally-freaked-out-brazilians-weigh-a-farewell-to-paradise-1533211200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With gun violence surging, along with pessimism about the country’s political and economic future, the number of Brazilians who are emigrating is soaring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort's accountants to take spotlight in trial's third day...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-manafort/manaforts-accountants-to-take-spotlight-in-trials-third-day-idUSKBN1KN1BK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial of U.S. President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman Paul Manafort is set to shift focus to the accountants who prepared years of his allegedly false tax returns as the court battle heads into its third day on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff: Radio host Art Bell died of prescription overdose...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-nevada/radio-host-art-bell-died-of-accidental-drug-overdose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clark County coroner’s office says mix of four drugs killed the popular chronicler of the paranormal in his home in Pahrump on April 13.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army using drug waivers, bonuses to fill ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2018/08/01/army-using-drug-waivers-bonuses-to-fill-ranks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under the gun to increase the size of the force, the Army is issuing more waivers for past drug use or bad conduct by recruits, and pouring an extra $200 million into bonuses this year to attract and retain soldiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot African air brings scorching heat, dust to Europe...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/heatwave-hits-iberian-peninsula-bringing-health-warnings-56983132</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the Iberian Peninsula braced Thursday for the year's first heatwave, with the mercury expected to soar before peaking at 47 degrees Celsius (116.6 Fahrenheit) in some areas of southern Portugal this weekend. Temperatures were being driven higher by a hot air mass moving northward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Mental Health Days' Costing Economy Billions...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mental-health-days-costing-economy-billions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the purposes of the study, poor mental health days were defined as work days that employees miss because of what they describe as mental health issues, citing conditions like depression, anxiety, excessive stress, and emotional problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen in time, Havana looks to put modern stamp on 500-year history...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180802-frozen-time-havana-looks-put-modern-stamp-its-500-year-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF kills armed terrorists in Syrian Golan; Prevents 'grave incident'...</title>
      <link>https://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-5321404,00.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ynetnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early morning strike, IAF attacks terrorists in the Syrian side of the Golan Heights 'preventing grave incident'; explosives and Kalashnikov rifles found in the area after the strike; Lieberman earlier: 'There is a clear address' to incidents on Syrian border now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
