<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bare-knuckle fighting poised for brand boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/bare-knuckle-fighting-could-poised-us-boom-215851932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — David Feldman staged a bare-knuckle boxing match on the undercard of a mixed martial arts show at a Yavapai Nation casino in Arizona in 2011. The promoter offered the fight on the internet as a paid streaming option, just to see if anybody would watch it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCain decides to discontinue cancer treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/arizona/2018/08/24/arizona-senator-john-mccain-legacy-national-security-hawk-gop-maverick/567264001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain prefers that he be remembered for his contributions to the national defense. But history likely will recall him as GOP "maverick."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE quietly purges user-generated reviews?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-might-hiding-fact-reviews-shoddy-135640955.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's local reviews have disappeared from normal search results, which brings to the surface that they may not be the best out there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK: Aides expect to go rogue on pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/24/trump-manafort-pardon-white-house-aides-795712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's comments are being read as a signal that he wants to ignore his lawyers and exonerate his former campaign chairman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> 'Sovereign Calculator' Explains Invented Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/08/24/venezuela-debuts-sovereign-calculator-app-explain-invented-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's Central Bank introduced a "sovereign calculator" app this week to help people work out the value of the country's new currency denominations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia Argento 'sent unwanted topless vid' to recovering sex addict...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6095413/Asia-Argento-sent-unwanted-nude-video-comedian-freaked-got-upset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Leach was appearing on the Legion of Skanks podcast when he shared this story during a discussion about the arrest of Harvey Weinsetein just days prior on charges of rape and assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_41.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY: NO ONE HAS CONCEDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8472093/sony-music-responds-claims-suit-michael-jackson-album-vocals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement released on Friday morning (Aug. 24), Sony Music did not concede that the three songs in question on the 2010 &amp;quot;Michael&amp;quot; album featured lead vocals by someone other than Jackson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting fraud charges filed against foreign nationals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfmynews2.com/article/news/local/19-illegal-immigrants-in-nc-voted-in-2016-election-federal-officials-say/83-587333046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfmynews2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A news release from United States Attorney for the Eastern District of North Carolina also said several of those charged voted in more than one election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goat rental industry taking off across USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/articles/2018-08-24/rent-a-goat-companies-gain-traction-across-the-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona flirts with sliding red to purple...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/the-report/articles/2018-08-24/races-for-governor-senate-test-arizonas-deep-shade-of-red</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson 'may not have' sung lead vocals on posthumous tracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/24/michael-jackson-may-not-have-sung-lead-vocals-posthumous-tracks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When an album of previously-unreleased songs from their hero Michael Jackson was released a year after his death it seemed, some astute fans feared, too good to be true.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,478-HP BUGATTI Hypercar Unveiled; Costs $5.8 Million!</title>
      <link>http://www.thedrive.com/news/23123/the-1478-horsepower-bugatti-divo-costs-5-8-million</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And you can't have one, because they sold out months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plea Reveals Link to Qatari Royals...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-guilty-plea-reveals-link-to-qatari-royal-family-1535127732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $100,000 real-estate brokerage fee that was part of former Trump attorney Michael Cohen’s guilty plea came from representing a company owned by a member of the Qatar royal family, according to interviews and real estate documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Muzzles Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/mueller-is-already-taking-measures-to-stop-manafort-from-making-this-claim-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG plans investigation into Cohen's taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/24/politics/michael-cohen-new-york-state-attorney-general-tax-law/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Attorney General's office is poised to pursue a criminal probe of Michael Cohen's potential state tax law violations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept cuts aid to Palestinians by $200 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3149b034ef4a4b92a6dbb9c4aa1f5ca7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration has decided to cut more than $200 million in bilateral aid to the Palestinians, following a review of the funding for projects in the We</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. calls foreign mail system unfair in surprise win for AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-mail-fees/u-s-calls-foreign-mail-system-unfair-in-surprise-win-for-amazon-idUSKCN1L91W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. State Department on Friday said it would push for foreign postal carriers to pay the U.S. Postal Service more to deliver small parcels within the United States, taking up a longtime complaint by Amazon.com , UPS and others who have alleged the current system is unfair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy re-establishes Atlantic fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/24/navy-atlantic-fleet-russia-751660</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's “back to the future,“ in the words of one former 2nd Fleet commander.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGM opens Massachusetts' 1st resort casino...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-mgm-opens-massachusetts-1st-resort-casino-193639913.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Mass. (AP) — The Latest on the grand opening of Massachusetts' first resort casino (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White farmer first to have land seized in SAfrica reveals 10-year battle; 'It's theft'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6094565/White-farmer-set-game-reserve-seized-South-Africa-calls-theft.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johan Steenkamp, 67, who co-owns a £10million hunting farm in Limpopo, has been ordered to hand over his land, following a ten-year battle to stop the government buying it for a tenth of its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters battle wind-whipped fire...</title>
      <link>http://www.hawaiinewsnow.com/story/38954656/brush-fire-in-lahaina-prompts-evacuations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hawaiinewsnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maui firefighters are responding to reports of a brush fire in Lahaina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Outages...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-storm-lane-churns-toward-main-hawaiian-islands-101601826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — The Latest on Hurricane Lane (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-in 'sex boxes' for prostitution, built by taxpayers, wild success...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/drive-sex-boxes-prostitution-built-taxpayers-wild-success-switzerland-182306115.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sex workers are required to submit to regular health checks and pay taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Arpaio's Long Goodbye: Redemption or 'Kamikaze' Mission?</title>
      <link>https://www.news965.com/news/national-govt--politics/joe-arpaio-long-goodbye-redemption-kamikaze-mission/3nJhRsFInbp4eTGL4bLZIL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news965.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CDC director arrested on sex abuse charges...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/24/former-head-of-cdc-arrested-for-groping-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former director of the Center for Disease Control and Prevention — and one-time NYC Health Commissioner — was arrested Friday for groping a woman inside his Brooklyn Heights apartment, police s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMBORGHINI unveils even faster supercar...</title>
      <link>https://money.cnn.com/2018/08/24/autos/lamborghini-aventador-svj/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lamborghi Aventador SVJ has a 770 horsepower V12 and a high-tech rear wing, helping to make it a super fast supercar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Cancels Pompeo NKorea Visit...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/24/trump-cancels-north-korea-meeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I feel we are not making sufficient progress'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Ushers in Human-Centric Discipline...</title>
      <link>https://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2018/08/24/artificial-intelligence-ushers-in-human-centric-engineering-discipline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The broad umbrella of artificial intelligence could spawn a new branch of engineering that will help develop of AI systems and applications, much as civil and mechanical engineering helped develop tall buildings and airplanes over a century ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge wildfire near Berlin sets off WWII arms blasts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1823e5cfb9224c32bd75d9e0c0e2dcec/Huge-wildfire-southwest-of-Berlin-sets-off-WWII-arms-blasts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Firefighters struggled Friday to tame a wildfire southwest of Berlin but had to maneuver carefully as the blaze set off old World War II ammunition that is still bur</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Updating Nuke Disaster Plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/danvergano/north-korea-nuclear-bomb-fema-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We are looking at 100 kiloton to 1,000 kiloton detonations,” a FEMA official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Communist Who Launched Keith Ellison's Career...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/jeryl-bier/the-communist-who-launched-keith-ellisons-career</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis Farrakhan isn’t the only radical lurking in the background of the No. 2 official in the DNC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CDC director arrested on sex misconduct allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/former-cdc-director-dr-tom-frieden-arrested-sexual-misconduct-allegations-n903586</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frieden, who stepped down as head of the federal agency when Trump took office, is accused of forcibly touching at least one woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAN RATHER:  STAY TUNED...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2018/08/23/dan_rather_what_mueller_knows_will_make_cohenmanafort_pale_by_comparison_stay_tuned.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Rather warned Wednesday night that if you think Tuesday was a shock with the Cohen guilty plea and Manafort's conviction, then "stay tuned." The former news anchor said other things Mueller is working on will "make yesterday pale by comparison."  "Always keeping in mind that Mueller knows so much more than he has shown," Rather said in an interview with CNN's Don Lemon. "If you think [Cohen guilty plea, Manafort conviction] was a shock to our democratic system, just stay tuned. Because the other things Mueller is working on, and sooner or later we'll find out what they are, is going to make yesterday pale by comparison."  "I think the evidence abounds," he added.  Rather said on Wednesday's CNN Tonight that he doesn't think Trump is crazy at all, just increasingly cornered.  "So we are in an ocean the likes of which no one has been on. And the head winds right now are against Donald Trump," he said. "I know his former aide, Omarosa, thinks he is crazy as a bull bat. I don't subscribe to that. I don't think he is crazy at all. I do think that he is increasingly cornered and people who get being in a corner frequently can't think as straight as they otherwise do. And the pressure is on Donald Trump now. Things changed dramatically yesterday. It was reminiscent of March 1974 when I think nine of President Nixon's close aides were indicted and fired."  He also said that there is "honor and integrity" in impeachment.  "When impeachment was being considered for President Clinton, and as you know, orders of impeachment, word against him, he won the trial in the Senate, but Lindsey Graham said that impeachment is about the honor and integrity of the President. If you apply that to the present situation, if what we're talking about is the honor and integrity of the President, this is a situation Donald Trump in the end may not win," he said.  DAN RATHER: The stakes for the upcoming mid-terms are now even higher as Democrats are openly discussing impeachment proceedings, should they gain control of the House and Republicans are dodging the questions. That is a lot to get to in one hour. But I want to bring in now a man who can makes sense of all this, he knows about a White House under siege, he has reported on it and live through it, Dan Rather, the host of AXS TV's "The Big Interview." Thank you very much.   DAN RATHER, HOST, AXS TV'S THE BIG INTERVIEW: Thank you, Don, for having me. Grateful to be here.   LEMON: That was a lot. I mean, before, you know, we get to the stuff that, you know, we had ready for you. What do you think? Is this madness? I've never seen this much in my --   RATHER: Well, it is a kind of madness. What goes through my mind, eventually the last 24 to 48 hours, with Cohen and Manafort, is President Abraham Lincoln had his team of rivals. Trump has his block of felons. That is what it is. He surrounded, he had drowned himself what turns out to be felons.   There's never been anything like this in American history. Watergate in the mid-1970s is the closest thing we've had with this. But the importance difference with Watergate, Watergate, it consisted of crimes of Americans committing crimes against Americans. At the core of this investigation, which we're not nearly at the end of it, is a foreign power trying to affect and possibly affecting our election. That is a very big difference.   LEMON: I've heard the term criminal enterprise a lot, over the last day or so, especially with Michael Cohen and Paul Manafort. Do you think that is befitting with what happened with campaign or what the Trump --   RATHER: Well, I wouldn't use the phrase myself, but I can't argue with anyone who does. Given the record. Look at how many people have either pled guilty or in Manafort's case, been found guilty. So we are in an ocean the likes of which no one has been on. And the head winds right now are against Donald Trump. I know his former aide, Omarosa, thinks he is crazy as a bull bat. I don't subscribe to that. I don't think he is crazy at all.   I do think that he is increasingly cornered and people who get being in a corner frequently can't think as straight as they otherwise do. And the pressure is on Donald Trump now. Things changed dramatically yesterday. It was reminiscent of March 1974 when I think nine of President Nixon's close aides were indicted and fired.   That is the closest we've had, but again, you can't use Watergate as a complete template, because of the allegation of Russian influence in our election.   LEMON: Yes, and also, it was whether or not he is going to face any ramifications, or whatever he faces, the Congress was different then.   RATHER: Well, exactly. And I find people forget this. That during the Nixon Watergate period, widespread criminal conspiracy, led by the President himself. That both Houses of Congress were in the hands of the Democrats. Whatever situation. Now just the opposite. And someone else said earlier this evening, and I agree with it. That the only chance that the Republican Party, the GOP Senators and the majority house members, are going to split with Trump is if he tries on fire Mueller. If he doesn't do that, they are going to stick with him through thick and thin.   LEMON: At their own peril? Or do you think even at the end it will be OK with them, because they're getting their agendas across and they are getting, you know, who they want to be.   RATHER: Unless something changes dramatically, I think that is it. And by the way, Don, Lindsey Graham, Senator, South Carolina, a very smart guy, good sense of humor. As a matter of fact, I know him a little bit and like him, but back at the time when impeachment was being considered for President Clinton, and as you know, orders of impeachment, word against him, he won the trial in the senate, but Lindsey Graham said that impeachment is about the honor and integrity of the President. If you apply that to the present situation, if what we're talking about is the honor and integrity of the President, this is a situation Donald Trump in the end may not win.   LEMON: This is something that you tweeted earlier today. OK? Dan Rather says, one has a sense of the GOP leaders holding on to Donald Trump for deer political life have no idea where this wild horror show of a ride is heading. Can this get even worse? Undoubtedly. How bad can it get? No one save Trump and likely Mueller's team really knows. So, I mean that is pretty pro boding about what may come.   RATHER: Well, I think probing is the proper attitude to have to it. Always keeping in mind that Mueller knows so much more than he has shown. If you think yesterday was a shock to our democratic system, just stay tuned. Because the other things Mueller is working on, and sooner or later we'll find out what they are, is going to make yesterday pale by comparison.   LEMON: Do you think so?   RATHER: I think the evidence abounds.   LEMON: Because yesterday, the President's fixer and attorney implicated the President in a crime.   RATHER: The President in effect became an unindicted co-conspirator in a criminal case. And what you had, you have a conspiracy to defraud the American voter. A criminal conspiracy for the American voters to win the election campaign. This is, to say serious, understates it. And I come back to, Mueller is digging away, he has been digging away. There is still a long way to go with this. Anybody that thinks yesterday was sort of the high mark, they're kidding themselves.   We have to be prepared as a people and I want to preach about it. We, as the people stay steady and depend on the checks and balances. I mean, give that jury credit to Manafort case and give the federal prosecutors in the case, you know, the federal prosecutors with a hostile judge presented a case that got convictions. The jury did their job. They started, they deliberated and came back with guilty verdicts. It is a reminder, you know of President John Adams once said, that our jury system is both the lungs and the heart of our Democratic system. We have a reminder that is in the Manafort trial.   LEMON: I was trying to look at -- did you guys -- did you know the date on this, (inaudible) 1973, I'm not exactly sure what it is, but this is October of 1973. Because you were, you tweeted about how things would undoubtedly get worse and this is a flash back, this is your reporting during Watergate. The Saturday night massacre, 1973, October. Here it is. Watch.   (BEGIN VIDEO CLIP)   RATHER: In breath taking succession tonight, the following historic events occurred. The President of the United States demanded that had the Attorney General Fire Special Prosecutor, Archibald Cox. The Attorney General, Elliott Richardson refused and resigned. The President then ordered the assistant Attorney General to William Ruckelshaus to fire the special prosecutor. Ruckelshaus refused. The President immediately fired Ruckelshaus. So solicitor general, Robert Bork was quickly named acting Attorney General. Bork was ordered to fire special prosecutor Cox. He did.   (END VIDEO CLIP)   LEMON: We discussed your reporting then before and you're anchoring then before. You said it is surreal, but that is -- now we're living through this. It is an indication that yes, things can always get worse.   RATHER: Yes. Particularly when we are in and see clear we are in. We're in a kind of political theater of the absurd now. And we should expect things at least for a while to get worse before they get better. By the way I am sorry to play that clip, I have more hair --   LEMON: I was going to say, who was the guy with all that hair back then?   RATHER: And a better color.   (LAUGHTER)   LEMON: It's always pleasure.   RATHER: Don, thank you very much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP'S RING OF FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/23/national-enquirer-boss-has-immunity-in-cohen-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feds have granted immunity to two top execs of the National Enquirer’s publisher so they can spill their guts about the roles President Trump and Michael Cohen played in hush- money payoffs to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Security guard had sex with female corpse at Memphis hospital...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/corpse-abuse-memphis-759201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 24--A security guard at a Tennessee hospital was found having sex with a female corpse in a body storage room, according to cops who arrested the man for the heinous act. Cameron Wright, 23, wa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_40.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drivers line up at food truck on snarled LA freeway...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/drivers-line-up-for-food-truck-while-stuck-in-traffic-after-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The traffic backup was so bad Friday morning on the 105 Freeway in Hawthorne after a fiery crash that many turned off their vehicles and stood in line for a food truck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNEAK PEAK:  Documentary to reveal how they manipulate your searches; power to control info...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HqlDtjnwyPA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA: George Conway tweets again...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/403421-conways-husband-to-trump-what-we-need-is-a-president-who-understands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, tweeted at President Trump on Friday that the country needs a leader who understands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We don't know quarter of what's in pocket of Mueller'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/403432-spiro-agnew-lawyer-trump-should-resign-to-keep-mueller-from</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin London, a lawyer who represented former Vice President Spiro Agnew, said that President Trump should resign from office to keep federal prosecutors from prosecuting his family.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amps Up AMAZON Fight With New Bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/bernie-sanders-ramps-up-amazon-battle-with-new-bill-demanding-living-wage-for-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the senator's office, the legislation would establish a 100 percent tax on large employers equal to the amount of federal benefits received by low-wage workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robin Leach Dead in Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/robin-leach-dead-lifestyles-rich-famous-host-dies-1137244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran journalist had been working as a celebrity columnist for the Las Vegas Review-Journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE HAWAII</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Weakening-Lane-Still-Track-Slam-Hawaii-Widespread-Floods-Mudslides</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Lane has embarked on its long-awaited weakening trend, but that may not be enough to spare Hawaii from a prolonged round of torrential rains, floods, mudslides, and related havoc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longtime Trump Organization CFO Weisselberg granted immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/allen-weisselberg-longtime-trump-organization-cfo-is-granted-immunity-by-federal-prosecutors-in-michael-cohen-investigation-1535121992</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen Weisselberg, President Trump’s longtime financial gatekeeper, was granted immunity by federal prosecutors for providing information about Michael Cohen in the criminal investigation into hush-money payments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Airport First to Catch Illegal Using Facial Biometrics...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2018/08/dc-airport-first-nation-catch-suspected-imposter-using-facial-biometrics/150777/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After three days of operation, Washington Dulles International Airport’s biometric cameras identified a man allegedly attempting to use someone else’s passport to enter the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct hit?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2018-08-23-hurricane-lane-impacts-hawaii-honolulu-maui-hilo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane Lane is bringing major impacts to Hawaii. Here's the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Etna volcano roars into action with ash and lava...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f642950f7d6b438c9c0e0aca80ab6649/Mount-Etna-volcano-roars-into-action-with-ash-and-lava</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Mount Etna in Sicily has roared back into spectacular volcanic action, sending up plumes of ash and spewing lava.        Italy's National Institute of Geophysic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crisis moment approaching in Venezuelan exodus...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/crisis-moment-approaching-venezuelan-exodus-u-n-agency-140101719.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The exodus of migrants from Venezuela is building towards a "crisis moment" comparable to events involving refugees in the Mediterranean, the U.N. migration agency said on Friday. Growing numbers are fleeing economic meltdown and political turmoil in Venezuela, threatening to overwhelm neighbouring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 Now Sick in Parasite Outbreak Linked to MCDONALD'S Salad...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/McDonalds-Salad-Outbreak-Sick-Parasite-Centers-for-Disease-Control-and-Prevention-491637051.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC is now reporting that 507 people in 16 states have been diagnosed with an intestinal illness after consuming salads at McDonald’s restaurants, marking a 16 percent increase in cases in two weeks and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida candidate: Alien abduction doesn't define me...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/os-florida-candidate-alien-abduction-20180823-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. House candidate Bettina Rodriguez Aguilera has a long list of accomplishments to bolster her campaign in Florida. But she is perhaps best known for claiming that she was abducted by space aliens as a child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the self-cannibals: Blood sausage and foot tacos...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7067752/online-self-cannibalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE texture was good, it looked tasty, there was a nice hint of spice… and if Gwen hadn’t have spent all day cooking it, she’d probably never have guessed that the sausage she was…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON employs 'ambassadors' to tweet back at criticism of working conditions...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6094075/Amazon-hires-unnerving-army-Twitter-Ambassadors-praise-working-conditions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The accounts frequently jump to the defense of the Seattle-based online retail giant in response to Twitter users criticizing its notoriously poor pay and working conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman who bit ex's testicles cleared of malicious castration...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/woman-who-bit-ex-s-testicles-cleared-of-malicious-castration/17791971/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Carolina woman accused of trying to bite off her ex-boyfriend's testicles has been found not guilty of malicious castration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fences go up in LA to keep out homeless...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/aug/24/where-the-sidewalk-ends-businesses-keep-out-homeless-with-fences</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As homelessness rises in the city, business owners are blocking off sidewalks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of guests at Egypt hotel where Brit couple died struck by food poisoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/inside-thomas-cook-hotel-brit-13130091</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Ownership Among Blacks Up 400% Since Trump Elected...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-08-22/small-business-ownership-among-black-americans-jumps-400-one-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Tremors 50% Above Normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.newswars.com/seismic-shocker-the-number-of-global-earthquakes-over-the-last-30-days-is-more-than-50-above-normal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newswars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is yet another story that the mainstream news is “too busy” to talk about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegally-grown marijuana ravaging national forests...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/growing-marijuana-illegally-national-forests-ravaging-environment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agents destroyed more than 1.4 million marijuana plants last year; operations are less a war on drugs and more a battle to protect the environment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Censors More Stories...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/facebook-censors-articles-from-salena-zito-jenna-lynn-ellis-saying-they-look-like-spam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are liberal viewpoints "spam," too?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela nightmare spreading to neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/23/venezuelas-nightmare-is-spreading-to-its-neighbors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the collapse of Chavism, which way will Latin America turn? It wasn’t long ago that Venezuela, led by a fiery caudillo and dedicated to spreading its brand of populist super-socialism, booste…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White farmer first to have land seized in SAfrica reveals 10-year battle; 'It's theft'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6094565/White-farmer-set-game-reserve-seized-South-Africa-calls-theft.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johan Steenkamp, 67, who co-owns a £10million hunting farm in Limpopo, has been ordered to hand over his land, following a ten-year battle to stop the government buying it for a tenth of its value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President who demands loyalty finds it fleeting in DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ee991311b0f449799161c64957d4270d/A-president-who-demands-loyalty-finds-it-fleeting-in-DC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Et tu, Michael Cohen?        Loyalty has long been a core value for President Donald Trump. But he's learning the hard way that in politics, it doesn't al</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP TO 40" OF RAIN</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tcpages/archive/2018/TCPCP2.EP142018.39A.201808241146</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_39A.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of Burning Man...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/graphics/2018/lifestyle/burning-man/?utm_term=.25679529b805</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a huddle of hippies on a beach to a city of 70,000 in the desert, here’s how a festival became a lifestyle for many.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attendees spending more money than ever...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1367064/who-goes-to-burning-man-four-charts-tell-a-changing-story/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can't manage what you don't measure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor contracts Ebola in 'dreaded' scenario...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-ebola-congo-who/doctor-in-eastern-congo-contracts-ebola-in-dreaded-scenario-who-idUSKCN1L90VC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A doctor has become the first probable Ebola case in one of the eastern Democratic Republic of Congo's "high insecurity zones" which are dogged by militia violence and hard to access, a scenario "we have all been dreading", the WHO said on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German military turns to under 18s to boost recruitment...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-germany-military-recruits/german-military-turns-to-under-18s-to-boost-recruitment-idUSKCN1L90MQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Marlon finished high school in Germany, a military career seemed far more appealing than working on a car production line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON: 100th murder; Set for record...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/100th-london-murder-investigation-launched-12984617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Full list of those killed after epidemic of knife crime sweeps the capital this year piling pressure on Metropolitan Police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine-year-old boy dies after beating by Buddhist monk...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180824-nine-year-old-boy-dies-after-beating-buddhist-monk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Site Hiring Spree Becomes Story in Itself...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/24/sports/the-athletic-netflix.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The subscription-based hyperlocal sports website and app is growing quicker than any sports media company in recent memory. But can its expansion be sustained?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Companies Gathering For Secret Meeting To Prepare Election Strategy...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/kevincollier/tech-companies-are-gathering-for-a-secret-meeting-to</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reps from up to a dozen of the US's biggest tech companies plan to meet in San Francisco to discuss efforts to counter manipulation of their platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us1000ggj4#map</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Dems fight over superdelegates...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/403325-dnc-to-confront-fate-of-superdelegates-after-bitter-2016-fight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the Democratic National Committee are gearing up for a potentially bitter fight this weekend over the role of superdelegates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7.1 MAG QUAKE ROCKS PERU...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180824093100-s8ev7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PERU-QUAKE/ (URGENT):Deep magnitude 7.1 quake strikes Peru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP TO 30" OF RAIN</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tcpages/archive/2018/TCPCP2.EP142018.039.201808240841</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_39.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tc_graphics/2018/graphics/EP142018_3day_cone_no_line_37A.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Chief Wants to Send Humans to Moon --  'To Stay'...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/41599-nasa-moon-space-priorities-jim-bridenstine-update.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA's new administrator, Jim Bridenstine, sat down with Space.com and other outlets to discuss his priorities for NASA going forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPV-related cancers on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20180823-us-hpv-related-cancers-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones replace farmers...</title>
      <link>https://www.csmonitor.com/Technology/2018/0823/As-Japan-s-farmers-age-drones-help-with-heavy-lifting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.csmonitor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rural communities in Japan are facing a labor shortage as farmers age and young people move to urban areas. The drones, which fly over fields quickly performing tasks strenuous to farmers, may be one part of how farms in the aging rural heartland can adapt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISA, MASTERCARD Cut Off Payments to Conservative Think Tank...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/08/23/david-horowitz-visa-mastercard-cut-off-payments-to-my-think-tank-based-on-splc-hate-group-label/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The David Horowitz Freedom Center has allegedly had their donation processing system blocked by Visa and Mastercard following a campaign by the Southern Poverty Law Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct hit?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/safety/hurricane/news/2018-08-23-hurricane-lane-forecast-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest forecast for this dangerous, rare Hawaii hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SONY $2900 robot pet dog...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6091615/Sony-unveils-litter-edition-version-Aibo-robot-dog-itll-set-2900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony's new-and-improved Aibo robot dog is finally coming to the US. A 'First Litter Edition' will go on sale in September with a hefty price tag of $2,899 that includes the dog, a set of toys and cloud access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest probiotic drink: baby poo smoothie...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/the-latest-probiotic-drink-a-baby-poo-smoothie-p3clssltn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s healthy, it’s organic, it already comes at a smoothie-like consistency — and it uses a resource that we would otherwise just throw away. What’s not to like about the latest promising probiotic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie accuses DISNEY of dodging fair pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2018/aug/23/pay-a-living-wage-bernie-sanders-accuses-disney-of-dodging-fair-pay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator and other critics say the company is forgoing government subsidies and tax breaks to avoid wage hikes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resurgence of black lung disease in coal miners...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coalminers/resurgence-of-crippling-black-lung-disease-seen-in-u-s-coal-miners-idUSKCN1L82FT </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Reuters Health) - Since the 1990s, annual numbers of U.S. coal miners with new, confirmed cases of an advanced form of so-called black lung disease known as progressive massive fibrosis have been steadily rising, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self esteem highest at 60?</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/08/23/at-what-age-is-self-esteem-highest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feeling insecure? Relax. Self-esteem gets higher as you age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic mushrooms to treat depression gets FDA okay...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/magic-mushrooms-to-treat-depression-this-peter-thiel-backed-startup-just-got-fda-okay-to-begin-trials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal agency has approved psychedelic magic mushrooms for a depression trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: No amount of alcohol safe...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/zero-tolerance-no-safe-level-alcohol-study-says-doc-18j2nt1 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Autopsy Reveals Illegal Alien Allegedly Stabbed Iowa Student to Death...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/23/autopsy-finds-iowa-student-killed-by-sharp-force-injuries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa college student who was allegedly abducted by a stranger while running last month was killed by multiple sharp force injuries, investigators announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not enough shelters...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/us/2018/08/22/hawaii-braces-for-hurricane-lane-as-officials-say-there-are-not-enough-shelters-for-everyone.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Hurricane Lane barrels towards Hawaii as a Category 4 storm packing sustained winds of 155 mph, officials in the Aloha state are warning residents they don't have enough shelter space to meet the estimated demands of the population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election handicapper moves 10 more races toward Dems...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/403267-election-handicapper-moves-10-races-toward-dems </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Election handicapper Sabato’s Crystal Ball shifted 10 House races toward Democrats on Thursday, including the election involving recently indicted Rep. Duncan Hunter (R-Calif.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: We are headed for hellish year...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/08/do-democrats-want-an-impeachment-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If anyone is looking for a good lawyer,” said President Donald Trump ruefully, “I would strongly suggest that you don’t retain the services of Michael Cohen.” Michael Cohen is no Roy Cohn. Tuesday, Trump’s ex-lawyer, staring at five years in prison, pled guilty to a campaign violation that may not even be a crime. Cohen […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie to billionaire Bezos: 'Pay your workers living wage'...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/23/bernie-sanders-to-jeff-bezos-who-earns-275-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One particular salary has irked Sen. Bernie Sanders: He cites Amazon founder Jeff Bezos makes $275 million a day, this according to Time magazine. Now the Vermont independent has launched a petition against the tycoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE:  Waikiki cam...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=832Sk1PND4M</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The camera is located in Waikiki facing Magic Island (south) of Oahu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE SECRETS IN A SAFE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/143be3c52d4746af8546ca6772754407/AP:-National-Enquirer's-safe-held-damaging-Trump-stories</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The National Enquirer kept a safe containing documents on hush money payments and other damaging stories it killed as part of its cozy relationship with Donald T</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP TO 30" OF RAIN</title>
      <link>http://www.prh.noaa.gov/cphc/tcpages/archive/2018/TCPCP2.EP142018.37A.201808240002</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.prh.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind vet rowing from CA to HI preps to ride out...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/steve-sparkes-blind-veteran-rowing-from-california-to-hawaii-prepares-to-ride-out-hurricane-lane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Sparkes has already capsized, lost oars and now faces Hurricane Lane</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Condo turns to DNA tests to police doggie doo...</title>
      <link>http://www.capitalgazette.com/news/annapolis/ac-cn-park-place-dog-poop-0822-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed up with messes left here and there by dogs, Park Place is laying down new rules — and relying on DNA samples to identify the perpetrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kavanaugh eases off call for presidential immunity...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/senate/403382-kavanaugh-eases-off-call-for-presidential-immunity-in-meetings-with-senators</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Democrats on Thursday pressed Judge Brett Kavanaugh on how he would view potential obstruction of justice or other possible criminal charges against President Trump if he were confirmed to the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ambassadors' say they get bathroom breaks, defend Bezos against Bernie comments... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/aug/23/amazon-fc-ambassadors-twitter-working-conditions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Army of fulfillment center employees jump to company’s defense online when it faces a barrage of bad press</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speedy flip in Earth's magnetic field could cause trillions in damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=12111725</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nzherald.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last time Earth's poles reversed was 780k years ago, if it happens again we're in trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran air quality 3x worse than Beijing!</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/air-quality-wildfire-smoke-fog-gray-breathe-health-13178427.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gray haze over San Francisco isn't just summer fog - it's also smoke from a series of wildfires burning on the West Coast, and it's pushed air quality into unhealthy levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Burning Man' threatens to sue Feds over traffic stops...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/life/arts/burning-man/2018/08/23/burning-man-threatens-sue-over-traffic-stops/1075780002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gloves are coming off in the battle of the Burning Man traffic stops.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi: 'Can take the heat, why I stay in the kitchen'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9fdc2cbb3cbf4326963d725e6d2e06ec/Defiant-Pelosi-says-she's-staying:-'I-can-take-the-heat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Nancy Pelosi is the chief villain of Republican campaign ads. The leader some Democrats promise to vote against. The subject of much speculation that her grip on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once nude beach, always nude beach? 'Anything goes' on secluded Jersey Shore sands...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/news/new_jersey/shore/higbee-beach-nude-jersey-shore-gunnison-cape-may-county-dogs-20180816.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If it were polite, everybody would be naked," said the 62-year-old Collingswood man explaining about why he covers up in mixed beach company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price gouging probes as shoppers clear shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.khon2.com/news/local-news/state-investigating-reports-of-price-gouging-as-hurricane-lane-nears/1390165431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khon2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shoppers clears the shelves at stores ahead of Hurricane Lane, some have reported seeing increasing prices at retailers as demand for goods like water have skyrocketed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusion, panic...</title>
      <link>http://www.mauinews.com/uncategorized/2018/08/rumors-swirl-ahead-of-hurricane-lane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mauinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker Network Turns Stolen Press Releases Into $100,000,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/22/17716622/sec-business-wire-hack-stolen-press-release-fraud-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International hackers based in Ukraine stole unpublished press releases and passed them to stock traders to reap tremendous profits.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
