<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO OFFERING 'FREE' GAS!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/chicago-to-offer-gas-public-transit-cards-to-combat-citys-gas-burden-lightfoot-announces/2796170/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago will offer free gas and public transit cards to residents as an new effort to combat spiking gas prices and inflation, Mayor Lori Lightfoot announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>83% Approve Of His Actions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-s-approval-ratings-soar-amid-russia-s-war-in-ukraine/ar-AAVI29R</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Office Cops Used Social Media Surveillance Program Illegally...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nmaz/post-office-cops-used-social-media-surveillance-program-illegally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Office of Inspector General found the agency did not have legal authority for searches in its "iCOP" surveillance program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View in Shanghai Camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5qna4/photos-shanghai-covid-camps-china-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is sticking to its “zero COVID” strategy as it fights its worst outbreak in two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wartime Press Corps' Hawkish History...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2022/03/30/ukraine-war-media-coverage-hawkish-journalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States’ most reputable media outlets have a long history of tilting toward military action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longer conflict could be in store as Donbas eyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220331-longer-conflict-could-be-in-store-as-russia-eyes-donbas-us-official</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's refocusing of its military efforts on the Donbas could herald a "longer, more prolonged conflict" as Ukrainian forces put up fierce resistance in the eastern region, a senior US defense offi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike in hit-and-run deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/31/economy/traffic-death-hit-and-run/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US roads saw the largest increase on record in deaths per mile traveled in 2020, including a 26% increase in hit-and-run fatalities that outpaced the increase in overall deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Reducing Numbers in Face of Recruiting Difficulties...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2022/03/30/army-reducing-its-numbers-in-face-of-recruiting-difficulties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Army this week admitted it was having problems recruiting and announced a reduction in its numbers for fiscal year 2022 and 2023.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists sequence complete human genome for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/complete-human-genome/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakthrough is a "Rosetta stone" for understanding complex mutations underlying illness and evolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-death penalty advocate weds man on death row...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oklahoma-treatment-of-prisoners-mcalester-3f29f9b0591e25235a942dd21c1a0aa6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McALESTER, Okla. (AP) — Anti-death penalty advocate Lea Rodger says she is keenly aware of the realities facing her and Richard Glossip, who she married this week inside the Oklahoma State Penitentiary where he sits on death row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fetuses found at home of anti-abortion activist, DC police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/crime/five-fetuses-found-at-home-of-anti-abortion-activist-dc-police-say-lauren-handy-jonathan-darnell-clinic/65-f4399616-16be-4e99-9951-e7d299d7e8cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Handy and eight others were indicted this week on felony charges stemming from the 2020 invasion of an abortion clinic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspector general says post office surveillance program exceeded legal authority...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/inspector-general-says-post-office-surveillance-program-exceeded-legal-authority-172808526.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inspector general probe into the U.S. Postal Service surveillance program, known as iCOP, concluded that the agency did not have the legal authority to conduct the sweeping intelligence collection and surveillance of American protesters and others. The program exceeded its legal authority when it monitored American protesters and others between 2018 and 2021, the inspector general concluded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Virus-Hunting Nonprofit at Center of Lab-Leak Controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2022/03/the-virus-hunting-nonprofit-at-the-center-of-the-lab-leak-controversy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chasing scientific renown, grant dollars, and approval from Dr. Anthony Fauci, Peter Daszak transformed the environmental nonprofit EcoHealth Alliance into a government-funded sponsor of risky, cutting-edge virus research in both the U.S. and Wuhan, China. Drawing on more than 100,000 leaked documents, a V.F. investigation shows how an organization dedicated to preventing the next pandemic found itself suspected of helping start one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas threatens to ramp up violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/hamas-threatens-to-ramp-up-violence-after-palestinian-gunmen-killed-in-idf-raid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaza-based terror group threatens to meet 'escalation with escalation' as Israel launches large-scale operation in West Bank following wave of deadly terror attacks in Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines' standards leading to eating disorders...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2022/03/31/marine-corps-body-composition-standards-may-be-leading-to-eating-disorders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Female Marines have the highest rate of eating disorder diagnoses across all of the branches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Wrote New Message to Intelligent Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/dypjbm/scientists-wrote-a-new-message-to-intelligent-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beacon in the Galaxy is the latest in a series of attempts to contact other lifeforms in the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginni Thomas, power player or gadfly? Depends who you ask...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/31/ginni-thomas-trump-world-power-00022042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longtime conservative activist and wife of Supreme Court justice pushed names of people to hire and met with Trump. How much further did her influence extend?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN passes residency bill to disqualify Trump-backed candidate...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/politics/2022/03/29/tennessee-general-assembly-passes-residency-requirement-bill-disqualify-trump-candidate/7199662001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill to place residency requirements on Tennessee congressional candidates cleared its final hurdle in the General Assembly on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA Director tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/31/cia-director-william-burns-test-positive-for-covid-after-biden-meeting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burns, who is fully vaccinated and boosted against Covid-19, last met with President Joe Biden on Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troops Suffer 'Acute Radiation Sickness' After Digging Chernobyl Trenches...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-troops-suffer-acute-radiation-083839177.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SeanGallupSeveral hundred Russian soldiers were forced to hastily withdraw from the Chernobyl nuclear power plant in Ukraine after suffering “acute radiation sickness” from contaminated soil, according to Ukrainian officials.The troops, who dug trenches in a contaminated Red Forest near the site of the worst nuclear disaster in history, are now reportedly being treated in a special medical facility in Gomel, Belarus. The forest is so named because thousands of pine trees turned red during the 19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish Supreme Court justice fined for shoplifting...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/swedish-supreme-court-justice-fined-for-shoplifting-01648738207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Supreme Court justice in Sweden has been fined for shoplifting a Christmas ham and meatballs among other items, the prosecutor in the case said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars Fib? Was Never Officially Asked To Leave...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/will-smith-chris-rock-slap-academy-didnt-ask-actor-to-leave-1234991778/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details are emerging that Will Smith wasn’t dircectly asked to leave the Oscar ceremony after slapping Chris Rock over his “G.I. Jane 2” joke to Jada Pinkett Smith, rather it was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prime Minister:  Israelis with gun licenses should carry arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/article-702754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What can Israel's citizens expect? "Be alert. Whoever has a weapons license, this is the time to carry it," said Prime Minister Naftali Bennett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did LA TIMES Investigation Force Retirement?</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/bruce-willis-years-of-struggle-will-smith-refused-to-leave-the-oscars-chris-rock-is-still-processing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Willis steps away from acting after years of struggle; Will Smith refused to leave the Oscars; Chris Rock tells cheering fans that he’s “still processing” but to expect some jokes soon. All in today’s Movie News Rundown, which you can sign up for here. Bruce Willis: Praise and love for Bruce Willis have poured […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of evangelists target 'Satan's headquarters' in New Hampshire...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/christianworld/article-702839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Q&amp;A with Pastor Randy Loubier</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pressure Mounts On Academy To Release Secret Three-Second Video...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/academy-pressured-release-secret-video-will-smith-chris-rock-slap-oscars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the three seconds of tape that only Academy bosses have seen. Crucial unseen video showing what Jada Pinkett Smith said to Will Smith in the seconds before he charged the Oscars stage and slapped Chris Rock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belligerent actor refused to leave Oscars...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/will-smith-oscars-slap-consequences-amapas-board-chris-rock-1234991296/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with more details: Just hours before Chris Rock is set to take the stage in Boston tonight, Will Smith’s fate from the actor’s rage-filled slap of the comic at Sunday’s Oscars now rests in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS SIGNS CAITLYN JENNER...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/fox-news-signs-caitlyn-jenner-contributor-1234991712/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner, the transgender athlete, reality star and California gubernatorial candidate, has signed on to Fox News Media as a contributor. Jenner’s first appearance will be on Hannity on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol riot pastor divides with increasingly extremist views...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/A-Jan-6-pastor-divides-his-Tennessee-community-17047880.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNT JULIET, Tenn. - The pastor promised his followers that this church service would be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American vets answer call to fight, but not all chosen...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-military-veterans-answer-zelenskys-call-to-fight-but-not-all-are-chosen/ar-AAVHFj9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE to make conservative kids' shows to rival 'woke' DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/03/31/daily-wire-kids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily Wire Kids is the conservative company’s newest push into the entertainment industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of 1970s-Style Shock Rising...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/risk-1970s-style-inflation-shock-112647130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Global price rises risk turning into 1970s-style inflation shock, which eventually led to recession and high unemployment, according to hedge fund giant Brevan Howard Asset Management. Most Read from BloombergNever Had Covid? You May Hold Key To Beating the VirusBiden Team Weighs a Massive Release of Oil to Combat InflationPutin ‘Misinformed’ by Advisers on the War, White House SaysApple and Meta Gave User Data to Hackers Who Used Forged Legal RequestsUkraine Update: Talks With Ru</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Exports to Be Halted If Payments Not Made in Local Currency...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/putin-says-gas-exports-halted-132631981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Most Read from BloombergNever Had Covid? You May Hold Key To Beating the VirusBiden Team Weighs a Massive Release of Oil to Combat InflationPutin ‘Misinformed’ by Advisers on the War, White House SaysApple and Meta Gave User Data to Hackers Who Used Forged Legal RequestsUkraine Update: Talks With Russia May Resume Friday, Kyiv SaysRussia will halt gas supplies to buyers from ‘unfriendly’ states unless they switch to payments in rubles from April 1, President Vladimir Putin said, t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunt double reveals how actor changed...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/5015168/bruce-willis-stunt-double-changed-before-aphasia-diagnosis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUCE Willis’ longtime stunt double revealed how the actor tragically ‘changed’ in the months before his heartbreaking aphasia diagnosis.  In an exclusive interview with The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate profits hit new record...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/corporate-profits-new-record-high-2021-c72e7459-233a-4b6e-ab73-f58e91146595.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies have been able to overcome and even profit from the inflationary wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Country Transformed by All That Money Can Buy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/want-visit-middle-east-start-084238475.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HandoutIt was pretty routine–I posted a selfie before taking off with a caption along the lines of, “So pumped for this trip. First up, Doha!” But 30 minutes into my flight when I connected to the WiFi, I had dozens of replies all asking me the same question: “Where are you going?”Um, what! I just said!And then I realized that for all these people, Doha only meant a place of transit, a stop before connecting to where you really wanted to go, not a destination in itself. Disheartening, perhaps, i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Le Pen's blandest campaign be most successful yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220331-closing-in-on-macron-could-le-pen-s-blandest-campaign-be-her-most-successful-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unruffled by defections and the rise of a far-right challenger, Marine Le Pen has steadied her ship in the final stretch of France’s presidential campaign, pulling ahead of rivals as she closes in on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First caravan sets off...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10670879/First-migrant-caravan-sets-Mexico-Biden-revealed-end-Title-42.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migrants at a refugee camp in Tapachula, Mexico, said that they would leave the city on Friday to head to Mexico City before trying to enter the US as Title 42 is set to be removed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details emerge about federal investigation into Hunter Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hunter-biden-investigation-federal-tax-new-details/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple sources tell CBS News the probe is exploring whether the younger Biden and his associates violated tax, money laundering and foreign lobbying laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key inflation gauge sets 40-year high as gas and food soar...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-prices-inflation-c9d81525f808b25ecd37e5c91d6bb0e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — An inflation gauge closely monitored by the Federal Reserve jumped 6.4% in February compared with a year ago, with sharply higher prices for food, gasoline and other necessities squeezing Americans' finances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Epic, Dystopian Novel Took Over Bookshelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/epic-dystopian-novels-11648728386</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed's preferred inflation gauge rises 5.4%; Highest since '83...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/31/the-feds-preferred-inflation-gauge-rose-5point4percent-in-march-the-highest-since-1983.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Staying Well-Hydrated Wards Off Heart Problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hydrated-water-heart-failure-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heart failure, which refers to when the heart is unable to pump enough blood to meet the body's needs, impacts over 6.2 million Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia drafts 134,500 conscripts...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-03-31/russia-drafts-134-500-conscripts-but-says-they-wont-go-to-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IS linked attacks spark fear of new enemy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220331-is-linked-attacks-in-israel-spark-fear-of-new-enemy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel has long been at war with Palestinian militants but recent deadly attacks claimed or inspired by the Islamic State group have raised fears of a new security threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popularity up since start of conflict...</title>
      <link>https://extra.cw/putins-popularity-up-since-start-of-ukraine-conflict-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;extra.cw&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;div class="txt-textContent tinyscrollbar-y jq_ScrollBar initialized scrol</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Receding -- and So Are Men's Hairlines...</title>
      <link>/https://www.wsj.com/articles/pandemic-balding-back-to-work-look-for-men-no-suit-no-tie-receding-hairline-11648661343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issues on sets...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/movies/news/concerns-about-bruce-willis-declining-cognitive-state-swirled-around-sets-in-recent-years/ar-AAVHiFT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operation 'Wave Breaker:' IDF aims to stem rising tide of terrorism...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-702782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Citizens of Israel, we are currently experiencing a wave of murderous terrorism and, just like in all the previous waves, we will prevail together,” Bennet said on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three dead as West Bank violence escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220331-three-dead-as-west-bank-violence-escalates</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli security forces on Thursday raided a West Bank town after three deadly attacks rocked the Jewish state in a week, with two Palestinians shot dead and a third killed after he launched a knife…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to issue gender-neutral 'X' passports...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/us-gender-neutral-x-passports-a5374c37-5bbe-4696-8df5-54e351086ce4.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a milestone for Americans who identify as nonbinary and gender-nonconforming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hungary, Orban Remakes Election to His Liking...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/31/in-hungary-viktor-orban-remakes-an-election-to-his-liking/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUDAPEST — During the dark winter of the 2020 coronavirus wave, the Hungarian government set up a website so anxious</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rugged Newcomer Looks to Fill Void Left by LAND ROVER...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/31/a-rugged-newcomer-looks-to-fill-a-void-left-by-land-rover/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMBACH, France — After a 33-year production run, the last original Land Rover Defender was built in 2016, ending a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK spy chief says soldiers disobey orders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-europe-australia-canberra-3d72fb96191029659575e4b368b80bd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Demoralized Russian soldiers in Ukraine were refusing to carry out orders and sabotaging their own equipment and had accidentally shot down their own aircraft, a U.K. intelligence chief said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'TRUTH' App Traffic Plummets; 93% Drop in Signups...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/trump-truth-social-app-93-drop-signups-traffic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The would-be Twitter killer has drawn only 1.2 million installations, according to Sensor Tower</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Indigenous people killed in 'clash' with Venezuelan military over WiFi...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/four-indigenous-people-killed-in-e2-80-98clash-e2-80-99-with-venezuelan-military-over-wifi/ar-AAVHKcR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Western sanctions, ruble and banks recovering...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Despite-Western-sanctions-Russian-ruble-and-17047731.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's ruble and banking system are showing continued signs of recovery from the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Weighs Massive Release of Oil to Combat Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-team-weighs-massive-release-005651511.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedy Clubs Worried About Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/comedy-club-security-will-smith-chris-rock-slap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget heckling. Do stand-ups need to brace themselves for physical assaults going forward?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China building Communist Party training school in Metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/beijing-building-communist-party-training-26582069</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The metaverse will be used in China for the first time at the state level as party authorities try to reinforce cadets' allegiance to the Communist Party using virtual reality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROCK STILL IN SHOCK</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/chris-rock-responds-will-smith-oscars-slap-1235218763/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What’s on Chris Rock’s mind? It’s a simple yet valid question, one that the world is wondering after Will Smith slapped the comedian on live television during the Oscars on Sunday…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Rocks Gets Standing Ovation In Boston...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/chris-rock-reaction-oscars-slap-will-smith-comedy-tour-1234991314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three days after he was attacked by Will Smith at the Oscars, Chris Rock made his first public appearance at the opening show of his Ego Death World Tour in Boston. Coming out on stage at about 8 P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor refused to leave Oscars after slap...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oscars-will-smith-entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-51713817b2f8aaf9c2ea5f06bcf234c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Academy of Motion Pictures Arts and Sciences on Wednesday said that Will Smith was asked to leave Sunday's Oscar ceremony after hitting Chris Rock but refused to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wanda Sykes slams for allowing to stay in theater...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10669497/Oscars-host-Wanda-Sykes-slams-Academy-allowing-Smith-stay-slapping-Chris-Rock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscars co-hosts Wanda Sykes called out the Academy for allowing Will Smith to remain in the theater after he slapped Chris Rock, a display she said made her feel 'physically ill.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Fighters Leaving Too...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akv898/foreign-fighters-quit-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A would-be fighter tells VICE World News that concerns over a lack of firepower, war tourists, and potentially being executed by the Russians have put him off joining Ukraine's foreign legion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tampered or deleted records?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/30/trump-used-white-house-phone-call-capitol-attack-jan-6-not-official-log</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s call to Republican senator should have been reflected in presidential call log on day of Capitol attack but wasn’t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, META GAVE USER DATA TO HACKERS</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-meta-gave-user-data-175918825.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. and Meta Platforms Inc., the parent company of Facebook, provided customer data to hackers who masqueraded as law enforcement officials, according to three people with knowledge of the matter.Most Read from BloombergNever Had Covid? You May Hold Key To Beating the VirusHome Prices Suggest Housing Bubble Brewing in U.S., Dallas Fed SaysUkraine Update: U.S. Doubts Russian Pullback; Lavrov in ChinaBiden Poised to Use Cold-War Powers to Boost Battery MetalsHackers Steal Abo</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
