<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Strange backdrop to G-20: Roman neighborhood built as fascist showpiece...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-strange-backdrop-to-the-g-20-a-roman-neighborhood-built-as-a-fascist-showpiece/ar-AAQ0l88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designed for the canceled the 1942 World’s Fair, EUR gets its moment in the spotlight eight decades later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA begins legal appeal to get Assange extradited...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-59063976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for the US say a judge who blocked Julian Assange's extradition was misled by a psychiatrist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb Tattoo Artist Kat Von D Closing Iconic West Hollywood Tattoo Shop...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/26/kat-von-d-west-hollywood-tattoo-shop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity tattoo artist Kat Von D is closing her famous West Hollywood shop, High Voltage Tattoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer star comes out as only known gay player...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/premier-league/3941634/josh-cavallo-gay-footballer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTRALIAN footballer Josh Cavallo has come out as gay – saying he is ‘tired of this double life’. He becomes the only currently active male professional in the world to do so. In…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYT columnist Kristof launches Oregon gov bid...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578682-ex-nyt-columnist-kristof-launches-oregon-governor-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Times columnist Nicholas Kristof said Wednesday he would formally enter the race to become Oregon’s next governor, setting up a race against what he called a system rigged against ordinary residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merchandise-Trade Gap Widens to Record as Exports Drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/u-s-merchandise-trade-gap-widens-to-record-as-exports-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Merchandise-Trade Gap Widens to Record as Exports Drop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild monkey sanctuary could be beginning of end for decades-old colony in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://lmtribune.com/nation/wild-monkey-sanctuary-could-be-beginning-of-end-for-decades-old-colony-in-florida/article_5f1de8f0-fd74-5ebd-94be-595d8c74781b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lmtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — A colony of wild monkeys in Dania Beach soon may get a permanent home, complete with fences, medical care and regular meals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines brace for 'onslaught' of travelers as USA opens borders...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/airlines-brace-for-e2-80-98onslaught-e2-80-99-of-travelers-as-us-prepares-to-open-its-borders/ar-AAQ0g4f </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced Colonics, Weekly Weigh-Ins: Feds Detail Creepy Child Abuse in Kansas 'Cult'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/forced-colonics-weekly-weigh-ins-220852842.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faleh Kheiber/ReutersLeaders of a Nation of Islam offshoot that has been labeled a “cult,” separated children from their parents, held them incommunicado under highly restrictive conditions, and made them work up to 16 hours a day for no pay, according to a shocking indictment unsealed Tuesday in Kansas federal court.The 20-page filing accuses eight officials with the United Nation of Islam (UNOI)—a splinter group that in 1978 broke away from Louis Farrakhan’s Nation of Islam—of conspiracy and f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick fingerprints all over NETFLIX biopic. Even what it leaves out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/colin-kaepernicks-fingerprints-are-all-over-his-netflix-biopic-even-what-it-leaves-out/ar-AAPYTju</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the hybrid docudrama 'Colin in Black and White,' the former NFL star teams with Ava DuVernay to dramatize his teen years 'without ambiguity.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: $547 million villa with world's only Caravaggio ceiling mural goes on sale...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/style/article/rome-villa-aurora-caravaggio-mural-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A stately villa in the heart of Rome, which houses the world's only ceiling mural by the Italian painter Caravaggio, will be auctioned at a starting price of 471 million euros ($547 million) in January, a court in Rome has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three FL teens killed classmate with sword in surprise attack, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Three-Florida-teens-killed-a-classmate-with-a-16567773.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulum Spiraling Into Deadly Cartel Battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dream-vacation-hotspot-spiraling-deadly-085732562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANIEL SLIM/AFP via Getty ImagesTwo foreign female tourists were caught in a crossfire between rival crime groups and shot to death last Thursday in the high-end resort town of Tulum, Mexico. Three other people were also wounded when the firefight broke out in the popular restaurant, La Malquerida, not far from the beach. Of the two women who were killed, one was from Germany and the other India.“They were just in the wrong place at the wrong time, and got caught in an exchange of gunfire betwee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Grapples With Death...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/features/halyna-hutchins-rust-death-investigation-1235098386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possibility of criminal charges resulting from the tragic death on the set of “Rust” is coming into focus as the industry grapples with the fallout from the Oct. 21 gun accident that left 42-ye…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities to present findings in Baldwin shooting... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prop-gun-shooting-entertainment-shootings-gun-politics-santa-fe-e6b4d769e5df47ee0c23d4ad69f1992d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — Investigators plan to discuss their initial findings Wednesday in the fatal movie-set shooting in which Alec Baldwin fired a prop gun, killing a cinematographer and wounding the director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian budget cautionary tale for USA...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/578527-a-brazilian-budget-cautionary-tale-for-the-united-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The moral of the Brazilian story for the U.S. is that U.S. policymakers should make every effort to quickly step off the Brazilian budget deficit and inflation path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slavery-era Georgia law key defense argument in trial over Ahmaud Arbery's killing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211027095855-nomq0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGIA-ARBERY-DEFENSE (PIX):Slavery-era Georgia law is key defense argument in trial over Ahmaud Arbery's killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan of hundreds of migrants press north across Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211027095855-1ve6m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MEXICO (PIX, TV):Caravan of hundreds of migrants press north across Mexico</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem billionaire tax faces constitutional, political hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/billionaires-tax-faces-constitutional-political-hurdles-n1282453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The question for tax writers and party leaders is whether they can thread those needles in drafting the details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance, first responders face 'crippling workforce shortage'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/labor/577879-ambulance-emt-first-responders-face-crippling-workforce-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 pandemic has dramatically worsened a nationwide staffing shortage for emergency medical technicians and paramedics bringing longstanding issues — including low federal reimbursement rates and salary con</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGETS 700 WEALTHIEST</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/578640-wyden-releases-billionaires-tax-proposal-for-spending-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Finance Committee Chairman Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) on Wednesday unveiled his proposal to tax billionaires’ investment gains annually, which could become a key provision in Democrats’ social-spending package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 40 Years, ABBA Takes Chance With Legacy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/27/after-40-years-abba-takes-a-chance-with-its-legacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STOCKHOLM — The small, tranquil island of Skeppsholmen holds a handful of the Swedish capital’s artistic treasures: Moderna Museet, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS UNVEIL BILLIONAIRE TAX</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-congress-319a4fe155a72dce4f71bc617547e3fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pushing past skeptics, Senate Democrats on Wednesday unveiled a new billionaires’ tax proposal, an entirely new entry in the tax code designed to help pay for President Joe Biden’s sweeping domestic policy package and edge his party closer to an overall agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot bought Epstein jet before sex-trafficking bust. He's now suing, calling plane 'tainted'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/10/27/jeffrey-epstein-jet-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgia man bought a jet and business from Jeffrey Epstein. Now he says the company is "damaged by the stigma" of Epstein's reputation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD top cop urges jab before Friday that could send quarter of force home without pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-nypd-dermot-shea-friday-covid-vaccine-mandate-deadline-20211026-bbegqkmknrgrrgvtgey6pnqefi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We have vaccines available throughout the city for our members,” Police Commissioner Dermot Shea said on NY1 Tuesday. “We have to prepare as if this is going to go into affect Friday evening and that’s exactly what we’re going to do.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markle was target of organized hate campaign on TWITTER, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/meghan-duchess-of-sussex-was-target-of-organized-hate-campaign-on-twitter-report-says/ar-AAQ09tr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After analyzing 114,000 tweets related to Harry and Meghan, an analytics company identified 83 accounts that it said were behind 70 percent of the more virulently anti-Sussex tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen. Milley Likens China Hypersonic Weapon Test to 'Sputnik Moment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/us-gen-mark-milley-likens-china-s-hypersonic-weapon-test-to-sputnik-moment/ar-AAQ048b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S.’s top uniformed military officer called China’s suspected test of a hypersonic weapons system a “very concerning” development in the escalating competition between Washington and Beijing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second California IN-N-OUT forced to close for violating rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/a-second-northern-california-in-n-out-is-forced-to-close-for-violating-covid-19-rules/ar-AAPZzdX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An In-N-Out Burger in Pleasant Hill was ordered to close Tuesday by Contra Costa County public health officials after refusing to comply with rules requiring restaurants to check indoor dining patrons for proof of COVID-19 vaccination or a negative test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Govt  crackdown intensifies in Cuba weeks ahead of planned opposition march...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/cuba/article255273001.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban authorities have threatened organizers of a pro-democracy march called for November with legal charges, while conducting a vast security operation to intimidate ordinary Cubans who express support of the initiative or criticize the government on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students assault girl, circulate video of attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/national/students-at-la-high-school-allegedly-assault-girl-and-circulate-video-of-attack/article_547c6896-9e06-516f-bd61-ac6105c72fee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A Hamilton High female student was allegedly sexually assaulted last week in a restroom by at least one male student — a reported attack partially captured on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Huma Says Senator Sexually Assaulted Her After DC Dinner...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/huma-abedin-says-senator-sexually-204944011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brendan McDermid/ReutersHuma Abedin writes in her forthcoming book that a U.S. senator sexually assaulted her in her 20s, kissing her unprompted and forcing his tongue in her mouth as the two conversed in his apartment.The longtime aide to Hillary Clinton, now 45, detailed the incident in her memoir Both/And: A Life in Many Words, set to be published next week, according to an excerpt obtained by the Guardian. Abedin withheld details of the senator’s identity, including his party affiliation, wh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Probe Social Media Footage of Sex Act in Class...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/10/25/woodlawn-high-school-baltimore-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A video clip circulating on social media that appears to show a sex act involving two students in a Woodlawn High School classroom is under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin machinations reach  crescendo as he distances from party...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/joe-manchins-machinations-reach-a-crescendo-as-he-distances-himself-from-his-party-while-cutting-deals-on-its-agenda-all-in-public-view/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Sen. Joe Manchin III started his Tuesday in a downtown hotel ballroom, trading stories with one of Washington's richest men in front of a crowd of hundreds of business leaders, journalists, and fellow politicians all scrutinizing his every...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases and deaths on rise again in Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.rte.ie/news/world/2021/1026/1255839-covid-global/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rte.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 infections and deaths are on the rise again in Europe, with Russia, Ukraine and Romania registering the highest fatalities on the continent, an AFP tally shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formula One racing gaining traction in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/formula-one-racing-is-gaining-traction-in-the-united-states-and-an-emerging-fan-base-is-along-for-the-ride/ar-AAPYQUF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Grand Prix drew 140,000 Formula One fans to Austin this past weekend, the latest sign of the sport’s popularity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago to create largest 'guaranteed basic income' program...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/chicago-poised-to-create-one-of-the-nation-e2-80-99s-largest-e2-80-98guaranteed-basic-income-e2-80-99-programs/ar-AAPWygB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Basic income programs are rapidly spreading across the country as critics raise concerns about record job openings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden makes final push for McAuliffe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-makes-a-final-push-for-mcauliffe-urging-virginia-voters-to-show-up-against-youngkin-e2-80-94-and-trump/ar-AAPZlOc </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  4TH COVID SHOT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/cdc-immunocompromised-covid-fourth-shot-1b47635c-c464-4d29-9832-3d94ea1cecf9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some immunocompromised people will be able to receive fourth doses six months after their third.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORT SAHL DEAD AT 94...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/10/mort-sahl-dies-groundbreaking-contrarian-comedian-was-96-1234863016/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mort Sahl, the acerbic 1950s comic whose pioneering style paved the way for such boundary-breaking comedians such as Lenny Bruce, Richard Pryor and George Carlin died Tuesday at his home in Mill Va…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criminal Charges Possible in Shooting on Baldwin Set, DA Says...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/26/criminal-charges-possible-in-shooting-on-alec-baldwin-set-d-a-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. — The Santa Fe County district attorney said on Tuesday that she was not ruling out criminal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romo under fire for 'creepy' comment about Brady's wife...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/26/tony-romo-under-fire-for-gisele-bundchen-comment-on-cbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cowboys legend Tony Romo is facing backlash over a comment he made about Tom Brady’s wife, Gisele Bündchen, during the “NFL on CBS” broadcast. On Sunday, the Buccaneers had to tra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate To Find Staff, Restaurants Recruiting Customers...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/10/26/fast-food-labor-shortage-recruitment-efforts-hiring-customers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raising Cane’s employees are approaching customers, asking them to apply at their Naperville dining room and drive-thru.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin 'COULD face charges', along with 2 others...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3935768/alec-baldwin-rust-shooting-civil-criminal-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEC Baldwin may be hit with civil charges over the film set shooting that killed a cinematographer while two others could face criminal charges, experts say. Dr. Leslie Y. Garfield Tenzer, a Pace …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA panel OKs for kids: 'Benefits outweigh risks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/26/fda-panel-endorses-covid-19-shot-for-kids-5-11-years-old-517236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Panel members voted 17-0 to recommend the shot, with one abstention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Star Challenges LeBron James To Visit Slave Labor Camps...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/26/enes-kanter-phil-knight-lebron-james-nike-china-slave-labor-camps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Celtics player Enes Kanter has continued to turn up the heat on Nike and China. He encouraged Phil Knight and LeBron James to visit the slave labor camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election 'distracted' from pandemic response, Birx tells Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation-politics/election-distracted-trump-team-from-pandemic-response-birx-tells-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Deborah Birx, who sat for interviews with a House subcommittee on Oct. 12 and 13, detailed advice that she said the White House ignored late last year. She estimated that more than 130,000 American lives could have been saved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'INFLATION HERE TO STAY'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/former-obama-economic-chief-inflation-is-here-to-stay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama's chief of global development on Tuesday predicted inflation was here to stay, contrary to the Biden administration's protestations to the contrary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil senators call for records of Bolsonaro's internet activity...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211026175257-30nxk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (PIX):Brazil senators call for records of Bolsonaro's internet activity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists may have found planet outside of Milky Way for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/10/26/1049282754/nasa-new-planet-discovered-outside-milky-way-galaxy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While researchers have found more than 4,000 planets in our own galaxy, this is the first time anyone has found what could be a planet that exists outside the Milky Way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen cancels appearance 'on medical advice'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211026-queen-elizabeth-cancels-cop26-attendance-on-medical-advice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's 95-year-old Queen Elizabeth II will not attend the COP26 UN climate conference in Glasgow, after "advice to rest" from doctors following an overnight hospital stay, her Buckingham Palace of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin Lead$ Cash on Hand...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/virginia/2021/10/finance-reports-show-youngkin-with-lead-in-cash-on-hand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the first three months of October, Republican candidate for Virginia governor Glenn Youngkin outraised Democrat Terry McAuliffe, while McAuliffe outspent Youngkin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Surtax' on Millionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/10/26/billioniare-tax-dems-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many lawmakers want to resolve their differences by the end of the week, but they are still stuck on the thorny issue of taxation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror groups in Afghanistan could launch international strikes in months...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/flashpoints/afghanistan/2021/10/26/terrorist-groups-in-afghanistan-could-launch-international-strikes-within-six-months-officials-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense officials say the threat demands vigilance from American forces, including counter-terrorism strikes in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reno Criminalizes Possessing Whips Without Permit...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/10/25/reno-criminalizes-possessing-whips-without-a-permit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carrying this archaeologists' accessory in the city's downtown without government permission is now a misdemeanor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Sends Troops Into Tulum After Shootout Kills Tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/mexico-sends-armed-forces-into-tulum-after-drug-shootout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico Sends Troopss Into Tulum After Shootout Kills Two Tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Is Lowest-Revenue Company to Hit $1 Trillion Market Value...</title>
      <link>https://www.ttnews.com/articles/tesla-becomes-lowest-revenue-company-hit-1-trillion-market-value</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ttnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc. has joined the trillion-dollar-valuation club as the member with the lowest revenue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Gets Pulled Into Virginia Gov. Race After Earlier Cold Shoulder...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-gets-pulled-into-virginia-race-after-earlier-cold-shoulder/ar-AAPYoic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Terry McAuliffe distanced himself from President Joe Biden earlier this month in a bid for more votes in the closely fought Virginia governor’s race, prompting some sharp retorts from the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems' New Target Is $5 Trillion in Billionaire Wealth...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/democrats-new-tax-target-is-5-trillion-in-billionaire-wealth/ar-AAPYq3W</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- With their latest tax proposal, Democrats are going after an elusive target: U.S. billionaires, and their growing piles of untaxed investment gains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'YEARLY BOOSTER'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/578448-moderna-chairman-says-booster-could-be-yearly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna Chairman Noubar Afeyan indicated on Tuesday that his company's COVID-19 shot could require yearly boosters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Tightens Discharge Rules for Covid Patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.rthk.hk/rthk/en/component/k2/1617056-20211026.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.rthk.hk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government has announced that patients who have recovered from Covid-19 and are ready to be discharged from hospital will need to spend an additio...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  40 FACEBOOK STORIES FROM PAPERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/facebook-papers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They paint a picture of Facebook that's very different from what Mark Zuckerberg likes to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Touch Screens Will Let You Feel Items Before You Buy...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2021/10/better-touch-screens-could-let-you-feel-stuff-you-buy-it/186294/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal is for the screen to mimic textures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey reveals photos of 15 alleged Mossad spies arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/turkey-reveals-photos-of-15-alleged-mossad-spies-arrested-683017</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged Mossad spies were of Arab descent and were reportedly present to spy on Palestinians living in Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK star accused of double murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/california-tiktok-star-pleads-not-guilty-to-double-murder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok star with nearly a million online followers pleaded not guilty to shooting and killing his newly estranged wife and a man she was with last week at a San Diego high-rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos to launch $10 billion luxury 'orbital reef' space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/jeff-bezos-build-luxury-orbital-25300989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon founder Jeff Bezos has announced that his space company, Blue Origin, will build the first private space station – it will host "exotic" space tourists and a "mixed-use business park"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms in Sights of Lawmakers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-algorithms-increasingly-sights-u-060000857.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. lawmakers investigating how Facebook Inc. and other online platforms shape users’ world views are considering new rules for the artificial intelligence programs blamed for spreading malicious content. Most Read from BloombergCities' Answer to Sprawl? Go Wild.Hamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaWhy Americans and Britons Are Rushing to Buy Idyllic Homes in ItalyOne of California’s Wealthiest Counties Could Run Out of Water Next SummerThe Top Money Mak</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
