<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Air Force struggles to recruit...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2022/01/21/air-forces-enlisted-recruitment-pipeline-is-drying-up-general-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 4,800 people entered the Air Force in the first quarter of fiscal 2022, down from around 7,100 at the same point in fiscal 2021. And there are fewer prospects in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to monitor for violence, extremist activity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/federal-officials-to-monitor-wasington-anti-vaccine-rally-for-potential-violence-and-extremist-activity-223850442.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement in Washington, D.C., have been closely monitoring social media for signs of potential violence and extremist activity ahead of a large demonstration against vaccine mandates this weekend, according to documents obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients hospitalized 'with' vs. 'for' shifting...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2022/01/21/number-of-patients-hospitalized-with-covid-vs-for-covid-is-shifting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But health experts say hospitals are still under strain and the virus remains serious business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunfire Erupts at Ritzy Cancun Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/gunfire-erupts-at-ritzy-playa-del-carmen-resort-one-dead/ar-AAT1i0z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unfiltered Year of Aaron Rodgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33088151/the-unfiltered-year-aaron-rodgers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This season, Aaron Rodgers has been brilliant on the field and unapologetically vocal off it. In an exclusive interview with ESPN, he explains why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for scapegoat leads to chief of staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/klain-under-scrutiny-biden-struggles-n1287801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the president rounds out his first year in office with multiple setbacks in his agenda and a sinking approval rating, some blame his chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 years since Covid confirmed in USA. Pandemic worse than anyone imagined...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/omicron-two-years-since-covid-was-first-confirmed-in-us-the-pandemic-is-worse-than-anyone-imagined.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the emergence of omicron, the future course of the pandemic is unclear as experts struggle to understand how new variants emerge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Media Doomed?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/21/media-journalism-future-527294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a Big Tech crackdown to the rebirth of local news, 16 future-minded thinkers predict where journalism will be in 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIVES OUT FOR KLAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/21/ron-klain-hot-water-527570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s chief of staff started strong and earned plaudits. But, increasingly, he’s under scrutiny for the state of the presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA wants to turn poo into 'space gold'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4513028/nasa-wants-to-recycle-poo-human-waste-space-missions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NASA is trying to work out how to recycle human waste, including poo and the carbon dioxide we breathe out, into useful products. Recycling waste could help astronauts go on longer missions without…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO REFUNDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/21/stubhub-adele-fans-wont-get-money-back-until-singer-reschedules-shows-cant-resell-tickets-now</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREET-PORTER: Sorry, can't take self-obsessed never-ending Sob Saga...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/debate/article-10428345/JANET-STREET-PORTER-just-chapter-Adeles-never-ending-Sob-Saga.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JANET STREET-PORTER: Adele has made millions from mining the trauma of her 'journey' from humble beginnings to millionaire single mum - but I have decided to get off the bus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX judge blocks vax mandate for federal workers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/21/texas-judge-blocks-biden-vaccine-mandate-for-federal-workers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ruling by Judge Jeffrey Brown stated that the order “amounts to a presidential mandate that all federal employees consent to vaccination against COVID-19 or lose their jobs.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In time for Olympics, China brings back anal swab testing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4512129/china-anal-swabs-covid-mandatory-winter-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has brought back its “undignified” anal Covid swabs just two weeks before the Beijing Winter Olympics begin. The Communist regime claims the virus test — which involves inserting …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Crash Erases $1 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crypto-meltdown-erases-more-1-171931934.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For Bitcoin, there’s only been one constant recently: decline after decline after decline. And the superlatives have piled up really quickly.Most Read from BloombergJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedTech Leads Late-Day Slide in Stocks; Bitcoin Sinks: Markets WrapEarly Omicron Breakthroughs Show mRNA Vaccines’ WeaknessCrypto Selloff Pushes Bitcoin to a Six-Month Low of $38,000American Airlines Sues The Points Guy Over Its Rewards Management AppWith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French politicians worry about surge in pre-election violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220121-french-politicians-worry-about-surge-in-pre-election-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French ruling party lawmaker Pascal Bois was at home asleep a few days after Christmas when firefighters banged on his front door to tell him his garage was in flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nation's largest abortion protest could be last under Roe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-texas-mississippi-constitutions-281018c3cd29f79d02444a539bc16d63</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Arriving by the busloads, thousands of anti-abortion protesters rallied in the nation’s capital Friday with a growing sense of optimism that their goal was finally in reach: a sweeping rollback of abortion rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probe gets over 700 pages of White House docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/january-6-riot-probe-gets-over-700-pages-of-trump-white-house-documents-after-supreme-court-ruling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The January 6 Capitol riot by Trump supporters began after Donald Trump falsely claimed he won the 2020 election over President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone -- that you sit in...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-59372326</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Personal drones that can transport one or two passengers will soon be available for anyone to buy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physicists developed bubble that didn't burst for more than year...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/french-physicists-developed-bubble-didnt-burst-year-rcna13077</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French physicists have figured out a way to extend the usually short lives of bubbles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The lonely final years of Andre Leon Talley...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10419739/Andr-Leon-Talley-spent-final-years-White-Plains-avoiding-covid-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;André Leon Talley, a fashion icon and driving and driving force behind Vogue's success, spent his last days secluded at home trying to protect himself from the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle, Detroit Move Toward Decriminalizing Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/20/seattle-and-detroit-move-toward-decriminalizing-psychedelics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two major cities, Seattle and Detroit, this fall approved measures aimed at protecting consumers of "entheogenic" plants and fungi from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are men drinking breast milk?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/why-are-men-drinking-breast-milk/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fetishists and bodybuilders have created a booming black market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic darlings fade as investors eye return to normal life...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-dump-pandemic-darlings-results-101014650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (Reuters) -Stay-at-home market darling Netflix slumped on Friday, joining a broad decline in shares of other pandemic favourites this week as investors priced in expectations for a return to normal life with more countries gradually relaxing COVID restrictions. The selloff, which began after Netflix and Peloton posted disappointing quarterly earnings, spread to the wider stay-at-home sector as analysts judged the new Omicron coronavirus variant will not deliver the same economic headwinds seen in the first phase of the pandemic in 2020. "This a confirmation that the economy is gradually moving towards some sort of normalisation," said Andrea Cicione, head of strategy at TS Lombard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% IN USA GET BOOSTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/booster-shots-in-us-have-strongly-protected-against-severe-disease-from-omicron-variant-cdc-studies-show/ar-AAT0Ijs?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAWN OF THE DIGITAL DOLLAR?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-federal-reserve-is-taking-the-next-step-toward-possibly-launching-a-digital-dollar/ar-AASZ8Vk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>END OF MARKET SUPERBUBBLE?</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/good-luck-well-all-need-it-u-s-market-approaches-end-of-superbubble-says-jeremy-grantham-11642723516</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is approaching the end of a 'superbubble,' potentially leading to the largest markdown of wealth in its history when pessimism returns to rule...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid  retreating? Data paints encouraging scenario...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/covid-retreating-u-data-paints-120602648.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (Reuters) -New coronavirus cases are falling in parts of the United States hit hardest by the fast-spreading Omicron variant, according to a Reuters analysis of public health data, offering an early indication the virus might once again be in retreat. COVID-19 infections have decreased in 19 states https://graphics.reuters.com/HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-OMICRON/zgvomadgmvd/USA-OMICRON.jpg plus Washington, D.C. and Puerto Rico, an analysis of the past week through Thursday compared with the prior week showed. In the Northeast, which saw some of the highest case loads during the latest surge, infections are down 40% week-over-week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAT LOAF DEAD AT 74...</title>
      <link>https://www.spin.com/2022/01/meatloaf-bat-out-of-hell-singer-dies-at-74/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meatloaf, the legendary '70s rock singer whose album 'Bat Out of Hell' became one of the best selling albums of all time, died</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX STOCK CRASHES AFTER SUB MISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/netflix-stock-down-20percent-after-earnings-show-growth-slowdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company still beat analyst expectations on the top and bottom line and in user numbers during the fourth quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Benedict XVI and the long history of scandal-plagued popes...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Pope-Benedict-XVI-and-the-long-history-of-16793703.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic Pope emeritus Benedict XVI committed "wrongdoing" in the way he handled sexual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent killings shock NYC, bring back bad memories...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/news/violent-killings-shock-ny-bring-back-bad-memories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One was thrown in front of an incoming subway train in Times Square. The other was shot over a few dollars at a burger joint. These recent violent deaths</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUIE ANDERSON DEAD AT 68...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/01/louie-anderson-dead-obituary-comedian-baskets-family-feud-emmy-winner-1234917040/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louie Anderson, the veteran comedian, game show host and three-time Emmy winner, has died. He was 68. The Baskets star died Friday morning in Las Vegas, where he had entered hospital this week for …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUIE ANDERSON DEAD AT 68...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/21/louie-anderson-dead-dies-blood-cancer-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louie Anderson Dead At 68, After Battle With Blood Cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic darlings face boot as investors eye return to normal life...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/finance/global-markets-stayhome-stocks-2022-01-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stay-at-home market darling Netflix slumped on Friday, joining a broad decline in the market value of other pandemic favourites this week as investors priced in expectations for a return to normality as more countries gradually relax COVID restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis won't say if boosted; Status could be used as 'weapon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/desantis-won-e2-80-99t-say-if-he-e2-80-99s-boosted-against-covid-19-says-status-could-be-used-as-e2-80-98weapon-e2-80-99/ar-AAT0HtA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom times back on Wall St with $15 million pay packages...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/goldman-partners-mint-15-million-pay-packages-as-boom-times-return-to-wall-street.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pay is up everywhere you look on Wall Street, from lowly first-year bankers to partners and top executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ DEEPER INTO CORRECTION... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/20/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks moved lower on Friday as sharp losses in streaming giant Netflix dragged the Nasdaq Composite deeper into correction territory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: Quarter Adults Too Lazy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/a-quarter-of-u-s-adults-are-too-lazy-new-cdc-map-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Quarter of U.S. Adults Are Too Lazy, New CDC Map Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID retreating? Data paints encouraging scenario...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/the-great-reboot/is-covid-retreating-us-data-paints-encouraging-scenario-2022-01-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New coronavirus cases are falling in parts of the United States hardest hit by the fast-spreading Omicron variant, according to a Reuters analysis of public health data, offering an early indication the virus might once again be on retreat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin McCarthy rallies support as he eyes pinnacle of power...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/21/politics/kevin-mccarthy-speaker-gop-conference/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin McCarthy was done being nice. The House Republican leader cast off his typically sunny demeanor during a December 8 meeting of the GOP conference to deliver a stern warning to his most raucous members: Quit trying to hold your vote for speaker over my head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>META, SNAP Sued Over Social Media 'Addicted' Girl's Suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/meta-snap-sued-over-social-media-addicted-girl-s-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta, Snap Sued Over Social Media ‘Addicted’ Girl’s Suicide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia records deadliest day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-australia-western-australia-new-south-wales-230fab794127d110d9df21ba1a22e244</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CANBERRA, Australia (AP) — Australia on Friday reported its deadliest day of the pandemic with 80 coronavirus fatalities, as an outbreak of the omicron variant continued to take a toll. But Dominic Perrottet, premier of the most populous state, New South Wales, said a slight decrease in hospitalizations gave him some hope about the strain the outbreak is putting on the health system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes erupt again over curbs on French island of Guadeloupe...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220121115830-fyrdd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-GUADELOUPE (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Clashes erupt again over COVID curbs on French island of Guadeloupe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID retreating? Data paints encouraging scenario...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220121115700-fg9q5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Computing Near Reality After Machine Reaches 99% Accuracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/quantum-computing-accuracy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists found it's possible to build these lightning-fast computers using current semiconductor manufacturing technology available today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pomegranate Extract May Hold Key To 'Fountain Of Youth' Treatment...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/pomegranate-fountain-of-youth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the fruit contains an extract called urolithin A, which they believe can protect against frailty during old age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax activists, reveling in successes, will rally in DC against mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anti-vaccine-activists-reveling-in-their-pandemic-successes-will-rally-in-dc-against-mandates/ar-AAT0re7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog duo helps provide first responders with extra support...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Dog-duo-helps-provide-first-responders-in-D-C-16793283.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - First responders defended the Capitol for hours on Jan. 6, many getting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury selection proceeds for Avenatti-Stormy Daniels trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-health-donald-trump-california-f2b48f32efd7f83b3fd0c6285eb1d977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Michael Avenatti, the once high-profile California attorney who regularly taunted then-President Donald Trump during frequent television appearances, was introduced Thursday to prospective jurors who will decide whether he cheated porn star Stormy Daniels out of book-deal proceeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has rule-breaker Johnson met his match in 'partygate'?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/boris-johnson-europe-london-92b49a05ae7210ef09486e276e968b9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — For Boris Johnson, facts have always been flexible. The British prime minister’s career is littered with doctored quotes, tall tales, exaggerations and mistruths. When called out, he has generally offered an apologetic shrug or a guilty grin, and moved on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ: BECAME SERIOUSLY ILL WITH COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/01/21/meat-loaf-dead-dies-singer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meat Loaf, one of the greatest rock singers of all time, has died at the age of 74 from COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's Monkey Queen Faces Challenge to Her Reign: Mating Season...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/21/japans-monkey-queen-faces-challenge-to-her-reign-mating-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smashing the patriarchy in the human world has been easier said than done. But last year, a 9-year-old female Japanese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Oral CBD Prevented COVID Infection in Real-World Patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/bvn743/oral-cbd-prevented-covid-19-infection-in-real-world-patients-study-suggests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While not a substitute for vaccines, "CBD has the potential to prevent infections, such as breakthrough infections," the study's lead author said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Brady &amp; Co. prep for RAMS -- West Coast version of BUCS title team...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/tom-brady-26-co-prep-for-rams-e2-80-94-a-west-coast-version-of-bucs-e2-80-99-title-team/ar-AAT02Dm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court, investigators force family on defensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-investigators-force-trump-and-his-children-on-the-defensive-on-multiple-fronts/ar-AAT080Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film Studio to Be Launched in Space in '24...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/film-studio-space-tom-cruise-see-1235077958/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEE-1 studio module, to be attached to a new commercial space station, comes from the company co-producing Tom Cruise's upcoming space movie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrencies tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/cryptocurrencies-bitcoin-falls-7percent-ether-down-9percent-in-the-last-24-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About $147 billion was wiped off the entire cryptocurrency market in the past 24 hours, according to data from Coinmarketcap.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAT LOAF DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4509131/meat-loaf-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGING legend Meat Loaf has died at the age of 74 after a stellar career spanning six decades. Born Marvin Lee Aday in Texas, he shot to fame with his powerful, wide-ranging voice. The star sold m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4507704/adele-reschedules-las-vegas-residency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADELE has cancelled her Las Vegas residency less than 24 hours before the first show was due to kick off. The British pop superstar, 33, posted a teary video on Instagram explaining why the highly-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Tory says Boris team blackmailed MPs to stem rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/politics/2022/jan/20/boris-johnson-ministers-confidence-vote-whipping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PM optimistic he can overcome a confidence vote as whipping alleged to veer into blackmail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel probes alleged police cyber-spying on citizens...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/world/middle-east/israel-probes-alleged-police-cyber-spying-on-citizens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The A-G have asked to receive all wiretapping and computer spying orders from 2020 and 2021. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa, Texas Republicans hail benefits from Biden infrastructure bill  -- they opposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/iowa-texas-republicans-hail-benefits-from-biden-infrastructure-bill-they-opposed/ar-AASYs8G?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON says its first clothing store will have palm-scanning checkout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/amazon-says-its-first-irl-clothing-store-will-be-tech-forward/ar-AASYIsN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED MAY ISSUE DIGITAL CURRENCY</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/the-federal-reserve-is-taking-the-next-step-toward-possibly-launching-a-digital-dollar/ar-AASZ8Vk?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driverless trucks set to take over roads in TX...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/texas-driverless-trucks-set-over-013928808.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A giant 18-wheel transport truck is barreling down a multi-lane Texas highway, and there is no one behind the wheel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears medical records stay SEALED...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britney-spears-conservatorship-documents-stay-194721664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Britney Spears and dad Jamie Spears squabbled over 'lies' and conservatorship finances during a heated hearing in L.A. Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASY ON HER:  ADELE CANCELS VEGAS...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/20/not-surprised-tearful-adele-postpones-vegas-says-weve-been-absolutely-destroyed-by-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/breaking-adele-tour-reschedule-cancelled-26006368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer says she's been 'destroyed' by Covid and it's 'impossible' to finish the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100 snakes found in home with dead man's body...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/more-than-100-snakes-found-in-maryland-home-where-mans-death-was-reported</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A death investigation is underway at a Charles County home full of more than 100 venomous and non-venomous snakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED MAY ISSUE DIGITAL CURRENCY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/20/fed-releases-long-awaited-study-on-a-digital-dollar-but-doesnt-take-a-position-yet-on-creating-one.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed released its exploration of a digital dollar, exploring the pros and cons of the much-debated issue and soliciting public comment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump friends worry legal pick for NY case lacks experience...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trumps-friends-alarmed-legal-pick-3e28ee26-3325-481d-9e08-245be18d56c9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Alina Habba frequents Trump’s Bedminster, N.J., country club, which is how they got to know one another, one source told Axios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Miami-London flight turns around over Atlantic after mask dispute...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2022/01/20/american-airlines-flight-london-turned-around-mask-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flight 38 was about an hour and a half into its flight to Heathrow Airport when it circled back and returned to Miami International Airport.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
