<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia put crucified body on public display after 37 executions...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-put-crucified-body-14579574</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amnesty International say teenagers are among those killed by the oil-rich state who has been accused of targeting the Shi'ite minority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coachella: Huge Spike In Herpes Reported On Festival Grounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.hotnewhiphop.com/coachella-2019-a-huge-spike-in-herpes-reported-on-festival-grounds-news.78249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotnewhiphop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coachella 2019 was an unforgettable experience for some of the more active participants. According to TMZ, the 2019 edition of Coachella has incited a nasty outbreak of herpes. Initially reported by HerpAlert, the internet's number one resource in diagnosing the STD, the outbreak was caused by, you ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Students appalled by 'creepy' touching...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=12141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"That's definitely excessive..."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen readies Western-style album...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f95c785e2f564a909d1e4d32e8fb5472</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Fresh off his Broadway run, New Jersey's Bruce Springsteen looked West for inspiration on a new album he's planning to release on June 14. The 13-song disc is his first new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside decision to run one more time...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0da41bc7243c434b8d6522cc344c61bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden spent a hot August day at his lakefront Delaware home watching hatred on display in Charlottesville, Virginia, where, days earlier, torch-wielding white supremacists had marched through...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Campaign going to be parody of self...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/836978/joe-bidens-campaign-going-parody-itself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get your bingo cards ready for the debates, folks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sloppy launch may cost him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/440603-bidens-sloppy-launch-may-cost-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden better finish strong, because the start couldn't be going much worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President taunts...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/440598-trump-mocks-sleepy-joe-after-biden-jumps-into-2020-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday mocked Joe Biden after the former vice president launched his campaign for the Democratic presidential nomination in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comAMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comAMAZON tops 'dirty dozen' list of most dangerous workplaces...&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says Never Asked McGahn to Fire Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-says-he-never-asked-mcgahn-to-fire-mueller-11556196379</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Thursday contradicted a detailed account in Mr. Mueller’s report, tweeting that he never told White House Counsel Don McGahn to fire special counsel Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BATTLE FOR SOUL OF NATION'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/joe-biden-launches-2020-presidential-run-n998236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president enters the race polling ahead of all 19 other candidates in the Democratic field, but will it last?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY UNLOADS: 'DERANGED DONALD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/george-conway-loses-it-deranged-donald-doesnt-need-books-because-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6958783/Ex-Vice-President-Biden-launches-2020-presidential-campaign.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden formally entered the race for the presidential race Thursday in an announcement that struck directly at President Donald Trump and laid out the former vice president's vision to led the nation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS JUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/25/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The underlying trend continued to point to labor market strength, however.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bartiromo stock rises at FOX...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-himi-maria-bartiromo-fox-news-20190425-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former CNBC anchor who originated live reporting from the New York Stock Exchange now anchors 17.5 hours of programming a week at Fox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans abandoning high-tax states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/economy/americans-high-tax-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from 2018 shows more Americans moved out of higher-tax states than into them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just 16 MINUTES less sleep than need can wreck whole day...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/real-life/774372/sleep-insomnia-how-much-cant-sleep-tired-better-nights-sleep</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Broadcaster Under Scrutiny for Disseminating Propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-broadcaster-under-scrutiny-for-disseminating-propaganda-11556184602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials are scrutinizing the U.S. government’s Radio Free Europe / Radio Liberty news service, established to promote democratic values abroad, after complaints it has distributed foreign propaganda favorable to authoritarian regimes in Central Asia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'Narcos' Danger Zone to Rising Tourist Star: Colombia's Medellin...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/from-narcos-danger-zone-to-rising-tourist-star-colombias-medellin-11556123510 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young entrepreneurs are turning Medellín and its surroundings—former Escobar country—into one of South America’s most dynamic destinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half Schizophrenia Cases Misdiagnosed; Just Anxiety...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/hopkins-study-half-schizophrenia-cases-misdiagnosed-anxiety/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A significant number of people declared schizophrenic by their doctors may be misdiagnosed. A small study of patients referred to the Johns Hopkins Early Psychosis Intervention Clinic (EPIC) with diagnoses of schizophrenia found that about half didn't have the disease at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Luxury Loses Luster in Hamptons as High-End Homes Pile Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-25/luxury-loses-luster-in-the-hamptons-as-high-end-homes-pile-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials Tried to Kill American Mall. Gen Z Might Save It...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-25/are-u-s-malls-dead-not-if-gen-z-keeps-shopping-the-way-they-do </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin praises Kim efforts to improve ties with rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fbe1a8e788aa444481ef8d3f638f834f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIVOSTOK, Russia (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said after his summit with Kim Jong Un Thursday that the North Korean leader is ready to proceed toward denuclearization — but needs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At WALMART, using AI to watch the store...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d416ba3945d64975994805db55467744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEVITTOWN, N.Y. (AP) — Inside one of Walmart's busiest Neighborhood Market grocery stores, high resolution cameras suspended from the ceiling point to a table of bananas. They can tell how ripe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven big decisions facing Joe in primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440573-seven-big-decisions-facing-biden-in-2020-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden announced his presidential candidacy on Thursday and joins the c</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete draws new scrutiny, criticism...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440556-buttigieg-draws-new-scrutiny-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pete Buttigieg’s early success in the Democratic primary has prompted scrutiny and rougher treatment from his rivals and the news media, creating new challenges for the rising star and his campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN LAUNCHES</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/d5c415b99a6945dbbecf60d57bcf68cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former Vice President Joe Biden formally joined the crowded Democratic presidential contest on Thursday, betting that his working-class appeal and ties to Barack Obama's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest presidential field in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/campaigns/biden-entry-makes-2020-democrats-the-largest-presidential-field-in-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With former Vice President Joe Biden set to enter the 2020 fray on Thursday, the Democratic field contesting the right to challenge President Trump for the White House next year will be a record 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star on Hollywood Walk of Fame defaced by vandal -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/04/24/president-trump-putins-bitch-vandalized-hollywood-walk-of-fame-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's Walk of Fame star got a fresh coat of paint, but he ain't gonna be thrilled about it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie gets tough reception at minority women's event, signaling challenges ahead... </title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Sanders-gets-tough-reception-at-minority-women-s-13793574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON - The groans erupted halfway through Bernie Sanders' appearance Wednesday at a presidential candidates' forum sponsored by She the People, a group that aims to drive up voter participation among women of color.  Before an audience of about 1,700, many of them African-American and Hispanic women, the moderator asked Sanders, I-Vt., how he would handle the rise in white supremacy. Sanders spoke of fighting discrimination and running a campaign "to bring our people together around an agenda that speaks to all people" - then returned to a familiar message on universal health care.  For many in the audience, that was insufficient. "Come on!" a woman shouted from the back, as others began to jeer and boo.  The reception reflected Sanders' struggle to win support from minority voters, a problem that dogged his 2016 primary campaign against Hillary Clinton. Sanders has taken steps since to improve his outreach, including meeting with black leaders and talking more frequently about the difficulties facing minorities, but Wednesday's event suggested the senator still faces challenges.  Sanders at one point mentioned his long record on civil rights, but it did little to mollify the crowd.  "I was actually at the March on Washington with Dr. King back in 1963, and - as somebody who actively supported Jesse Jackson's campaign, as one of the few white elected officials to do so in '88 - I have dedicated my life to the fight against racism and sexism and discrimination of all forms," Sanders said. That prompted audible groans.  Sanders may have come into the event at a disadvantage, since many black women supported Clinton in 2016. Some Clinton backers believe Sanders did too little to help her after she won the nomination.  Sanders did eventually coax a warmer reception when he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEX AT 60: MADONNA FIGHTS FOR AIRPLAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6957033/Madonna-transforms-bride-snogs-male-suitor-licks-TOE-dramatic-video.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pop legend, 60, reveals at the beginning of the visual extravaganza that she will now only be known by the moniker Madame X, which is the name of her new album.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey mayor tells TWITTER user to call the cops on Jewish 'invaders'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/04/24/new-jersey-mayor-tells-twitter-user-to-call-the-cops-on-jewish-invaders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Jersey mayor is facing mounting backlash for telling a constituent to call the cops on Jewish people for going to the beach. Brick Township Mayor John G. Ducey was responding to a flat-out an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Can't Afford to Keep Talking About Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2019/04/24/britain-cant-afford-to-keep-talking-about-brexit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The never-ending conversation about leaving the EU has stalled all other progress on economic policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaffolding firm says workers smoked at Paris' Notre-Dame...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424184708-qxte6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-NOTREDAME/ (PIX):Scaffolding firm says workers smoked at Paris' Notre-Dame</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanic Temple Says Recognized as Church by IRS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/satanic-temple-tax-exempt-hail-satan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organization is the first satanic group granted tax-exempt status of other religious institutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie Warns: White Working-Class Trump Voters Could Hand 2020 Election to Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/chris-christie-white-working-class-trump-voters-could-hand-2020-election-to-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Playoff Ratings Sink to New Lows...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/04/24/nba-playoffs-ratings-sink-new-lows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a small rise in viewers last weekend, the NBA playoffs are still sinking in the ratings, according to the numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS RELEASING 1,400 ILLEGALS INTO USA EVERY DAY... </title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/04/24/dhs-releases-seven-thousand-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-five-days-released-every-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's DHS has released about 7,000 border crossers and illegal aliens into the interior of the U.S. in the last five days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57% SEE ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AS THREAT TO HUMAN RACE...</title>
      <link>https://scottrasmussen.com/57-see-artificial-intelligence-as-threat-to-human-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;scottrasmussen.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty-seven percent (57%) of voters believe that Artificial Intelligence (A.I.) is at least somewhat of a threat to the human race. A ScottRasmussen.com national survey found that 43% disagree and do not see it as a threat.Those figures include 16% who consider A.I. is a Very Serious threat while 10% say it is not a threat at all.Concern about A.I. threatening the human race has been a regular feature of science-fiction films, including classics such as The Matrix. The number currently considering A.I. to be a threat is up three points since November. Other recent studies show a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA May Ban Schools From Suspending Students For Defiance Of Teachers...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/23/willful-defiance-bill-senate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California State Senate voted to ban schools and principals from suspending students for "willful defiance" of teachers, staff, and administrators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Stars Demand FOXDISNEY Bring Smollett Back -- Or Else...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/empire-cast-crew-letter-jussie-smolett-return-fox-disney-1202601208/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Empire co-creator Lee Daniels told a New York City morning show Wednesday that the fate of Jussie Smollett on the Fox hit is “in discussions” right now, but Taraji P. Henson, Terrence Ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases hit highest level since eradication in 2000...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190425000013-u7mcf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-U.S. measles cases hit highest level since eradication in 2000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel chair accuses President of 'massive' obstruction...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424233941-6j2nq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/ (UPDATE 7, PIX):UPDATE 7-House panel chair accuses Trump of 'massive' obstruction; Trump vows to fight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC tickets 12 people for defying measles vaccination order...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424194017-a9z9p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MEASLES/:New York City tickets 12 people for defying measles vaccination order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of armed militia group attacked in jail...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424190640-j4n8c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MILITIA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Leader of self-styled U.S. citizen border patrol attacked in jail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated pilots get Navy to stop dismissing UFO sightings...</title>
      <link>https://www.philly.com/news/nation-world/unidentified-flying-objects-ufos-navy-document-encounters-20190424.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent uptick in sightings of unidentified flying objects - or, as the military calls them, "unexplained aerial phenomena" - prompted the U.S. Navy to draft formal procedures for pilots to document encounters, a corrective measure that former officials say is long overdue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULTRA music stressed fish more than chase by predator...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/article229610019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstate blocked as 30,000 pounds of TV dinners spill off big rig...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/24/gold-run-tv-dinner-big-rig-fire-i-80/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A truckload of TV dinners caught fire and blocked Interstate 80 in the Sierra Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked pics of China 11,509-mph HYPERSONIC rocket...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8933644/leaked-china-secret-hypersonic-nuke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHILLING photos have been leaked onto the internet which some fear show China’s top secret 11,509mph hypersonic rocket system aimed at dodging US defences. Images of the impressive Jia Geng N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: 80% of tweets come from small minority of accounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewinternet.org/2019/04/24/sizing-up-twitter-users/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewinternet.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter users are younger, more likely to identify as Democrats, more highly educated and have higher incomes than U.S. adults overall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FIGHTING ALL SUBPOENAS'</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/trump-blasts-house-oversight-probes-says-white-house-fighting-all-n998046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump called himself the "most transparent president ever" amid blocking officials from appearing before Congress and suing to keep financial documents secret.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama staying on sidelines as VP set to launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/obama-staying-on-the-sidelines-as-biden-gets-ready-to-launch-his-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden’s expected to declare his candidacy for president on Thursday. But when he does, don’t expect his running mate – former President Barack Obama – to speak out in support of his bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIEBER DENIES COACHELLA LIP SYNC -- SORTA...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/music/news/justin-bieber-ariana-grande-address-coachella-lip-synch-controversy-1203197026/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Justin Bieber joined Ariana Grande on stage at the Coachella Festival Sunday night to perform his hit “Sorry,” there was little doubt in anyone’s mind about whether it was co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: STARTS WITH EDGE OVER TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/04/24/joe-biden-is-the-front-runner-over-democrats-and-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As former Vice President Joe Biden prepares to enter the race for the Democratic presidential nomination, he’s doing so as the front-runner, polling ahead of both fellow Democrats and President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Police!' Lookout parrot trained to alert drug dealers keeps beak shut after arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/24/brazil-drug-parrot-trained-as-lookout-for-dealers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bird was taught to alert criminals to officers’ presence, according to reports: ‘As soon as the police got close he started shouting’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacked LIME Scooters Shout Sexual Messages at Riders...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/lime-scooters-hacked-to-say-sexual-things-to-riders-in-1834264534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight Lime e-scooters have been pulled from the streets of Brisbane, Australia this week after they were hacked to say sexual and otherwise offensive things. Lime calls the hack “disappointing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT HITS TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/24/microsoft-q3-2019-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft kicked off tech earnings season and the stock jumped after revenue topped estimates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beset by infighting, NRA faces toughest foe: Own members...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/bda97817dabf492e9be8099bdd1a4cd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association is used to battling forces that criticize its fiery and unbending efforts to protect gun rights. But as the group gathers for its annual convention this week, the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds probe claims Governor removed mansion toilets to get tax break...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/04/24/report-feds-investigating-claims-pritzkers-removed-mansions-toilets-to-get-tax-break/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — The so-called "toilet fiasco" that dogged Gov. J.B. Pritzker during his campaign has not gone away, as new reports indicate the matter is currently the subject of a federal investigation. During the same week Pritzker marks 100 days in office,  WBEZ reports investigators are looking into whether he and his wife broke the law by removing toilets from their Gold Coast mansion to get a tax break.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Fighting to Keep Most Watched Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netflix-battles-rivals-for-its-most-watched-shows-friends-and-the-office-11556120136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood studios that licensed old TV shows to Netflix are getting into streaming and want their hits back. It’s a threat to Netflix because its viewers spend much of their time watching reruns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tabby with longest rap sheet seeks day in court...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/eastside/miska-bellevues-most-persecuted-tabby-cat-seeks-her-day-in-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miska's owner, Anna Danieli, has filed a lawsuit against Regional Animal Services of King County, alleging the agency has unfairly targeted the 10-year-old cat as a “vicious,” trespassing animal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How THE INTERCEPT Fueling Democrat Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/24/the-intercept-greenwald-grim-profile-media-politics-left-liberal-226710</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The national security site has found fresh energy as a savvy, progressive attack dog in national politics. But is it undermining its own side?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Kissing bug' returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.delawareonline.com/story/news/health/2019/04/23/remember-kissing-bug-cdc-confirms-one-found-delaware/3548857002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delawareonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "kissing bug"Â â€” which bites people around their mouths and can pass along theÂ fatal disease Chagas â€” has officially made it to Delaware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidates confront letting notorious felons vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/66cc1a8de27e460096b8147aec0a2dcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential contenders are facing a new debate over whether criminals in prison, even notorious ones like the Boston Marathon bomber, should be able to win back their right to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Worker Falls Into Meat Grinder At Processing Plant...</title>
      <link>https://wnep.com/2019/04/22/worker-killed-after-falling-into-meat-grinder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wnep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUNCY TOWNSHIP, Pa. -- The Lycoming County coroner says a worker is dead after falling into a meat grinder at a processing plant near Muncy. It happened at Economy Locker Storage Company in Muncy Township. The coroner says Jill Greninger, 35, fell into the machinery around 11:30 a.m. Monday. Greninger's death has shocked people who live near the meat packing plant near Muncy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE 'BADDEST' CAT IN AMERICA?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/04/24/americas-baddest-cat-gets-trouble-police-30-times-9313764/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miska, 'America's baddest cat,' has been in trouble with the law 30 times in her life, but now her owner is claiming that her cat has been unfairly targeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handshakes could be BANNED under new workplace physical contact rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8930608/handshakes-banned-workplace-rules-sexual-harassment-claims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS celebrate deadliest-ever attack with poster of burning Pope...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8930150/isis-poster-sri-lanka-bombings-celebrate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUMMINGS: 'Massive' obstruction by Trump, Barr...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-oversight/house-oversight-chairman-cites-massive-obstruction-by-trump-barr-idUSKCN1S02KE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic chairman of the House Oversight Committee accused the Trump admin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Police Say Crash Into 8 People On CA Street May Be 'Domestic Terrorism'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/24/sunnyvale-pedestrians-crash-fbi-investigation-terrorism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI was assisting Sunnyvale police Wednesday in investigating a driver who allegedly intentionally slammed his vehicle into eight people on a Sunnyvale street, severely injuring several of them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic microbe lurks on SC coast. Older fat men should worry most...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/state/south-carolina/article229621849.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High school's new dress code bans leggings, pajamas -- for parents...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-high-school-s-new-dress-code-bans-leggings-13791086.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not exactly unusual for school dress codes to become a source of controversy. But the latest flare-up has a new twist: This time, it's parents being told what they can and can't wear on campus.  As the Houston Chronicle first reported, one high school principal warned parents earlier this month that they will be turned away if they show up at their child's school wearing hair rollers, leggings, silk bonnets or any other items on a list of banned clothing. The announcement followed a widely publicized incident in which a prospective parent was turned away from the school for showing up in a T-shirt dress and headscarf.  "We are preparing your child for a prosperous future," Carlotta Outley Brown, the principal of James Madison High School in Houston, wrote in a letter to parents on April 9. "We want them to know what is appropriate and what is not appropriate for any setting they might be in."  To many parents, KTRK reported, the dress code appeared to be laden with racial undertones. For one thing, it didn't apply to the whole school district, just to one high school with a majority of minority and low-income students. According to the Houston Independent School District, 58 percent of the students at Madison High School are Hispanic, and 40 percent are African American. Nearly three-quarters of the students are eligible for free and reduced-price lunch.  "I'm almost insulted," said Tomiko Miller, the mother of a current student, told the Chronicle. "I really think it was discriminatory, the language that was used. It was demeaning. And I'm African American - and if it's misty outside and I have a hair bonnet on, I don't see how that's anyone's business."  In her letter to parents, Brown wrote that sagging pants or shorts were off limits, and men couldn't arrive in undershirts. Low-cut tops were banned, as were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte threatens war on Canada if they don't take back trash...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/04/24/716692612/philippines-duterte-talks-trash-literally-to-canada-threatening-war-over-garbage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 100 shipping containers had been declared to hold recyclable plastic scraps. But when they arrived in Manila, officials found household trash, including adult diapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOY SCOUTS face demands to open 'perversion files'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/lawyer-demands-boy-scouts-open-perversion-files-n997786</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The organization has identified 7,819 scoutmasters who allegedly molested boys.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measles cases hit highest mark in 25 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d9ea7938e026451e885aca6128351c39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — U.S. measles cases in 2019 have climbed to their highest level in 25 years in a resurgence largely attributed to misinformation that is turning parents against vaccines. New...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic device winds own way through beating heart...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/22f2c18962fa4c8da74e95e790398489</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Borrowing from the way cockroaches skitter along walls, scientists have created a robotic device that safely guides itself through the delicate chambers of a pig's heart as it's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON 'Alexa' Listeners Have Customers' Home Addresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/amazons-alexa-reviewers-can-access-customers-home-addresses/ar-BBWfwuH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franklin Graham to Buttigieg: Repent, don't 'flaunt' being gay...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article229629454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Approves First-Ever Electric Shock Treatment For ADHD...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/04/23/adhd-treatment-electrical-shocks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monarch eTNS is a small electrode patch worn on the forehead, usually overnight, that stimulates branches of the sensory trigeminal nerve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Use AI to Turn Brain Signals Into Speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/scientists-use-artificial-intelligence-to-turn-brain-signals-into-speech-11556125200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have harnessed artificial intelligence to translate brain signals into speech, in a step toward brain implants that one day could let people with impaired abilities speak their minds, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More people than ever dying in CA jails...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/investigations/california-prisons/article229376524.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON 'Alexa' Listeners Have Customers' Home Addresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-24/amazon-s-alexa-reviewers-can-access-customers-home-addresses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROID RAGE: Man Behind Pipe Bombs Sent To Lawmakers Blames Steroids!</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/04/24/pipe-bomb-cesar-sayoc-steroids/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cesar Sayoc made the assertion in lengthy and rambling letters to a federal judge that were posted in his court case file Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen Walks Back Guilty Plea in Tom Arnold Calls...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-cohen-in-recorded-phone-call-walks-back-parts-of-guilty-plea-11556121974</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s former lawyer has disavowed responsibility for some of the crimes to which he has pleaded guilty, privately contending in a recent recorded phone call that he hadn’t evaded taxes and that a criminal charge related to his home-equity line of credit was “a lie.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picture emerges of well-to-do young bombers behind Sri Lankan carnage...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sri-lanka-blasts/picture-emerges-of-well-to-do-young-bombers-behind-sri-lankan-carnage-idUSKCN1S00G2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details began to emerge in Sri Lanka on Wednesday of a band of nine, well-educat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President opposed to aides testifying before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-says-he-is-opposed-to-white-house-aides-testifying-to-congress-deepening-power-struggle-with-hill/ar-BBWe7Ho</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  White hopefuls face 'woke litmus test'...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/texas/article/White-presidential-candidates-face-woke-litmus-13790431.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — After touring the National Lynching Memorial recently, former Colorado Gov. John Hickenlooper spoke of the "shame" he felt that some white people "kind of looked the other way during these lynching incidents." Former U.S. Rep. Beto O'Rourke of Texas has acknowledged he "clearly had advantages" as a white man. Sen. Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts has said that any struggle she faced as a single mom was much more challenging for black women. U.S. Rep. Tim Ryan of Ohio has talked about not knowing many black people when he was growing up. And Mayor Pete Buttigieg of South Bend, Indiana, recently said , "Any white candidate needs to show a level of consciousness around issues like white privilege." Such rhetoric surrounding race is becoming what Democratic strategist Joel Payne called a "woke litmus test" for any white person who wants to win the Democratic presidential nomination. In a field celebrated for its historic racial and gender diversity, white candidates are talking about systemic racism and white privilege to connect with voters of color and prove that America's racial divisions aren't lost on them. "All candidates, especially nonethnic minority candidates, need to be fluent in the issues that matter most to black America — police brutality, criminal justice reform, reparations, social justice," said Payne, an alumnus of Hillary Clinton's 2016 presidential campaign. White presidential candidates are among the contenders who will have another chance to connect with voters of color on Wednesday at the She the People forum in Houston. The event, which is focused on women of color, includes O'Rourke, Warren and Sen. Bernie Sanders of Vermont as speakers. There are clear risks to Democrats who embrace talk of white privilege. Candidates could lose the moderate white men who live in suburbs...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Already $107M in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/avengers-endgame-track-100m-china-opening-day-1204309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on early data, analysts are predicting the superhero tentpole will become Hollywood's first film to earn more than half a billion dollars in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS BLUFFING?</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/white-house-to-fight-dems-subpoena-of-ex-white-house-counsel-don-mcgahn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House will fight House Democrats' subpoena of testimony and documents from ex-White House counsel Don McGahn, Fox News is told -- and almost immediately, House Judiciary Committee chairman Jerry Nadler, D-N.Y, characterized the move as "one more act of obstruction" by the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS HIT MORE RECORD HIGHS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/24/stock-market-wall-street-looks-to-facebook-microsoft-earnings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks traded slightly higher on Wednesday as Wall Street also digested another batch of corporate earnings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katzenberg in 'tug-of-war' to host fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/81deb09157d64b138a0b6493cac004af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pete Buttigieg is suddenly the hottest ticket for Democratic donors in the 2020 presidential contest. Entertainment moguls are fighting over who will host Hollywood...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump suggests Mexican army disarmed US troops as cover for drug smuggling...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-says-sending-armed-soldiers-us-mexico-border-132914220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said Wednesday the US is sending armed soldiers to the southern border after Mexican soldiers recently "pulled guns" on US troops. Trump appeared to be referring to an April 13 incident in which Mexican troops reportedly questioned and pointed their weapons at two US</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors at Ebola epicenter threaten strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/doctors-ebola-epicenter-congo-threaten-strike-150024444.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BUTEMBO, Congo (AP) — Doctors at the epicenter of Congo's Ebola crisis are threatening to go on strike indefinitely if health workers are attacked again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disaffected Venezuelan military tell of rising desertions to Brazil...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424134550-qr20h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VENEZUELA-POLITICS/MILITARY (PIX, TV):Disaffected Venezuelan military tell of rising desertions to Brazil</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leader of armed militia group attacked in jail...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190424121135-e0bd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/MILITIA:Leader of U.S. border armed militia group attacked in jail -attorney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUST SAY NO...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/04/white-house-escalates-battle-to-keep-don-mcgahn-silent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is pulling out all the stops to keep his former White House counsel from testifying before Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump accuses Britain of spying on him ahead of visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8929990/donald-trump-accuses-britain-of-spying-on-him-as-he-ramps-up-tensions-ahead-of-showdown-uk-visit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has accused the UK of helping the Obama administration SPY on him during the 2016 presidential campaign. The US President made the sensational claim in a tweet today, quoting the right…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: NO SCREENS UNDER TWO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8929504/kids-under-two-no-tv-screens-obesity-who/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIDS under two should never be allowed to watch TV, tablets or smartphones, according to the World Health Organisation. The first ever global guidance on physical activity and sleep for young child…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University hosts no-whites-allowed meetings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/university-hosts-no-whites-allowed-faculty-and-staff-listening-sessions-to-promote-inclusivity/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workshops scheduled amid racial tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man impersonates ICE officer to rob construction workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/local/crime/article229601599.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE SHOWDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-plans-to-fight-house-subpoena-of-former-counsel-donald-mcgahn-for-testimony-on-mueller-report/ar-BBWdPXY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents vote on removing Michael Jackson's name from school auditorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-edu-michael-jackson-name-on-school-debate-20190424-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Gardner Street Elementary School principal scheduled the vote following a documentary in which two men accused Jackson of molesting them as children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caveman's poop reveals he ate entire rattlesnake...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/774321/archaeology-poop-coprolites-prehistoric-caveman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump suggests Mexican army disarmed US troops as cover for drug smuggling...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/440356-trump-suggests-mexican-soldiers-disarmed-national-guard-troops-as-cover-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump in a tweet Wednesday morning accused Mexican soldiers involved in a recent confrontation with U.S. troops along the border of aiding drug cartels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete doubts Sanders can win general election...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440398-buttigieg-says-he-doubts-sanders-can-win-general-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg said he doubts fellow hopeful Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) can beat President Trump in a general election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WELD:  We would be much better off with Pence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/440381-weld-we-would-be-much-better-off-with-a-president-mike-pence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Massachusetts Gov. William Weld (R), who is challenging President Trump in the 2020 Republican presidential primary, says the country would be better off if Trump resigned immediately.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to fight impeachment effort in Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/776978c0f18c43d09da644c320bf0658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump said Wednesday he'll go directly to the U.S. Supreme Court "if the partisan Dems" ever try to impeach him. But Trump's strategy could run into a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea Kim upbeat as he arrives for Putin summit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5fb86dab3ebd4bcb9f26318c88afc25c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIVOSTOK, Russia (AP) — North Korean leader Kim Jong Un stepped off his khaki-green armored train in far-eastern Russia on Wednesday, smiling and upbeat ahead of a much-anticipated summit with...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
