<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters confronted; Pushes camera, waves papers, sticks out tongue!</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/watch-laura-loomer-confronts-maxine-waters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Clings To Hood Of Speeding MERCEDES On I-95 In FL --  While Talking On Cellphone!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/25/man-seen-on-hood-of-car-on-i-95/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just when you thought you had seen everything on South Florida roadways, along comes something that makes you shake your head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters confronted: Pushes camera, waves papers, sticks out tongue!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-maxine-waters-confronted-by-reporter-pushes-camera-waves-papers-sticks-out-tongue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxine Waters can dish it out, but she can’t take it. Big League Politics reporter Laura Loomer met (confronted?) the California Congresswoman in the hallway of a House office building on Monday, and Waters didn’t appreciate being asked a few questions. ﻿ After Loomer told Water she’s an investigative journalist, Waters repeatedly demanded, “Who are …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDakota town could abolish itself to stop white supremacist takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article213792799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2013 white supremacist Craig Cobb tried to turn Leith, North Dakota into a white enclave but failed. Now Leith's mayor, Ryan Schock, concerned that two possible Cobb followers were elected to the town council, wants to scrap the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Considers Creating 'Fake News Advisory Group' To Monitor Media...</title>
      <link>http://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2018/06/25/california-considers-fake-news-advisory-group/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California is considering creating a "fake news" advisory group in order to monitor information posted and spread on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-mansions for world's elite compete for most extreme home ever built!	</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6627569/most-expensive-mansions-helipad-cinema-extreme-millionaire-man-caves-built/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SWANKY mega-mansion with a rooftop helipad, 40-person cinema and a swimming pool is vying to be crowned the ultimate man cave. Six glamorous homes, which are all on the market for eye-watering su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berserk at 33,000FT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6626700/spirit-airlines-passenger-screaming-meltdown-plane-diverted-medical-emergency-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the moment a furious passenger launched into a foul-mouthed tirade on a busy plane after it was diverted due to a medical emergency yesterday. The woman is seen screaming and sprinting towa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montage: Media Framing Trump Voters as Public Enemy No. 1...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-montage-media-turning-trump-voters-public-enemy-no-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘If you vote for Trump, then you, the voter, you, not Donald Trump, are standing at the border, like Nazis’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Rare 'Roll Cloud' Sparks Fears Of UFO Near Memphis...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/06/24/ominous-formation-identified-as-rare-roll-cloud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roll clouds usually appear to be "rolling" about a horizontal axis, but should not be confused with funnel clouds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  ABCNEWS reporter encounters smuggler with illegals at US-Mex border...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/video/smugglers-border-56157099</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABC News' Tom Llamas travels a path near McAllen, Texas, used by smugglers use to illegally transport immigrant families</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY REBOOT?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mitt-romney-against-state-lawmaker-senate-primary-140955039--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Mitt Romney will learn Tuesday if he'll continue the reboot of his political career as voters were deciding a primary in the race for a Utah Senate seat vacated by Orrin Hatch, who is retiring after more than 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aliens? Russians? Who owns mysterious object that washed up on Outer Banks?</title>
      <link>http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article213776794.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious metal object washed ashore along in Corolla at the North Carolina Outer Banks. Locals are trying to figure out who it belongs to, what it does, who is responsible for removing it. The Navy and Army Corps of Engineers don't know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waters confronted: Pushes camera, waves papers, sticks out tongue!</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-maxine-waters-confronted-by-reporter-pushes-camera-waves-papers-sticks-out-tongue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxine Waters can dish it out, but she can’t take it. Citizen Journalist Laura Loomer met (confronted?) the California Congresswoman in the hallway of a House office building on Monday, and Waters didn’t appreciate being asked a few questions. ﻿ After Loomer told Water she’s an investigative journalist, Waters repeatedly demanded, “Who are you?” “I’m …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED HEN owners 'followed Sanders into next restaurant'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5885663/Mike-Huckabee-says-liberal-Red-Hen-owners-harassed-daughter-more.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Arkansas Governor Mike Huckabee said his daughter was heckled even more than what was originally said by owners of a Virginia restaurant who asked her to leave last Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bikini-clad women in HUGE brawl as Pride festival turns into chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/712297/Bikini-women-brawl-San-Francisco-Pride-Parade-festival-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese blogger stabbed to death after internet abuse seminar...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/26/japanese-blogger-kenichiro-okamoto-stabbed-to-death-after-internet-abuse-seminar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cybercrime expert Kenichiro Okamoto reportedly killed by man who abused him online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank staffing branches with humanoids that dance, take selfies and push credit cards...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/26/this-bank-is-staffing-branches-with-humanoid-robots-that-dance-take-s.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HSBC is the first to employ humanoid robots in a U.S. bank branch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scourge of Mexico establishment poised to capture presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-election-lopez-obrador-newsmak/scourge-of-mexico-establishment-poised-to-capture-presidency-idUSKBN1JM189</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For 13 years, Mexico's perennial political outsider Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador has covered tens of thousands of miles crisscrossing the nation in dogged pursuit of its highest office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Austria deploys troops for immigration exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/austria-deploys-police-troops-immigration-exercise-border-130118812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria deployed police, soldiers and Black Hawk military helicopters on Tuesday in an exercise, overseen by the far-right interior minister, which enacted the arrival of hundreds of migrants on its border with Slovenia. The drill, designed to show Austria's preparedness for any repeat of Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American money -- flowing back into America...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/american-money-is-flowing-back-into-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. companies return billions to America in repatriation record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Unveils Hypersonic Airliner...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/712276/boeing-hypersonic-plane-concorde-airliner-new-york-london-mach-5-plane-future</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red meat allergies caused by ticks on rise...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/red-meat-allergies-caused-tick-bites-rise/story?id=56140087 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say that this year's tick season is shaping up to be possibly the worst in recent memory. Beyond Lyme disease and other tick-borne ailments, a new threat is emerging from ticks whose bites can prompt an allergy to red meat. Can a tick bite make you allergic to red meat? Tick bites can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens HARLEY: If moves overseas 'will be taxed like never before!'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/26/trump-says-harley-davidson-using-trade-tensions-as-an-excuse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said that Harley-Davidson will be "taxed like never before" and that the U.S. motorcycle company was using increased trade tensions as an excuse to justify planned shifts in production overseas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Unveils Hypersonic Airliner...</title>
      <link>http://aviationweek.com/commercial-aviation/boeing-unveils-hypersonic-airliner-concept</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;aviationweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mach 5 cruise speeds will enable intercontinental day return flights, even across the Pacific, and increase asset utilization, says Boeing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. King: America heading toward another civil war...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/onpolitics/2018/06/25/steve-king-america-civil-war/733226002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"America is heading in the direction of another Harpers Ferry," controversial conservative Rep. Steve King tweeted Sunday. "After that comes Ft. Sumter."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog performs CPR on 'collapsed' officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/dog-performs-cpr-collapsed-officer-12792928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The video of Poncho the police dog performing CPR and doing mouth-to-mouth on his officer has gone viral</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poliovirus used to fight brain tumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/enemy-turned-ally-poliovirus-used-110117288.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world's most dreaded viruses has been turned into a treatment to fight deadly brain tumors. Survival was better than expected for patients in a small study who were given genetically modified poliovirus, which helped their bodies attack the cancer, doctors report. It was the first human</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealed: World's most (and least) expensive cities...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/revealed-most-expensive-places-emigrate-104253535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four of the five most expensive cities in the world in which to live are in Asia, according to a new ranking of the cost of living. Hong Kong topped the 24th annual survey by Mercer, reclaiming the title of world’s dearest city from the oil-rich capital of Angola, Luanda, which ranked highest last year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Flight attendants have higher risk of all types of cancers...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/cabin-crew-cancer-risk-flight-attendant-radiation-exposure-sleep-cycle-obesity-smoking-a8416166.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exposure to cancer-causing radiation, usually blocked by atmosphere, sleep disruption and other carcinogens may all factor in disease rates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man born without penis to have sex for first time with bionic manhood...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5882201/Man-44-born-without-penis-finally-able-sex-time.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Wardle, 44, from Manchester, has spent the last four years undergoing surgery to have a bionic penis fitted. Now he has completed the final stage, and he can look forward to having sex in six weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers in America killing selves in staggering numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/american-farmers-rising-suicide-rates-plummeting-incomes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farming has by far the highest suicide rate of any occupation in the U.S. -- plummeting incomes may be one reason</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Even Swedes Questioning Welfare State...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2018/06/26/now-even-swedes-are-questioning-the-welfare-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now Even Swedes Are Questioning the Welfare State</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller Poised to Zero In on Trump-Russia Collusion Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/uselections/2018/06/26/mueller-poised-to-zero-in-on-trump-russia-collusion-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller Poised to Zero In on Trump-Russia Collusion Allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out 'climate change' suits against big oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/science/article/Judge-throws-out-SF-and-Oakland-climate-change-13025637.php?cmpid=gsa-sfgate-result</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge Monday tossed out two groundbreaking lawsuits by San Francisco and Oakland that sought to hold some of the world’s largest oil companies liable for climate change. In an exhaustive, 16-page ruling that touched on such scientific matters as the ice age and early observations of carbon dioxide, U.S. District Judge William Alsup acknowledged the problem of a warming planet but said it is just too big for the courts to solve. The cities are trying to get five oil and gas giants, including Bay Area-based Chevron, to help cover the costs of dealing with sea-level rise, like picking up the tab for seawalls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising concerns over hackers using satellites to target USA...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/394037-satellites-become-latest-tool-for-hackers-targeting-businesses-consumers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapidly expanding number of satellites transmitting GPS locations, cellphone signals and other sensitive information is creating new opportunities for hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest suspended for rapping to congregation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nation.co.ke/counties/migori/Migori-priest-suspended-for-rapping/1183306-4628346-m5frgv/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nation.co.ke&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Father Paul Ogalo given time to "change his ways".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WANTED' FLYERS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/25/protest-outside-white-house-adviser-stephen-millers-apartment-pass-out-wanted-flyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'defeating fascism and the Trump regime ... '</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even low-level officials bullied...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article213805514.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As feelings harden over Trump's immigration policies, internet shaming campaigns arise alongside open calls for harassment of administration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Feds Warn Antifa To End ICE Occupation Or Be Arrested...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/25/federal-authorities-warn-antifa-ice-occupation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Subject to arrest and prosecution in federal court'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities abandon 'zero-tolerance' for families...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/23c44b26627f4adcbcdb69504f9dab88/Authorities-abandon-'zero-tolerance'-for-immigrant-families</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McALLEN, Texas (AP) — The Trump administration has scaled back a key element of its zero-tolerance immigration policy amid a global uproar over the separation of more than 2,300 m</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES PAGE ONE TUESDAY:  Resist too far?</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-democrats-shaming-trump-20180625-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Democrats are embracing idea of harassing Trump administration officials in public, but others fear it will backfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bourdain participated in 'death ritual' months before suicide...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2018/06/25/anthony-bourdain-participated-in-death-ritual-months-before-suicide/?_ga=2.26482495.383149507.1529978748-173086073.1518796806</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late TV chef talked about his own mortality — and participated in an ancient death ritual — in the season finale of his CNN show “Parts Unknown.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents Rescue 57 Illegals in AZ Record Heat...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/az-border-patrol-agents-rescue-57-illegal-immigrants-in-record-heat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group included a pregnant teen and a one-year-old child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERGER MANIA: Media deal would create 3rd-largest TV station group... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/media-merger-create-3rd-largest-tv-station-group-160355990.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Gray Television Inc. and Raycom Media Inc. are announcing a merger that would create the third-largest television broadcast group in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aims for the stars...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/head-space-nation-aims-stars-183056989.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It sounds appealing given the state of politics on Earth: a plan to launch a utopian "space nation" with the aim of transcending earthly divisions. At a lavish ceremony in Vienna's Hofburg Palace on Monday, some 200 attendees inaugurated Russian scientist and businessman Igor Ashurbeyli</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beginning of End of Bilderberg?</title>
      <link>https://www.mintpressnews.com/bilderberg-era-end/244731/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mintpressnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like him or hate him, President Trump has played a major part, if only by saying the unsayable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Space kingdom' seeks citizens for life beyond Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/space-kingdom-seeks-citizens-life-beyond-earth-very-201140050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIENNA (Reuters) - Feel like the world is going to the dogs? Want to get away from it all? Here's a solution: become a citizen of the nation of Asgardia and hope it makes good on its promise to colonise the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autism traits could be 'edited' out...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2018/06/25/autism-traits-significantly-reduced-breakthrough-gene-editing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Autism traits may be &amp;ldquo;edited&amp;rdquo; out using new genetic techniques, scientists have said, following a successful trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanist says prayers blocked him from committing acts of evil...</title>
      <link>https://www.christiantoday.com/article/former-satanist-says-christian-prayers-blocked-him-from-committing-acts-of-evil/129815.htm </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.christiantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#MeToo Snares More Than 400 High-Profile People...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/25/-metoo-snares-more-than-400-high-profile-people-as-firings-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;#MeTooc campaign: From March-May, 60% of those accused of misconduct were fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOBY: POP MUSIC IS TERRIBLE...</title>
      <link>http://www.tv3.ie/xpose/article/entertainment-news/270457/Pop-music-is-terrible-says-electronica-star-Moby</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tv3.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The star urged pop musicians to 'make something that's actually worth listening to'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA crowd heckles CNN Acosta...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/curtis-houck/2018/06/25/go-home-jim-trump-supporters-heckle-fake-news-jim-acosta-ahead-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours before President Trump arrived on Monday night at a South Carolina campaign rally with incumbent Republican Governor Henry McMaster, CNN’s chief White House correspondent and carnival barker Jim Acosta faced quite the crowd behind him during a live shot with chants of “go home, Jim” and “fake news Jim,” while one attendee moved from side to side with a “CNN Sucks” sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey intervened to kill WIKILEAKS immunity deal...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/394036-How-Comey-intervened-to-kill-Wikileaks-immunity-deal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A limited immunity deal, which might have temporarily freed the WikiLeaks founder from exile in a London embassy, fell apart with distrust on both sides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media's Anti-Trump Rhetoric Increasingly Violent...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/05/12/media-rhetoric-trump-administration-violent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned animal carcass left on porch...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/government/2018/06/increasing-threats-to-homeland-security-include-burned-animal-carcass-left-on-staffers-porch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA SPYSCRAPERS ACROSS USA REVEALED</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/06/25/att-internet-nsa-spy-hubs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These fortress-like AT&amp;amp;T buildings are central to a secret NSA program that has monitored billions of communications, documents and sources reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Who Yelled 'F*ck Trump' At President is Dem Senator's Intern...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/25/democrat-intern-yelled-at-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'will continue to work there'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals Label Dems Who Discourage As 'Accomplices'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/25/us/politics/trump-liberal-activists-shaming.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent days, Democratic deliberations over how to confront President Trump have been swamped by activists’ public shaming, worrying Democratic officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities force hermit living naked on deserted island to return to civilization after 29 YEARS...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5883941/Hermit-lived-naked-deserted-island-29-YEARS-returned-Japan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;82-year-old Masafumi Nagasaki shunned a life in the entertainment industry to go live on the remote island of Sotobanari in 1989. But now authorities have forced him to return to mainland Japan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Fallon Forgets to Log Off Before Praising Himself for Anti-Trump Tweet...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/jimmy-fallon-forgets-log-praising-anti-trump-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy Fallon deleted a tweet in which he praised himself for a donation to a pro-immigration non-profit intending to troll President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando ends surveillance using AMAZON tech [for now]...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/2018/06/25/orlando-ends-amazon-rekognition/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial period simply ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Into Wild With Kanye: 'Lost Who I Was Living In Mob-Thought Universe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/25/arts/music/kanye-west-ye-interview.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three days in Wyoming as the hip-hop firebrand tends to his scars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Extends Training to Make Grunts More Lethal...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2018/06/25/army-add-2-months-infantry-course-make-grunts-more-lethal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army is refining a plan to extend by two months the service's 14-week infantry one station unit training, or OSUT.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Swedes insert microchips into bodies...</title>
      <link>http://nationalpost.com/news/world/thousands-of-swedes-are-inserting-microchips-into-themselves-heres-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’ve been inserting NFC chips somewhere between the thumb and the index finger. These are the same microchips that have been used to track animals and packages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delaware Backs Overhaul of Shell-Company Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/delaware-backs-overhaul-of-shell-company-rules-1529946813</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State with more companies than people endorses a federal change to corporate registration law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Tank Relationship With Funder: 'GOOGLE is a person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonian.com/2018/06/24/has-new-america-foundation-lost-its-way-anne-marie-slaughter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scandal over the encroachment of big business triggered a debate over the identity of a prestigious Washington think tank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New supervolcano brewing under New England...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/science/2018/06/25/new-supervolcano-is-brewing-under-massachusetts-vermont-and-new-hampshire.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something unexpected has been gradually making itself known to geologists in the United States. A huge mass of molten rock is creeping upwards beneath the nation’s north eastern states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP AIDES URGED TO GET GUNS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/amid-threats-trump-aides-urged-to-get-concealed-carry-permit-guns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing a new wave of potentially dangerous threats, called for by a top Democratic lawmaker, legal and gun experts are calling on top Trump aides to get their concealed carry permit and back it up with a pistol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occupy protesters ordered to abandon camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/index.ssf/2018/06/feds_order_occupy_ice_pdx_prot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street's Newest Hot Commodity: $185 Sandwich...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2018-06-25/don-wagyu-review-185-wagyu-steak-sandwiches-on-wall-street</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the only place to find this beef in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whale crashes like 'torpedo' into ferry...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/wildlife/2018/06/22/whale-crashes-like-torpedo-into-alaska-ferry-may-have-suffered-fatal-injuries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A whale struck the side of the ferry Tustumena traveling a scheduled route between Homer and Kodiak. The ferry sustained minor damage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico arrests town's ENTIRE police force over murder mayoral candidate'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5882607/Mexico-arrests-towns-ENTIRE-police-force-28-murder-mayoral-candidate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each officer from the town of Ocampo was cuffed, disarmed, and made to lie on the floor face down with their hands cuffed behind their backs before they were interrogated by internal affairs officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In England, Hillary Trashes Electoral College...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-england-hillary-trashes-americas-electoral-college</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We will leave discussion of the American Electoral College for another day’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  INSTAGRAM estimated to be worth $100 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-25/value-of-facebook-s-instagram-estimated-to-top-100-billion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook Inc.’s Instagram is estimated to be worth more than $100 billion, if it were a stand-alone company, marking a 100-fold return for the app was purchased in 2012, according to data compiled by Bloomberg Intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Navy scrambles after 2 Russian warships head toward UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/712095/russian-warships-intercepted-royal-navy-english-channel-boikiy-stoikiy-hms-monstrose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper boycotting Super Bowl over NFL anthem policy...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/watch-atlanta-rapper-says-boycotting-the-nfl/bUIBwNKE3cHqsG3EjkXM2L/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta rapper and well-known Atlanta Falcons fan T.I.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARS Found RAISING Prices In 'Liquidation Sale' As Stores Prep To Close...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/06/22/liquidation-deals-compared-sales/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WCCO compared prices on several items at the Brooklyn Center Sears just before liquidation started, and again on the first day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Fires Back At Maxine...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/25/donald-trump-to-maxine-waters-be-careful-what-you-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump slammed Rep. Maxine Waters on Monday afternoon, after her speech calling for supporters to heckle members of the Trump administration went viral over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATERS HISTORY OF PRAISING VIOLENCE...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/25/maxine-waters-race-riots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Coast Guard Alert After Plane Lands On NJ Beach, Pilot Seen Running Away...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/25/pilot-flees-scene-landing-small-engine-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A small engine plane lands on the beach in Cape May after witnesses say the pilot was flying erratically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Introduces $5 Million Phone Hacking Surveillance Van...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/company-introduces-5-million-phone-hacking-surveillance-van/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'SpearHead 360' van reportedly comes with zero-day exploits for Android and Apple devices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duterte slammed for calling God 'stupid'...</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/world/article213778869.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Philippine president, notorious for having cursed the pope and former U.S. President Barack Obama, has sparked outrage for calling God "stupid" in Asia's largest Catholic country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Glover facing plagiarism charges for 'THIS IS AMERICA'...</title>
      <link>http://pitchfork.com/news/childish-gambino-collaborator-denies-this-is-america-plagiarism-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Crowe to play Roger Ailes in SHOWTIME series...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/06/25/russell-crowe-roger-ailes-fox-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime has greenlit a limited series that gives a behind-the-scenes look at the rise of Fox News and landed a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Feds slip into Portland ICE HQ as protesters sleep outside...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/index.ssf/2018/06/feds_enter_portlands_ice_headq.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves first marijuana med...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/06/25/fda-approves-countrys-first-medicine-made-from-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Epidiolex, a drug manufactured by GW Pharmaceuticals, is made of a cannabidiol, or CBD, a component of marijuana, and is prescribed as an oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poking the bear: US Air Force builds in Russia backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/smr/nato-priorities/2018/06/25/poking-the-bear-us-air-force-builds-in-russias-backyard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force is quietly ramping up investments that would enable it to deploy to allied bases in Eastern Europe and operate close to Russia’s western flank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAXINE CALLS IN THE MOB</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/393937-Sarah-Sanders-Red-Hen-moment-shows-mob-medias-mentality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s time for a mutual de-escalation before things get worse...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming question for Mueller probe: How much to make public?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/looming-mueller-probe-much-public-043721298.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — America has waited a year to hear what special counsel Robert Mueller concludes about the 2016 election, meddling by the Russians and — most of all — what Donald Trump did or didn't do. But how much the nation will learn about Mueller's findings is very much an open question</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo stops play during Australian soccer match...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5881211/Socceroos-need-sub-Roo-make-final-16-leaves-players-shock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A kangaroo invaded a Canberra women's premier league match on Sunday afternoon. The kangaroo jumped from the stands and dashed madly across the field during the soccer game in ACT.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
