<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Criminal summons 'erroneously issued' against Cuomo...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesunion.com/state/article/Criminal-summons-erroneously-issued-against-16572344.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesunion.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A criminal summons charging Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo with forcible touching was erroneously...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulances could be scarce...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/drastic-nyc-first-responder-shortages-feared-as-vaccine-mandate-deadline-hits-friday/3358544/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no pool of substitutes this time around. And the FDNY expects 20% fewer ambulances on the road and 20% of fire companies closed come Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Weirdness of LaPierre, NRA's Reluctant Leader...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/10/the-weirdness-of-wayne-lapierre-the-nras-reluctant-leader</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the National Rifle Association can’t shoot, can’t schmooze, and has the “backbone of a chocolate eclair,” says a former board member—yet commands one of the most influential right-wing organizations in politics. In his new book, ‘Misfire,’ Tim Mak outlines LaPierre’s fall upward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK GOES META</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-mark-zuckerberg-facebook-5ad543ab7780caae435935f0aca9fac6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg said his company is rebranding itself as Meta in an effort to encompass its virtual-reality vision for the future — what Zuckerberg calls the “metaverse.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brother-in-Law Called Stock Broker 1 Minute After Call With Senator...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/burrs-brother-in-law-called-stock-broker-one-minute-after-getting-off-phone-with-senator</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the SEC, Sen. Richard Burr of North Carolina, then chairman of the Senate Intelligence Committee, had material nonpublic information about coronavirus impact. He and his brother-in-law dumped stock before the market dropped in March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange lawyer argues WIKILEAKS founder still suicide risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/video/20211028-assange-lawyer-argues-wikileaks-founder-still-suicide-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US general warns China's military progress 'stunning'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/28/politics/hyten-stunning-china-military-progress/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the wake of China's test of a hypersonic missile, the second most senior US general said Thursday that the pace at which China's military is developing capabilities is "stunning" while US development suffers from "brutal" bureaucracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NHL Player Sexually Assaulted By Coach Comes Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3948206/kyle-beach-chicago-blackhawks-john-doe-sexually-assaulted-coach/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOCKEY player Kyle Beach has come forward as “John Doe”, the former Chicago Blackhawks player suing the franchise for failing to act on sexual assault claims he aired against the team&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor creates world's first unisex condom...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10138783/Malaysian-gynecologist-creates-worlds-unisex-condom.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malaysian gynaecologist Dr John Tang Ing Chinh said he designed the Wondaleaf Unisex Condom to allow people take better control of their sexual health regardless of their sex.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools debate: Gifted and talented, or racist and elitist?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-education-new-york-city-united-states-race-and-ethnicity-f8cbdb50edba9802fe9ad503cfe7d467</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Communities across the United States are reconsidering their approach to gifted and talented programs in schools as vocal parents blame such elite programs for worsening racial segregation and inequities in the country’s education system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidding war over two-year-old minivan? Used car market 'bananas'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/10/28/used-car-prices-chip-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unraveling of the used car market is the most tangible result of a problem that has plagued the global economy for the last year: a dire shortage of computer chips that has hobbled auto manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devastating Life Of Long Hauler: 299 Days Later, 44-Year-Old Man Leaves Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-long-hauler-alex-castro-299-days-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the number of COVID cases is trending downward, some survivors are having a hard time recovering from the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On front lines of culture wars: Cable news...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/578582-on-the-front-lines-of-americas-culture-war-cable-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cable TV news, with its blurred line between news and opinion, has become one of America's most divisive institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. mystery: Mourning doves stopped singing. What happened to them?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/l-mystery-mourning-doves-stopped-120034266.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hearing the mourning dove again was a revelation, but with it came a realization: the wistful coo hadn't been in the air for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality TV's Absurd New Extreme...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2021/10/alter-ego-sexy-beasts-reality-tv-disguise/620508/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a genre premised on artifice got obsessed with disguise</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/10/28/biden-framework-for-build-back-better-social-climate-bill.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden will announce Thursday that he has reached a deal with Senate Democratic holdouts on a social spending and climate bill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEVIES ON INCOME ABOVE $10 MILLION...</title>
      <link>https://nz.finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-poised-unveil-framework-spending-114312711.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nz.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden Thursday was laying out for House Democrats a framework for a $1.75 trillion tax and spending package that his administration believes will pass Congress -- a potential breakthrough that still hinges on support from key moderates and progressives.Most Read from BloombergA Deep Dive Into Squid Game's World of InequalityMeet Six People Fighting Water Scarcity Across the GlobeHamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaThe Terrifying Rise of Hau</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican to Exorcists: Please Don't Try to Cast COVID Out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vatican-exorcists-please-don-t-085357986.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast/GettyROME—The pandemic was hard on almost everyone with lockdowns and other restrictions, but it appears to have been particularly trying for the demonically possessed. The world’s Catholic exorcists were unable to carry out their work in person, creating what was essentially a devil’s playground for those who believe.And so the 15th annual exorcism conference, held in Rome this week after a one-year hiatus due to COVID, has turned up all sorts of new pandem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN JOE SELL IT?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-joe-biden-business-wv-state-wire-congress-60a1bc276d0ab8eb3e0347fc54ee8c2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden traveled to Capitol Hill early Thursday to make the case to House Democrats for a dramatically scaled-back domestic policy package, $1.75 trillion of social services and climate change programs the White House believes can pass the 50-50 Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT warns BILLIONS of passwords hacked...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/3950378/microsoft-billions-passwords-hacked-check-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICROSOFT has issued a stark warning to those who reuse their passwords across multiple online accounts. In a blog post this week, the US tech titan said it had identified an uptick in the use of &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gave Nazi salute at school board meeting to oppose mask rules. Cruz defended...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-man-gave-a-Nazi-salute-at-a-school-board-16570878.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - In a hearing on Wednesday, Sen. Ted Cruz, R-Texas, pressed Attorney General...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Chinese city placed under lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211028-third-chinese-city-placed-under-covid-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China placed a third city under lockdown on Thursday to tackle Covid-19 numbers, with around six million people now under orders to stay home as Beijing chases zero cases before the upcoming Winter O…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow shuts down as Russia sees record virus cases, deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211028-moscow-shuts-down-as-russia-sees-record-virus-cases-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia reported record numbers of daily coronavirus cases and deaths on Thursday as Moscow shut down non-essential services for 11 days to combat the surge in infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Humans are mistake': More young women getting sterilized...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/27/why-more-young-women-are-getting-sterilized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Diamond looks like most of the moms at the Park Slope café where we meet. Except the 31-year-old isn’t a mom. And she never will be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky principal investigated after getting lap dance at homecoming event...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/27/kentucky-principal-probed-after-getting-lap-dance-at-homecoming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kentucky school district is investigating after a student gave lap dances to his high school principal and other staff members during a provocative homecoming event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAN JOE SELL IT?</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211028130350-cggtv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-BIDEN/INFRASTRCTURE-FRAMEWORK (URGENT):Biden to urge Democrats to back new $1.75 trillion spending framework</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: AMERICAN Plane Diverted After Passenger Bloodies Flight Attendant...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/10/28/aa-flight-from-new-yorks-jfk-to-john-wayne-airport-diverts-to-denver-after-flight-attendant-attacked-by-passenger/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An American Airlines flight from John F. Kennedy International Airport in New York on its way to John Wayne Airport in Orange County Tuesday diverted to Denver International after a passenger assaulted a female flight attendant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Members told to defy order...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/head-new-york-city-firefighters-union-says-members-insulted-by-vaccine-mandate-2021-10-27/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the New York City firefighters union said on Wednesday he had told unvaccinated members to report for duty regardless of an order by Mayor Bill de Blasio to place them on unpaid leave if they fail to get the COVID-19 shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomalies or attacks? Fear, uncertainty and politics of Havana Syndrome...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/healthcare/578246-anomalies-or-attacks-fear-uncertainty-and-politics-of-havana-syndrome</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With over 200 cases around the globe, the cause of the mysterious symptoms reported by U.S. personnel remains unknown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo race becomes early test for divided Dem Party...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578815-buffalo-race-becomes-early-test-for-a-divided-democratic-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unexpected showdown between Buffalo, N.Y.’s mayor and the young progressive activist who defeated him in a Democratic primary earlier this year is becoming a new proving ground for New York Democrats ahead of what is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What did nuke sub hit in South Sea?</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2021/10/27/navy-not-sure-what-uss-connecticut-struck-in-the-south-china-sea-beijing-accuses-u-s-of-cover-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy still isn’t positive what one of its most powerful attack submarines hit in the South China Sea, as repair assessments continue in Guam, four sources familiar with the results of the preliminary investigations told USNI News this week. As of Tuesday afternoon, the undersea object that damaged the forward section of USS …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk, Bezos  worth half trillion!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ph/money/business/elon-musk-and-jeff-bezos-are-now-worth-almost-half-a-trillion-dollars/ar-AAQ2dS8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk, co-founder of Tesla and SpaceX. Image by Daniel Oberhaus/Flickr/CC BY 2.0The combined net worth of Elon Musk and Jeff Bezos approached $500 billion on Wednesday, fueled by the unrelenting rally in Tesla Inc. shares and a broad surge in tech stocks that sent the Nasdaq 100 to an intraday record. The value of the two fortunes — a sum bigger than the market value of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Judge denies NYPD bid to halt vax mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-vaccine-mandate-judge-denies-nypd-union-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 vaccine mandate is set to take effect on November 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaires in crosshairs of new tax proposals...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/578838-tech-billionaires-in-the-crosshairs-of-new-tax-proposals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America’s richest tech executives and their companies are in the crosshairs of a new effort by Democrats to pay for the party’s ambitious social spending plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDNY companies to close...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/27/covid-vaccine-mandate-could-force-20-of-fdny-companies-to-close/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDNY is preparing to shutter as many as 20 percent of all NYC fire companies ahead of the impending deadline for all city workers to be vaccinated against COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Crackdown 'Tip of Iceberg' as CFTC Seeks More Powers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-crackdown-tip-iceberg-cftc-164041605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The nominee to lead the U.S.’s top swaps regulator has a warning for lawmakers: Crypto misconduct the agency has already exposed is “the tip of the iceberg” and it likely needs more authority to police the white-hot market. Most Read from BloombergA Deep Dive Into Squid Game's World of InequalityMeet Six People Fighting Water Scarcity Across the GlobeHamburg Is at the Heart of Germany’s Growing Dilemma Over ChinaRostin Behnam, the Biden administration’s pick to head the Commodity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James Preparing Announcement on Run for Gov...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/27/letitia-james-is-preparing-announcement-on-run-for-governor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Letitia James, New York’s attorney general, is preparing to announce as soon as Thursday that she will run for governor,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 'Jewitches' embrace Judaism, witchcraft...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/religion-judaism-aa34f2501659dfb3a31ca5956860ebc5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — In a scene from a recently released movie, three older women in a small room slowly walk clockwise around a table covered in candles, chanting curses softly. A scene from the latest “Macbeth” remake?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheap antidepressant shows promise treating...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-antidepressants-db60608bedde0149247ce9a64a394802</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cheap antidepressant reduced the need for hospitalization among high-risk adults with COVID-19 in a study hunting for existing drugs that could be repurposed to treat coronavirus. Researchers tested the pill used for depression and obsessive-compulsive disorder because it was known to reduce inflammation and looked promising in smaller studies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadline tomorrow...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-religion-new-york-lawsuits-0e8c7e0276ea2acea9fa489656f838da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge on Wednesday refused to pause a COVID-19 vaccine mandate set to begin Friday for the city’s municipal workforce, denying a police union’s request for a temporary restraining order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden bound for global summits as domestic agenda in limbo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-joe-biden-business-rome-scotland-30c46a7eda7f8549d12fd70bd264b4f3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden promised to show the world that democracies can work to meet the challenges of the 21st century. As he prepares to push that message at a pair of global summits, his case could hinge on what's happening in Washington, where he is rushing to finalize a major domestic legislative package.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting for Money, Dems Rush to Rewrite Tax Code...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/27/hunting-for-money-democrats-rush-to-rewrite-tax-code/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — As they hunt for revenue to pay for their sprawling spending bill and try to unite a fractured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How live ammo got on set still mystery in Baldwin shooting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prop-gun-shooting-entertainment-shootings-movies-santa-fe-4a8e63727b0824d7a402f731b6ec54ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — Light from a high afternoon sun slanted through the tall windows of the weathered wooden church, catching on the plank floorboards and illuminating the stained glass. Outside, the arid ground of the northern New Mexico foothills stretched for miles — a picturesque setting for an Old West gun battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado barrels across TX highway sparking blinding explosions...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3945891/tornado-orange-county-texas-highway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TORNADO has been filmed barrelling across a Texas highway sparking blinding explosions and leaving drivers stunned. Footage shows as the twister passing in front of motorists with debris thrown i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painting of YALE namesake, enslaved child back on display...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arts-and-entertainment-education-race-and-ethnicity-painting-slavery-5a8066d42eeadf5fcdf2763b4cc42380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An early 18th-century painting depicting Yale University's namesake with an enslaved Black child has been returned to public display at one of its museums even as art experts investigate its origins and campus discussions about the school's ties to slavery continue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOT to referee World Cup '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/premier-league/3945451/fifa-robot-linesmen-world-cup-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBO-LINESMEN at the 2022 World Cup will come a step closer today as law-makers are told the technology is good to go. Fifa is keen to introduce “semi-automated offside” calls at next year’s tourna…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drop paid family, medical leave from bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/manchin-skeptical-billionaire-tax-proposal-democrats-push-deal-n1282507</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House had hoped to get to an agreement on the overall bill before Biden leaves this week for meetings in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA ISSUES GENDER 'X' PASSPORT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-travel-colorado-united-states-jessica-stern-2c29e18fc6566d549b9a06fda0857602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — The United States has issued its first passport with an “X” gender designation, marking a milestone in the recognition of the rights of people who do not identify as male or female, and expects to be able to offer the option more broadly next year, the State Department said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paid leave likely to fall out of bill...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/us-policy/2021/10/27/biden-democrats-spending-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“An agreement is within arm’s length, and we are hopeful that we can come to a framework agreement by the end of today,” Schumer said on the Senate floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden closes in on deal with Manchin, Sinema as liberals wince...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/10/27/top-dems-social-spending-deal-manchin-sinema-517332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It’s lamb eat lamb. There is no bad decision. We have to choose,” Speaker Nancy Pelosi told her members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon FIRED after saying parents should make mask decisions for kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10137505/Minnesota-doc-fired-telling-officials-parents-right-decide-children-wear-masks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Jeffrey Horak spoke before the school board at a public meeting in Fergus Falls on October 11. He gave a speech against the school's mask mandate. He claims he was later fired nine days later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK Won't Say Whether China Can Access User Data...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/tiktok-executive-wont-say-whether-china-can-access-american-user-data/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok executive on Tuesday refused to tell Congress whether the Chinese government could access American users' data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware group claims to have infiltrated NRA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/cybercriminals-claim-hacked-nra-rcna3929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A notorious Russian cybercriminal group has posted what appear to be National Rifle Association files to the dark web.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain plans to remove travel 'red list', hotel quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211027192321-lfo4i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-TRAVEL (URGENT):Britain plans to remove travel 'red list' and hotel quarantine - The Telegraph</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satanists convince school district to alter dress code...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/satanic-organization-satanism-delaware-county-schools-rose-tree-media-school-district/11170595/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Satanic organization has convinced a school district in Delaware County that its dress code was discriminatory against Satanists.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
