<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists train bees to identify infection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/552486-scientists-train-bees-to-identify-coronavirus-infection</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Dutch scientists are enlisting the help of an unusual group of participants for a new kind of rapid COVID-19 test: bees that have been specially trained to detect the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBERATTACK SHUTS TOP U.S. PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210508152642-o9z7n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-PRODUCTS/COLONIAL PIPELINE (UPDATE 6, PIX):UPDATE 6-Cyber attack shuts down top U.S. fuel pipeline network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Neanderthals Weren't Cannibals, So Who Ate Them?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/these-neanderthals-werent-cannibals-so-who-ate-them-stone-age-hyenas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME — When a Neanderthal skull was discovered in a cave on the property of a beachfront hotel south of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Separate Worlds of Bill and Melinda Gates...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/the-separate-worlds-of-bill-and-melinda-gates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates and Melinda French Gates were stuck at home. When the pandemic hit last March, the couple retreated to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson Urges 'Step Back' From 'Sexist' HFPA...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/scarlett-johansson-hfpa-statement-criticism-diversity-inclusion-reform-1234752398/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scarlett Johansson has joined the outcry against the Hollywood Foreign Press Association, adding her voice to fellow Avenger Mark Ruffalo, who spoke out on Friday. They unite with numerous publicis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walls closing in on Gaetz?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/may/08/matt-gaetz-florida-sleazy-scandal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigation into Florida congressman is reported to have grown beyond sex trafficking allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W Virginia factory center stage in supply chain crisis, showing economy's strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/west-virginia-factory-is-center-stage-in-supply-chain-crisis-as-u-s-economy-seeks-to-rebound-from-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The scene inside one plant illustrates the deepening production challenges roiling American industry as it shakes off the pandemic. Parts shortages, price spikes, port delays, labor trouble - all are complicating the economy's rebound.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In small NH town, 2020 election still rages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-new-hampshire-campaign-2016-election-2020-house-elections-e50dfae66446197767bd255882d19439</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WINDHAM, N.H. (AP) — Meetings of the Windham Board of Selectmen are usually as sleepy as they sound — a handful of residents from the New Hampshire town, a discussion of ambulance fees, maybe a drainage study...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLDPLAY Chris Martin says lockdowns forced him to re-evaluate fame...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/may/07/coldplay-chris-martin-lockdowns-forced-re-evaluate-fame</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frontman says Covid pandemic means he has tried ‘to not attach too much to being a pop star’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College Students Suspended Over Photos Showing Them Not Wearing Masks Off-Campus...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/05/07/umass-amherst-students-suspended-masks-outside-off-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three UMass Amherst students said they are not being treated fairly after they were suspended for not wearing masks at an off-campus outdoor event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild VIP Group-Sex Party About to Invade NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-wild-vip-group-sex-party-is-about-to-invade-new-york-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On May 15, SNCTM—an exclusive sex club—is set to host an 80-person bash in Downtown Manhattan. Masks are not optional.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Internet Turned on Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/05/08/elon-musk-snl-saturday-night-live-host-internet-controversy-485781</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unlikely, polarizing SNL hosting stint for the mogul reveals the boundaries and tensions of our ever-present culture wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did DeSantis violate First Amendment with FOXNEWS-only bill signing?</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida-politics/2021/05/07/did-desantis-violate-first-amendment-with-fox-news-only-bill-signing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts said the Florida governor likely ran afoul of the U.S. Constitution with his staged event in West Palm Beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origin story of Medina Spirit, Derby winner born on patch of Florida dirt and sold for $1,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/more-sports/the-origin-story-of-medina-spirit-a-derby-winner-born-on-a-patch-of-florida-dirt-and-sold-for-241000/ar-BB1gvbQi </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In India's surge, religious gathering attended by millions helped spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/In-India-s-surge-a-religious-gathering-attended-16161841.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI - As coronavirus cases in India shot upward last month, millions of people...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheney effort to turn Republicans from Trump threatens her ambitions. She says it's only beginning...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Liz-Cheney-s-effort-to-turn-Republicans-from-16161868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Rep. Liz Cheney had been arguing for months that Republicans had to face the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young causing Florida to have among highest hospital rates in country...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/younger-patients-causing-florida-to-have-among-the-highest-covid-hospital-rates-in-country/article_d0232b9b-f2ff-5a15-8236-702f84555174.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — As state and local officials drop mandates on COVID-19 restrictions, the virus continues to circulate throughout Florida, sending increasingly younger people to the hospital at rates that are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones? Lasers? New study suggests ways park service could clean Gateway Arch...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/drones-lasers-new-study-suggests-ways-park-service-could-clean-gateway-arch/article_349f30df-911e-5625-833d-d4f4301157f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. LOUIS — The Gateway Arch gradually is losing some of its silver sheen, as a variety of forces — from salt to body oils to graffiti — take a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man tried to track robbery victim by attaching iPhone to his car, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Florida-man-tried-to-track-his-robbery-victim-by-16161191.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He'd been at the Millenia Mall in Orlando, Fla., for less than an hour when he allegedly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210508-alarm-as-german-anti-maskers-co-opt-nazi-resister-sophie-scholl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alarm as German anti-maskers co-opt Nazi resister Sophie Scholl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese rocket debris set for uncontrolled plummet back to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/asia-pacific/20210508-chinese-rocket-debris-set-for-uncontrolled-plummet-back-to-earth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Debris from parts of China’s Long March 5B rocket is set to crash down to Earth this weekend – but space agencies do not know when or where.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA and LaPierre's Fate Lies in Hands of TX Bankruptcy Judge...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-08/nra-and-lapierre-s-fate-lies-in-hands-of-texas-bankruptcy-judge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association, long a feared power broker, will learn its fate next week in a court ruling that could hobble the gun rights group and imperil the three-decade reign of its controversial boss, Wayne LaPierre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON warehouse employee dies at site of unionization drive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/07/amazon-employee-dies-at-bessemer-alabama-warehouse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon declined to share further details about the situation, noting that it was a personal medical incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Rachel Levine's Rise as Trans Issues Gain Prominence...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/this-is-politics-dr-rachel-levines-rise-as-transgender-issues-gain-prominence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Rachel Levine was not a particularly aggressive football player at the elite all-boys school she attended in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA Chief, Pressured by State Laws, Pushes to Let Athletes Cash In...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/n-c-a-a-chief-pressured-by-state-laws-pushes-to-let-athletes-cash-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CORAL GABLES, Fla. — The University of Miami has long been able to make a glossy pitch to the students</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri House passes bill to create 'Rush Limbaugh Day'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/rush-limbaugh-michael-brown-8ff0013141d209410e4777035cdc913e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JEFFERSON CITY, Mo. (AP) — The Missouri House on Thursday voted in favor of creating “Rush Limbaugh Day.” The GOP-led House tacked the provision on another bill, which then passed the chamber...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Da Vinci 'Head of Bear' drawing seen fetching $16 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/da-vincis-head-bear-drawing-seen-fetching-up-16-mln-2021-05-08/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A drawing of a bear's head by Leonardo da Vinci is seen fetching up to $16.7 million, potentially setting a record, when it heads to auction in July, Christie's said on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANS FIGHT SPLITS REPUBLICANS; New front in culture wars backfiring?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/05/06/transgender-athlete-laws-gop-484799</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;States are considering an unprecedented number of bills targeting transgender women and girls who play sports, but Republican support for the measures is not universal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mogul Behind LA TIMES Says Papers Need Govt Aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/biotech-mogul-behind-la-times-says-papers-need-government-aid/ar-BB1gtRIe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owner of the Los Angeles Times is calling on the government to throw its support behind newspapers, saying the loss of advertising to tech companies and declining readership threaten local journalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS SUPERYACHT SO BIG IT NEEDS 'SUPPORT YACHT' WITH HELIPAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.maxim.com/rides/jeff-bezos-megayacht-support-yacht-with-helipad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.maxim.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like a lot of divorced folks, billionaire Jeff Bezos is making some changes in his life. In February he stepped down as Amazon CEO, and Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Dogecoin whale owns $22 billion of cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://markets.businessinsider.com/currencies/news/single-dogecoin-whale-owns-22-billion-elon-musk-february-warning-2021-5-1030404506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;markets.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last wild macaw in Rio lonely and looking for love...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-environment-and-nature-3632d009dc9f6929e4cf15a38fa58b00</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Some have claimed she’s indulging a forbidden romance. More likely, loneliness compels her to seek company at Rio de Janeiro’s zoo. Either way, a blue-and-yellow macaw that zookeepers named Juliet is believed to be the only wild bird of its kind left in the Brazilian city where the birds once flew far and wide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CYBERATTACK SHUTS TOP U.S. PIPELINE</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/08/cyberattack-forces-a-shutdown-of-a-top-u-s-pipeline-operator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cyberattack forced the shutdown of one of the largest pipelines in the United States, in what appeared to be</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
