<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>N.Y. Assembly passes single-payer health care...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/17/new-york-assembly-passes-single-payer-universal-he/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York state Assembly has again endorsed a single-payer universal health care system. The proposal would allow all New Yorkers to enroll for health coverage that comes with no network restrictions, deductibles or co-pays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-associate-Roger-Stone-reveals-new-contact-13001555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI - One day in late May 2016, Roger Stone - the political dark sorcerer and longtime confidant of Donald Trump - slipped into his Jaguar and headed out to meet a man with a Make America Great Again hat and a viscous Russian accent. The man, who called himself Henry Greenberg, offered damaging information about Hillary Clinton, Trump's presumptive Democratic opponent in the upcoming presidential election, according to Stone - who spoke about the previously unreported incident in interviews with The Washington Post. Greenberg, who did not reveal the information he claimed to possess, wanted Trump to pay $2 million for the political dirt, Stone said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman shouting 'Allahu akbar' attacks 2 with box cutter at France supermarket...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/06/17/woman-shouting-allahu-akbar-attacks-2-with-box-cutter-at-supermarket-in-france.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who allegedly shouted Allahu akbar attacked two people with a box cutter at a supermarket in southern France on Sunday before she was arrested, local media reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392662-roger-stone-russian-wanted-trump-to-pay-2m-for-dirt-on-clinton-during</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign adviser Roger Stone said that he met with a Russian man during the 2016 campaign who wanted President Trump to pay $2 million for damaging information on Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress claims TESLA 'spontaneously' burst into flames...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5852195/Actress-Mary-McCormack-claims-husbands-Tesla-Model-S-spontaneously-combusted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is what happened to my husband and his car today,' McCormack wrote on Twitter Friday, posting a shocking video of a Model S spewing flames from the front driver's side front wheel well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mount Everest, The High-Altitude Dump...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mount-everest-high-altitude-rubbish-dump-033148000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades of commercial mountaineering have turned Mount Everest into the world's highest rubbish dump as an increasing number of big-spending climbers pay little attention to the ugly footprint they leave behind. "It is disgusting, an eyesore," Pemba Dorje Sherpa, who has summited Everest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist launches hunt for Loch Ness 'monster DNA'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/scientist-launches-hunt-loch-ness-monster-dna-035644306.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tales of a giant creature lurking beneath the murky waves of Loch Ness have been around for more than 1,500 years -- and one academic hopes the marvels of modern science can finally unravel the mystery. Neil Gemmell has travelled from the University of Otago in New Zealand to collect water samples in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON 'WILD WEST'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5853179/Less-one-20-street-robberies-burglaries-solved-police-new-figures-reveal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than one in 20 street robberies and burglaries are being solved in the UK, shocking new figures have revealed. The statistic will fuel concerns there is a crisis in the nation's policing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Rapid Retreat in Midwest...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/669236?unlock=L6H53FDW9A8QQYG9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans have abandoned Senate races in states Trump carried, and could lose several key governorships as well. Trump’s boasting of crashing the blue wall is rapidly becoming ancient history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE:  FBI Informant Tried to Spy on Me...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-associate-roger-stone-reveals-new-contact-with-russian-national-during-2016-campaign/2018/06/17/4a8123c8-6fd0-11e8-bd50-b80389a4e569_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime political operative suspects the meeting in a South Florida restaurant was an FBI setup designed to hurt the Republican nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian on Running for Office: 'Never Say Never'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kim-kardashian-running-office-never-say-never-1120748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new interview with CNN's Van Jones, she also discussed her marriage to Kanye West and how being a mom has changed her for the better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Chicago, Stormy muses: 'Should I run for president?'</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-stormy-daniels-20180616-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though Stormy Daniels is at the center of one of the largest scandals to hit any White House in recent history, the adult film star says her bare-it-all show at the Admiral Theatre this weekend is, like the rest of her shows nationwide, not about politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Shooting At NJ Art Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/1-Dead-Several-Injured-in-Trenton-Art-Festival-Shooting-485766011.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say at least one person has been killed and several others injured when shooting broke out at an all-night cultural event in Trenton, New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 injured...</title>
      <link>http://6abc.com/20-injured-suspect-killed-in-trenton-arts-festival-shooting/3612187/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty people including a child were injured and a suspect was killed after shots were fired during a 24 hour arts festival in Trenton, New Jersey where hundreds were in attendance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE Columnist Suspended For Fabrications...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/local_coverage/2018/06/boston_globe_suspends_columnist_accused_of_embellishing_boston_marathon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston Globe columnist Kevin Cullen has been suspended without pay for three months after “serious violations” in remarks he made about the Boston Marathon bombings — a penalty his union says he’s going to fight.Scott Steeves, president of the Boston Newspaper Guild, told the Herald last night Cullen will take his case to arbitration.“Kevin looks forward to defending himself,” Steeves said. “The guild stands behind Kevin 100 percent.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Use of Driver's License Databases to Nab Crooks Spurs Privacy Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-use-of-drivers-license-databases-to-nab-crooks-spurs-privacy-concerns-1529233200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Law-enforcement officials who advocate for using facial recognition searches of driver’s license photos argue that it is a valuable tool; civil liberties advocates say it infringes on privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moped thieves steal UK Home Secretary's phone...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6550824/ive-been-robbed-by-a-moped-crook-says-sajid-javid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOME Secretary Sajid Javid has revealed he was a moped mugging victim — as he launches a blitz on street crime. He admits it left him fearing for his kids’ safety when they go out. The Tory, 48, wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama gas station clerk shoots customer as he walks out of store...</title>
      <link>http://www.thestate.com/news/local/crime/article213196489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a man was shot at the Obama gas station on Farrow Road, police have arrested the store's clerk, according to a Columbia police statement. Antar Daralhaj was arguing with a customer Saturday afternoon about overcharging for gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue ships dock in Spain as migrant debate roils Europe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3eeb4671542a40b39ded7b736cd685ff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VALENCIA, Spain (AP) — Ships in the Aquarius aid convoy docked Sunday at the Spanish port of Valencia, ending a weeklong ordeal for hundreds of people who were rescued from the pe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NBA player charged for home invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/former-nba-player-charged-with-armed-robbery-coweta-county/RKsjSFosvDioSvzq2AkqzO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former NBA player who went to high school in Cobb County was arrested Friday night in connection w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How string of violent sex crimes traced to ex-NFL star...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/17/how-a-string-of-violent-sex-crimes-were-traced-to-former-nfl-star/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An eagle-eyed neighbor helped crack the bizarre case of a former NFL star now accused in a slew of attacks on women. It was just after 2:30 p.m. on June 7 when the Encinitas, Calif., resident spott…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Likens Abortion to Nazi Eugenics...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/pope-francis-likens-abortion-to-nazi-eugenics-1529178587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In unusually blunt language, Pope Francis said that “to have an easy life, one does away with an innocent.” The pope also said the only real families are those based on marriage between a man and a woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nigeria's entire 200 million population plunged in to darkness by power grid meltdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/world-cup-2018/6551013/nigerias-power-grid-meltdown-world-cup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIGERIA has suffered a power cut across the entire country. A power grid melt down comes on the same day the national team played Croatia in the first World Cup fixture. The Super Eagles lost 2-0 o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyonce and Jay Z Drop Surprise Album...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/06/16/beyonce-and-jay-z-drop-surprise-album-everything-is-love-plus-video-watch-here-apesht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprise! Beyonce and Jay Z have dropped a surprise album and single. It’s available on their Tidal service, but the single and video are here. “Ape-sh*t” is terrific. What a nice…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local billionaire to take control of the LA TIMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/local-billionaire-control-l-times-190522470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — A biotech billionaire who purchased the Los Angeles Times with an eye toward restoring its independence and vigor will officially take control of the news organization Monday, the newspaper reports .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump keeps his promises on trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-keeps-promises-trade-144239362.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By inflicting tariffs on the steel and aluminum of his allies, and then on tens of billions of dollars in goods from China, US President Donald Trump has quickly moved to fulfill the tough campaign pledges he made on trade. During his first year in office, Trump and his top economic aides made repeated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets Palestinians launching 'fire balloons' from Gaza...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israel-targets-palestinians-launching-fire-balloons-gaza-194205932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli army on Saturday wounded two Palestinians in the Gaza Strip attempting to launch incendiary balloons across the border into Israel, officials said. An Israeli military spokeswoman said an "aerial device" had fired at a group near the Gaza border that was launching "fire balloons</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA dilemma: Notify people carrying cancer genes?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/nation-world/article213014904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iceland, with extensive DNA databases, has the ability to identify citizens with deadly breast-cancer genes, and notify them. But government so far refuses to do so. That infuriates Kári Stefánsson, a brilliant but polarizing geneticist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reiner denounces De Niro, celebrities for anti-Trump remarks...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/media/392574-rob-reiner-denounces-robert-de-niro-and-other-celebrities-for-anti-trump-remarks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Rob Reiner denounced Robert De Niro and other celebrities for their remarks against President Trump, saying it only helps the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow taxi driver mows down fans...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5851807/Seven-injured-taxi-ploughs-World-Cup-fans-Moscow.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among those injured included Mexican fans who were gearing up to watch their nation's opening World Cup game against Germany tomorrow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC 'ROSEANNE' Spinoff Clears Key Hurdle as Negotiations Heat Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/abcs-roseanne-spinoff-hinges-barr-relinquishing-fee-1120723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should a new take on the successful revival move forward, the WGA has made it clear any series will retain the comedian's credit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TEAM PREDICTS MUELLER REPORT SOON...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-mueller-trump-russia-20180616-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's lawyers and special counsel Robert Mueller are hurtling toward a showdown over a yearlong investigation into the president's conduct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans to colonize ASTEROIDS?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/710067/asteroid-nasa-cities-space-mining</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Officials Rush to Support U.S. Envoy After Death Threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-16/canadian-officials-rush-to-support-u-s-envoy-after-death-threat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Canadian officials, led by Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, rushed to express support for Ambassador Kelly Craft after a package containing a suspicious substance and a death threat was mailed to the U.S. diplomat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican to Host Conference on 'Xenophobia, and Politically Motivated Populism'...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/national-security/2018/06/16/vatican-host-conference-migration-xenophobia-politically-motivated-populism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The World Council of Churches (WCC) has announced a joint venture with the Vatican to co-host a meeting next September on "migration, xenophobia, and politically motivated populism."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 killed after nightclub brawl in Caracas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/906d30f06bfa47d69433ed7865d697bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS,Venezuela (AP) — Venezuela's government says 17 people were killed Saturday after a nightclub brawl in the capital led to a stampede.        Interior Minister Nesto</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite cancer, McCain's maverick ways press on in tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/despite-cancer-mccains-maverick-ways-press-tweets-154857911--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. John McCain's legacy was thrust into focus nearly one year ago when he announced his brain cancer diagnosis. The six-term Senator and decorated Vietnam War veteran is now fighting the illness from his beloved Arizona, and filling the role of one of the few Congressional Republican voices to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/venezuelas-interior-minister-says-17-dead-nightclub-brawl-160758668.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's interior minister says 17 dead after nightclub brawl .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL'S LAST WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/975166/Angela-Merkel-Germany-Bundestag-EU-migration-crisis-Kai-Whittaker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMAN Chancellor Angela Merkel could lose her powerful seat in the heart of Europe as soon as next week amid clashes within her coalition Government over EU migration policies, claimed German MP Kai Whittaker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists and tech bring resilient Iceland back from the brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/16/iceland-tourists-tech-resilient-bank-from-brink-financial-crisis </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the country lets its banks go bust 10 years ago, there seemed to be no timetable for recovery. Things have changed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest stabbed in Bethlehem as religion shrinks in conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/974431/christian-persecution-christianity-bethlehem-palestine-israel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST in Bethlehem has been stabbed while protecting his congregation from thugs in the latest example of Christianity in Palestine coming under threat.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
