<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210810-brazil-s-bolsonaro-flexes-muscles-with-military-parade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil's Bolsonaro flexes muscles with military parade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech-savvy teens falling prey to online scams faster than grandparents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/10/tech-savvy-teens-falling-prey-to-online-scams-faster-than-their-grandparents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of individuals under age 21 reporting that they've been victims of cyber-fraud has surged 156% over the last three years, a study shows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We rented CA vacation home and got spied on by surveillance camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/travel/article/California-vacation-rental-surveillance-camera-law-16346246.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you pull up to your vacation rental, you might be greeted by a surveillance camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Mask Mandate May Be in Effect Through Thanksgiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/dc-mask-mandate-may-be-in-effect-through-thanksgiving-if-vaccinations-dont-increase/2767657/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;D.C. health officials hope the indoor mask mandate can be dropped by Thanksgiving — but that may not be possible if the numbers don’t improve.  As D.C. enters its second week of a new mask mandate and the delta variant spreads, the number of people getting tested at pop-up testing sites has jumped. The number of new cases is rising…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cape Cod man catches Great White Shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2021/08/09/watch-cape-cod-man-catches-great-white-shark/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Pieciak caught a shark while fishing at Nauset Beach in Orleans on Sunday, according to a video he posted on instagram.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBIN COMES OUT AS BISEXUAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/08/10/robin-comes-out-bisexual-dc-comics-batman-urban-legends-series/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robin comes out as bisexual in DC Comics series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting Machine Tampering Coming From Inside The MAGA House...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/voting-machine-tampering-is-coming-from-inside-the-maga-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The truth is, these are not very bright guys, and things got out of hand.” – Hal Holbrook After months of being promised by the former President and his stooges that Dominion Voting Systems had RIGGED the election, we finally have our first credible investigation into voting machine tampering. The lede in Monday’s Grand Junction […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Going door-to-door dragging out girls as young as 12 to make them sex slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3448281/taliban-grabbing-girls-sex-slaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Taliban are “going to door to door” to round up young girls to be “sex slaves” to fighters in the terror group, reports claim. An inside source suggests that Taliban leaders are att…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$611 Million Stolen in Massive Hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/611-million-cryptocurrencies-stolen-massive-hack-1617999</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will take legal actions and we urge the hackers to return the assets," Poly Network tweeted in a thread. The hack has been labeled the largest DeFi hack in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China weighs whether to abandon Covid zero-tolerance approach...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/china-weighs-whether-abandon-covid-zero-tolerance-approach-n1276333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Even if you can lock down all the regions in China, people might still die, and more might die due to hunger," a Yale University health economist says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worst governor during pandemic? Lot of candidates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/melinda-henneberger-the-worst-governor-during-this-pandemic-there-are-a-lot-of-candidates/ar-AAN8Y28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of the 18 months since Americans began dying of COVID-19, some of my friends in Missouri, Texas and Florida have been arguing about which of us has the worst wartime governor in the country. Missouri’s Mike Parson got off to a fast start, doing nothing at first, and as little as possible ever since: By April 1, 2020, according to a state compilation of every action taken by every ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon scraps requirement for high school students to read, write...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9879959/Oregon-scraps-requirement-high-school-students-prove-proficiency-math-reading-writing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Oregon has suspended its requirement that high school students demonstrate a proficiency in math, writing and reading in order to receive a diploma.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Banana republic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/10/bolsonaro-banana-republic-military-parade-condemned-by-critics-brazil</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tanks roll through streets of Brasília as congress prepares to vote on plans to change Brazil’s voting system</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student proves TWITTER algorithm bias toward lighter, slimmer, younger faces...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2021/aug/10/twitters-image-cropping-algorithm-prefers-younger-slimmer-faces-with-lighter-skin-analysis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Company pays $3,500 to Bogdan Kulynych who demonstrated flaw in image cropping software</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greeks battle to protect town from ferocious blaze...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/huge-force-struggling-contain-greek-105045534.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Volunteers and firefighters are workinground-the-clock, often without masks or helmets, in a desperate bid to stop a violent blaze from reaching a key town on Greece's Evia island, one of hundreds of fires that have raged through the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gamblers lifting casino market to its best year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-39f5928cee71d63ba06549e75b5a70fa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Gamblers anxious to hit the slot machines and table games in person after a year of coronavirus restrictions are lifting the U.S. casino industry to its best year ever. But the great unknown is whether a new, more contagious variant of COVID-19 will slow an industry that is now winning money at a record pace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-caribbean-brazil-74267e007a4c09417d905b5447d16782</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRASILIA, Brazil (AP) — Brazil's military staged an unusual convoy of troops and armored vehicles through the capital on Tuesday — an event announced only a day before and that coincided with a scheduled vote in Congress on one of President Jair Bolsonaro's key proposals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decline of traditional TV happening fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-spiral-spelling-trouble-for-traditional-tv-7a50241a-6c96-4bec-94f7-b81367c86922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a big long-term problem for NBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor responds after officers turn backs on her following cop killing...</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/wbbm780/news/local/chicago-cops-turn-backs-on-lightfoot-after-officer-killed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Lori Lightfoot has responded to reports that a group of Chicago police officers turned their backs on her after the murder of a female cop over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire-backed mining firm to seek electric vehicle metals in Greenland...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/billionaire-backed-mining-firm-seek-electric-vehicle-metals-greenland-2021-08-09/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mineral exploration company KoBold Metals, backed by billionaires including Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates, has signed an agreement with London-listed Bluejay Mining (JAY.L) to search in Greenland for critical materials used in electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penélope Cruz Movie Poster Featuring Lactating Nipple Censored on INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/penelope-cruz-movie-poster-featuring-lactating-nipple-censored-instagram-1617842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A striking poster for "Madres Paralelas" (Parallel Mothers) was recently unveiled, ahead of it opening the Venice Film Festival in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC investigating 2 deaths, 2 illnesses from rare bacterial disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/melioidosis-us-cases-cdc.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The source of the infections remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER suspends Marjorie Taylor Greene for vax tweet...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/10/tech/twitter-marjorie-taylor-greene/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter has suspended Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene's account for one week following another violation of the platform's rules, the company said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eviction moratorium forces small landlords to consider selling...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/with-tenants-who-won-e2-80-99t-pay-or-leave-small-landlords-face-struggles-of-their-own/ar-AAN9niL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many corporate apartment chains catering to white-collar workers are raising rents and booking enormous profits while some small landlords are giving up and deciding to sell as the eviction moratorium stretches on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another city falls...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldsun.com.au/news/breaking-news/thousands-flee-as-taliban-noose-tightens-around-afghan-north/news-story/54b01324939add545b6ce02d3292b3a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldsun.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban seized another Afghan provincial capital Tuesday -- the seventh in less than a week -- as tens of thousands of people fled their homes in the north for the relative safety of Kabul and other centres.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810140426-j6vax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-POLITICS/ (PIX, TV):Brazil military parade at presidential palace rattles politicians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Face of Dem Party?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/08/hakeem-jeffries-nancy-pelosi-speaker-house/619695/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hakeem Jeffries could end up being the first Black speaker of the House—but not all progressives are happy about his rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: War Against Federal Prosecutor...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/andrew-cuomos-war-against-a-federal-prosecutor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A call to the Obama White House that some legal experts say is impeachable fits a pattern of the Governor smearing those who scrutinize him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AI system could diagnose dementia in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/3444806/new-ai-system-diagnose-dementia-in-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW artificial intelligence (AI) system could diagnose dementia in just one day, experts have discovered. At present it takes several scans to diagnose dementia and scientists have claimed the ne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL REQUESTS VENTILATORS</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/local/2021/08/09/florida-sets-another-covid-case-record-as-hospitals-face-sheer-exhaustion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida has again broken a record for new COVID-19 cases, reporting 56,633 of them over the past two days, according to the latest CDC data, an average of more than 28,000 per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot shops opening on Main Street America. And they look like Margaritaville...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90663444/pot-shops-are-opening-on-main-street-america-and-they-look-like-jimmy-buffets-margaritaville</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, cannabis dispensaries tried to channel the sophisticated look of an Apple Store. Now they’re embracing their inner Jimmy Buffett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER: Miami orders residents to evacuate condo...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/miami-orders-residents-evacuate-story-condo-building-79377888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another South Florida condo building is being evacuated some six weeks after the collapse of a Surfside condominium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Distrust In Government Rising Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/covid-burden-distrust-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were also surprised to find that COVID-19 burden does not need additional triggers to motivate political violence,” researchers say. “It is seemingly enough on its own.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Bush admin hid truth about attack targeting Cheney...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/2021/08/10/afghanistan-papers-book-dick-cheney-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bush administration hid the truth about an attack targeting Dick Cheney, amid fears it was losing the war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to defund agencies following CDC rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/news/rand-paul-covid-cdc-masks-b1899354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Controversial US senator Rand Paul has been blasted after insisting Americans should reject government-mandated regulations, including wearing masks, in a “dangerous” anti-Covid rant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel threatens to kill TV news anchor, claiming unfair coverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/azucena-uresti-tv-anchor-threatened-jalisco-new-generation-cartel-mexico/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Committee to Protect Journalists considers Mexico the deadliest country in the Western Hemisphere for journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci supports mandates for teachers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/567094-fauci-supports-mandates-for-teacher-vaccinations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Fauci, the nation's leading infectious disease doctor, on Tuesday, said he supports any effort from local governments to mandate that teachers be vaccinated against the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid delta surge, confusion again reigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Amid-delta-surge-confusion-again-reigns-16376462.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, IDAHO - Ben Lemons, an elementary school principal, received a coronavirus vaccine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov Threatens to WithHold Salaries...</title>
      <link>https://npr.org/2021/08/09/1026299001/florida-governor-desantis-school-superintendent-salary-masks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis ratcheted up a confrontation with school superintendents on Monday, saying anyone who defies his ban on mask mandates might lose a paycheck. Teachers and staff wouldn't be punished.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810082158-s7pg3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-CHINA/DRILLS (TV):Russia, China hold large-scale joint military drills</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women filmmakers denounce cinema prize for Depp...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-arts-and-entertainment-9b1b8b4ab954f19552c3240e53edc39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Spain's leading group of women filmmakers on Tuesday condemned the San Sebastian film festival’s decision to award Johnny Depp its highest honor, saying it gave the international event a bad name after a British judge ruled last year that allegations of domestic violence against the actor were “substantially correct".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Sell Fast, Homeowners Making Mansions Move-In Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/corcoran-ceo-pamela-liebman-interview-which-houses-selling-fast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Sell Fast, Homeowners Are Making Their Mansions Move-In Ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals parceling out beds, hunting for doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/delta-strains-hospitals-across-u-s-as-unvaccinated-fill-icus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Strains Hospitals Across U.S. as Unvaccinated Fill ICUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN fears erasure of human rights...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210810111411-58tfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AFGHANISTAN-CONFLICT/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Taliban tighten control of Afghan north as UN fears erasure of human rights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job openings record 10.1 million...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-4c614d89c69b4afd3504a4d92dd574f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. employers posted a record 10.1 million job openings in June, another sign that the job market and economy are bouncing back briskly from last year's coronavirus shutdowns. Job openings rose from 9.5 million in May, the Labor Department reported Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Deliberately Left Deadly Variant Out of Press Briefings During Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/tokyo-deliberately-left-deadly-new-lambda-covid-variant-out-of-press-briefings-during-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even after a Lambda case was conclusively identified at the airport, the government omitted the findings from two press releases, reluctant to raise alarms during the Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk slammed over plan to put satellite ad billboard in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/elon-musk-slammed-over-spacex-24725021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans announced earlier this week would see SpaceX team up with Geometric Energy Corporation on its CubeSat project and launch the ad billboard into Earth's orbit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS CRYPTO CRACKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/change-to-crypto-provision-in-infrastructure-bill-blocked/ar-AAN7B3r?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A change to cryptocurrency reporting rules in the infrastructure bill was blocked in the Senate Monday, leaving language for broad oversight of virtual currencies still in the legislation that’s set to pass the Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.tropicaltidbits.com/storminfo/06L_tracks_latest.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tropicaltidbits.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/refresh/AL062021_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/233154_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor Who Said Donald Would Be Back in Office Says He Was Inaugurated in March...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/pro-trump-pastor-who-said-trump-would-be-back-in-office-in-june-now-says-he-was-inaugurated-in-march/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right-wing Pastor Jeff Jansen has baselessly claimed that he knows "for a fact" that former President Donald Trump was inaugurated on March 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World 'nowhere near end of pandemic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/09/covid-epidemiologist-larry-brilliant-on-delta-variant-vaccinations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The delta variant of Covid-19 is extremely contagious, noted epidemiologist Larry Brilliant. Relatively few worldwide have gotten the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical storm watches issued for Caribbean islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/developing-tropical-system-is-one-for-the-us-to-watch/996147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been more than a month since any tropical activity has remotely approached the U.S., but a budding threat could track toward Florida or the Gulf of Mexico, AccuWeather meteorologist say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools go against DeSantis, require masks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-education-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-a24acbc39533b222a580548ae3422298</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — The superintendent of the school district in Florida’s capital said Monday that he will require students to wear masks amid an increase in COVID-19 hospitalizations fueled by the delta variant, defying the governor’s attempts to block schools from imposing such a mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas reports new record for hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-arkansas-coronavirus-pandemic-7ed21edba1069f6c57e07c42540021fe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Arkansas on Monday set a new record for the number of people in the state hospitalized because of COVID-19 as its coronavirus surge continued. The state reported its COVID-19 hospitalizations rose by 103, its biggest one-day increase, to 1,376.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 LONE STAR:  APPEAL FOR OUT OF STATE COVID HELP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-education-coronavirus-pandemic-368eb9eb57b1d3b1a473d4414c42a522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Greg Abbott appealed for out-of-state help Monday to fight the third wave of COVID-19 in Texas. The request came as a county-owned hospital in Houston raised tents to accommodate their COVID-19 overflow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics Viewership Plummeted 42% From Rio...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tokyo-olympics-ratings-viewers-down-rio-2016/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics came one year late and were watched by 42% fewer viewers than the Rio games in 2016, according to Nielsen and Adobe data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine enthusiasts getting extra shots without FDA approval...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/covid-19-boosters-some-in-us-getting-extra-shot-without-fda-approval</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An untold number of Americans have managed to get COVID-19 booster shots even though the U.S. government hasn't approved them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man vows to defy judge's 'crazy' order to get dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9877299/Ohio-man-ordered-judge-COVID-19-vaccine-two-year-probation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ohio Judge Christopher Wagner ordered Brandon Rutherford on Wednesday to get a Covid vaccine as part of a condition of probation for his felony conviction on fentanyl possession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew sued in New York for sex assault...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/09/prince-andrew-may-be-sued-in-new-york-by-virginia-roberts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein accuser Virginia Roberts Giuffre may file a lawsuit against Prince Andrew this week in New York court, accusing him of “improper sexual violations,” her lawyer said in a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pediatrician warns: 'Not your grandfather's Covid'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/live-updates/covid-delta-variant/?id=79359387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is facing a COVID-19 surge this summer as the more contagious delta variant spreads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Host Criticizes FOXNEWS: 'Not Acceptable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/this-is-not-acceptable-fox-news-host-dan-bongino-rips-fox-news-for-editing-trump-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dan Bongino faced the wrath of his supporters after a clip of his Fox News interview with President Donald Trump was edited to remove false claims about the 2020 election. In an interview that aired on Fox News Saturday night, Trump told Bongino that the 2020 election he lost to Joe Biden was “fake.” While […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 more women contacted AG with allegations...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/09/two-more-women-contacted-ag-with-allegations-against-cuomo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two more women approached the state Attorney General’s Office with allegations against Gov. Andrew Cuomo after Letitia James released her sexual harassment report against him last week, The P…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variant sucking joy out of back-to-school...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-variant-sucking-joy-back-120001605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead of a back-to-normal back-to-school, the coronavirus casts new shadows over the return to full-time, in-person schooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plant-Based Fish Rattling Seafood Industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/plant-based-fish-is-rattling-the-multibillion-dollar-seafood-industry/ar-AAMYzVU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beyond and Impossible showed the potential for plant-based proteins. Now tomatoes are coming for tuna</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Budget Includes Green Card Giveaway, Mass Amnesty...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/dem-budget-includes-green-card-giveaway-mass-amnesty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new budget proposal from Senate Democrats will dramatically increase the number of available green cards and include amnesty for illegal immigrants, according to an official fact sheet on the $3.5 trillion budget circulated by leadership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likely 'JEOPARDY!' successor defends himself on allegations he mistreated colleagues...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/09/media/mike-richards-jeopardy-host-controversy/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Richards, who is in line to become the new host of "Jeopardy!," is defending himself against allegations that he mistreated colleagues at another game show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The animals changed by human contact...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210805-the-animals-changed-by-proximity-to-humans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not just domestication that has changed animals – simply sharing their environment with humans has radically altered the behaviour of some species.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Denies Britney Spears' Request To Toss Father Off Conservatorship...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/britney-spears-conservatorship-latest-jamie-spears-court-filings-1234810638/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 12:46 PM: Britney Spears won’t get an earlier chance to try to chuck her father off of her restrictive conservatorship. In a tactical victory for Jamie Spears over his daughter&amp;#8217…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
