<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Niagara freezes over!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2387097/niagara-falls-freezes-america-storm/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NIAGARA Falls froze over yesterday as a brutal storm continues to batter swathes of the US. Ice formed at the top of the famous waterfall after temperatures fell to -19C (-2F) in Niagara, New York …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID WOMAN CHARGED WITH BREATHING ON COP...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article249448255.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She was being processed into jail in connection with a stabbing, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China taunts USA over TX blackout debacle; 'Failure of capitalism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2388816/china-taunts-us-capitalism-texas-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has taunted the United States over the Texas winter storm blackout as a “failure of capitalism” that is affecting “desperate” Americans. An opinion piece in the Englis…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACUCI:  TRUMP 'DENIAL' LED TO MASS CASUALTIES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dr-fauci-says-trumps-denial-and-lack-of-facts-contributed-to-magnitude-of-u-s-covid-death-toll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci has been reluctant to say Donald Trump is the reason why the coronavirus impacted the United States so badly, but he came close to blaming the former president for the death toll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN:  He's headed for jail!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/michael-cohen-predicts-trump-tax-210300790.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's ex-attorney Michael Cohen told MSNBC's Katy Tur that he thinks his old client ought to start looking into getting a "custom made jumpsuit." Cohen's prediction that Trump could wind up in jail came a few hours after the Supreme Court ruled that Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance can obtain Trump's tax returns as part of New York prosecutors' investigation into his past business dealings. Cohen said he's not sure what exactly the documents may reveal, but was confident enough to claim "it does not look good for" Trump. . @MichaelCohen212 says Trump should look into getting a "custom made jumpsuit, because it does not look good for him."@JoyceWhiteVance says Cy Vance has "sent signals that this is a serious investigation." pic.twitter.com/gBW5rc5PXs — MSNBC Live with Katy Tur (@KatyOnMSNBC) February 22, 2021 Cohen, of course, may not be the most neutral prognosticator — the disbarred lawyer, who is serving a prison sentence under house arrest after pleading guilty to multiple counts of campaign finance violations and fraud in 2018, has become one of Trump's most prominent public enemies in recent years and even testified against him before Congress in 2019. Tur's other guest, former U.S. Attorney Joyce Vance (no relation to Cyrus Vance), felt it was unwise to predict the result of the investigation, but she did argue the Manhattan DA has sent signals the probe has been a "serious" and "productive" one, and he may proceed toward indictment. More stories from theweek.comTed Cruz says his wife is 'pissed' over leaked Cancun textsTexas racked up a $50 billion energy bill last week. It's not clear who's going to pay it.Late night hosts mock Ted Cruz's lame post-Mexico photo ops, cheer Trump's tax returns defeat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN HOLDS CANINE MEETING IN OVAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/pets/president-joe-biden-poses-his-dogs-oval-office-t209733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's German shepherds look right at home in the White House's inner sanctum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission 'to colonize Red Planet' could start THIS week...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2389351/elon-musk-spacex-starship-rocket-fly-this-week-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has revealed that a SpaceX rocket designed to take humans to Mars could take to the skies in the coming days. In a tweet on Sunday, the billionaire said the latest Starship prototype has …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RASMUSSEN:  Plurality Believes Worst Behind Us!</title>
      <link>https://ballotpedia.org/Scott_Rasmussen%27s_Number_of_the_Day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ballotpedia.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED KEEPS PUMPING</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/powell-signals-fed-to-keep-buying-bonds-even-as-outlook-improves/ar-BB1dWhAi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell signaled that the central bank was nowhere close to pulling back on its support for the pandemic-damaged U.S. economy even as he voiced expectations for a return to more normal, improved activity later this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't mope - move!: Woman becomes TIKTOK fitness star at 81...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210223142925-qil05</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANY-FITNESS GRANNY/ (TV, PIX):Don't mope - move!: German woman becomes TikTok fitness star at 81</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mt Etna's latest eruptions awe even those who study volcanos...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-europe-italy-geophysics-fdfd723edc960de35308d04d67de8596</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanessa Bryant calls out rapper Meek Mill for 'insensitive' Kobe lyric...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/popculture/vanessa-bryant-calls-out-meek-mill-insensitive-kobe-lyric-t209742</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial lyrics to Meek Mill's unreleased song were reportedly leaked online last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Summer of freedom could be brought to crashing end by FOURTH wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14133270/summer-freedom-end-fourth-coronavirus-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUMMER freedoms may be capped once again by a fourth Covid wave, scientists fear. The roadmap out of lockdown has given hope for a world without restrictions by June 21 at the earliest – with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wants to stop these reptiles from becoming next python. Breeders call it overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/florida-wants-to-stop-these-reptiles-from-becoming-the-next-python-breeders-call-it-overreach/ar-BB1dW8AJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Wildlife managers in Florida are finally moving to address an existential question: If the state is like an all-you-can eat buffet for invasive reptiles originally introduced as exotic pets, then why are some of those species still imported and sold by breeders and pet stores? Until 2010, the now infamous Burmese python was easily found at pet stores across Florida, even as scientific ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life amid ruins of QANON: 'I wanted my family back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Life-amid-the-ruins-of-QAnon-I-wanted-my-family-15972209.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She bought ammunition, camping gear, a water purifier and boxes of canned food. Then, Tyler's mother started wearing a holstered pistol around the house, convinced that 10 days of unrest and mass power outages were coming.  The chaos would culminate, she assured her son, in former president Donald Trump's triumphant return to power on March 4, the original Inauguration Day before the passage of the 20th Amendment in 1932.  Tyler, 24, had been living with his mother an hour north of Minneapolis since he graduated college in 2019. The paranoia and fear that had engulfed his home had become unbearable in the months since Trump began to falsely claim that the 2020 election had been stolen from him.  "Any advice for dealing with a qanon parent who thinks ww3 will happen during the inauguration?" Tyler asked last month on r/QAnonCasualties, a fast-growing Reddit group for those whose loved ones have been consumed by the bizarre and byzantine universe of baseless conspiracy theories known as QAnon.  "Do they have weapons?" one of the site's moderators asked.  "Yep. A lot of them," Tyler replied. "I would leave, but I don't have anywhere to go." He said he couldn't imagine cutting ties to his mother.  In Washington, rioters, inflamed by unfounded allegations of a stolen election, had stormed the Capitol leaving five dead and triggering the impeachment of a president. Far from Washington, the falsehoods that had whipped so many into a frenzy were wreaking a different sort of chaos; one that was tearing families apart.  Family members spoke of their loved ones as if they were cult members or drug addicts, sucked in by social media companies and self-serving politicians who warped their views of reality. They begged and bargained with parents and partners to put down their phones for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists accused of breaking Hawaii rules by pretending to be locals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/23/tourists-accused-of-breaking-hawaii-covid-quarantine-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California couple has been accused of trying to break quarantine rules in Hawaii by pretending to be locals, prosecutors said. Miriam Rosas, 22, and Abel Rosas, 34, of Fresno tried to check into …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Building World's 'Most Powerful' Laser Weapon...</title>
      <link>https://interestingengineering.com/us-army-is-building-the-worlds-most-powerful-laser-weapon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;interestingengineering.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army is allegedly building what may be the world's most powerful laser weapon. Read all about it here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security officials cast blame for Jan. 6 failures at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-riots-hearing-security-officials-a9ecf8efd4d76f02d5ab9c7a01c5bdb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Most Likely Timeline for Life to Return to Normal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/family/archive/2021/02/pandemic-daily-life-normal-summer-fall/618108/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uncertain spring, an amazing summer, a cautious fall and winter, and then, finally, relief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROE V. WADE' Filmmaker Loeb Says Film Is 'Not Preachy, Pro-Life Religious Movie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/roe-v-wade-filmmaker-nick-loeb-clarifies-reports-about-conservative-film-its-not-a-preachy-pro-life-religious-movie</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nick Loeb opens up about his controversial title, saying how personal experiences with two of his partners who had abortions helped shape his stance on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant fish born with human face...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9290591/The-real-life-baby-shark-Mutant-fish-born-human-face.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of all the weird and wonderful creatures you might come across in the sea, a mutant shark with 'a human face' doesn't spring to mind. But a fisherman off the coast of Indonesia came across just that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First look at Roman Abramovich's new $600million superyacht...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9290231/Roman-Abramovichs-new-430million-superyacht-Solaris-nears-completion-German-shipyard.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 460ft Solaris, equipped with a helipad and swimming pool, will soon undertake sea trials before 54-year-old Roman Abramovich sets sail in the summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA TUMBLES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/23/tesla-drops-another-6percent-in-premarket-bringing-two-day-losses-to-14percent.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla's recent slide continued on Tuesday, as investors rotated out of high-flying tech names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TECH BLOODBATH</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/22/stock-market-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks dropped again on Tuesday as tech shares continued to fall sharply in the face of higher interest rates and a rotation into cyclical stocks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Best Age -- 36?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/perfect-age-forever-36/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you could be one age for the rest of your life – what would you choose? Would you stay a child forever?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Best beaches 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-9287353/Tripadvisors-best-beaches-2021-Australias-Whitehaven-Beach-No1-overall-Bournemouth-20th.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scratch your wanderlust itch with a look at this year's stunning winners in the 2021 Tripadvisor Travellers' Choice Best of the Best Awards for Beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWEDISH MASK SKEPTICISM FADES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/swedish-face-mask-skepticism-fades-as-infection-rates-rise/ar-BB1dWtnS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Stockholm and a number of other regions across Sweden are abandoning their earlier skepticism and advising people to rely more on face masks, as the country braces for a third wave of coronavirus infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax access codes for Black, Latino communities used in affluent LA areas...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/vaccine-access-codes-for-black-latino-communities-improperly-used-in-affluent-la-areas/article_5164c8d6-0a2a-5d72-81c9-695362879d7f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — A California program intended to improve COVID-19 vaccine availability to people in hard-hit communities of color is being misused by outsiders who are grabbing appointments reserved for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Naked Festival' goes ahead despite superspreader fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/world-famous-naked-festival-goes-23549854</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Hadaka Matsuri in Okyama, Japan, which began almost 1,000 years ago, involves men battling with "holy sticks" and wearing nothing but loincloths and socks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Ag Commissioner won't lower flags to honor Limbaugh, defying DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/news/politics/fl-ne-nikki-fried-limbaugh-flag-20210222-nfrc6bx2pbhtzf2yoe6mrl6744-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Nikki Fried is defying Gov. Ron DeSantis and refusing to lower flags at her state agriculture offices to honor Rush Limbaugh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERMANY EXTENDS BORDER CHECKS</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/eu-germany-roth/germany-defends-covid-border-curbs-idUSL8N2KT2D5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German minister on Tuesday defended the latest border restrictions as necessary to curb the spread of more contagious variants of the coronavirus as the EU faces a fresh wave of disjointed travel curbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk moved to Texas and embraced celebrity. Can TESLA run on Autopilot?</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/business/article/Elon-Musk-moved-to-Texas-and-embraced-celebrity-15971784.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO - Elon Musk says he is stretched too thin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindell bleeding cash amid lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9289537/MyPillow-CEO-Mike-Lindell-expects-lose-65-MILLION-boycotts-election-fraud-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Lindell, whose enthusiastic embrace of Trump's election fraud claims saw him hit with a $1.3 billion defamation suit on Monday, claims a boycott is costing his company millions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price now directly tied to bitcoin?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/23/tesla-and-bitcoins-value-are-now-linked-analyst-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla's stock is now directly linked to the price of bitcoin after Elon Musk's firm invested $1.5 billion into the cryptocurrency, according to an analyst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas AG left Austin for Utah during power outages. Dems say he 'couldn't care less about people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Texas-AG-Ken-Paxton-left-Austin-for-Utah-during-15971868.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Wednesday, Austin residents entered their third day of frigid temperatures,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE EYES NEW RESTRICTIONS</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210223111341-j82sk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-DUNKIRK (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-French port of Dunkirk proposes ban on public gatherings over COVID surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>160 Confederate symbols taken down in year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-race-and-ethnicity-virginia-us-supreme-court-laws-9a4d17b9728f15e6972b17f708e6a4b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate to hold public hearing on Capitol insurrection...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/senate-hold-1st-public-hearing-capitol-insurrection/story?id=76050569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hearing includes top officials who were responsible for security at the Capitol on Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 3 know someone who died...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-death-know-someone-263d12d2-9296-4547-8d57-e619f65d47e2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. surpassed 500,000 COVID deaths on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci sees CDC relaxing some guidelines soon...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210223112812-qpv2o</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FAUCI (URGENT):Fauci says he sees U.S. CDC relaxing some COVID-19 guidelines soon -CNN</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VACCINATED ISRAEL TRIES REOPENING</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/even-the-world-e2-80-99s-most-vaccinated-economy-faces-a-tough-reopening/ar-BB1dVw6Y?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the world waits for a vaccine-driven return to normal, Israel is showing what a long and arduous road it will be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lee Harvey Oswald instructed by Khrushchev to assassinate JFK, ex-CIA chief says...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9289315/Lee-Harvey-Oswald-told-Soviet-leader-Nikita-Khrushchev-kill-JFK-ex-CIA-chief-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;R. James Woolsey, who ran the CIA from 1993-1995, and Ion Mihai Pacepa, former head of Romania's spy service, have written a book reinterpreting the 1964 Warren Report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate heats up over vaccinating with just one dose...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/539980-debate-heats-up-over-vaccinating-more-people-with-just-one-dose</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Debate is intensifying over the idea of accelerating the U.S. vaccination campaign by giving people just one dose instead of two for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden mourns dead, balancing nation's grief and hope...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/617e9759d427af84320eae7b8d7b40c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLATE Suspends Podcast Host After Debate Over N-Word...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/slate-suspends-podcast-host-mike-pesca-after-debate-over-n-word/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This was not a decision based around making an isolated abstract argument in a Slack channel," a Slate spokeswoman says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITCOIN extends slide, tumbling below $50,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/23/bitcoin-btc-price-falls-below-50000-as-janet-yellen-raises-alarm.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin resumed its slide on Tuesday, tumbling as low as $45,041 according to data from Coin Metrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-1 bombers arrive in Norway in historic first...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/air-force/540000-us-b-1-bombers-arrive-in-norway-in-historic-first</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Air Force B-1B Lancers from Dyess Air Force Base in Texas arrived in Norway on Monday as part of a training mission in Europe, marking the first time U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK to restore Australia news, pay media companies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-restore-australia-news-pages-041017328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook said Tuesday it will lift a contentious ban on Australian news and pay local media companies for content, after a last-gasp deal on pending landmark legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING: Bezos Linked to WASHINGTON FOOTBALL TEAM Sales Talk...</title>
      <link>https://frontofficesports.com/jeff-bezos-washington-football-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;frontofficesports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bezos’ attorney spoke with Baltimore-based sports investment banking firm Moag &amp; Co., which led the effort to sell shares of the team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future Vaccines Depend on Test Subjects in Short Supply: Monkeys...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/23/future-vaccines-depend-on-test-subjects-in-short-supply-monkeys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Lewis was desperate to find monkeys. Millions of human lives, all over the world, were at stake. Mr. Lewis,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bristling Standoff Rattles Gun-Friendly Vermont...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/02/23/a-bristling-standoff-rattles-gun-friendly-vermont/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAWLET, Vt. — Fear has gradually spread in the town of Pawlet. In the hills west of town — which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agony of post-COVID-19 loss of smell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-france-coronavirus-pandemic-nice-570a3750912c47aa30b94f0be639fbd1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PASSES 500,000 COVID DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-deaths-over-500k-coronavirus-acab3cc916330a3f068b7589350a18cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo wife arrested in Virginia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/el-chapo-wife-arrested-us-drug-charges-70bf4320547802587246adc2bff342c8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What NY prosecutors could learn from Trump tax records...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-personal-taxes-new-york-courts-trump-investigations-0fa3d5f8dba60353aa8a5b25b94b1071</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects Trump effort to shield tax records from NY prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/22/supreme-court-rejects-trump-effort-to-shield-tax-records-from-ny-prosecutors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court rejected a last-ditch bid by former President Trump to keep years of his tax returns out of the hands of Manhattan DA Cy Vance Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA PASSES 500,000 COVID DEATHS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-new-york-new-york-city-bill-de-blasio-nashville-4ffa86c709f6a843de9cf0711e7215cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion insiders turn on André Leon Talley amid nasty eviction battle...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/22/george-malkemus-backed-by-fashion-insiders-in-andre-leon-talley-battle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Friendship and devotion have been distorted into a web of petty lies.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA releases Mars landing video: 'Stuff of dreams'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-mars-74a315f5d8412803aae89aa03fe91b80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (AP) — NASA on Monday released the first high-quality video of a spacecraft landing on Mars, a three-minute trailer showing the enormous orange and white parachute hurtling...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'El Chapo' wife arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/wife-of-el-chapo-drug-cartel-chief-arrested-us-justice-department-659853</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General left state!</title>
      <link>https://theeagle.com/news/state-and-regional/texas-ag-ken-paxton-and-his-wife-state-sen-angela-paxton-traveled-to-utah-during/article_d67c93c0-e768-59b2-850b-23f69bce14f2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paxton's campaign confirms he attended "a previously planned meeting with the Attorney General of Utah to discuss several matters, including strategizing on imminent action in the Google lawsuit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPAC cancels speaker over offensive tweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/featured-cpac-speaker-young-pharaoh-said-judaism-is-a-complete-lie-pushed-pizzagate-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Young Pharaoh also attacked fellow conservative commentator Ben Shapiro for his Judaism, according to Media Matters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese media use Times Sq  video screen for virus ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/china-runs-times-square-ads-touting-covid-fight-cooperation-who-relationship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The international community has continued to call for Beijing to fully cooperate with investigations into the origin of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA shares first video and audio, new images from Mars rover...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/02/22/world/mars-rover-new-video-images-scn-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During its harrowing descent to the surface of Mars last Thursday, NASA's Perseverance rover captured video that the agency is calling "How to Land on Mars." The video, along with other newly released footage, gives earthlings back home a better sense of the sights and sounds on the red planet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL COHEN:  Headed for jail!</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/968332/michael-cohen-predicts-trump-tax-investigation-end-jail-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Donald Trump's ex-attorney Michael Cohen told MSNBC's Katy Tur that he thinks his old client ought to start looking into getting a 'custom made jumpsuit.' Cohen's prediction that Trump could wind up in jail came a few hours after the Supreme Court ruled that Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance can obtain Trump's tax returns as part of New York prosecutors' investigation into his past business dealings. Cohen said he's not sure what exactly the documents may reveal, but was confident enough to claim 'it does not look good for' Trump. . @MichaelCohen212 says Trump should look into getting a 'custom made jumpsuit, because it does not look good for him.'@JoyceWhiteVance says Cy Vance has 'sent signals that this is a serious investigation.' pic.twitter.com/gBW5rc5PXs — MSNBC Live with Katy Tur (@KatyOnMSNBC) February 22, 2021 Cohen, of course, may not be the most neutral prognosticator — the disbarred lawyer, who is serving a prison sentence under house arrest after pleading guilty to multiple counts of campaign finance violations and fraud in 2018, has become one of Trump's most prominent public enemies in recent years and even testified against him before Congress in 2019. Tur's other guest, former U.S. Attorney Joyce Vance (no relation to Cyrus Vance), felt it was unwise to predict the result of the investigation, but she did argue the Manhattan DA has sent signals the probe has been a 'serious' and 'productive' one, and he may proceed toward indictment. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem calls for Cuomo to be impeached...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/22/democrat-kim-calls-for-cuomo-impeachment-over-nursing-home-scandal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo should be impeached over the nursing home scandal that saw state officials intentionally obscure the extent of the coronavirus’ death toll on the facilities, frequent critic…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sounds Bitcoin Warning...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/22/yellen-sounds-warning-about-extremely-inefficient-bitcoin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen issued a warning Monday about the dangers that bitcoin poses both to investors and the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie theaters in NYC to open at 25% capacity...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/02/22/movie-theaters-in-new-york-city-can-open-in-march-at-25percent-capacity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After nearly a year of closures, New York City cinemas will be permitted to open on March 5, Gov. Andrew Cuomo said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Way Traffic: Cities shrinking because no one moving in...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/business/2021/02/us-cities-shrinking-why-new-york-los-angeles.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not that people are moving out in a pandemic. It's that nobody new is moving in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NRA 'out of ammo' as it faces legal mess of own making...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/nra-ammo-faces-legal-mess-making-experts/story?id=75949839</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association has found itself tangled in a legal web of its own making, many experts say, as a federal judge considers the fate of its bankruptcy claim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funeral Home 'Running Out Of Granite For Headstones'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-deaths-us-500000-funeral-home-headstones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.J. legalizes pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/marijuana/2021/02/murphy-signs-nj-legal-weed-bills-ending-3-year-saga.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Phil Murphy signed the legal marijuana bill into law after several stops and starts that left many doubting it would become a reality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless for years, she wants off the streets -- or does she?</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/in-depth/news/local/phoenix/2021/02/22/homelessness-through-the-eyes-of-1-woman-on-streets-of-phoenix/5872816002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet Darlene Carchedi. Homeless for six years, she struggles with the idea of moving out of a tent and into an apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man reportedly faked own kidnapping -- to get out of work...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/02/22/arizona-man-faked-own-kidnapping-to-get-out-of-work-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s hating your job — and then there’s this guy. An Arizona man was so desperate to get out of work that he staged his own kidnapping, authorities said. Brandon Soules was arr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Paying Employees to Quit Right Before Critical Union Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7vy4m/amazon-is-paying-employees-to-quit-right-before-critical-union-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Employees are being offered thousands of dollars to leave and never work for Amazon again, weeks before a historic union election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 hedge fund managers earn $20 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-hedgefunds-performance/worlds-top-10-hedge-fund-managers-earn-20-1-billion-in-2020-idUSKBN2AM28U</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennium Management's Israel Englander earned $3.8 billion last year, landing him the biggest payday of any hedge fund manager in 2020, showed data from Institutional Investor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarter of patients experience HAIR LOSS after infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-9287057/Coronavirus-linked-hair-loss-22-patients-study-warns.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new paper by experts from the Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences, almost a quarter of Covid-19 survivors may be dealing with hair loss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama, Springsteen announce new podcast...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/obama-springsteen-podcast-spotify-f09f188f-15a7-49ea-8a59-689ce08b8191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Renegades: Born in the U.S.A."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PILLOW MAN CLAIMED VOTING MACHINE EXPERTISE...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-lawsuits-minnesota-elections-rudolph-giuliani-f8faf58b4c2017c6d165a1293c78c02a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Dominion Voting Systems filed a $1.3 billion defamation lawsuit Monday against the founder and CEO of Minnesota-based MyPillow, saying that Mike Lindell falsely accused the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second quake shakes Tennessee-North Carolina border...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article249422900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost a dozen people reported feeling the tremor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media users more likely to believe misinformation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/social-media-users-more-likely-162941874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans who rely on social media as their main source of news are more likely believe false or unproven stories about important topics such as politics and Covid-19, a survey showed Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen Signals Interest in Digital-Dollar...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yellen-signals-interest-backing-digital-164843289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen signaled the Biden administration supports research into the viability of a digital dollar, a shift from the lack of enthusiasm shown for the concept under her predecessor, Steven Mnuchin.“It makes sense for central banks to be looking at” issuing sovereign digital currencies, Yellen said at a virtual conference on Monday hosted by the New York Times.She said a digital version of the dollar could help address hurdles to financial inclusion in the U.S. among low-income households.“Too many Americans don’t have access to easy payments systems and banking accounts, and I think this is something that a digital dollar, a central bank digital currency, could help with,” she said. “It could result in faster, safer and cheaper payments, which I think are important goals.”A number of central banks, including the U.S. Federal Reserve, have been conducting research into how digital versions of their own currency would work. Officials generally see both opportunity and risks and many central banks have moved slowly to embrace the idea, while China has proceeded with pilot-program tests of a digital yuan.Treasury ‘Endorsement’“This is the most forward-leaning a Treasury secretary has ever been in endorsing a digital dollar,” Josh Lipsky, director of the Atlantic Council’s GeoEconomics Center, said of Yellen’s comments Monday. “I read it as an endorsement for Treasury to be involved in the exploration of central bank digital currencies, and we hadn’t seen that before.”The U.S. central bank announced last year that staff members at the Federal Reserve Bank of Boston were conducting research in conjunction with the MIT Media Lab in Cambridge, Massachusetts, seeking to construct and test a hypothetical digital dollar.Some lawmakers have expressed interest. Senate Banking Committee Chair Sherrod Brown, an Ohio Democrat, has advocated using digital technology to help reduce costs for accessing and transferring money, especially those outside the traditional banking system.Bitcoin, for its part, is championed by its supporters as essentially a separate financial system, independent from the control of central banks and any potential state-sponsored digital currencies.Even so, Fed Chair Jerome Powell has stressed it’s more important for the U.S., as keeper of the world’s most popular reserve currency, to be right rather than first on this front.Yellen echoed that, saying officials must first address a number of issues -- including how a digital currency might affect traditional bank deposits, financial stability, consumer protection and illicit transactions.“There’s a lot to consider here, but it’s absolutely worth looking at,” she said.Yellen’s predecessor was cool on the idea. In 2018, he said the Fed and Treasury were studying the pros and cons of digital dollars, but “we don’t think there’s any need for that at this point.”For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
