<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LAST HOURS OF 'THE KING'... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/last-ditch-effort-netanyahu-offered-to-resign-let-gantz-serve-as-pm-670783</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last offer came a little after midnight on Thursday, with Netanyahu's team reportedly telling Gantz that Netanyahu is "ready to resign this morning."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man killed by angry residents after urinating in middle of street...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-urinating-in-middle-of-north-houston-street-shot-and-killed-by-confronting-residents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preliminary information from HPD suggests the unidentified man first arrived at the location to buy drugs from someone. However, at some point, the man began urinating in the middle of the roadway, resulting in a large confrontation with the area residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPMORGAN Staff Irked Over Order to Save Texts on Personal Phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.businesstimes.com.sg/banking-finance/jpmorgan-staff-irked-over-order-to-save-texts-on-personal-phones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businesstimes.com.sg&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy Suffers Another Court Loss; Trial Certain In Big Battle Over CBS Deal...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/judge-judy-lawsuit-loss-cbs-rebel-library-sale-1234773722/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Judge Judy concluded shooting her long-running syndicated series earlier this year, but her efforts to shut down a $5 million lawsuit against her and CBS over profits from the lucrative …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un: K-pop 'vicious cancer' that merits execution...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/06/11/kim-jong-un-k-pop-fans-north-korea-culture-bts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BTS vs. The Dictator ... that's the new battlefront for Kim Jong-un, who reportedly sees the rise of K-Pop and its fans as a serious threat to North Korean socialism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US tourist hit by stray bullet in Cancun by jet-skiing cartel!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3064457/us-tourist-hit-by-stray-bullet-in-cancun-attack/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO’S TOURIST mecca Cancun became a crime scene after assassins on jet skis shot and killed two men as a stray bullet struck an American tourist.  The brazen hydro hitmen reportedly were ri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr doesn't recall...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/11/barr-distances-democratic-subpoenas-493491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments come as Democratic congressional leaders demand the former attorney general testify about the leak probes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandmother killed at Florida grocery store fought gunman, police say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/grandmother-killed-at-florida-grocery-store-fought-gunman-police-say/ar-AAKX9rh?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROYAL PALM BEACH, Fla. – A grandmother who was killed with her grandson in a South Florida Publix fought with the gunman, police said Friday. The gunman shot the toddler first. His grandmother grabbed the gun, jamming it in the process, said Palm Beach County Sheriff Maj. Talal Masri. As the gunman tried to reload, he pushed the grandmother to the ground. Then he shot her before turning the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocaine washes ashore at Space Force base...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/1-2-million-worth-of-cocaine-washes-ashore-at-cape-canaveral-space-force-station</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Space Force says 24 packages of cocaine washed ashore on a Cape Canaveral beach. The drugs have an estimated street value of approximately $1.2 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demanded Data on 73 Phone Numbers, 36 Email Addresses from APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/11/politics/justice-department-apple-congress-leak-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice sent a broad request in February 2018 to Apple as part of its investigation that collected data on members of Congress, staffers and their families. The department demanded metadata on 73 phone numbers and 36 email addresses from Apple, the company said Friday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violators of Olympic Games virus rules to face fines...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Violators-of-Summer-Games-virus-rules-to-face-16242277.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO - Athletes and others involved in the Tokyo Olympics who violate rules to prevent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines see unprecedented rise in disruptive passengers. It could get even worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Airlines-have-seen-an-unprecedented-rise-in-16241877.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The headlines had barely faded after a Southwest passenger reportedly knocked out a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  White boys who grew up with Black neighbors more likely to become Dems...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/white-boys-grew-black-neighbors-180023073.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White men who had a Black neighbor in 1940 are more likely to be registered with the Democratic Party 70 years later, researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro booed on plane, tells critics to 'take a donkey'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-booed-plane-tells-critics-211231009.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say Brazil is polarized under far-right President Jair Bolsonaro, but the divide was literal Friday, when he boarded a commercial plane to greet supporters in the front -- as opponents booed him at the top of their lungs from the back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe's first foreign trip as VP was a breeze: Harris's was into the lion's den...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bidens-first-foreign-trip-vp-182712451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contrasting inaugural vice presidential trips — Biden's to Europe in 2009 and Harris' to Latin America — show their different roles in the No. 2 job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN PRAISES TRUMP; SLAMS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/nbc-interview-putin-calls-trump-colorful-says-he-can-work-n1270561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Putin told NBC's Keir Simmons that accusations that he is a "killer" are "Hollywood macho."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abuse of power'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/justice-dept-watchdog-to-probe-trump-era-leak-investigations-including-secret-subpoenas-for-data-from-congress-journalists/ar-AAKWXvm?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats on Capitol Hill called on former attorneys general Jeff Sessions and William Barr to testify over the subpoenas of Democratic Reps. Adam Schiff and Eric Swalwell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC Sh-t Show: 'ULTIMATE SLIP 'N SLIDE' Production Shut Down Over Explosive Diarrhea Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/slip-n-slide-show-nbc-diarrhea-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC's upcoming series "Ultimate Slip 'N Slide" has halted production after dozens of crew members fell ill with "awful explosive diarrhea" on set</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gore pressed Biden to stick with climate plans as liberals fear White House softening agenda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/gore-pressed-biden-to-stick-with-climate-plans-as-liberals-fear-white-house-is-softening-its-agenda/ar-AAKVgkY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president and former vice president had a private phone call amid concerns the White House might strip climate measures from infrastructure deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Tax Leak Referred to FBI as Probe Grows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/billionaire-tax-leak-referred-to-fbi-as-probe-grows-irs-says/ar-AAKV0rD?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disclosure of the personal income and tax data of some of the wealthiest Americans has been referred to additional federal investigators to probe the leak of confidential information, an Internal Revenue Service official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Geophysicist Who Stormed Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/06/11/jeffrey-sabol-capitol-riot-jan-6-radicalization-491975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Sabol lived in a quiet Colorado town and had some doubts about government spending. On January 6, he was photographed with a baton in his hand on the Capitol terrace. How does someone cross the threshold from belief to action?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweeping Overhaul...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/lawmakers-taking-aim-at-big-tech-push-sweeping-overhaul-of-antitrust/ar-AAKX5QY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — House lawmakers on Friday introduced sweeping antitrust legislation aimed at restraining the power of Big Tech and staving off corporate consolidation. If passed, the bills would be the most ambitious update to monopoly laws in decades. The bills — five in total — take direct aim at Amazon, Apple, Facebook and Google and their grip on online commerce, information and entertainment. The proposals would make it easier to break up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago cop broke in,bragged he 'knocked out a commie'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-chicago-police-officer-broke-into-the-capitol-in-january-and-bragged-in-a-text-that-he-knocked-out-a-commie-new-court-filings-show/ar-AAKXgZ1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karol Chwiesiuk, 29, has been a member of the Chicago Police Department since December 2018. He also worked for the Cook County Sheriff's Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland 'legally required' to spend wall money...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jun/11/dhs-legally-required-spend-trumps-border-wall-mone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security officials said Friday they are “legally required” to spend billions of dollars Congress allocated to Mexican border wall construction, but said they will focus on projects that “mitigate” damage from previous construction rather than on finishing the wall President Trump had planned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAMER: Soak the Rich!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnbcs-jim-cramer-calls-for-billionaire-tax-after-propublica-report-these-revelations-make-me-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC's Jim Cramer is calling for a billionaire's tax following the release of a stunning ProPublica report earlier this week exposing the IRS returns of the mega-rich, and showing how little they pay in taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Big-Donor Lobbying for Plum Ambassadorships...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/06/inside-the-big-donor-scramble-for-a-biden-ambassadorship.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They are the closest things we have to somebody being declared a lord or a lady.” But the White House might be changing the rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE suspends Senator for touting unproven Covid treatments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/558056-youtube-suspends-ron-johnson-for-7-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YouTube suspended Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: The scandals we don't know about...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/donald-trump/1001454/doj-subpoenas-scandals-we-dont-know-about</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest revelation of administration abuses won't be the last</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists demanding more action against online harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-journalists-racial-injustice-business-race-and-ethnicity-d986426b7211a67fffb621f0a2414001</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The Associated Press' recent firing of a young reporter for what she said on Twitter has somewhat unexpectedly turned company and industry attention to the flip side of social media engagement — the online abuse that many journalists face routinely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attackers hit Teamsters -- but they refused to pay...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/security/ransomware-attack-hit-teamsters-2019-they-refused-pay-n1270461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI advised the union to "just pay" the ransom, according to sources. Union officials chose to rebuild their computer network instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lobster Diver Survives After Nearly Swallowed Off Cape Cod...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/11/lobster-diver-swallowed-by-whale-cape-cod-michael-packard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lobster diver says he was nearly swallowed by a whale in a terrifying encounter off Cape Cod.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn star who posed nude pic at George Floyd mural found dead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/11/porn-star-who-posed-nude-pic-at-george-floyd-mural-found-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 27-year-old was discovered dead in her Los Angeles motorhome by her husband.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaders agree to keep money taps open...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611180646-8xykl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/ECONOMY (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-G7 leaders agreed to keep the money taps open -source</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gives Biden framed Frederick Douglass photo printed from WIKIPEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/newsletter/london-playbook/politico-g7-playbook-carbis-bay-fitness-regime-hug-and-walk-turbot-charged-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's driving the day in Westminster. Politics and policymaking in the UK capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress, Justice Dept. probing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-donald-trump-ca-state-wire-europe-business-76af370a04c6d80613c9e9ba1e54c8c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Justice Department's internal watchdog launched an investigation Friday after revelations that former President Donald Trump's administration secretly seized phone data from at least two House Democrats as part of an aggressive leaks probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists sent freeze-dried mouse sperm to ISS...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/06/11/space-radiation-sperm-international-space-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists sent freeze-dried mouse sperm to the International Space Station to study the effects of space radiation on reproduction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Doge' meme NFT breaks record, selling for $4 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/iconic-doge-meme-nft-breaks-records-selling-roughly-4-million-n1270161</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meme of an excited Shiba Inu named Kabosu is officially the most expensive meme NFT ever sold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN to drop in-flight magazine...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-a990ef02a12b6a4681613e12b7258c70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT WORTH, Texas (AP) — After more than half a century in airplane seatback pockets, the American Airlines in-flight magazine American Way is going away. An airline spokeswoman said Friday that American will retire the magazine and its online version at the end of June.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will yoga classes in public school lead kids to convert?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-religion-lifestyle-yoga-6596351665214b0f271da3ca8c2808db</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — As soon as Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey signed a bill lifting the state’s 30-year ban on teaching yoga in public schools last month, the critics began weighing in. Christian conservatives said yoga classes might lead students to convert to Hinduism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mocking man's manhood spurs reverse #MeToo in SKorea...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2021-06-11/whats-size-got-to-do-with-it-the-pinching-hand-anti-feminist-backlash-drive-up-the-fever-pitch-of-south-koreas-gender-wars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pinching hand symbol has become a point of contention in a charged battle over gender and anti-feminist backlash by men's rights groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How hedge funds took over struggling industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/11/how-hedge-funds-took-over-americas-struggling-newspaper-industry-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the largest U.S. newspaper groups — like Tribune, McClatchy and Media News Group — are owned, controlled by or in debt to hedge funds or private equity groups. CNBC looks at how this happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate threat to subpoena Barr, Sessions... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/trump-justice-department-democrats-congress/2021/06/11/7c2b1aa8-cace-11eb-a11b-6c6191ccd599_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer and Judiciary Committee Chairman Richard J. Durbin called the secret subpoenas “a gross abuse of power.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bled red as pandemic hit...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/money/other/rupert-murdoch-slashes-value-of-the-sun-newspaper-to-zero/ar-AAKWHqN?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch slashes value of the Sun newspaper to zero</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris tells G7 to build 'more gender neutral, feminine' world...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/politics/15244060/pm-urges-g7-to-build-gender-neutral-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson today called on G7 leaders to build a “more gender neutral, more feminine” world after the pandemic. The PM’s odd rallying cry came as he opened the weekend summit i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  UK's Biggest Paper for Decades -- Now Worth Zero?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jun/11/rupert-murdoch-writes-down-value-of-sun-newspapers-to-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Move follows £200m loss caused by Covid-19 pandemic and one-off charges related to phone hacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When will pandemic end? Where we'll be in 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/when-will-the-pandemic-end-and-will-you-need-a-booster-shot-where-we-ll-be-in-2022/ar-AAKUqXG?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — It’s 2022. And people have learned to live surrounded by the novel coronavirus and its many variants moving across the world that cause COVID-19. Employees are back in the office using a staggered schedule. Kids are in the classroom again. Live theater, concerts and sporting events are playing to audiences across South Florida. And people no longer need to wear a mask to enter a store ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAST HOURS OF 'THE KING'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-middle-east-israel-religion-a8e8517989213286c206d709b212dada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — If all goes according to plan, Israel will swear in a new government on Sunday, ending Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's record 12-year rule and a political crisis that inflicted four elections on the country in less than two years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON ordered to throw out 60 MILLION vaccine doses... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3061480/johnson-covid-vaccine-throw-out-millions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHNSON &amp; Johnson has been ordered by the FDA to throw out 60million Covid jab doses. The discarded shots were made at a facility in Baltimore where there were several violations. The issues le…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inflation storm coming for housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/an-inflation-storm-is-coming-for-the-u-s-housing-market-11623419869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some economists suggest the government may be misunderstanding the size of the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district strips all holiday names to avoid offending anyone!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-jersey-school-district-removes-names-of-all-holidays-from-school-calendar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an outcry at a raucous public meeting over a previous decision to rename Columbus Day as Indigenous Peoples Day, the board of education at a New Jersey school district decided to strip all holiday names off of the school calendar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sets all-time record low tornado activity...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/may-snaps-long-standing-us-streak-for-ef3-tornadoes/955116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been eight years since an EF5 tornado touched down in the U.S., and May ended another streak for strong tornadoes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He 'won lottery' of Israeli politics. But Naftali Bennett remains enigma...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/won-lottery-israeli-politics-naftali-180258953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Naftali Bennett, a right-wing Israeli politician, now stands somewhat surprisingly on the cusp of supplanting Benjamin Netanyahu as prime minister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV employees blamed for theft...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jun/11/italian-tv-employees-blamed-for-theft-of-dozens-of-works-of-art-rai</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Priceless’ pieces removed from Rai’s offices by employees and replaced with fakes, police believe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drug That Could Break American Health Care...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/06/aduhelm-drug-alzheimers-cost-medicare/619169/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aduhelm, the first new Alzheimer’s drug in 18 years, may not work. But states and Medicare might pay billions of dollars for it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch's SUN, UK's Biggest Paper for Decades, Now Worth Zero...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-06-11/murdoch-s-sun-u-k-s-biggest-paper-for-decades-now-worth-zero</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch’s News Corp. wrote down the value of its once high-flying Sun title to zero, underscoring the dramatic decline in Britain’s newspaper industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>400,000 without power in Puerto Rico after fire, cyberattack...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/557957-400000-without-power-in-puerto-rico-after-fire-cyberattack</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were at least 400,000 people without power in Puerto Rico on Thursday night as the company that took over the island’s power transmissions has been faced with fire and cyberattack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details of torture, cover-ups in China internment camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/new-details-torture-cover-ups-china-s-internment-camps-revealed-n1270014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese officials spent days burning documents after government information leaked to global media exposed conditions in the camps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motor neurone disease linked to 'vigorous exercise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-57431412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regular and strenuous exercise can increase the risk of MND in people who are vulnerable, scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden wants world to know America back. But has everyone moved on?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/g-7-summit-biden-looks-reassert-american-leadership-wary-weary-n1270278</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's election has seen "a dramatic shift in America's international image," Pew said, with public opinion rebounding in a dozen key countries since he became president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-thirds of millennials have homebuyer regrets, new survey says...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2021/06/11/millennials-facing-financial-and-physical-regrets-after-buying-homes/7594826002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent Bankrate survey found that 64% of millennials are facing regrets after buying a home, with the main factors being financial and physical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Op-eds in Chinese state tabloid slammed U.S. policy. Author works at Pentagon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/op-eds-in-a-chinese-state-tabloid-slammed-us-policy-the-author-works-at-the-pentagon/ar-AAKWfp2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Franz Gayl, a celebrated whistleblower and former Marine, is being investigated after attacking American policy on Taiwan in a Chinese government mouthpiece.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC to hold 'emergency meeting' on heart inflammation after vax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/557944-cdc-to-hold-emergency-meeting-on-heart-inflammation-after-covid-19-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An advisory panel of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention will hold an emergency meeting on June 18 to discuss rare reports of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of delta variant...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210611100743-8vhsc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SWEDEN-VACCINE:Sweden sees 'dark clouds' with outbreaks of COVID delta variant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blowout Year for CEO Pay...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/11/behold-the-highest-paid-c-e-o-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Want to get the DealBook newsletter in your inbox each day? Sign up here. Paying (a lot) for performance Six</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 inmates escape federal lockups in 18 months; Half not caught...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/government-and-politics-prisons-prison-breaks-business-c1979d6ad6e7b3531968dab0e61eb22d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Over the past 18 months, 29 prisoners have escaped from federal lockups across the U.S. — and nearly half still have not been caught. At some of the institutions, doors are left unlocked, security cameras are broken and officials sometimes don't notice an inmate is missing for hours.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
