<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ARMY 'Google Earth On Steroids' Can Look  Inside Buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-05-28/armys-google-earth-steroids-can-look-inside-buildings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Stuck' weather pattern fuels month of Mayhem....</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/05/29/tornadoes-stuck-weather-pattern-brings-month-mayhem/1273501001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A "stuck" weather pattern has produced a month of stormy mayhem across the central USA, one that's fueled hundreds of tornadoes and boatloads of rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wife of man killed in Hawaii shark attack: 'He went out for one last swim'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article230917393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMATCH:  Despite Warning From Trump, Roy Moore Says He Can Win Alabama Senate Seat... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/29/roy-moore-hits-back-at-trump-in-defiant-interview-1487921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial former judge says the president &amp;quot;doesn't control&amp;quot; Alabama voters, and he can win despite Trump's opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER bans passengers with low ratings...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/05/29/728005817/uber-to-start-banning-passengers-with-low-ratings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Respect is a two-way street, and so is accountability," a company official announced. Riders will get advice on how to improve their ratings before being deactivated, including being polite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI BALKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/congress/article230951583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The dam has burst'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article230956313.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district to become first to use facial recognition technology...</title>
      <link>https://www.lockportjournal.com/news/local_news/lockport-to-test-new-school-safety-system-next-week/article_159eff1c-74f1-5490-83ac-1ba1c5123ab9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lockportjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockport City School District will begin testing its new facial and object recognition system next week, Superintendent Michelle Bradley announced Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL UNPRECEDENTED REPEAT ELECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/Elections-set-for-Sept-17-after-coalition-talks-fail-591044</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exactly one month after the 21st Knesset were sworn in, a majority of the Knesset voted late Wednesday to disperse themselves and initiate an unprecedented repeat election on September 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY IGER: 'Very Difficult' to Work in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/bob-iger-very-difficult-disney-work-georgia-new-abortion-law-enacted-1214329</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company has filmed blockbuster movies in the state such as 'Black Panther' and 'Avengers: Endgame.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Makes Texas play...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2019/05/29/dallas-mayor-mike-rawlings-endorsesjoe-biden-president-spurning-beto-orourke-julian-castro</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dallas Mayor Mike Rawlings is backing Joe Biden for president, saying the nation needs someone who will beat Donald Trump in 2020.Job No. 1 is to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military doomsday plane can endure aftermath of nuke blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/29/us-military-doomsday-plane-can-withstand-aftermath-of-nuclear-blast.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The modified Boeing 747 is born and bred for battle, standing nearly six stories tall, equipped with four colossal engines and capable of enduring the immediate aftermath of a nuclear detonation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Mexicans Arrested Crossing -- Canadian Border...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/05/29/four-mexican-migrants-arrested-in-vermont-after-crossing-canadian-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swanton Sector Border Patrol agents and a K-9 arrested four Mexican nationals who illegally crossed the Canadian border into Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA passenger mauled by emotional support dog files lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/business/delta-passenger-mauled-emotional-support-dog-files-lawsuit/EVZblhoh7JXtDtu4k19GxN/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who was attacked by another passenger's emotional support dog on a flight has sued Delta Air Lines and the other passenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu's future in turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-hold-elections-netanyahu-apos-213023687.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli leader couldn’t cobble together a coalition government within the allotted six weeks, which expired Wednesday night. Elections were set for Sept. 17. “Elections are like wars,” said Shmuel Sandler, a political science professor at Bar-Ilan University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain intensifies flooding in saturated Arkansas, Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e3e7bb59268450ebdb214e9d469d13c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT SMITH, Ark. (AP) — Brad Hindley planned to be vacationing on a lake this week. Instead, he's been on a boat in his swamped Fort Smith neighborhood trying to keep gas in generators that are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuels Impeachment Push...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/251faa8cfa8347438b6513e65d34ab62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller's first — and possibly last — public statement on the Russia investigation is fueling fresh calls on Capitol Hill to begin impeachment proceedings...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rabid bat hiding in iPad attacks senior...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/south-hampton-man-bit-by-bat-hiding-in-his-ipad-case/27617219</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South Hampton man is on the mend after a bat somehow got inside his home and bit him last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN!  Bernie backers see DNC-media sabotage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/may/29/bernie-sanders-supporters-distrust-joe-biden-poll-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For hardcore Bernie Sanders supporters, Joe Biden’s early domination of the race smacks of 2016, when the Democratic National Committee attempted to sabotage Mr. Sanders and clear the way to the nomination for Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's smallest newborn who weighed same as an APPLE survives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/fabulous/9181959/worlds-smallest-baby-survives-saybie/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MIRACLE baby thought to be the world’s tiniest newborn at 8.6oz survived despite her parents being warned she’d only live for an hour, it was revealed last night. The little girl, nam…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal prosecutors demand Cindy Yang records from Mar-a-Lago, Trump campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article230946518.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski's Wife Takes Aim at Tarantino Over 'HOLLYWOOD'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/roman-polanskis-wife-criticizes-tarantino-including-husband-once-a-time-hollywood-1213976</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polish actor Rafał Zawierucha plays Polanski in Tarantino's film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sets himself on fire outside White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7083457/Man-sets-fire-seen-engulfed-flames-near-White-House.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man set himself on fire Wednesday near the White House, the Secret Service said. He was taken to hospital with 'life threatening injuries' after suffering burns to 85% of his body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese video urges war with USA...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/chinese-video-urges-war-with-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's Communist Party-controlled media stepped up a war of words with the United States recently urging an escalation of the trade dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RETIRES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/94323cfc164c4759ba6bf84ad2a46203</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Special counsel Robert Mueller said Wednesday that charging President Donald Trump with a crime was "not an option" because of federal rules, but he used his first public remarks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGING TRUMP 'NOT OPTION'</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/special-counsel-robert-mueller-make-statement-amid-democratic/story?id=63344952</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller said Wednesday he does not intend to testify as Democrats want, says charging Trump with a crime was "not an option."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHTMARE:  Man lifts toilet seat and is bitten by python snake rising from bowl...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/toiletsnake-attacks-189536</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 29--As a Florida Man lifted the toilet seat in his bathroom early Sunday morning, a four-foot ball python “rose out of the toilet and bit him” on the arm, according to a police report brimming w</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Democrat Governor Set to Sign Strict Abortion Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.theadvocate.com/baton_rouge/news/politics/legislature/article_203ff9f8-80ba-11e9-b1d1-af1136fb73ae.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana lawmakers have approved a bill that would ban abortions at about six weeks of pregnancy, if upheld by the courts, sending it to the governor's desk without exceptions for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot summer ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/05/robert-mueller-press-conference-impeachment-politics-democrats/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel just upped the pressure on those in the party who think impeaching Trump is politically ill-advised.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key differences with Barr...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Mueller-s-statement-highlights-key-differences-13905087.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Departing special counsel Robert Mueller finally spoke publicly Wednesday, and his carefully chosen comments highlight the ways in which he disagrees with his boss, Attorney General William Barr, about the facts and the law surrounding the investigation into President Donald Trump.  "If we had confidence that the president clearly did not commit a crime, we would have said that," Mueller said Wednesday.  Barr had that confidence. He declared in March that while Mueller's principal conclusions did not include a determination of whether the president had committed the crime of obstruction of justice, Barr had reviewed the evidence and concluded that Trump did not break the law.  "The Special Counsel's decision to describe the facts of his obstruction investigation without reaching any legal conclusions leaves it to the Attorney General to determine whether the conduct described in the report constitutes a crime," Barr wrote to Congress at the time.  In his report and his public remarks, Mueller indicated that he holds a different view on the question of potential presidential crimes, refusing to clear Trump and alluding to Congress' impeachment power as the constitutional arbiter.  Mueller's remarks also made clear how heavily his office relied on a long-standing legal opinion from the Justice Department's Office of Legal Counsel that a sitting president cannot be indicted. That opinion, Mueller said Wednesday, "says that the Constitution requires a process other than the criminal justice system to formally accuse a sitting president of wrongdoing."  Asked about his disagreements with Mueller, Barr has made a point of emphasizing that when the two men met privately on March 5 to discuss the findings, Mueller said he would not say the president would have been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare color footage brings D-Day memories alive...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/europe/2019/05/rare-color-footage-brings-d-day-memories-alive-75-years-on/slide/9/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprising color images bring an immediacy to wartime memories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python leaps out of toilet to bite man...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/coral-springs/fl-ne-coral-springs-snake-attack-20190528-togijbdkvvgspd2nfjptngzsh4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Florida, beware of creatures that may lurk in the toilet bowl. A 52-year-old man opened the seat of his toilet and found a ball python, which bit him. (On the arm, not on the ... well, you know.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana Democrat Governor Set to Sign Strict Abortion Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.nola.com/politics/2019/05/louisiana-lawmakers-pass-a-strict-ban-on-abortion.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nola.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louisiana lawmakers pass a strict ban on abortion as early as six weeks of pregnancy, without rape or incest exceptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange health 'deteriorating', moved to prison hospital wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7084541/Julian-Assange-moved-hospital-wing-Belmarsh-prison-losing-weight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a statement, WikiLeaks said: 'WikiLeaks has grave concerns about the state of health of our publisher, Julian Assange, who has been moved to the health ward of Belmarsh prison.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing leads to censoring political satire, dissent?</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/613592/facebook-pelosi-video-misinformation-censorship-free-speech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking down the ‘drunk ’ Pelosi video could set a precedent for censoring political satire or dissent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER SLAPS PRESIDENT ON WAY OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/robert-mueller-make-public-statement-about-russia-probe-wednesday-n1011331?DFds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The special counsel, speaking publicly for the first time, said in a statement that he was bound by Justice Department policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD NOT CLEAR HIM OF OBSTRUCTION!</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/breaking-mueller-says-hes-not-confident-that-trump-did-not-commit-a-crime/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller finally made a public statement today, weeks after finishing his investigation and his report––with redactions––was made available to the public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V I D E O</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?461196-1/special-counsel-robert-mueller-make-statement-russia-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PODHORETZ: Disgraceful Mess...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/29/muellers-final-statement-was-a-disgraceful-mess/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special prosecutor Robert Mueller’s statement upon the shuttering of his two-year investigation into the Trump campaign was weird even by the standards of the weirdness of the past couple of years.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUELLER RETIRES</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/latest-white-house-says-told-mueller-might-speak-141544632--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on special counsel Robert Mueller and the Russia investigation (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLOSES OFFICE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mueller-first-public-statement-russia-135537084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If we had had confidence the president clearly did not commit a crime we would have said so,” Mueller said in his first public remarks in the two years since he was named special counsel. The special counsel also said he found “insufficient evidence to charge a broader conspiracy” on election interference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Stops Private Org From Building Wall... </title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/05/liberal-mayor-of-sunland-park-issues-cease-and-desist-order-against-we-build-the-wall-for-building-border-wall-to-protect-americavideo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPS use increases developing Alzheimer's risk, expert warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/05/29/google-maps-increases-risk-developingalzheimers-expert-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satellite navigation aids like Google Maps could be damaging people&amp;rsquo;s brains and may even contribute to the development of Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, a navigation expert has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy drinks linked to frightening side effects...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/energy-drinks-may-be-linked-to-frightening-side-effects-for-your-heart-2019-05-29</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drinking 32 ounces in an hour increased the risk of electrical disturbances in the heart, an American Heart Association study found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle to dethrone LeBron for 'best player' label in NBA finals...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/05/29/best-player-nba-finals-analysis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The upcoming Finals between the Raptors and the Golden State Warriors, which begins Thursday night, will feature three stars — Stephen Curry, Kevin Durant and Kawhi Leonard — who can ma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead dolphins keep washing up on Delaware beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.delmarvanow.com/story/news/2019/05/29/dead-dolphins-washing-up-delaware-heres-what-we-know/1268738001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delmarvanow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delaware's marine mammal experts were busy with dolphin strandings this Memorial Day weekend, but they say it's no reason for alarm, for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kawhi Silent Superstar: Not Playing For Fame...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/kawhi-championship-not-fame-190606713--nba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kawhi Leonard loses zero sleep pondering his place in the pantheon of NBA greats. The Toronto Raptors' All-Star is restlessly pursuing only one thing: a championship ring. "I'm not playing the game for (notoriety)," Leonard said at NBA Finals media day Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tickets selling for $45,000!</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/05/29/nba-finals-2019-warriors-raptors-game-4-tickets-181740/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person spent a ton of cash on tickets to game four of the NBA finals between the Warriors and Raptors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Tehran mayor confesses to killing his wife on TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Former-Tehran-mayor-confesses-to-killing-his-13904200.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Mohammed Ali Najafi turned himself in to Iranian authorities Tuesday night, he wore a nice suit and a smile and was greeted warmly by police.  But Najafi, a former mayor of Tehran, was there to make a confession. He said he had killed his wife, Mitra Ostad, ,the night before after threatening her with a gun because she refused to grant him a divorce.  Najafi, 67, a reformist politician, said he killed her accidentally after surprising her in the bathroom at their home in a wealthy Tehran neighborhood.  The dramatic case, Najafi's bizarre and televised confession, and the hands-off approach of investigating authorities have scandalized, enraged and baffled Iranians, who have long criticized the preferential treatment given to government officials in matters before the law.  State television filmed Najafi, who also once served as education minister and is a graduate of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, as he sat un-handcuffed and casually sipping tea in a police commander's office. The officials shook Najafi's hand and bowed deferentially, while a reporter interviewed him.  "We had an argument and then I showed her this gun to scare her while she was getting ready to take a bath," Najafi said. "She panicked and attacked me in order to take the gun and I mistakenly touched the trigger."  In a separate segment aired by the state broadcaster IRIB, the reporter handles the alleged weapon used in the killing and counts the number of bullets left in the chamber, asserting that two struck Ostad and that a third was fired into the wall.  "So far, [this case] is not a criminal investigation, even by the standards of the Iranian judiciary," Tehran-based lawyer Shady Sadr said on Twitter.  "The tests on the murder weapon, from the finger prints to matching the bullets with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area more racially segregated now than in '70s...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/The-Bay-Area-of-1970-was-less-racially-segregated-13902101.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven of the Bay Area’s nine counties had more segregation in 2010 than they did in 1970. The only two that saw declines — San Francisco and Alameda counties — remain classified as “high” segregation places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Turns on FACEBOOK:  'Willing Enablers' of Russians...</title>
      <link>https://www.kqed.org/news/11750792/nancy-pelosi-doctored-videos-show-facebook-willing-enablers-of-russians-in-2016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kqed.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi lashed out at Facebook on Wednesday, saying the social media giant's refusal to take down altered videos of her calls into question their contention that they were unwitting victims of Russian interference in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City To Ticket Drivers $50 For Giving Money To Panhandlers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/05/28/newark-ticketing-drivers-who-give-money-to-panhandlers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may want to think twice before giving money to panhandlers in Newark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawn mower accidents maiming kids...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/lawn-mower-accidents-are-maiming-children-simple-fix-might-have-n1010761</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although human error is an obvious factor, another is a choice by some mower manufacturers to design their machines so they can mow in reverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Frees NASA Scientist Imprisoned for 2 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/business/article230951448.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 4,400 Steps-A-Day To Save Life...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/many-steps-per-day-improve-183755603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If 10,000 steps a day sounds like too lofty a goal, take heart: People who step less than half that amount may still see significant health benefits, according to a new study published in the jou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUCCI jumps into abortion war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/855ca8e1f14941bb8bce6a9dce64a8cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — Gucci creative director Alessandro Michele has made a clear abortion rights message in his latest Cruise collection, as the debate over abortion heats up once again in the United...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FERRARI Reveals Hybrid Supercar...</title>
      <link>https://jalopnik.com/the-ferrari-sf90-stradale-hybrid-is-a-very-busy-superca-1835093749</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;jalopnik.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pictures of Ferrari’s much anticipated new hybrid supercar has already been leaked a bit, in a now-deleted blurry picture on Instagram, but now there’s a full set of what appear to be Ferrari press photos of what is called the SF90 Stradale. It’s clearly crammed full of Ferrari DNA, though it does have a somewhat busy, techno-fetishy sort of look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microbes may predict future health...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1a44a418eb6b455681bdde01b3fcda3b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — We share our bodies with trillions of microbes that are critical to staying healthy, but now scientists are getting a much-needed close look at how those bugs can get out of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas lifts ban on brass knuckles, kitty keychains and clubs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/texas-legislature/2019/05/15/brass-knuckles-kitty-keychains-ban-lifted-texas-lawmakers-heads-gov-abbotts-desk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN — Texas lawmakers have passed legislation lifting the state ban on brass knuckles, kitty keychains and other self defense items.The bill...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Pet dog snatched from home, covered in acid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/782116/pet-dog-acid-attack-newry-co-down-pound-road-northern-ireland-animal-cruelty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell Angers Dems With Vow to Fill a 2020 Supreme Court Vacancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-05-29/mcconnell-vows-to-fill-any-new-high-court-vacancy-unlike-2016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGE OF OVERTOURISM...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f30f813a9d5e46c7b6a3de8b85b855cb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Paris, the Louvre Museum closed for a day this week because workers said the crowds were too big to handle. In the Himalayas, climbers at Mount Everest are concerned that the peak has gotten...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BONDS FLASH RECESSION WARNING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/29/stock-markets-wall-street-monitors-intensifying-global-growth-fears.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell as bond yields declined again, triggering concerns about the economic outlook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress, health of whales might be in giant mouths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be254d3e5ed942f6a1eb32d425330d65</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Whale researchers in New England believe they've found a new way to measure the amount of stress felt by whales when they experience traumas such as entanglements in fishing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  'Free' apps spying on you...</title>
      <link>https://www.wrdw.com/nbc26/content/news/No-your-smartphone-is-not-listening-to-you-but-the-free-apps-youre-downloading-are-tracking-your-every-move-510559571.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wrdw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you own a smart phone, this has probably happened to you: you're talking to someone about a product or activity-- and ads for it start popping up on your social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of illegals detained near Mexico border transferred to NYC-area jails...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-borders-crossers-nyc-20190529-jspoiqkm7bd3foedvon2nlkopu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 230 undocumented immigrants detained at the border have been transferred to jails around New York and New Jersey in the last week as the feds struggle to find beds for a growing number of detainees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four poachers dead in shootout over tigers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190529-four-poachers-shot-dead-bangladesh-mangrove-gunfight </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four poachers shot dead in Bangladesh mangrove gunfight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POKEMON turns 'sleep into entertainment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-48443194</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How long a user has slept for and when they wake up will be a part of game play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA RARE EARTH THREAT...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/china-gears-weaponize-rare-earths-002041977.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flurry of Chinese media reports on Wednesday, including an editorial in the flagship newspaper of the Communist Party, raised the prospect of Beijing cutting exports of the commodities that are critical in defense, energy, electronics and automobile sectors. The world’s biggest producer, China supplies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia 'conducting nuke tests'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190529131704-lmcky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DEFENSE/ (URGENT):U.S. believes Russia conducting low-level nuclear tests -official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Bay Area of 1970  less racially segregated than 2010...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/The-Bay-Area-of-1970-was-less-racially-segregated-13902101.php?psid=7hRlH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven of the Bay Area’s nine counties had more segregation in 2010 than they did in 1970. The only two that saw declines — San Francisco and Alameda counties — remain classified as “high” segregation places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC makes it more difficult to qualify for 3rd debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/05/29/abc-univision-democratic-debate-1346099</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate is set for Sept. 12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden 18-point lead on Dem field...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445896-poll-biden-has-18-point-lead-on-democratic-field-sanders-only-other </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie spoiler?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445859-democrats-worry-bernie-sanders-could-play-spoiler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are worried that if he doesn’t win the party’s presidential nomination himself, Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) will be a thorn in the side of the Democratic nominee for president — especially if it’s former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood 'de-aging' gone too far? Scorsese thinks so...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/shortcuts/2019/may/29/hollywood-de-aging-digitally-martin-scorsese-will-smith-anthony-hopkins-robert-downey-de-niro-pacino</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will Smith, Anthony Hopkins and Robert Downey Jr have all been digitally rejuvenated. Now Robert De Niro and Al Pacino are having their wrinkles zapped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank deploys droid...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/business/fl-bz-hsbc-deploys-robot-to-assist-customers-20190529-b73uhzbngfbtlmoctg5kgh5h54-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-five years after Atlanta National Bank introduced its customers to ATMs by portraying them up as a woman named "Tillie the All Time Teller," HSBC Bank is deploying a mobile, rolling assistant named Pepper to interact with its lobby customers at its Brickell branch in Miami. The rollout follows Pepper deployments at HSBC branches in New York, Seattle, and Beverly Hills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Merkel's succession plan unravelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.newstatesman.com/world/europe/2019/05/how-angela-merkel-s-succession-plan-unravelled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newstatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For German Christian Democrat leader Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, once regarded as Angela Merkel’s natural successor as chancellor, recent weeks have been politically enfeebling. As the European parliament election results were announced on Sunday night (26 May), it became clear that the Christian Democrats (CDU) had endured their worst-ever nationwide performance (winning just 28.9 per cent of the vote). The consolation for the 56-year-old Kramp-Karrenbauer (known in Germany as AKK) was that the rival Social Democrats (SPD) had fared yet worse. Their vote share of 15.8 per cent left them in third place behind the Greens, who surged to 20.5 per cent. Added to this, the CDU defeated the SPD in Bremen, the city state the centre-left party had governed for over 70 years. Yet, incredibly, AKK has since managed to divert attention away from the CDU’s hapless coalition partners. The party leader repeated her misguided attack on a group of 70 YouTube influencers who urged young voters not to support the ruling parties. On Monday (27 May) she sharply criticised their campaign and spoke of the need for new rules to govern the online sphere, leading to accusations that she was infringing freedom of speech. While AKK’s comments may have been misinterpreted, her decision to refuel the controversy demonstrated remarkable political ineptitude. It’s a trap the sphinx-like Merkel would never have fallen into. It’s not AKK’s first gaffe: a joke about transgender people during a stand-up routine at a festival alienated party moderates. Her approval ratings have notably plummeted since her narrow election victory as CDU leader in December (ending Merkel’s 18-year reign). The more Germans see of AKK, it appears, the less they like her. But it’s the party leader’s wider political strategy that could cause her greater problems. AKK’s move to push the CDU to the right in order to take on the far-right Alternative für Deutschland (AfD), has merely opened up the centre ground, which Merkel always sought to occupy, allowing the Greens to rush in. In the European elections, the CDU lost four times as many votes to the Greens as to the AfD. A stunning 1.2 million voters switched from the conservatives to the environmentalist party, almost as many as the 1.5 million who deserted the SPD. Meanwhile, in eastern Germany, the CDU’s attempt to court AfD voters failed, with the far-right party finishing first in Saxony and Brandenburg, both of which hold state elections in September. While the CDU can forgive missteps such as the YouTube controversy, electoral losses are far more serious. Merkel’s centrist trajectory may have been highly unpopular with many sections of the party, but her repeated election victories (she has retained office for 14 years) made her position almost unassailable. Merkel is thought to be increasingly unhappy with her protégé. On Tuesday (28 May), Bloomberg, citing two unnamed German officials, reported that the chancellor had lost faith in AKK’s ability to take on the role and was increasingly determined to remain in office until 2021. At an EU summit on Tuesday evening, however, Merkel described such reports as “nonsense”. Furthermore, Merkel has always suggested that she intends to serve out this legislative period. After that, it’s ultimately up to the party to decide on its candidate for chancellor, not Merkel. More significantly, perhaps, AKK’s internal rivals were already manoeuvring against her. Armin Laschet, the influential CDU leader of North Rhine-Westphalia, pointedly defended press freedom on Tuesday. And Friedrich Merz, an old rival of Merkel’s, who AKK narrowly defeated in the leadership contest, denounced both women over their climate policies in comments to Der Spiegel. If Merz, who is popular with the economically liberal wing of the party, were to oust AKK, it is inconceivable that Merkel could stay on as chancellor. Meanwhile, the increasingly fragile grand coalition — between the CDU and the SPD — could still fall apart. The SPD is reeling from its electoral humiliation and its leader Andrea Nahles is fighting for survival. Many on the SPD left now argue the only way to revive the party is by exiting the grand coalition when it is reviewed this autumn. Yet the SPD’s departure from government could further marginalise them, leaving the Greens to take over as Germany’s main progressive force. The Greens, says Carsten Nickel of political risk firm Teneo, are benefiting from a realignment across Europe as traditional left/right divides are replaced by ones between liberal progressives and conservative nationalists. They have also managed to address young people’s environmental concerns — a remarkable 36 per cent of first-time voters backed them — while exploiting wider dissatisfaction with the government, despite historically low unemployment (5 per cent) and a relatively robust economy. The Greens’ charismatic co-leader, 49-year-old Robert Habeck, is increasingly spoken of as a potential chancellor, either in coalition with the SPD and the Left Party or, perhaps more likely, in a CDU-Green coalition. Yet here too, AKK has demonstrated a lack of political prowess, firmly rejecting many climate protection proposals and failing to take the school strike movement (Friday for Futures) seriously. Her political mishaps mean she will likely face the wrath of her party at a CDU gathering this weekend. Ironically, she called the meeting, without first notifying Merkel, in what was regarded as an unsuccessful attempt to push the chancellor to step down. Yet it is Merkel, still highly popular among German voters, who holds the advantage ahead of the conference. Relatively untainted by the EU election results, she has played the role of global stateswoman this week, delivering a speech at Harvard University, giving a lengthy interview on CNN and sparring with French president Emmanuel Macron over the top EU jobs at a Brussels summit. Meanwhile, if AKK survives the coming weeks, her next electoral test will soon be upon her, with two state elections in September. Should the CDU and the SPD perform poorly, the grand coalition could crumble and AKK would likely never lead the CDU into another election. That would mean the question of who succeeds Merkel — and leads Europe’s largest country — would once again be wide open. Siobhán Dowling is a Berlin-based journalist who has written for publications including Spiegel International, the New York Times and the Guardian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French #MeToo founder sued for slander by man she accused...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190529-french-metoo-founder-sued-slander-man-she-accused</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French #MeToo founder sued for slander by man she accused</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIDEST CURVE INVERSION SINCE FINANCIAL CRISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/05/29/us-bonds-wall-street-monitors-fresh-batch-of-economic-data-auctions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Treasury yields fell broadly on Wednesday as continuing trade worries sparked fears of an economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham draws Dem challenger who mocks his ties to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Lindsey-Graham-draws-a-Democratic-challenger-who-13903136.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jaime Harrison, the former chairman of the South Carolina Democratic Party, formally kicked off his campaign Wednesday to topple Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., with a video that highlights his humble roots and Graham's evolving views on President Trump.  Harrison, who was the state party's first black chairman and is a former aide to Rep. James Clyburn, D-S.C., has been encouraged to run by national party leaders in a state that has not elected a Democrat to the Senate since 1998.  In his announcement video, Harrison highlighted his birth to a 16-year-old mother, his upbringing by his grandparents, his education at Yale University and Georgetown Law School and his return to South Carolina.  The video also included clips of derogatory comments that Graham made about Trump as they both were pursuing the Republican presidential nomination in 2016, including Graham labeling Trump "a kook," "crazy" and "not fit to be president of the United States."  "He's a race-baiting, xenophobic religious bigot," Graham said in one highlighted clip.  In subsequent clips, Graham is shown saying, "No, I don't think he's a xenophobic, race-baiting, religious bigot," and that Trump "deserves the Nobel Peace Prize and then some."  "Here's a guy who will say anything to stay in office," Harrison said in the video. "Lindsey Graham can't lead us any direction because he traded his moral compass for petty political gain."  Graham, who is serving his third term, defeated his Democratic challenger in 2014 by more than 16 percentage points. Trump carried the state over Democrat Hillary Clinton in 2016 by 14 percentage points.  In an interview with The Washington Post in March, as he was considering a Senate bid, Harrison said that Graham's reelection "is not a slam dunk for him" given his emergence as a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX horror movie making people physically sick...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/05/28/netflix-horror-movie-the-perfection-is-making-people-sick/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix’s new movie “The Perfection” is sick — and not in the good way. Viewers are reporting headaches, nausea and even vomiting after watching the 90-minute horror flick’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will we all be having sex without human contact by 2050?</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/05/28/will-we-all-be-having-sex-without-human-contact-by-2050-9674895/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex robots, virtual reality, sophisticated holograms - how will we have sex in the future?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Danes make welfare hot election issue as cracks show in Nordic model...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-denmark-election-welfare-insight/danes-make-welfare-a-hot-election-issue-as-cracks-show-in-nordic-model-idUSKCN1SZ0IC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nordic welfare model, long the envy of many across the world seeking an egal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson to face trial for alleged Brexit lies...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/boris-johnson-trial-brexit-court-lying-prosecution-nhs-vote-leave-a8934451.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots taking on more warehouse jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bendbulletin.com/business/7192925-151/robots-are-taking-on-more-warehouse-jobs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bendbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — Tephnee Usher stands in a McDonough, Georgia, warehouse, separated from the stored goods by a black chain-link fence, and waits for robots to deliver the goods to her.Human workers are confined to opposite edges of this 17-acre roofed space: delivery bays and shipping bays about a football field apart. The vast concrete area between them belongs to 225 electric powered, eerily silent robotic Butlers that perform tasks people used to do.E-commerce, growing at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dems look to retool campaigns as Biden lead widens...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/445472-2020-democrats-look-to-retool-campaigns-as-biden-takes-wide-lead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential candidates chasing former Vice President Joe Biden in the polls are shifting gears as they seek to gain momentum heading into the first debate next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor claims Lorne Michaels pressured him to have sex with director...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/05/28/chris-kattan-claims-lorne-michaels-pressured-him-to-have-sex-with-a-director/?_ga=2.4400378.836796910.1558907218-463512201.1557541843</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday Night Live alum Chris Kattan claims in a new book that producer Lorne Michaels once pressured him to have sex with a director so she would stay attached to the 1990s comedy film “A N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coalition or New Vote? Israel in Nail-Biter as Deadline Looms... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coalition-vote-israel-nail-biter-085956120.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Israeli prime minister, who managed to glide past a tangle of corruption scandals to win a fifth term in April 9 elections, hasn’t been able to resolve an impasse between prospective governing partners on who should serve in the army. If he can’t assemble a majority government by the deadline, he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floating sweatshops: Fish you eat caught by 'slaves'?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/floating-sweatshops-fish-eat-caught-slaves-054944487.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enslaved, beaten, malnourished, and so desperate for water he had to collect condensation to drink: Rahmatullah left Indonesia seeking better prospects at sea -- instead he endured a living hell. The global fishing industry is riddled with forced labour, anti-trafficking experts say, warning that consumers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX satellites pose new headache for astronomers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spacex-satellites-pose-headache-astronomers-012453689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looked like a scene from a sci-fi blockbuster: an astronomer in the Netherlands captured footage of a train of brightly-lit SpaceX satellites ascending through the night sky this weekend, stunning space enthusiasts across the globe. The launch was tracked around the world and it soon became clear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Johnson denies mistreating employees during Lakers' stint...</title>
      <link>https://news.abs-cbn.com/sports/05/29/19/nba-magic-johnson-denies-mistreating-employees-during-lakers-stint</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reacting to an ESPN report earlier Tuesday that described a toxic culture in the Los Angeles Lakers' front office, Magic Johnson denied mistreating any employees during his stint as team president that ended last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crackdown on internet 'will put free Press at risk', warns Society of Editors...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7080003/Crackdown-internet-free-Press-risk-warns-Society-Editors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new rules drawn up by the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) will wreak ‘untold harm’ on newspapers and websites, the Society of Editors has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore ransomware attack could be coming to your city  -- or hospital... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2019/05/28/baltimore-ransomware-attack-could-be-coming-your-city-or-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These attacks tend to select victims that have weak cybersecurity practices and the means to pay substantial ransoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500  --  in 30-day period!</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/world/2019/05/28/daily-tornado-streak-has-us-approaching-uncharted-territory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  CNN to make cuts to London bureau...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/may/28/cnn-preparing-cuts-london-based-news-operation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surprise announcement likely to result in at least a dozen employees losing their jobs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces new attacks over draft... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Trump-faces-new-attacks-over-draft-13902323.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump, who has touted himself as an unmatched ally of military veterans, is facing pointed new attacks from Democratic presidential candidates who question his medical deferment from service in Vietnam - and, in turn, his patriotism and integrity.  Leading the assault are two military veterans: South Bend, Indiana, Mayor Pete Buttigieg and Rep. Seth Moulton, D-Mass. They have offered searing assessments of Trump, accusing the president of faking a disability and forcing another American of Trump's generation to risk his life in the jungles of Southeast Asia.  Trump, who had been traveling in Japan, has not yet responded to either Democrat, but he has long defended his deferments as legitimate. More broadly, he portrays himself as a vigorous friend to the military, pushing for a buildup of the armed forces, praising military leaders, reaching out to veterans and promising to avoid misguided wars.  But the questioning of the 1968 diagnosis of bone spurs in his heels presents a challenge for a commander in chief who has tapped generals for his Cabinet and asked the Pentagon to plan a parade celebrating the military. It could test whether the president's political coalition, which includes many military families, can be cracked.  "I don't think that lying to get out of serving your country is patriotic. It's not like there was just some empty seat in Vietnam. Someone had to go in his place," Moulton said Sunday on MSNBC. "I'd like to meet the American hero who went in Donald Trump's place to Vietnam. I hope he's still alive."  Buttigieg, speaking at a Washington Post Live event last week, said of Trump, "This is somebody who, I think it's fairly obvious to most of us, took advantage of the fact that he was a child of a multimillionaire in order to pretend to be disabled so that somebody could go...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Fooled Secret Service, Snuck into Mar-a-Lago While Trump in Town...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/news/20190528/college-freshman-slipped-into-mar-a-lago-while-trump-was-in-town</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of Wisconsin student fooled Secret Service and got past security at an underground tunnel during the Thanksgiving break. It took 20 minutes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cult  'sex slave' was illegal immigrant whose status was used to keep her in line, she testifies...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-20190528-pjhequqt4bf7pmucsw2obohqlu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TKTK</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri to be first in country without clinic...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/planned-parenthood-missouri-last-abortion-clinic-says-it-may-lose-its-license-this-week-exclusive-2019-05-28/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is not a drill," said Planned Parenthood president Dr. Leana Wen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amash gets standing ovation at first town hall after calling for Trump's impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/445862-amash-gets-standing-ovation-at-first-town-hall-after-calling-for-trumps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Justin Amash (R-Mich.) received a standing ovation Tuesday evening at his first public event since becoming the first Republican to call for President Trump's impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Sees Succession Plan Unraveling...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/merkel-sees-succession-plan-unraveling-105234243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel has decided that Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, who took over as leader of the Christian Democratic Union in December, is not up to the country’s top job, according to two officials with knowledge of her thinking. Asked about Bloomberg’s report at a news conference in Brussels late on Tuesday, Merkel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 months later, gene-edited babies stir new interest, debate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f5ece0d3e53f4991bd0b6c71cf936588</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six months after a Chinese scientist was widely scorned for helping to make the world's first gene-edited babies, he remains out of public view, and new information suggests that others may be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois to expand abortion rights as other states restrict...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bb3a6dd970b4e42a70411ae5b92dc04</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPRINGFIELD, Ill. (AP) — The Illinois House voted to bolster the right to abortion on Tuesday as Democratic-led states respond to restrictions placed by some Republican-led states that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After quiet years, tornadoes erupt in United States...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/496ec60aef0d4585b40f563fedb54855</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANPOLIS, Ind. (AP) — After several quiet years, the United States was threatening to break a major record for tornado activity this week as a volatile mix of warm, moist air from the Southeast...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEVASTATED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3ae113ae56e74e7fa8f6248de7edf05e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROOKVILLE, Ohio (AP) — A swarm of tornadoes so tightly packed that one may have crossed the path carved by another tore across Indiana and Ohio overnight, smashing homes, blowing out windows and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing may restrict rare-earth exports to USA...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190528140832-3a6p6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-USA/RAREEARTH (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China may restrict rare-earth exports to U.S., Global Times editor says</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
