<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>GILLETTE Ad Challenges Men to Shave Their Toxic Masculinity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/p-g-challenges-men-to-shave-their-toxic-masculinity-in-gillette-ad-11547467200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gillette addresses ‘toxic masculinity’ in a new digital ad campaign aimed at men, the latest message from an advertiser attempting to change societal norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Fall of Porn's Julian Assange...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-rise-and-fall-of-porns-julian-assange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donny Long ran Porn Wikileaks, which terrorized adult actors and outed ‘crossover’ performers. Then he fled the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERHUMAN babies?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/752949/stephen-hawking-designer-baby-crispr-he-jiankui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Debated Whether Trump Was Following Putin 'Directions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/14/politics/trump-fbi-debate-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the chaotic aftermath at the FBI following Director James Comey's firing, a half-dozen senior FBI officials huddled to set in motion the momentous move to open an investigation into President Donald Trump that included trying to understand why he was acting in ways that seemed to benefit Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish Mayor Dies After Stabbed In Heart On Stage At Charity Event...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/fc1f50c3b8964efabf012002f712bfa6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — The popular liberal mayor of the Polish port city of Gdansk died on Monday after he was stabbed during a charity event the evening before by an ex-convict who stormed onstage and said it was revenge against a political party the politician once belonged to. Pawel Adamowicz, 53, died as a result of wounds to the heart and abdomen in spite of efforts to save him that involved a five-hour operation and blood transfusions, Health Minister Lukasz Szumowski said. "The fight for his life has been lost," Szumowski said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 most likely impeachment scenarios...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/817163/5-most-likely-trump-impeachment-scenarios</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats' favorite subject, ranked</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Father of DNA' Stripped of Honors Over Race Comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/father-of-dna-james-watson-stripped-of-accolades-in-ugly-racism-row</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The acclaimed Nobel Prize-winning scientist James Watson will be forever remembered as one of the 'fathers of DNA'. But also as something much worse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris Opera drops star dancer after homophobic rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-paris-opera-drops-star-dancer-after-homophobic-rant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris Opera drops star dancer after homophobic rant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to Build Conscious Robots Using Insect Brains?</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/darpa-wants-conscious-robots-insect-brains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Even small insects have subjective experiences, the first step towards a concept of 'consciousness.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German newspaper says employee attacked by far-right group...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/german-newspaper-says-employee-attacked-far-group-112549672.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A German newspaper says one of its employees has been attacked by members of a far-right group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady &amp; Drew Brees: Beware the Zombie Geezers!</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/tom-brady-drew-brees-beware-the-zombie-geezers-11547470483</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patrick Mahomes and Jared Goff are brilliant young talents, but if either wants a Super Bowl, they’ll have to pry it from ancient fingers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Court Sentences Canadian National to Death for Drug Crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/chinese-court-sentences-canadian-national-to-death-for-drug-crimes-in-retrial-11547470636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese court ordered the death penalty for a Canadian national after convicting him in a hurried retrial that legal experts called an attempt by Beijing to up its leverage over Ottawa for the arrest of a prominent Chinese executive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside NETFLIX all-out blitz to win Best Picture...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90291385/inside-netflixs-all-out-blitz-to-win-a-best-picture-oscar-for-roma </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming giant really, really wants the Academy to like it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest aircraft goes mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/airlander-10-prototype-new-model-gbr-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's largest aircraft, Airlander 10, has been retired after six test flights. Its developers plan to produce a new, commercial model to take to the skies in the early 2020s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jay-Z's TIDAL Under Investigation on Streaming Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/jay-z-s-tidal-under-investigation-in-norway-on-streaming-fraud#gs.SYUvMOG5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay-Z's Tidal Under Investigation in Norway on Streaming Fraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Democratic primary set to intensify...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f6c539eb9ff244ddbf3437f53912bfe9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — After months of speculation and secrecy, the 2020 presidential primary season is about to explode. With several Democrats already in the race, a half dozen more are locking down final travel, staffing and strategy to launch White House bids in the coming weeks. While plans may change, the announcements are expected to come in waves, the first featuring a group of ambitious Senate Democrats including New York Sen. Kirsten Gillibrand, California Sen. Kamala Harris and New Jersey Sen. Cory Booker, who face pressure to join the race after Massachusetts Sen. Elizabeth Warren's entrance two weeks ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heavy smog, worsened by weather, raises alarm across Asia...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f2c23aed11bd4d6fab023d14784a02f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — Unusually high levels of smog worsened by weather patterns are raising alarm across Asia, with authorities in Thailand's hazy capital Bangkok handing out face masks and preparing to seed clouds for rain to clear the air. A combination of construction dust, auto exhaust and other pollutants, lingering over Bangkok due to prevailing weather patterns, has taken air quality to unhealthy levels in recent days. "I admit these are temporary solutions but we have to do it. Other long term measures will also be implemented, Police Gen. Aswin Kwanmuang told a meeting of army, police, pollution control and other officials on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh-faced Venezuelan lawmaker emerges as Maduro rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/143774a1887345c2983513327dc85a62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — When Venezuelans rang in the new year, few in the crisis-wracked nation had even heard of Juan Guaido. Two weeks later, the young backbench lawmaker has emerged as a key power broker as he leads the opposition-controlled congress in a high-stakes standoff with socialist President Nicolas Maduro, who is increasingly seen as a dictator both at home and abroad. "Guaido for president!" people shouted Friday at the largest street rally in over a year to take on Maduro, eagerly waiting for the fresh-faced 35-year-old to speak. "Out with Maduro!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signs Of Times? Plague Of Locusts; Earth's Magnetic Pole 'Shift'...</title>
      <link>http://theeconomiccollapseblog.com/archives/signs-of-the-times-a-plague-of-locusts-hits-mecca-and-earths-magnetic-pole-is-experiencing-a-sudden-shift</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeconomiccollapseblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Really strange things are starting to happen all over the world.  We'll talk about "the North Pole's sudden shift" later in this article, but first I want to focus on the very unusual event which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market about to get bad news from corporate America?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/finance/news/q4-earnings-season-preview-news-priced-in-163705017.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With companies about to release earnings for the fourth quarter, early indications are that commentary about the global economy will be very discouraging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Super-Secure Quantum Cable Hiding in Holland Tunnel...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/the-super-secure-quantum-cable-hiding-in-the-holland-tunnel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super-Secure Quantum Cable Hiding in the Holland Tunnel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger with gun made it through TSA, onto DELTA flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/traveler-carries-gun-from-atlanta-to-japan-after-going-through-airport-screening/903900169</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The current partial government shutdown had started about a week and a half before the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ROMA' top winner at Critics' Choice Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-cuarons-roma-top-winner-critics-choice-awards</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuaron's 'Roma' a top winner at the Critics' Choice Awards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's first 'cyber-dissident' faces trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190114-chinas-first-cyber-dissident-faces-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's first 'cyber-dissident' faces trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA SAYS TRADE SURPLUS WITH USA HIGHEST IN DECADE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/14/china-2018-full-year-december-trade-exports-imports-trade-balance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's trade surplus with the U.S. grew 17 percent from a year ago to hit $323.32 billion in 2018 — the highest on record dating back to 2006, according to Reuters' calculations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge-Fund-Backed Group Preps GANNETT Bid; Contentious History With Newspapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/hedge-fund-backed-media-group-prepares-bid-for-gannett-11547427720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hedge-fund-backed media group known for buying up struggling local papers and cutting costs is planning to make an offer for USA Today publisher Gannett, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 CATS rent $1,500-a-month Silicon Valley apartment...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/01/13/landlord-rents-1500-studio-to-two-cats-hits-peak-silicon-valley/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They definitely have the nicest cat apartment in Silicon Valley,” says their owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Taunts 'Bozo', Praises NATIONAL ENQUIRER...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/donald-trump/trump-unleashes-on-jeff-bozo-for-ownership-of-washington-post-says-national-enquirer-reporting-is-far-more-accurate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loophole allows MS-13 members to go free...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/13/unaccompanied-child-immigration-loophole-releases-/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All three of the illegal immigrants entered the U.S. in 2016 as unaccompanied alien children, meaning they crossed the border without parents — a status that earned them a quick release into the country, where they were quickly reunited with their family and began to live while awaiting deportations that never came.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'McJesus' Sculpture Causes Violent Clash In Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/arab-christians-in-violent-clash-with-police-in-haifa-over-mcjesus-sculpture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;3 officers wounded as hundreds of protesters try to forcibly enter Haifa Museum during demonstration against depiction of Ronald McDonald on a cross</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady wrongly pronounced dead dies from hypothermia in morgue...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/01/13/woman-62-wrongly-pronounced-dead-dies-from-hypothermia-in-morgue-8340922/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A morgue worker was fixing a number tag to the foot of the ‘corpse’ when she suddenly started moving.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST FRONT MONDAY: Court filing in Manafort case shows Mueller's intense focus on Russia contacts... </title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/revelations-about-manaforts-2016-interactions-with-russian-associate-show-special-counsels-intense-focus-on-russia-contacts/2019/01/13/0f3733dc-144b-11e9-803c-4ef28312c8b9_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new details inadvertently revealed in a court filing serve as a reminder that President Trump’s White House bid was led for a time by a man with long-standing ties to powerful Russian figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady revels in washed up talk: 'Everyone thinks suck'...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/01/13/tom-brady-revels-in-perception-that-patriots-are-washed-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Consecutive losses to the Dolphins and Steelers prompted many to conclude that it was finally over for the Patriots. And that may be exactly what the Patriots wanted. After consecutive wins to end …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONRAD BLACK: America's resurgence  reshaping world...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/opinion/conrad-black-americas-resurgence-is-reshaping-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is demonstrating almost effortlessly how illusory is the idea that any other country or group of countries can challenge its pre-eminence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators feeling pressure of longest shutdown in history...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75cb070bc4414b778a13add8c13eb4a1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What's up with the partial government shutdown on Day 23. WHAT'S NEW TODAY Sen. Lindsey Graham, R-S.C., who is close to President Donald Trump, says he's been pushing the president to reopen the government for a few weeks to continue negotiating with Democrats over funding for a border wall before bypassing Congress and declaring a national emergency. Canadian air traffic controllers are buying pizzas for their American counterparts in Salt Lake City, Utah, and Anchorage, Alaska, as a show of support. Some 10,000 air traffic controllers in the U.S. have been working without pay since Dec. 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Sought Options to Strike Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-sought-options-to-strike-iran-11547375404</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National security adviser John Bolton asked the Pentagon to provide the White House with military options to strike Iran in the wake of attacks near the U.S. Embassy and consulate in Iraq last September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Impasse Frustrates Many Newly Elected House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wall-impasse-frustrates-many-newly-elected-house-democrats-11547380801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some House Democrats, many who beat Republicans in the 2018 midterms, want party leadership to chart a clearer strategy in trying to end the government shutdown and compromise with President Trump on border security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Economic Growth Pinched...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/shutdown-pinches-economic-growth-11547423636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The partial federal government shutdown is showing signs of disrupting commerce as hundreds of thousands of federal workers missed out on their first payday of the closure late last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing Dems to Left, Whether They Like It or Not...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ocasio-cortez-pushes-democrats-to-the-left-whether-they-like-it-or-not/ar-BBSbkCl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Stop obsessing over Ruth Bader Ginsburg's health...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Stop-obsessing-over-Ruth-Bader-Ginsburg-s-health-13530389.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first scene of the documentary "RBG," Gloria Steinem calls Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg "a superhero." The label could not be more appropriate - or more stifling. In recent years, Ginsburg, 85, has acquired a cultlike following.You can buy baby onesies and stud earrings of the jabot she wears when she delivers dissents; her workout routine has become a source of fitspiration; and, most recently, Felicity Jones played a young Ginsburg in the movie "On the Basis of Sex." But, at the same time, her fragility has become clearer. Since Ginsburg's appointment to the Supreme Court, she has survived both colorectal and pancreatic cancers. In November, she took time off after a fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron Tells French It's Time to Channel Anger Away From Streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-13/macron-tells-french-it-s-time-to-channel-anger-away-from-streets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham Blinks:  Urges Trump to open govt 'temporarily'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190113192336-1wc1i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (PIX):Republican ally Graham urges Trump to open US government temporarily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration court backlog could grow by years...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/nation/immigration-court-backlog-could-grow-by-years-after-government-shutdown/article_4a847c79-3f1f-586a-8ac5-2ee46b506a9a.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES –– The shutdown of the federal government over the president’s campaign promise to build a wall along the southern U.S. border is taking its toll on already backed-up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Confrontse Prospect of 'Nonstop Political War' for Survival...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-confronts-the-prospect-of-a-%E2%80%98nonstop-political-war%E2%80%99-for-survival/ar-BBSb33j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES FRONT SUNDAY:  Executive privilege threat hangs over Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/russia-investigation-could-spark-battle-to-learn-robert-muellers-findings/ar-BBS7JSs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hate groups' are about to find lawmakers eager to scrutinize them...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/latest-news/article224234360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New House Homeland Security Committee Chair Bennie Thompson plans more scrutiny of domestic far-right groups</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another body found in rubble of Paris bakery blast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6586489/Death-toll-Paris-bakery-blast-killed-two-firefighters-Spanish-tourist-rises-four.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death toll from a gas explosion in central Paris has risen to four after rescue workers found the body of a missing woman in the rubble. Two firefighters and a Spanish tourist were also killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Warn Watching NFL Playoffs Can Affect Blood Pressure, Stress Levels...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/01/11/watching-an-eagles-game-is-literally-a-workout-doctors-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because this isn't just a game, it really does impact your health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio won't rule out run...</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-pol-deblasio-run-for-president-2020-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I never rule things out, because you never know what life brings,” Mayor de Blasio said of a possible 2020 presidential bid Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gronkowski done?</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001010163/article/patriots-te-rob-gronkowski-to-weigh-retirement-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trying to handle bumps and bruises related to his ankle and back, Rob Gronkowski is having his worst statistical season since his rookie year. Is that enough to convince the Pats tight end to hang it up?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUT LONGEST EVER...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190112175730-lhlf3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-U.S. government shutdown breaks record, with no end in sight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Impasse Frustrates Many Newly Elected House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/wall-impasse-frustrates-many-newly-elected-house-democrats-11547380801?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some House Democrats, many who beat Republicans in the 2018 midterms, want party leadership to chart a clearer strategy in trying to end the government shutdown and compromise with President Trump on border security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Turn to Emergency Loans...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/government-workers-idled-by-shutdown-turn-to-emergency-loans-11547246027</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of workers affected by the government shutdown have applied for emergency loans and requested delays in mortgage payments, as many of them on Friday missed their first paycheck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS PARTY IN PUERTO RICO DURING SHUTDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/30-dems-in-puerto-rico-with-109-lobbyists-for-weekend-despite-shutdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 30 Democratic lawmakers left the government shutdown behind Friday on a chartered flight to Puerto Rico for a winter retreat with 109 lobbyists and corporate executives during which they planned to see the hit Broadway show “Hamilton” and attend three parties including one with the show’s cast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed feedback for Kamala Harris in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/12/us/politics/kamala-harris-democrats.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“She’s my first choice to be my first choice.” In Manhattan, voters met Ms. Harris, a Democratic senator from California, as she prepares for a possible presidential run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE's famous 'walled garden' starting to show cracks...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/09/apple-walled-garden-starting-to-show-cracks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple will have to look beyond its tight ecosystem of hardware and software if it wants to grow its services business</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Oversight Chair Cummings to 'Hit Ground "Flying'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elijah-cummings-talks-to-60-minutes-in-first-interview-as-house-oversight-committee-chairman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new chair of the House Oversight and Reform Committee tells 60 Minutes he’ll have to hit the ground “flying” with majority power to investigate the Trump administration. Sunday at 7 p.m. ET/PT on CBS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez becomes TWITTER queen...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/ocasio-cortez-dominates-twitter-6a997938-b8a5-4a8b-a895-0a1bcd073fea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A freshman congresswoman who has held office for a week is dominating the national conversation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US govt has amassed terabytes of internal WIKILEAKS data...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/the-u-s-government-has-amassed-terabytes-of-internal-w-1831640212</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last year, the U.S. government accidentally revealed that a sealed complaint had been filed against Julian Assange, the founder of WikiLeaks. Shortly before this was made public, the FBI reconfirmed its investigation of WikiLeaks was ongoing, and the Wall Street Journal reported that the Department of Justice was optimistic that it would be able to extradite Assange. Soon after, portions of sealed transcripts leaked that implicate WikiLeaks and Assange in directing hackers to target governments and corporations. The charges against Assange have not been officially revealed, though it’s plausible that the offenses are related to Russian hacking and the DNC emails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tehran Using Space Launch to Test ICBMs...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-space-launch-cover-for-test-of-nuclear-capable-missile-tech-u-s-determines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. says Iran's planned launch of satellites into space is actually a cover for the regime's continued testing of advanced missile technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Ever Woman To Officiate NFL Playoff Game...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/01/11/sarah-thomas-nfl-history-inspiring-female-football-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sarah Thomas will be the first woman to officiate an NFL playoff game. Among all the eyes sure to be on her – a special group of supporters – her fellow female football officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska eyes regulations on the word 'meat'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c7924a64199e46da88488d5a0fe8c7bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LINCOLN, Neb. (AP) — More than four months after Missouri became the first U.S. state to regulate the term "meat" on product labels, Nebraska's powerful farm groups are pushing for similar protection from veggie burgers, tofu dogs and other items that look and taste like real meat. Nebraska lawmakers will consider a bill this year to prevent companies that package and sell food from advertising plant-based, insect-based and lab-grown products as meat. Similar measures are pending in Tennessee, Virginia and Wyoming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Stagecraft won't win battle...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bb78c70cbe3345e7b77946d004e9dff3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Military salutes. Heaps of contraband. Oval Office optics. President Donald Trump, who has long put a premium on stagecraft, is discovering he cannot resolve the partial government shutdown simply by putting on a show. With the standoff over paying for his long-promised U.S.-Mexico wall dragging on, the president's Oval Office address and visit to the Texas border this past week failed to break the logjam. Aides and allies are fearful that he has misjudged Democratic resolve and is running out of negotiating options.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
