<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Thousands protest in El Salvador against 'dictator' Bukele...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20211018-thousands-protest-in-el-salvador-against-dictator-president-bukele</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people in El Salvador took to the streets on Sunday in protest against President Nayib Bukele, who has stoked concern that he is steadily concentrating power and who responded by changin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strikes!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/enoughs-enough-tight-u-job-100623109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of workers remain on strike across the United States demanding higher pay and better conditions despite Hollywood make-up artists and camera operators reaching a deal over the weekend to avoid a walkout, and the tight jobs market has only emboldened them. Kevin Bradshaw is an employee at Kellogg Co's cereal plant in Memphis, Tennessee, where most of North America's Frosted Flakes are made. "Enough is enough," said Bradshaw, vice president of Bakery, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers International Union Local 252G at the Memphis plant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep calm': Georgia town calls for unity as prepares for Black jogger murder trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018095844-jkibn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGIA-ARBERY-BRUNSWICK (PIX, TV):'Keep calm': A Georgia town calls for unity as it prepares for Black jogger murder trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China denies report of hypersonic missile test, says tested space vehicle...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211018094212-lg9ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-SPACE/DIPLOMACY (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-China denies report of hypersonic missile test, says tested space vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Shares Roaring Back...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tesla-shares-roaring-back-081557874.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Tesla Inc. shares are staging a comeback as investors expect the Elon Musk-led electric carmaker to navigate the crippling semiconductor shortage better than rivals that have been severely disrupted.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkWhy Buying a Second or Even Third Home Is Becoming More Popular Than EverGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightOut-of-Pract</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music, Barbecues, Wi-Fi: Managing Morale for Those Idled at Sea...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/music-barbecues-wi-fi-managing-060000826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Plenty of things might keep container-ship captain Markus Grote up at night while sailing across the ocean, but lately there’s another kind of sinking feeling that worries him: crew morale.Most Read from BloombergGoogle’s Biggest Moonshot Is Its Search for a Carbon-Free FutureThe Biggest Public Graveyard in the U.S. Is Becoming a ParkWhy Buying a Second or Even Third Home Is Becoming More Popular Than EverGoogle’s CEO: ‘We’re Losing Time’ in the Climate FightOut-of-Practice Airlin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 'Great Resignation' goes global...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/The-Great-Resignation-goes-global-16541578.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the United States, the phenomenon dubbed as the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jefferson Statue May Be Removed After More Than 100 Years at City Hall...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/18/jefferson-statue-may-be-removed-after-more-than-100-years-at-city-hall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 100 years, a 7-foot-tall statue of Thomas Jefferson has towered over members of the New York City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Nuke Bomb Could Save Earth From Stealthy Asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/18/how-a-nuclear-bomb-could-save-earth-from-a-stealthy-asteroid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One day, astronomers may spot an asteroid months away from a cataclysmic rendezvous with Earth. Our only chance of survival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA'S LEAP IN HYPERSONIC MISSILE TECHNOLOGY SHAKES U.S. INTELLIGENCE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10101953/Beijing-mocks-America-saying-new-21-000mph-nuclear-capable-missile-new-blow-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese military launched the Long March rocket, a nuclear-capable missile, in August carrying a hypersonic glide vehicle' in low orbit. It circled the globe before returning to Earth to strike its target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychosis cases soar as pandemic hits mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/oct/18/psychosis-cases-soar-in-england-as-pandemic-hits-mental-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;75% rise in referrals for first suspected episode of psychosis between April 2019 and April 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creepy Kanye goes white...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3876391/kanye-west-balenciaga-mask-venice-divorce-kim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KANYE West wore a creepy mask and an all black Balenciaga outfit after performing at a wedding in Venice, Italy, as his divorce from Kim Kardashian moves forward. Kanye, 44, went undercover in Veni…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jon Stewart Torches Media for Hyping Stories to Stir Up Conflict...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/jon-stewart-torches-the-media-on-cnn-for-hyping-stories-to-stir-up-conflict-who-gives-a-sht-about-gender-neutral-toy-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jon Stewart delivered a scathing critique of the media on CNN Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMITH:  At AXEL SPRINGER, POLITICO's New Owner, Allegations of Sex, Lies and a Secret Payment...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/17/business/media/axel-springer-bild-julian-reichelt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A high-flying German media giant is ahead on digital media but seems stuck in the past when it comes to the workplace and deal-making.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE MAN WHO WILL TAKE ON ORBAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/hungary-e2-80-99s-opposition-parties-unite-to-challenge-far-right-leader-orban/ar-AAPDDRU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six parties from across the political spectrum banded together to pick Catholic conservative Peter Marki-Zay as their candidate in the 2022 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Literary world chaos as acclaimed female crime writer revealed to be 3 men...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/17/europe/spanish-female-writer-revealed-intl-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain's literary world has been thrown into chaos after a coveted book prize was given to "Carmen Mola" -- a lauded female thriller writer who turned out to be the pseudonym of three men.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'More immediate, more visceral' and a lot tougher on Eric Clapton: A plan for reviving ROLLING STONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/More-immediate-more-visceral-and-a-lot-tougher-16539068.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last Monday in Manhattan, outside the Fifth Avenue offices of Rolling Stone, dozens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN reporter leaving company over requirements...</title>
      <link>https://awfulannouncing.com/espn/allison-williams-is-leaving-espn-over-covid-19-vaccine-mandate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;awfulannouncing.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ESPN sideline reporter Allison Williams hasn't been on CFB sidelines after choosing not to get vaccinated. She's now leaving the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21,000 mph nukes that can hit anywhere in MINUTES...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3874979/china-hypersonic-arms-race-russia-north-korea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA appears to have taken a shock lead in the hypersonic arms race as the world’s powers battle it out for the next generation of devastating nuclear weapons. Revelations that Beijing flew …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE' RATINGS HIT ALL-TIME LOW...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/10/17/lowest-rating-to-date-rami-malek-hosted-saturday-night-live-with-surprise-guest-daniel-craig</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Bond walks into a gay bar. But should he?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/nbc-out/out-life-and-style/james-bond-walks-gay-bar-rcna3115</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Bond actor Daniel Craig made headwinds this week when he revealed that he is a big fan of gay bars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British lawmakers could get police protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/british-lawmakers-could-get-police-protection-when-meeting-constituents-in-wake-of-david-amess-killing/ar-AAPDctw?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home Secretary Priti Patel says the government is also considering asking constituents to pre-book appointments with their elected representatives for weekly public meetings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strikes!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/strikes-are-sweeping-the-labor-market-as-workers-wield-new-leverage/ar-AAPCOoa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The labor activism runs the gamut of American industry, powered by the same grievances about wages, benefits and quality of life driving the Great Resignation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 5 Nights in Hospital, Bill Clinton Released...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bill-clinton-heads-home-spending-150526164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinton, 75, was treated for a urological infection that spread to his blood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan's health ministry warns of '6th wave'...</title>
      <link>https://mainichi.jp/english/articles/20211002/p2a/00m/0na/020000c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mainichi.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO -- The Japanese health ministry has sent a notice to prefectural governments requesting that they review their medical systems in preparation fo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clashes intensify between city officials, police...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/17/across-the-u-s-clashes-intensify-between-city-officials-and-the-police-over-vaccination-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many cities across the country, there is friction between governments and law enforcement unions over requirements that officers get</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Supreme Court: Late nights, courtesy votes, unwritten 6-vote rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/17/politics/supreme-court-conference-rules-breyer/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of the US Supreme Court's business occurs in private, but there are some customs everyone should know</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warnock's record-breaking haul sends national message...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/warnocks-record-breaking-fundraising-sends-national-message/5WW3GRJM6BCI5LKUX3CLB6RBF4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Raphael Warnock amassed another record-breaking fundraising haul in the Georgia 2022 Senate race, while GOP donors came off the sidelines to boost Republican Herschel Walker’s challenge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says dosed can enjoy holidays with family...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/577088-fauci-says-americans-can-enjoy-holidays-with-family-if-fully-vaccinated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden’s chief medical adviser Anthony Fauci provided reassurance to Americans eager to spend time with relatives in the coming months, saying on Sunday that they could convene if all are fully vaccina</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGES: Man Turns Backyard Field Into Private Airport!</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/10/16/twin-cities-man-accused-of-operating-airstrip-in-field-behind-his-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Twin Cities man is facing charges after allegedly carving a runway into a field behind his home and using it as a private airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems find their anti-Rubio warrior in Val Demings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/dems-find-their-anti-rubio-warrior-in-val-demings/ar-AAPCWN7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida congresswoman is amassing an army of small donors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 5 Nights in Hospital, Bill Clinton May Be Released...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/16/bill-clinton-expected-to-be-released-from-hospital-sunday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Bill Clinton is expected to be released from a California hospital Sunday after five days of treatment for a urological infection, a spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TN Fans Throw Trash At Cheerleaders, Coach...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/10/17/tennessee-fans-throw-trash-ole-miss-lane-kiffin-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tennessee fans melted down during a 31-26 loss to Ole Miss late Saturday night. Fans threw trash at Lane Kiffin and Ole Miss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest drawing of ghost discovered on Babylonian tablet...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2021/oct/16/figures-of-babylon-oldest-drawing-of-a-ghost-found-in-british-museum-vault</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3,500-year-old image tablet of a ‘miserable male ghost’ gives up its secret</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marriage Rates Plummeting. Why Reality Dating Series So Popular?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/10/17/reality-dating-series-conservatism-515581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the dating-and-marriage storyline still appeals so much to audiences who are increasingly opting out of the tradition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lawless city?' Worry after Portland police don't stop chaos...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/wireStory/lawless-city-worry-portland-police-stop-chaos-80613763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crowd of 100 people wreaked havoc in downtown Portland, Oregon, this week, smashing storefront windows, lighting dumpsters on fire and causing at least $500,000 in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Tahoe so low, boats marooned...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/renotahoe/article/Lake-Tahoe-drought-water-rim-algae-16533020.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no telling how low Tahoe will get if we don’t see a massive winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia records highest daily new case number...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/russia-records-highest-daily-new-covid-19-case-number-rcna3151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is reporting its largest daily number of new coronavirus infections, more than 70 percent up on the number a month ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservatives change their tune on big government...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/577021-the-memo-conservatives-change-their-tune-on-big-government</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Old political orthodoxies are being scrambled by a combination of the COVID-19 pandemic, the influence of former President Trump and the deep current of polarization tearing through the nation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
