<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>WILL BIDEN PAY PRICE?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-worry-biden-could-pay-the-political-price-for-rising-inflation/ar-AASIutK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala  team works to improve her public image...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article257152827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Kamala Harris is retooling her press and communications operation as she begins her second year in office. Allies of Harris hope the reset will help with criticism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron disrupts essential services...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/12/covid-news-omicron-disrupts-essential-services-as-workers-call-out.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's hard to process what's actually happening right now, which is most people are going to get Covid," acting FDA Commissioner Janet Woodcock said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NYC mayor puts younger brother in charge of his security detail despite lingering ethics concerns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ny-mayor-eric-adams-puts-024800555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK — New York City Mayor Eric Adams is putting his younger brother in charge of his security detail, backing off a previous push to install him in a high-ranking NYPD post — but the switch up did not mollify government watchdogs concerned that the intrafamily hire flies in the face of city ethics law. Bernard Adams, who hasn’t served in law enforcement since retiring as a New York Police ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California's overflowing coffers hand Newsom 'every politician's dream'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/californias-overflowing-coffers-hand-newsom-130016756.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The governor's allies say his good fortune provides him a rare opportunity to focus on creating a better California, allowing him to spend time on a long-term agenda that could become his legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits recall heartbreaking sacrifices they made...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/britain-s-boris-johnson-apologizes-amid-national-anger-over-lockdown-party-at-his-residence/ar-AASHvhj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO:  Death rate 'remains unsustainably high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/12/who-says-omicron-cases-are-off-the-charts-as-global-infections-set-new-records.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The sheer volume of cases is putting a burden on health-care systems," said Maria Van Kerkhove, WHO's technical lead on Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  NYC mayor reassigns brother to head his security detail...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/york-mayor-reassigns-brother-head-001317685.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City Mayor Eric Adams has reassigned his younger brother to a job overseeing his physical security, the New York Times reported on Wednesday, days after naming him deputy police commissioner of the largest U.S. police department. Bernard Adams, a retired police sergeant of the New York Police Department, will serve as executive director of mayoral security, a job with a typical salary of $210,000, the Times reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans grapple with prolonged testing woes...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220112211721-lxugd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Americans grapple with prolonged testing woes amid Omicron surge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quebec tax on unvaccinated sets risky precedent...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220112210250-ufxpn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/QUEBEC-TAX:Quebec tax on unvaccinated may be lawful but sets risky precedent - experts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Rich Terrified Of 'Social Cohesion Erosion'...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90712209/why-global-leaders-are-terrified-about-social-cohesion-erosion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new survey from the World Economic Forum, it’s the fastest-growing threat to our planet since the COVID crisis struck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWYER PLANS DEPO...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/12/prince-andrew-sex-abuse-lawsuit-can-go-forward-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge on Wednesday ruled that the sex abuse lawsuit against Prince Andrew brought by a longtime Jeffrey Epstein accuser could move forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Chernobyl' At State Department As Virus Decimates Agency...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chernobyl-state-department-covid-decimates-211049058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid international crises, the key national security agency is experiencing a stunning surge in coronavirus cases, three U.S. officials told HuffPost this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada drops mandate for its truckers after pressure from industry...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220113034627-2356h</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia covid infections hit record amid runaway outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220113020254-pgxzb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROYAL SHOCK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prince-andrew-sex-abuse-lawsuit-fca8488a4553e74cdfc0a722d2960442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A judge has — for now — refused to dismiss a lawsuit against Britain’s Prince Andrew by an American woman who says he sexually abused her when she was 17. Stressing Wednesday that he wasn’t ruling on the truth of the allegations, U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic admits travel declaration had incorrect information...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/immigration-coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-health-591c103de643abc147b0fb7e2703afc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE, Australia (AP) — Novak Djokovic has acknowledged that his Australian travel declaration form contained incorrect information, as the government nears a decision on whether to deport the Serbian tennis star, who is not vaccinated against COVID-19, on public interest grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-kevin-mccarthy-mark-meadows-bennie-thompson-congress-92d310c0bb0232afc0c3d0a6b179874a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House panel investigating the U.S. Capitol insurrection requested an interview and records from House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy on Wednesday, as it continues to seek first-hand details from members of Congress on former President Donald Trump’s actions on the day hundreds of his supporters brutally beat police, stormed the building and interrupted the certification of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalizations rise in Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-hawaii-honolulu-86e9e562c48cffb79401019a6f0e9649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii recorded an increase in COVID-19 hospitalizations Wednesday as the omicron variant continued to spread throughout the islands. State data initially showed was a 35% increase in hospitalizations from the previous day, the Honolulu Star-Advertiser reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION HIGHEST IN 40 YEARS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/consumer-prices-inflation-c1bfd93ed1719cf0135420f4fd0270f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Inflation jumped at its fastest pace in nearly 40 years last month, a 7% spike from a year earlier that is increasing household expenses, eating into wage gains and heaping pressure on President Joe Biden and the Federal Reserve to address what has become the biggest threat to the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm at rise of illegal pot farms...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/12/oregon-marijuana-illegal-farms-environment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed men in pickup trucks rule over vast illicit industry that has transformed rural counties, depleting water and scaring locals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don Roasts 'Gutless' DeSantis for Keeping Booster Status Secret...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-roasts-gutless-desantis-for-keeping-his-booster-status-a-secret</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president has ridiculed politicians who don’t want to say they’ve taken a third shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vaxxers Paying Sick $150 for Dinner and Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/desperate-no-vaxxers-paying-covid-positive-people-dollar150-for-dinner-and-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new vaccination mandate in Italy requires everyone over 50 to be vaccinated or pay a hefty fine. Some are opting to pay to get infected with COVID instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge MMA fighter pummels 'little boy' who stepped in for fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4447659/mma-fans-evolution-of-combat-mistmatch-mma-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIXED MARTIAL ARTS fans were left disgusted after the discovery of one of the most shocking mismatches on a UK show last September. Evolution of Combat 9 pitted up-and-coming fighter Aron Lee again…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN: He's in big trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4446947/piers-morgan-warning-boris-johnson-lockdown-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PIERS Morgan has warned Boris Johnson he is in “big trouble” after he was today forced to apologise over a No10 lockdown-busting bash. The embattled PM finally admitted attending the pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWITCH HITTER:  Guilfoyle and first husband Newsom years before secret engagement to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4443461/kimberly-guilfoyle-trump-unrecognizable-picture-gavin-newsom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIMBERLY Guilfoyle looks completely different in this throwback picture from 2004. Before Donald Trump Jr. came along, the former Fox News host was married to California Governor Gavin Newsom. In a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man claims penis shrank from virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4445676/mans-penis-shrinks-covid-permanent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN claims his penis has shrunk by an inch-and-a-half due to Covid, and doctors say it can’t be fixed. The anonymous male said the lasting effect of the virus has damaged his self confidenc…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Tablespoon Olive Oil Daily Lowers Risk Of Cancer, Heart Disease, Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/olive-oil-fatal-heart-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers found consuming more than 7 grams - or half a tablespoon - each day were less likely to die from heart disease, cancer, or dementia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAG SNUBS 'WEST SIDE'; GOES GAGA...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/12/updating-live-sag-noms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL TO $100?</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/oil-prices-could-hit-100-demand-outstrips-supply-analysts-say-2022-01-12/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices that rallied 50% in 2021 will power further ahead this year, some analysts predict, saying a lack of production capacity and limited investment in the sector could lift crude to $90 or even above $100 a barrel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin Threatening War. Are Russians Willing to Fight It?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/12/russia-ukraine-putin-war-526967</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russians largely believe Putin is right about Ukraine and NATO. But it’s not clear whether they are willing to go to war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 committee seeks testimony from Republican leader McCarthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/12/jan-6-select-panel-to-seek-mccarthys-testimony-526983</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It follows months of speculation about when the panel would seek the California Republican's cooperation with their probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. says '99% sure' of identity of man in blackface...</title>
      <link>https://www.pilotonline.com/government/virginia/dp-nw-northam-blackface-question-20220111-klk7l6kdujemrglws4ara54kc4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ralph Northam told The Washington Post he's “99% sure” of the identity of the man featured on his medical school yearbook page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz's Ex-Girlfriend Testifies to Grand Jury...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/matt-gaetz-s-ex-girlfriend-testifies-grand-jury-sex-trafficking-n1287352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The development suggests the Department of Justice may be moving closer to indicting the Florida Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men vandalized Key West landmark. Bartender recognized one because he hadn't tipped...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/two-men-vandalized-a-key-west-landmark-a-bartender-recognized-one-of-them-because-he-hadn-e2-80-99t-tipped/ar-AASHqd7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Making Friends Midlife Is So Hard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-to-make-new-friends-at-40/ar-AASI47r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vax Dad 'On Run' With 7-Year-Old Daughter to Keep From Jab...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/anti-vax-dad-on-the-run-with-7-year-old-daughter-to-keep-her-from-covid-jab/ar-AASI4Cp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/uknews/serial-liar-boris-johnson-should-go-former-tory-attorney-general-says/ar-AASEG8l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominic Grieve said the Prime Minister should be ousted after the latest allegations about Downing Street rule-breaking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hangs Up on NPR After Challenged...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-hangs-up-npr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump called in for an interview with NPR's Steve Inskeep and was challenged on baseless allegations of election fraud. Fireworks ensued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran attempt to recruit Israelis as spies thwarted...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-692312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walls closing in?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10395519/Gaetzs-ex-girlfriend-gives-testimony-federal-grand-jury-sex-trafficking-case-report-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Gaetz's ex-girlfriend had sought deal to avoid prosecution for obstruction of justice in return for giving evidence against Florida Republican.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewership at CNN plummets as much as 90%...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10394997/CNN-loses-nearly-90-advertiser-coveted-demographics-overall-total-audience.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN averaged just 548,000 viewers during the week of January 3, a precipitous drop to the nearly 2.7 million viewers from the same week in 2021. The ratings come amid multiple scandals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech founder born in Soviet Union compares metaverse to communist propaganda...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/metaverse-hype-communist-propaganda-evernote-founder-phil-libin-soviet-union-2022-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You can smell a bad idea before it's fully built," Phil Libin, Evernote's founder, told journalists Eric Newcomer, Katie Benner, and Tom Dotan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un Hypersonics Show He Can Hit Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/kim-jong-un-s-new-hypersonic-missiles-show-he-can-hit-u-s-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong Un’s New Hypersonic Missiles Show He Can Hit U.S. Back</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman stuck in lockdown with blind date...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-china-59969509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swift lockdown in China’s Zhengzhou means a woman is stuck at her date’s house.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGNORED FOR YEARS, 'YELLOWSTONE' FINALLY BREAKS INTO AWARDS RACE...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/tv/news/yellowstone-sag-nomination-awards-1235152314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paramount Network’s “Yellowstone” is finally a major television awards contender after four seasons thanks to the 2022 Screen Actors Guild Awards. The family western drama is nomi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WV Gov. 'extremely unwell' after positive...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/589346-wva-governor-extremely-unwell-after-positive-covid-19-test</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice (R) announced on Tuesday he had tested positive for COVID-19 and was feeling "extremely unwell."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Is a Snitch...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/01/12/facebook-is-a-snitch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This shouldn't be a revelation, but posting the details of your life online is not an effective way to keep...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED:  Saying Goodbye to Stars Who Left Us in 2021...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/12/saying-goodbye-the-stars-who-left-us-in-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are loved, envied, gossiped about and gone.  Here’s a toast to their final year, and a thimble of hope for 2022, when no matter how bad things get there is comfort in the knowledge that …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icon Ronnie Spector dead at 78...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/12/ronnie-spector-rock-icon-behind-be-my-baby-dead-at-78/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her trademark beehive and unapologetic bad-girl swagger made waves in the music industry when the rock group first hit the airwaves in 1963.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lasers and Hypersonic Missiles: Navy Unveils Next Gen Warship...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/01/12/navy-unveils-next-generation-ddgx-warship-concept-with-hypersonic-missiles-lasers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Va. – The Navy wants its next warship to fire hypersonic missiles and lasers that would be ten times more powerful than the service’s existing laser weapons, according to the most detailed outlook to date of the DDG(X) next generation warship issued by the service. The warship, the largest the Navy’s attempted in more …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA push to create single-payer health care plan passes 1st hurdle...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/california-democrats-push-to-create-single-payer-healthcare-plan-passes-1st-hurdle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In any other year, Gov. Gavin Newsom’s proposal to add an estimated 700,000 immigrants without legal status to the state’s healthcare program for low-income residents would be a monumental lift. On…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's U-Haul Revolution...</title>
      <link>https://issuesinsights.com/2022/01/11/americas-u-haul-revolution/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;issuesinsights.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s no civil war. Americans are voting with their feet, a new revolution built on freedom of movement and belief, not guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis Compounds Prevent Infection?</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2022/01/12/cannabis-compounds-stop-covid-virus-infecting-human-cells-lab-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the study, the compounds bound to spike proteins found on the virus and blocked a step the pathogen uses to infect people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Claims Ability to Control 25 TESLAs Worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://europe.autonews.com/automakers/teen-hacker-claims-ability-control-25-teslas-worldwide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;europe.autonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Colombo said a software flaw allowed him to unlock doors and windows, start the cars without keys and disable their security systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Army of Millions Who Enforce China's Zero-Covid Policy, at All Costs...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/12/the-army-of-millions-who-enforce-chinas-zero-covid-policy-at-all-costs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s “zero Covid” policy has a dedicated following: the millions of people who work diligently toward that goal, no matter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigarettes Make Comeback With Younger Crowd...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/12/that-cloud-of-smoke-is-not-a-mirage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a recent not-so-wintry Thursday in the Bushwick neighborhood of Brooklyn, when the only snowflakes seen were over text, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Miami-Bound Passenger Storms Cockpit in Honduras, Causing Flight Delay...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/12/miami-bound-passenger-storms-cockpit-in-honduras-causing-flight-delay/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the thousands of cancellations and delays of airline flights in the past month, most have been caused by Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People behave more sadistically when bored...</title>
      <link>https://digest.bps.org.uk/2022/01/12/people-behave-more-sadistically-when-theyre-bored/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;digest.bps.org.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Emma Young. Even people low in trait sadism acted more sadistically when made to feel bored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA PLAYING DOWN CASE COUNTS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/omicron-changing-news-outlets-covid-data-da9272f7c4c8a109c3bfb56bed9e9c76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For two years, coronavirus case counts and hospitalizations have been widely used barometers of the pandemic's march across the world. But the omicron wave is making a mess of the usual statistics, forcing news organizations to rethink the way they report such figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sculpture by controversial artist attacked with hammer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-arts-and-entertainment-london-sculpture-5a325e6a63754f26da5bf85db393e5d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British police on Wednesday cordoned off an area outside the BBC's Broadcasting House in central London after a man was spotted scaling the building and using a hammer to attack a statue by controversial sculptor Eric Gill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army ups bonuses to $50K as struggles to lure soldiers continues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-army-us-army-b6be4a79b014327e1105dc7a857c8f56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. Army, for the first time, is offering a maximum enlistment bonus of $50,000 to highly skilled recruits who join for six years, The Associated Press has learned, as the service struggles to lure soldiers into certain critical jobs during the continuing pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT TURN: Lula holds big lead in Brazil as voters worry about inflation, virus...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220112132115-sdt1j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
