<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Legal powerhouse BOIES suffers lawyer exodus over controversies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/boies-schiller-loses-lawyers-over-controversies-involving-theranos-harvey-weinstein.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boies Schiller Flexner has experienced a rapid exodus of several top attorneys, many of whom were bothered by purported decisions by the firm's founders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Sheen daughter claims she was 'trapped' in 'abusive' home...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/10/charlie-sheen-denise-richards-daughter-claims-she-was-trapped-in-abusive-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sami Sheen said she dropped out of high school and moved out of the “Real Housewives of Beverly Hills” star’s home in a viral TikTok, but a source told us there’s more to he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 million viewers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-entertainment-nfl-dallas-texas-61cf595dc61bc315737dcdca61a5110d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL came into kickoff weekend looking for increased audiences over last season. After one game, the league is off to a strong start with the most-watched opener in six years. Thursday night's 31-29 victory by the Tampa Bay Buccaneers over the Dallas Cowboys averaged approximately 26 million viewers on NBC, Peacock and the NFL's digital platforms according to preliminary data from Nielsen and Adobe Analytics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Imminent Threat' or Aid Worker: Did Drone Strike Kill Wrong Person?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/video/world/asia/100000007963596/us-drone-attack-kabul-investigation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Times obtained exclusive security camera footage and witness accounts to show how the military launched a drone strike that killed 10 people in Kabul on Aug. 29 without knowing who it was hitting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French ex-health minister charged over handling of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210910-french-ex-health-minister-charged-over-handling-of-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French ex-health minister charged over handling of pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fetuses found at funeral home were university collection...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-biology-idaho-pocatello-idaho-state-university-2dfe8459de3335607fd1a61a878318de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POCATELLO, Idaho (AP) — Police say the remains of roughly 50 fetuses found at a Pocatello, Idaho, funeral home were part of a biological collection that Idaho State University provided to the funeral home for cremation in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver Stone, Hollywood A-Listers Helped Pentagon After 9/11 to 'Dream Up' Future Terror Plots...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hollywood-pentagon-secret-9-11-summit-oliver-stone-dick-wolf-david-fincher/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oliver Stone, David Fincher and John Singleton were among the industry figures recruited to imagine new disaster scenarios just weeks after the terror attacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Calls Policy 'Somewhat Moderate'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fauci-calls-bidens-vaccine-mandate-somewhat-moderate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci said in an interview that he viewed President Joe Biden's vaccine mandate as "moderate."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Office exempt from requirement?</title>
      <link>https://www.govexec.com/workforce/2021/09/postal-service-takes-wait-and-see-approach-covid-19-vaccine-mandates/185277/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.govexec.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USPS may soon have to set up widespread testing for unvaccinated staff, but agency officials do not yet know how many employees have received shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozen gorillas at Zoo Atlanta have virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/coronavirus/more-than-a-dozen-gorillas-at-zoo-atlanta-diagnosed-with-covid-19/K4XFA5FS5RATPJPZ4VKOCGOVJI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zoo Atlanta is treating 13 western lowland gorillas who have tested positively for COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew 'served with papers' over bombshell sex assault allegations...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3637928/prince-andrew-served-papers-rape-accuser-lawyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAWYERS for Prince Andrew’s rape accuser tonight told The Sun they have served him – after help from a British policeman and a judge appointed by the Queen. Virginia Roberts Giuffre’s legal team’s …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer '21 edges out 'Dust Bowl' summer as hottest ever for US...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/summer-2021-edges-dust-bowl-summer-as-hottest-ever-contiguous-us/1015753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the sweltering summer of 2021 draws to a close, a new report from NOAA confirmed what you might already have been thinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Privacy experts' defending FACEBOOK funded by Zuck..</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/facebooks-smart-glasses-give-people-a-good-reason-not-t-1847644409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook put cameras in a pair of Ray-Bans. What could possibly go wrong?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wigged out: Venezuelan spymaster's life on the lam...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-venezuela-caribbean-arrests-spain-ace9c61ddb87e0608133f97cc4af3cfa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — Wigs, a fake moustache, plastic surgery and a new safe house every three months — these are just some of the tools of deception authorities in Spain believe a former Venezuelan spymaster relied on to evade capture on a U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana Use At 'Historic High' Among College Students...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/marijuana-use-college-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the National Institute on Drug Abuse (NIDA) say marijuana use hasn't been this high since the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan evacuee flights halted over 'health concerns'...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/government/2021/09/us-afghan-evacuee-flights-halted-from-two-key-bases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has halted all U.S.-bound flights of Afghan evacuees from two main bases overseas for unspecified “health safety concerns,” a move U.S. officials warn will have a severe impact on the evacuation operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC member of Congress denies setting zebras loose...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/09/my-alibi-is-solid-dc-del-norton-denies-setting-zebras-loose-in-prince-georges-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A D.C. representative known for fighting for freedom is denying any responsibility for setting a group of zebras loose in Prince George's County, Maryland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive war games with 200,000 troops spanning 1,200 miles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/16099913/putin-launches-massive-war-games-along-europes-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has launched massive war games with 200,000 troops spanning 2,000km on Europe’s doorstep in a warning to the West. The Zapad-2021 military drills include Belarus and run north …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many Americans will buck mandate -- and quit jobs?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/how-many-americans-will-buck-biden-s-vaccine-and-testing-mandate-and-quit-their-jobs/ar-AAOiPJi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Washington Post-ABC News poll showed that as many as 7 in 10 unvaccinated people say they would quit rather than get a required vaccination. But that probably oversells the resistance that lies ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE SERVED: Suit Accusing Andrew of Sexually Abusing Epstein Victim Reaches Royal...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/prince-served-lawsuit-accusing-andrew-of-sexually-abusing-jeffrey-epstein-victim-reaches-embattled-royal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew, the embattled Duke of York, has been successfully served with a lawsuit by a woman who claims he sexually assaulted her in three locations when she was 17 years old, court documents indicated on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's rep says royals back BLM movement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-television-arts-and-entertainment-queen-elizabeth-ii-death-of-george-floyd-abe2adc9e5e3910339ebe8ef0c642867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II and the royal family back the Black Lives Matter movement, one of her senior representatives said in a television interview to be broadcast Friday. Philanthropist Kenneth Olisa, the first Black Lord Lieutenant of Greater London, told Channel 4 News that he had discussed the issue with members of the royal family since George Floyd died in police custody in the United States last year, sparking global protests over racial injustice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia blames U.S. tech giants for interference in election...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910165847-5cogd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/DIPLOMACY-ELECTION (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Russia blames U.S. tech giants for interference in election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4mECX60FVJQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Blue Banisters’ The New Album Out October 22nd Pre-Order - https://Lana.lnk.to/BlueBanistersAlbumIDListen to Arcadia - https://Lana.lnk.to/ArcadiaIDFollow L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANA DEL REY WARNS IN SONG:  AMERICA NEEDS A MIRACLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.justjared.com/2021/09/08/lana-del-rey-debuts-new-song-arcadia-watch-the-music-video-read-the-lyrics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justjared.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch inside and read the lyrics!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mental Health Hinges On Diet?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mental-health-diet-and-lifestyle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BINGHAMTON, N.Y. — The old saying goes “you are what you eat,” but a recent study finds it may be more accurate to say your mood is what you eat. Researchers from Binghamton University find people can optimize their mental health through diet and lifestyle changes. “There is increasing evidence that diet plays a major…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA to DOUBLE fines on mask violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/tsa-will-double-fines-on-mask-mandate-violations-at-airports-on-flights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new range of penalties, which take effect Friday, will be $500-$1000 for first offenders and $1000-$3000 for second offenders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesale prices jump 8.3% in year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/august-wholesale-prices-rise-8point3percent-on-an-annual-basis-biggest-advance-on-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The producer price index for final demand products was expected to increase 0.6% in August, according to economists surveyed by Dow Jones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Christie calls on Republicans to stop 'pretending we won' in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/christie-calls-on-gop-to-renounce-the-conspiracy-theorists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie offered a sweeping critique of the GOP on Thursday, urging it to become "the party that's perceived to be telling the American people the truth" after months of "pretending we won" the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feud escalates...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/amazon-takes-personal-swipe-at-musk-as-satellite-feud-escalates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc.'s satellite subsidiary, Kuiper Systems LLC, filed a scathing comment with the Federal Communications Commission, accusing Elon Musk and his companies of flouting regulations with a general attitude that "rules are for other people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New deepfake tool will transform you in real-time during live streaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/deepfacelive-deepfake-live-streaming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new deepfake tool known as 'DeepFaceLive' will let users change their appearance in real-time during live video streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the Amish take over America?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/will-the-amish-take-over-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So writes David Larson in Crisis magazine, examining the rapid growth of a community which has doubled in size in just 20 years. There are now 350,000 Amish in the United States, and their demographic growth shows no real sign of letting up. The Amish are notorious for their restrictive lifestyles, with their communities essentially [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/911-20-years-world-affairs-cc497f11743fcbd48b0b3e0c3ed2da5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the ghastly rubble of ground zero's fallen towers 20 years ago, Hour Zero arrived, a chance to start anew. World affairs reordered abruptly on that morning of blue skies, black ash, fire and death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supply bottlenecks continue...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210910134804-4c8jj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ECONOMY/ (WRAPUP 1, PIX):WRAPUP 1-Supply bottlenecks keep heat on U.S. producer prices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing risk of once-in-century solar superstorm that could knock out internet...</title>
      <link>https://ktvz.com/cnn-regional/2021/09/10/growing-risk-of-once-in-a-century-solar-superstorm-that-could-knock-out-internet-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktvz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Alexandra Mae Jones Click here for updates on this story     TORONTO (CTV Network) — Imagine if one day the internet was down not just in your neighbourhood, but across the globe, knocked out by a threat from space: an enormous solar superstorm. It sounds like science fiction, but a new study says it could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia begins military games with Belarus...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-begins-major-military-drills-with-belarus-after-moves-toward-closer-integration/ar-AAOiCXU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia’s Putin plans to unify Russia’s military space with Belarus, but offered no details on what it means.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden-Xi Call Raises Key Question: Who Will Blink First?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/biden-xi-phone-call-raises-key-question-who-will-blink-first/ar-AAOisZy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of little progress in U.S.-China relations, Joe Biden’s frustration led him to initiate a call with Xi Jinping in search of a breakthrough. Now the question is who will be first to take concrete action.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapiro Says DAILY WIRE Will Defy Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/ben-shapiro-declares-the-daily-wire-will-use-every-method-and-resource-to-defy-biden-vaccine-mandate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Daily Wire, the conservative website co-founded by Ben Shapiro, announced on Friday that it will be resisting the Biden administration’s vaccine requirement for employers. The emergency rule announced by President Joe Biden on Thursday night will require all private-sector businesses with more than 100 employees to require their workers to be fully vaccinated against […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't call it relaxation. On this Maine island, vacation is for rusticating...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Don-t-call-it-relaxation-On-this-Maine-island-16448721.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's been a big year for Mount Desert Island, a craggy hump of pink Maine granite that's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin weeps over coffin of friend killed in drills...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3635235/putin-weeps-over-pals-coffin-who-died-in-arctic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISTRAUGHT Vladimir Putin has wept over the coffin of a close pal who died “trying to save a man’s life in an Arctic drill”. A grief-stricken Putin appeared devastated as he said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's best superyachts revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-9972911/The-worlds-best-superyachts-2021-revealed-including-British-built-floating-work-art.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fourteen trophies were handed out to 12 vessels at Boat International's World Superyacht Awards, with the British-built 33.9m (111ft) Geist taking home the coveted award for Sailing Yacht of the Year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In China elite circles, thousand-dollar soups, detention roulette...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/New-book-details-on-China-s-elite-circles-16448244.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese businessman is offering a rare peek into the luxe lifestyles of former premier...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans turn pessimistic amid concerns over economy, virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/10/politics/americans-biden-economy-coronavirus/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tentatively positive public outlook that marked the first months of the Biden administration has faded, according to a new CNN poll conducted by SSRS. The survey, released Friday, finds a rising share of Americans who say things in the US are going badly and that the economy is in poor shape, with increased worries about the coronavirus, the economy and crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food getting more and more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/10/climate-change-supply-chain-and-labor-issues-are-making-food-pricier.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Climate change, labor costs, transportation issues, Covid catalysts and other supply chain disruptions are wreaking havoc on the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 MILLION AMERICANS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-executive-branch-18fb12993f05be13bf760946a6fb89be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In his most forceful pandemic actions and words, President Joe Biden on Thursday ordered sweeping new federal vaccine requirements for as many as 100 million Americans — private-sector employees as well as health care workers and federal contractors — in an all-out effort to curb the surging COVID-19 delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creator says mass boosters may be unnecessary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-immunizations-65f8508c653fd6be7c1a8e7537e47c13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Booster shots to extend the protection of COVID-19 vaccines may be unnecessary for many people, a leading scientist behind the AstraZeneca vaccine said on Friday. Oxford University Professor Sarah Gilbert told The Telegraph newspaper that immunity from the vaccine was holding up well — even against the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury brands flock to suburbs, vacation hot spots where rich riding out pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Luxury-brands-flock-to-suburbs-and-vacation-hot-16448294.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget Fifth Avenue and Rodeo Drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Capitol rioter says ankle monitor beeps too loudly. He wants judge to let him remove it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-alleged-capitol-rioter-says-his-ankle-monitor-beeps-too-loudly-he-wants-a-judge-to-let-him-remove-it/ar-AAOigwO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabriel Garcia, who's accused of inciting a mob of rioters to charge Capitol police on Jan. 6, wants a judge to let him remove his GPS ankle monitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Strategists Say Storm Brewing in Stock Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-10/deutsche-team-sees-risk-of-hard-equity-valuation-correction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strategists from almost all the top Wall Street banks have come out this week with a nervous message about the U.S. stock market.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
