<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Laguna Beach mansion breaks record sale price at $70 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2021/11/29/laguna-beach-mansion-breaks-oc-record-sale-price-at-70-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 18,000-square-foot residence last sold for $32.7 million in 2018.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDEX driver dumped packages 6 times into Alabama ravine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/30/us/alabama-fedex-packages/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities investigating the discovery of hundreds of FedEx packages in an Alabama ravine have questioned the driver they think is responsible -- and believe the driver dumped packages there at least six times, a sheriff said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Finds Superbug-Killing Potential in Human Proteins...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/an-ai-finds-superbug-killing-potential-in-human-proteins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team scoured the human proteome for antimicrobial molecules and found thousands, plus a surprise about how animals evolved to fight infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why China Is Sticking to Its Tough Zero-COVID Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vvnw/china-covid-zero-omicron-new-variant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say China would face a “disaster” if it adopted the U.S. approach of coexistence with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRISTIE BOMBS: Book Sells Only 2,289 Copies...</title>
      <link>https://thetriad.thebulwark.com/p/phony-phoni-phone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thetriad.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chris Christie fails. Again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland teachers union proposes self-taught Fridays for high schoolers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/portland-teachers-union-proposes-self-taught-fridays-for-high-schoolers-says-educators-need-more-planning-time/ar-AARj3bL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy medical team heading to New Mexico to help...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-navy/2021/11/30/navy-medical-team-heading-to-new-mexico-to-help-with-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The military team is being deployed at the request of the Federal Emergency Management Agency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook County Surpasses 1,000 Homicides For First Time Since '94...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/30/cook-county-1000-homicides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago alone has had 777 homicides so far this year, according to the medical examiner's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorsey's Exit Could Worsen Tech Censorship...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/11/29/jack-dorsey-twitter-resignation-parag-agrawal-censorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Dorsey has resigned as CEO of Twitter, having served in various leadership roles at the company since its inception in 2007. "I've decided to leave</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 injured in shooting at Michigan high school... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/multiple-people-injured-shooting-oxford-high-school-michigan-officials-rcna7128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people were injured in a shooting Tuesday at Oxford High School in suburban Detroit, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds Probing Sidney Powell...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/prosecutors-demanded-records-of-sidney-powell-s-fundraising-groups-as-part-of-criminal-probe/ar-AARjdpU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quest begins to drill Antarctica's oldest ice...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-59475410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A near-3km-long core of ice should contain a record of climate change going back 1.5 million years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo's Wife Sentenced to 3 Years in Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/y3vv5w/el-chapos-wife-emma-coronel-aispuro-prison-sentence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emma Coronel Aispuro, El Chapo’s current wife, was just sentenced to three years in a U.S. prison—more than a decade less than she faced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First signs that jab DOES protect against...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/covid-1st-data-about-vaccine-efficacy-against-omicron-expected-tuesday-687392</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC opening first city-run shooting galleries for drug users...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/30/de-blasio-opening-supervised-injection-sites-for-drug-users-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mayor tried to push the controversial proposal to open a total of four sites before, but was blocked by former Gov. Cuomo and former President Trump who both opposed the plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA accidentally disclosed more than 2,000 flight records associated with Epstein's private jets...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/faa-accidentally-disclosed-more-2-180500812.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domestic flight records associated with Jeffrey Epstein's private jets, provided by the FAA, reveal more than 700 previously unknown flights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY ROE MAY GO!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/11/will-the-supreme-court-overrule-roe-and-casey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 1973, the Court invented a right to abortion that makes the U.S. an extreme outlier in the world. Now, it has a chance to undo that grievous wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC Cramer Demands Biden Impose Nationwide Mandate in Epic Rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/cnbcs-jim-cramer-demands-biden-impose-nationwide-vaccine-mandate-in-epic-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Cramer demanded that President Joe Biden impose a nationwide vaccine mandate on every American in an impassioned rant at the end of his show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man with TESLA face tattoo busted on felony DUI charge...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/dui/tesla-tattoo-motorist-312097</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A motorist who has a Tesla logo tattooed on his face was driving a 1992 minivan when he was arrested Friday on a felony DUI count and multiple vehicular charges, according to Illinois police. Jordan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don Insists 'Everybody Wants Me on TV' Despite 'Zero Takers' for His Election Fraud Debate Challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-insists-everbody-wants-me-on-television-despite-zero-takers-for-his-election-fraud-debate-challenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump lamented the fact that he has had "zero takers" for his challenge to debate ANYONE over his baseless election fraud claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is not going to be good': MODERNA CEO on omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-not-going-to-be-good-moderna-ceo-on-what-scientists-are-telling-him-about-the-omicron-coronavirus-variant-11638266621</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CEO of Moderna told the Financial Times there's no world where current vaccines are as effective as against the delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline stocks suffer broad selloff as fear spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/airline-stocks-suffer-broad-selloff-as-fear-of-omicron-variants-impact-on-travel-spreads-2021-11-30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of airline companies took a broad beating Tuesday, as part of a selloff in the broader stock market, as fears spread that the omicron variant of COVID...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER STOCK CONTINUES PLUNGE; -20% YTD...</title>
      <link>https://www.google.com/finance/quote/TWTR:NYSE?sa=X&amp;ved=2ahUKEwjQxf64v8D0AhUZJzQIHWPDC34Q3ecFegQIDxAU&amp;window=YTD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the latest Twitter Inc (TWTR) real-time quote, historical performance, charts, and other financial information to help you make more informed trading and investment decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Tunnel to hell' drilled under active volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/boffs-drilling-tunnel-hell-build-25580123</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We may finally be able to journey to the centre of the Earth thanks to an ambitious new project which hopes to drill a giant tunnel deep into the centre of a volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK WARNS OF SPACEX BANKRUPTCY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/elon-musk-to-spacex-starships-raptor-engine-crisis-risks-bankruptcy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk is angry with the lack of progress SpaceX has made in developing the Raptor engines that power its Starship rocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTAGION</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks tumbled on Tuesday, reversing Monday's rebound on Wall Street, as investors reassessed risks associated with the new omicron Covid variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decade-old tweet causes viral headache for new boss...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/twitter-ceo-parag-agrawal-old-daily-show-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He's only been CEO for just a few hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don called aides hours before Capitol riot to discuss how to stop Biden victory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/30/donald-trump-called-top-aides-capitol-riot-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources tell Guardian Trump pressed lieutenants at Willard hotel in Washington about ways to delay certification of election result</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could fate really deliver Brady-Belichick encore at Super Bowl?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/could-fate-really-deliver-a-brady-belichick-encore-at-the-super-bowl/ar-AARiTtO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON  Accused of Under-Reporting Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/amazon-accused-of-under-reporting-covid-cases-contracted-at-work/ar-AARiKzx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein pilot resumes testimony at Maxwell trial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-entertainment-jeffrey-epstein-0aada37f104368c3dbbe127f1525f322</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A longtime pilot for the late financier Jeffrey Epstein resumed his testimony at Ghislaine Maxwell's sex trafficking trial Tuesday, saying that the British socialite charged with helping the financier find teenage girls to sexually abuse was “Number 2” in the hierarchy of Epstein's operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German doctor administered homemade vaccine to 20K people...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/europe/583542-german-doctor-administered-his-own-homemade-vaccine-to-20k-people</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winfried Stöcker, a millionaire doctor from Germany, is facing criminal charges after vaccinating an estimated 20,000 people with a COVID-19 vaccine that he concocted, according to a report from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hit strip club, bought LAMBORGHINI with coronavirus aid. Received 9 years in prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-texas-man-hit-the-strip-club-and-bought-a-lamborghini-with-coronavirus-aid-he-received-9-years-in-prison/ar-AARixeQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Troubled' Mennonite boys were trafficked, forced into physical labor, and abused at farm, suit says...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pennsylvania/mennonite-church-liberty-ridge-farm-abuse-20211130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two former residents claim the Eastern Pennsylvania Mennonite Church and Liberty Ridge Farm violated federal laws against human trafficking, racketeering, and forced labor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mom told son to back out of frat boxing match. He died days after 'Fight Night'...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-mom-told-her-son-to-back-out-of-a-16662189.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcer revved up the crowd with a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices peak?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/30/home-price-hikes-slow-down-according-to-sp-case-shiller.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home prices are still higher than a year ago, but the gains are now decelerating for the first time since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confessions of prolific serial killer have LA detectives chasing ghosts...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/confessions-prolific-serial-killer-left-130015414.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Little confessed to killing 93 women across the U.S. Nearly a third of those admissions are uncorroborated, and most of those are in L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our Money Has No Value': Frustration Rises in Turkey at Lira Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/our-money-has-no-value-frustration-rises-in-turkey-at-lira-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL — Lines outside bread stores and gas stations; farmers defaulting on loans; impromptu street demonstrations. The signs of economic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Pandemic Changed Where Californians Live...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/how-covid-19-has-changed-where-californians-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the earliest days of the pandemic, we’ve been hearing about Californians abandoning their usual way of life for greener,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dueling mass rallies planned...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/29/dueling-mass-rallies-planned-supreme-court-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect plenty of opinions Wednesday at the Supreme Court when crowds of demonstrators converge for rallies timed to oral arguments on a Mississippi abortion law that could upend Roe v. Wade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right figure Zemmour announces presidential run to 'save' France...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211130114609-3zt61</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANCE-ELECTION/ZEMMOUR (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Far-right figure Zemmour announces presidential run to 'save' France</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fattest Profits Since 1950 Debunk Inflation Story Spun by CEOs...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/fattest-profits-since-1950-debunk-120000558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the second year of a pandemic that began by wiping out 20 million jobs, American workers are doing surprisingly well. It’s just that American business is doing even better. Most Read from BloombergChina Cash Flowed Through Congo Bank to Former President’s Cronies‘Pension Poachers’ Are Targeting America’s Elderly VeteransReliving the New York Subway Map DebateIn the past two quarters, U.S. corporations outside of the finance industry posted their fattest margins since 1950 -- on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In shadow of TX gas drilling sites, health fears escalate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-environment-and-nature-texas-asthma-ae7e3b327293247642c99d8126c8f12d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ARLINGTON, Texas (AP) — At a playground outside a North Texas day care center, giggling preschoolers chase each other into a playhouse. Toddlers scoot by on tricycles. A boy cries as a teacher helps him negotiate over a toy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger tries to wave down plane at LAX; Cops tackle on tarmac...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4172026/woman-apprehended-at-lax-after-running-on-tarmac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLICE have apprehended a woman who allegedly tried to run out on the tarmac at Los Angeles International Airport. The woman apparently tried to wave at a plane, according to an eyewitness. A video…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Good As Original?</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/west-side-story-2021-movie-reviews-preview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The early reactions to West Side Story are in!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Teens Getting Six Figures to Quit High School for Basketball...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/the-teenagers-getting-six-figures-to-quit-high-school-for-basketball/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jalen Lewis liked high school, and why not? At 6-foot-9, with a bird’s nest of hair on top, he was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Injection Sites for Drug Users to Open in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/supervised-injection-sites-for-drug-users-to-open-in-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an attempt to curb a surge in overdose deaths caused by increasingly potent street drugs, New York City will</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In China, TESLA Is Catfish, and Turns Auto Companies Into Sharks...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/30/in-china-tesla-is-a-catfish-and-turns-auto-companies-into-sharks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forty-two years ago, Liu Siong Song built machines to help factories make cheap toys and watches. Then he made them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell sex abuse trial to resume with Epstein pilot's testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/maxwell-sex-abuse-trial-resume-with-epstein-pilots-testimony-2021-11-30/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislaine Maxwell's criminal sex abuse trial was set to enter its second day on Tuesday, with prosecutors expected to question a longtime pilot of the deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WEST SIDE STORY' First Reactions: 'Top-Tier Spielberg,' Zegler Star Shines Bright...</title>
      <link>https://www.indiewire.com/2021/11/west-side-story-first-reactions-steven-spielberg-musical-1234682024/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indiewire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Spielberg’s musical has finally screened, and ecstatic first reactions are pouring in: “Everyone is at the top of their game.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Spectacular'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/news/west-side-story-first-reactions-praise-steven-spielberg-1235121757/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first reactions to 20th Century Studios’ “West Side Story” are beginning to pour in following the film’s premiere in New York City on Monday evening. Those who attended …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Jan. 6 panel set for faceoff... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/583492-trump-jan-6-panel-are-set-for-tuesday-faceoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Trump and the Jan. 6 select committee will face off in court on Tuesday over whether he can use executive privilege claims to block lawmakers from obtaining extensive internal White House records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boebert, Omar fight leaves Republicans scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/583500-boebert-and-omar-fight-leaves-gop-scrambling</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House is grappling with yet another fight between a far-right Republican and a member of the progressive “squad” — this time Reps. Lauren Boebert (R-Colo.) and Ilhan Omar (D-Minn.).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow war in space heating up fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/11/30/space-race-china-david-thompson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space Force general: China and Russia are attacking U.S. space assets “every day.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex shops offer Brazil Evangelicals taste of heaven...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211130-sex-shops-offer-brazil-evangelicals-a-taste-of-heaven</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes, she disguises her merchandise as medication. Others, as a bakery delivery. Whatever the packaging, Andrea dos Anjos knows discretion is key when Brazil's emerging Evangelical sex shops sen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right pundit Zemmour launches bid for French presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20211130-far-right-pundit-eric-zemmour-announces-2022-bid-for-french-presidency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French far-right commentator Eric Zemmour on Tuesday announced he will be running in the 2022 presidential election, joining a crowded field of candidates aiming to unseat President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTISTS BUILD 'LIVING' ROBOTS THAT REPRODUCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10254773/Scientists-build-living-robots-reproduce.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny 'living machines' aren't traditional robots, nor a species of animal, but living, programmable organisms. They were created by Tufts University and University of Vermont scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Manson's house raided by LA police...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/29/marilyn-manson-house-raided-los-angeles-county-sheriff-sexual-assault-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marilyn Manson's home was raided by L.A. County Sheriff's detectives as part of a sexual assault investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  CHRIS MUST EXIT...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/11/fire-chris-cuomo/620835/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New revelations show the CNN anchor betrayed his obligation to his viewers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor: 'Secret plan' for hate crime on himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jussie-smollett-had-a-secret-plan-for-hate-crime-on-himself-prosecutor-says-as-trial-begins/ar-AARhb8X?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden faces uncertain threat as evolving pandemic tests nation's patience...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/biden-faces-uncertain-threat-with-omicron-variant-as-evolving-pandemic-tests-nation-s-patience/ar-AARgkEC?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayors scramble for face time with Buttigieg with billions of infrastructure dollars at stake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/article256078832.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The competition started months before the infrastructure bill even passed, but now it’s kicked into high gear, with city leaders crafting ambitious plans in hopes of securing a windfall of federal funds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan hits new record for hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hastingstribune.com/ap/agriculture/michigan-hits-new-record-for-adult-covid-19-hospitalizations-80-of-beds-full/article_87a6731a-09f6-59f5-8370-af5589ad681b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hastingstribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan reached a new record of adults hospitalized with COVID-19 on Monday with 4,181 hospitalized with confirmed cases of the virus, the most since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He sued SeaWorld to liberate the whales. Then he started getting postcards from them...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/column-one-sued-seaworld-liberate-130034325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten years after a legal activist filed a lawsuit for orcas held in captivity, he began receiving postcards from them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZOOM EARTH</title>
      <link>https://zoom.earth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;zoom.earth&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;View LIVE satellite images, rain radar, and animated wind speed maps. Track the latest hurricanes, wildfires and weather in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY ROE MAY GO!</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/05/why-its-unlikely-democrats-would-pack-the-supreme-court-even-if-roe-were-overturned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Where does it stop? Democrats add three seats; Republicans add four more. Pretty soon you have a 100-person unelected third-chamber of the legislature.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETS ON CRYPTO FUTURE</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/fintech/jack-dorsey-bitcoin-crypto-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The departure of @jack from Twitter may have seemed sudden, but it reflects his obsession with bitcoin, an interest that’s been building for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorne Michaels, 77,  still lives for Saturday night...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/lorne-michaels-still-lives-for-saturday-night/ar-AARgSAU?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New opioids, more powerful than fentanyl, discovered in DC amid deadly wave of overdoses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-opioids-more-powerful-than-fentanyl-are-discovered-in-dc-amid-deadly-wave-of-overdoses/ar-AARgxFB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Fails to Halt Art Basel Miami as People Crave Normalcy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/other/omicron-fails-to-halt-art-basel-miami-as-people-crave-normalcy/ar-AARgxAx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutations alarm scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/omicron-mutations-alarm-scientists-but-new-variant-first-must-prove-it-can-outcompete-delta/ar-AARhgqb?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLIONAIRE OUT AT  TROUBLED SOCIAL</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4167154/jack-dorsey-step-down-twitter-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACK Dorsey announced on Monday that he will step down as Twitter’s CEO today. Parag Agrawal, the current Chief Technology Officer at Twitter, is set to replace the tech giant, who faced a st…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COMPANY BEFORE EGO'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/jack-dorsey-stepping-down-as-twitter-ceo-cnbc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey is resigning from the platform he co-founded, CNBC reported Monday. Dorsey confirmed his resignation in a tweet. Sources told CNBC’s David Faber that Dorsey, a Twitter founder who now serves as its chief executive, is expected to announce he will be stepping down “in the near term.” Faber said he did not […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military readying 'Plan B' if Iran nuke talks fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iran-news/israeli-military-readying-for-plan-b-if-iran-nuclear-talks-fail-687220</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER JACK STEPS DOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-is-expected-to-step-down-sources-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Dorsey was serving as both the CEO of Twitter and Square, his digital payments company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine sex trafficking trial begins...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ghislaine-maxwell-nyc-trial-starts-17f7c28591c1f32c802f3b7bc413bfe0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Ghislaine Maxwell and Jeffrey Epstein were “partners in crime” in the sexual abuse of teenage girls, a prosecutor said Monday, while Maxwell’s lawyers said she was being made a scapegoat for a man’s bad behavior as the British socialite’s sex trafficking trial got underway in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Six-Foot Rule' Doesn't Protect...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/6-foot-rule-doesnt-protect-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The policy could have been set anywhere between three to 10 feet, depending on the risk tolerance of the local public health authority putting out the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another House retirement spells even more trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/29/politics/suozzi-retirement-2022-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Monday, New York Democratic Rep. Tom Suozzi announced he plans to leave his 3rd District seat behind to run for governor in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METS Agree To Record $130M Contract Over 3 Years With Aging Ace...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/max-scherzer-mets-agree-to-record-contract-as-right-hander-signs-three-year-130-million-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mets appear to be adding Scherzer to a rotation that already includes Jacob deGrom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bradley Cooper reveals he 'got held up at KNIFEPOINT' in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4170028/bradley-cooper-held-up-knifepoint-nyc-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRADLEY Cooper revealed he was “held up at knifepoint” in New York City while on his way to pick up his daughter Lea, 4, from school. While detailing the traumatic experience, the 46-year-old actor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most infectious yet?</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/11/29/1059861661/the-omicron-variant-may-be-the-most-infectious-one-yet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in South Africa say preliminary data suggests the omicron coronavirus variant is already widespread across southern Africa — and this happened in a very short period of time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Done as Full-Time Golfer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/29/tiger-woods-reveals-future-golf-plans-after-scary-car-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tiger Woods is done as a full-time golfer, but says he is channeling Ben Hogan in his eventual return to the links.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER TALKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.golfdigest.com/story/tiger-woods-exclusive-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.golfdigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with Golf Digest, Tiger Woods opens up about a painful year, a possible return to golf, and son Charlie's progress as a player.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWELL:  Complicates inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/29/fed-chair-powell-says-omicron-variant-poses-risk-to-economy-complicates-inflation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed Chair Jerome Powell believes that the omicron variant of Covid-19 and a recent rise in coronavirus cases pose a threat to the U.S. economy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
