<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Charges direct assault on press freedom, experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/apr/12/julian-assange-charges-press-freedom-journalism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parts of the indictment go head-to-head with basic journalistic activities protected by the first amendment, academics say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What became of his cat?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/julian-assange-cat-embassy-what-happened-wikileaks-ecuador-a8866611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Manhattan's Newest Hangout for Sex-Positive Millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/inside-manhattans-newest-hangout-sex-positive-millennials-1200120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private club NSFW — or New Society for Wellness — caters to entertainment, media and fashion insiders: "There is literal, not figurative, star f—ing here."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY STOCK SOARS IN STREAMING WAR</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/12/disney-shares-rocket-higher-after-unveiling-streaming-cheaper-than-netflix.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney shares jumped more than 10% Friday after the company announced its Disney+ video streaming service would be $6.99 a month, two dollars a month cheaper than Netflix.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest designed to make sure didn't press mysterious panic button...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/assange-arrest-ecuador-prevent-alleged-panic-button-2019-4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks' founder, Julian Assange, was dramatically arrested and dragged out of the Ecuadorean Embassy in London on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S. Korean babies born Dec. 31 become 2-year-olds next day...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/082ab3d8f16d4360bf9ade45c41925f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAEJEON, South Korea (AP) — Just two hours after Lee Dong Kil's daughter was born on New Year's Eve, the clock struck midnight, 2019 was ushered in, and the infant became 2-years-old. She wasn't...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Set For Ratings Record With 'GAME OF THRONES'?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/04/game-of-thrones-season-8-premiere-ratings-hbo-prediction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Season 8 premiere of ‘Game of Thrones’ is one of the most highly anticipated episodes in TV history. Could it pull in the show’s biggest numbers yet?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency panel meets as Ebola outbreak gathers pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/apr/12/emergency-panel-meets-as-congo-ebola-outbreak-gathers-pace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Faltering national response to epidemic prompts experts to consider official announcement of public health crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans already ran campaign blasting Dems as socialists. It didn't work...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/04/12/republicans-socialists-democrats-campaign-2020-1271706</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swing-state experiment in last year's midterms offer a cautionary tale for the GOP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Was 'Diehard Conservative'?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/04/12/elizabeth-warren-profile-young-republican-2020-president-226613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren doesn’t like to talk about it, but for years she was a registered Republican. Why she left the GOP—and what it means for her campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete hottest thing in politics. Can it last?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-mayor-pete-buttegieg-democrats-president-2020-20190412-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Bend mayor hopes to become the youngest president, the first openly gay one, and the first to go straight from City Hall to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rome opens door to underworld of Nero's ruined palace...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fifty-communal-toilets-where-slaves-114152784.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The remains of a vast palace built by the Emperor Nero, including a 50-seat latrine where slaves and workers would chat while they attended to their needs, opens to the public for the first time today.   The Domus Transitoria was a huge palace on the Palatine Hill, in the heart of ancient Rome, which</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts threaten death blow to Venezuela's industrial survivors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-politics-industries/blackouts-threaten-death-blow-to-venezuelas-industrial-survivors-idUSKCN1RO196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest power outage started another tough week for factory owner Antonello L...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indonesian island rocked by 6.8 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-indonesia-earthquake-sulawesi-hit-14291387</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States Geological Survey said the quake struck 174 miles south of the province of Gorontalo, just months after more than 2,000 died in a 7.5 magnitude earthquake and tsunami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGETOWN students vote to pay reparations to descendants of slaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/11/us/georgetown-students-slavery-reparations-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgetown University might not be here today if the Maryland Society of Jesuits who oversaw the school hadn't sold 272 slaves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They're in our heads': TV series tackles big-tech nightmare...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/theyre-heads-tv-series-tackles-big-tech-nightmare-113616810.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Channing Powell, the creator of the hit horror television series "The Walking Dead", is not someone who is easily spooked. The Amazon show is set in the near future when we can share emotions, thoughts and what we see with our eyes on a social network embedded in our brains. If that sounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farage Plans Revolution as Brexit Party Targets EU Election...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/farage-plans-revolution-brexit-party-085117444.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farage, the former leader of the U.K. Independence Party, is spearheading a new vehicle -- the Brexit Party -- which launches its contest for next month’s European Parliament elections on Friday. Addressing an event in the pro-Brexit city of Coventry, England, Farage warned opponents his approach was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Sued Over Abuse of Search Power, Opening Path for More Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/suit-could-raise-googles-liabilities-in-price-comparison-case-11555056397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German price-comparison service has become the first major company to sue Google following a 2017 European antitrust decision to fine the U.S. firm for abusing its dominant position in the search-engine market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Key To Happiness? Smiling...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/key-to-happiness-smiling-more-frequently/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're having a rough day, one way to help turn that frown upside down may be as simple as doing just that. A new study reveals that smiling actually makes people feel happier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Millionaire Bernie Sanders Prepares to Reveal Income...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/millionaire-bernie-sanders-prepares-reveal-080000366.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I wrote a best-selling book,” Sanders told the New York Times this week. The senator refused to release his full tax returns when he vied for the Democratic presidential nomination in 2016. When he ran against Hillary Clinton in 2016, Sanders released a lone return, from the 2014 tax year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT work with Chinese military university raises eyebrows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/microsofts-chinese-military-university-raises-eyebrows-071632855.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft has been collaborating with researchers linked to a Chinese military-backed university on artificial intelligence, elevating concerns that US firms are contributing to China's high-tech surveillance and censorship apparatus. Over the past year, researchers at Microsoft Research Asia in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude oil touted as health cure...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/crude-oil-touted-health-cure-azerbaijan-034915549.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Immersed up to her neck in a dark viscous liquid, Sulfiya smiles in delight, confident that the fetid substance will cure her painful condition. Sulfiya, a Russian woman in her 60s, has travelled to Azerbaijan's north-western city of Naftalan in the hope that crude oil baths at a local sanatorium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banned at home, Mexican narco anthem group plays Coachella...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/banned-home-mexican-narco-anthem-group-plays-coachella-052922405.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite their name, Los Tucanes de Tijuana -- one of Mexico's most famous narco-ballad bands -- cannot perform in Tijuana. The northern border city banned them in 2008 over their glorification of drug traffickers. Los Tucanes (The Toucans) are among the best-known bands of Mexico's norteno,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy Stairs 'Jesus climbed before crucifixion' unveiled in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/holy-stairs-believed-climbed-jesus-prior-crucifixion-unveiled/story?id=62331625</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get breaking national and world news, broadcast video coverage, and exclusive interviews. Find the top news online at ABC news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitch McConnell tells 2020 Republicans to run 'independent' of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/apr/11/mitch-mcconnell-tells-2020-republicans-run-indepen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Majority Leader Mitch McConnell said Republican senators running for re-election next year should not couple their messaging to President Trump but rather run “independent” campaigns built around how they’ve helped their states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planet of the Apes fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/771498/planet-of-the-apes-monkeys-human-brain-genes-implanted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Regulators Launch Antitrust Investigation Into APPLE's App Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/04/11/tech/apple-antitrust-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has another antitrust problem in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite hospitals plunge into unproven stem cell treatments...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/elite-hospitals-plunge-into-unproven-stem-cell-treatments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics are concerned about the explosion in controversial stem cell procedures offered by clinics — and, increasingly, respected hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Struggles To Keep Making Movies Amidst Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/woody-allen-turmoil-tries-to-keep-making-movies-1202594144/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some years ago I helped architect a film deal for a Woody Allen movie (Play It Again Sam) and Woody resented that he was not specified as director. A week later, when I encountered him, he looked r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assange fears being beaten up in US prison, called Trump crowd 'clowns'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/assange-fears-beaten-us-prison-called-trump-crowd/story?id=62332466</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange has been dreading the prospect of American prison, one of his regular visitors told ABC News' The Investigation podcast today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems blame Trump for worsening border crisis...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411223957-45pvx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/DEMOCRATS:U.S. House Democrats blame Trump for worsening border crisis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator eyes social media bill for 'hate' speech...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411221126-8277f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TECH/WARNER (PIX, TV):U.S. Senator Warner eyes social media bills for hate speech, data portability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-pope says sexual revolution led to abuse crisis...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190411184922-bh00c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-ABUSE/BENEDICT (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Ex-pope says sexual revolution led to abuse crisis, sparking debate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Chinese youth sent to villages in 'Cultural Revolution' echo...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/apr/12/millions-of-chinese-youth-volunteers-to-be-sent-to-villages-in-echo-of-mao-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communist Youth League students to ‘spread civilisation’ in countryside and ‘promote technology’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former city employee guilty of using public money for voodoo hex on ex...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-hra-employee-guilty-voodoo-hex-fraud-theft-20190411-77jf7c443jbv5fow5jrksxxpii-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Human Resources Agency employee for the city pleaded guilty on Thursday to using public money to put a voodoo hex on an ex-boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More penmanship, less keyboard: Texas cursive curriculum...</title>
      <link>https://abc11.com/education/texas-schools-bringing-cursive-back-to-classrooms/5240180/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the cursive debate continues around the country, Texas will introduce the penmanship instruction in the second grade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cord-Cutter Savings Shrink as Streaming TV Services Raise Prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/cord-cutters-savings-shrink-as-online-tv-services-raise-prices-11555001280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online television bundles are getting bigger and prices keep rising, edging closer to the cable bundles they were designed to replace and muddling the economic equation that has prompted millions of Americans to cut the cord.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to host screening of pro-life film 'GOSNELL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lifesitenews.com/news/trump-to-host-white-house-screening-of-gosnell-film-that-exposed-mass-murdering-abortionist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifesitenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Gosnell' tells the true story of Philadelphia abortionist Dr. Kermit Gosnell’s arrest, trial, and conviction for the first-degree murder of three born-alive babies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia ethics chief investigating Stacey Abrams campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.13wmaz.com/article/news/politics/stacey-abrams-campaign-under-investigation-by-new-georgia-ethics-head/93-9d765c89-8e4e-4558-a4f9-c43ecba74267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.13wmaz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New appointee says complaints against Kemp are unfounded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark NASA Twins Study Reveals Space Travel Effects on Humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/nasa-twins-study-kelly-astronauts-results.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's what happens on long-duration space missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSTED: Fugitive taunts cops on 'most wanted' post, reveals location arguing with commenters...</title>
      <link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/crime-courts/2019/04/11/fugitive-Facebook-taunts-greene-county-waynesburg-chloe-jones-police/stories/201904110104</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wanted Pennsylvania woman who taunted a sheriff's department online by asking if they</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE Edits Piece Suggesting Servers 'Tamper' With Trump Admin Food...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/boston-globe-edits-op-ed-that-suggested-servers-tamper-with-food-of-trump-officials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGE: Hid $4M Settlement from 'Mentally Ill Paraplegic' Client...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-avenatti-indicted-fraud-theft-charges-20190411-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal grand jury has indicted Michael Avenatti on charges of fraud, perjury, tax dodging and embezzlement from clients in a sweeping expansion of the criminal case against the Los Angeles lawyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TULSI: Arrest threatens journalists -- 'Be quiet, behave, toe line'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/438542-gabbard-assange-arrest-is-a-threat-to-journalists</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic presidential hopeful Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avenatti Faces Up to 335 Years in Prison!</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/michael-avenatti-is-going-to-be-hit-with-more-federal-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria mulls online registration law to deprive anonymity...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.at/20190410/austria-mulls-user-registration-for-online-platforms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.at&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria said Wednesday it was considering a law to make it mandatory for big internet platforms to register their users and deprive those behind hate posts of anonymity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler miraculously survives SIX-STORY plunge as car breaks fall...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/child-falls-from-balcony-at-redmond-complex/938880441</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 20-month-old boy who fell six stories from a window on the top floor of a Redmond apartment complex was in serious but stable condition Wednesday night, after landing on the roof of a parked car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CRABBY' MCAULIFFE FUELS SPECULATON...</title>
      <link>https://wtkr.com/2019/04/11/mcauliffe-fuels-speculation-with-twitter-post/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtkr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAuliffe post bizarre tweet, setting off speculation about 2020 run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=stTMt1tLT4g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange has been evicted from the Ecuadorian Embassy in London where he has spent the last six years. Ecuador's president has announ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: DARK MOMENT FOR FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/edward-snowden-assanges-arrest-a-dark-moment-for-freedom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former National Security Agency contractor Edward Snowden on Thursday lamented Julian Assange's arrest by authorities outside the Ecuadorian embassy in London, calling the event "a dark moment" for freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGGED OUT OF EMBASSY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8839586/julian-assange-arrested-by-cops-and-removed-from-ecuadorian-embassy-in-london/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“NARCISSIST” Julian Assange faces a year in British jail after his dramatic arrest at the Ecuadorian Embassy ended seven years in hiding today. The bearded WikiLeaks founder has spent 2…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW ECUADOR LOST PATIENCE...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/apr/11/how-ecuador-lost-patience-with-houseguest-julian-assange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WikiLeaks founder’s visit became uncomfortable for both him and his hosts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAWYER:  RISKS TORTURE IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ecuador-assange-lawyer-spain/assange-may-risk-torture-in-united-states-his-lawyer-says-idUSKCN1RN2CJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wikileaks founder Julian Assange may risk torture if he is extradited to the Uni...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Charges could unsettle liberals, conservatives -- and Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/16/julian-assange-charges-wikileaks-997122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some liberals have defended Assange as a journalist, conservatives celebrated him in 2016 and Trump once declared his 'love' for WikiLeaks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER, Losing $1.8 Billion a Year, Reveals I.P.O. Filing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/11/technology/uber-ipo-filing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s largest ride-hailing service unveiled its prospectus for what is likely to be the biggest initial public offering for years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'How about paying taxes?' WALMART response to AMAZON wage challenge...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/how-about-paying-your-taxes-walmart-responds-amazon-s-challenge-n993461</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Amazon's Jeff Bezos called on retailers to match his company's employee benefits, Walmart fired back: "How about paying your taxes?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD RAGES...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/glenn-greenwald-rages-against-assange-arrest-battles-journos-its-the-criminalization-of-journalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ INDICTMENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.justice.gov/usao-edva/pr/wikileaks-founder-charged-computer-hacking-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.justice.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian P. Assange, 47, the founder of WikiLeaks, was arrested today in the United Kingdom pursuant to the U.S./UK Extradition Treaty, in connection with a federal charge of conspiracy to commit computer intrusion for agreeing to break a password to a classified U.S. government computer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRANSPARENCY ICON OR ENEMY OF STATE?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190411-julian-assange-transparency-icon-or-enemy-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange: Transparency icon or enemy of the state?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DECADE OF STUNNING LEAKS OF SECRETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190411-julian-assange-decade-stunning-leaks-us-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange: a decade of stunning leaks of US secrets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIFREAKS: ASSANGE ARRESTED IN LONDON</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6911187/Wikileaks-founder-Julian-Assange-arrested-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange has been arrested by British police today following an extradition request by the US after Ecuador dramatically withdrew his political asylum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA CHARGES WITH COMPUTER HACKING...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/11/us-charges-wikileaks-co-founder-julian-assange-with-conspiracy-to-commit-computer-hacking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. wants to extradite Assange, who was arrested at the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, where he had been living for nearly seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron struggling to recruit NBA stars for 'SPACE JAM 2'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/giannis-antetokounmpo-declines-invitation-to-star-in-space-jam-2-alongside-lebron-james/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This comes on the heels of a report suggesting LeBron is struggling to recruit costars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEVEN YEARS IN HIDING...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f9878e358d1a4cde9685815b0512909d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British police on Thursday hauled a bearded and shouting Julian Assange from the Ecuadorian Embassy where he was holed up for nearly seven years, and the U.S. charged the WikiLeaks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAM ANDERSON: UK 'AMERICA'S BITCH'...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/04/11/pamela-anderson-flips-out-over-julian-assange-arrest/?_ga=2.110593286.28225014.1554910023-1672167919.1554054498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former “Baywatch” star lashed out against President Trump, Britain and “Equador” following the arrest of her close pal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDANCE co-founder charged with sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8a5f420ec1834e0d890ed29d577fb972</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A Utah filmmaker who co-founded the Sundance Film Festival and produced an Oscar-winning movie in the mid-1980s has been charged with sexual abuse of a young...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would Patients Be Able to Escape BernieCare?</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/would-patients-be-able-to-escape-berniecare-11555009346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For all but a very few, the answer is no.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL'S MOON LANDING FAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/How-to-watch-the-Beresheet-spacecraft-land-on-the-moon-586454</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, who was at hand to watch the landing, said that Israel will continue to try landing on the moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Main Engine...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-israel-s-lunar-spacecraft-will-attempt-historic-touchdown-tonight-1.7109263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter from Obama read at Nipsey Hussle LA memorial...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/81ca5889719c4e32a012698da30e66bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Nipsey Hussle's legacy as a community activist, uniter, a doting father and a loving son were underscored at his public memorial service on Thursday, with deeply personal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Girlfriend sent home after threesome admits setting boyfriend's house on fire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/gloucester-county/2019/04/girlfriend-sent-home-in-taxi-after-threesome-tells-cops-she-set-boyfriends-house-on-fire-displacing-7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her boyfriend lived in the Woodbury house that burned Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama White House counsel indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/11/obama-white-house-counsel-gregory-craig-charged-by-federal-prosecutors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craig is charged with lying about work that his law firm was doing for Ukraine during an Oct. 19, 2017 special counsel interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants Riot At Mexican Immigration Station To Stop Deportations...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/04/11/migrants-riot-mexican-immigration-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Migrants staged a riot at an immigration station in Tapachula, Mexico early Wednesday morning, multiple Mexican media outlets reported</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's sister retires, negating judicial ethics complaints...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/872fc6adeaca4bd8a2875b23c3f3782a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — President Donald Trump's sister has retired as a federal appellate judge in Philadelphia, ending a civil misconduct inquiry launched after a report that she participated in Trump...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dust Blown North From Texas Turns Snowfall Yellow -- In Minnesota!</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2019/04/11/minnesota-weather-why-is-this-snow-yellow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This near mid-spring snow storm is bringing many in Minnesota a fresh and not entirely welcome dumping of snow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete leads Harris, Warren, Beto in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/democrat-president-candidates-2020-poll-joe-biden-bernie-sanders-pete-buttigieg-lead-2020-democrats-in-new-iowa-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former vice president leads Sen. Bernie Sanders and Mayor Pete Buttigieg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P&amp;G Puts FACEBOOKGOOGLE On Notice...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-04-11/p-g-is-putting-ad-platforms-like-facebook-and-google-on-notice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masters cell phone ban called greatest rule in history of sports...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/sports/2019/04/millennials-talking-strange-things-happen-at-the-masters-where-cell-phones-are-banned.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The penalty for bringing a cell phone into The Masters is a lifetime ban from the event. It is quite possibly the greatest rule in the history of sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Welcome Billboard: 'Where You Can Get Safe, Legal Abortion'...</title>
      <link>http://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/04/11/abortion-billboard-illinois-missouri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A head-turning billboard that encapsulates the state-to-state differences of Roe v. Wade recently appeared on the side of an Illinois highway--near a women's health clinic that services patients from Missouri, where abortion laws are tougher than in Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airport seeks traveler who left human ashes at security checkpoint...</title>
      <link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/anchorage/2019/04/10/anchorage-airport-seeks-traveler-who-left-human-ashes-at-security-checkpoint/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ashes may have been moved from an urn or box into a plastic bag for electronic screening by the TSA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretive Liberal Club Plots $275 Million Blitz...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/confidential-memo-secretive-liberal-donor-club-plots-275-million-for-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A secretive group of top liberal donors has budgeted $275 million to be injected into progressive infrastructure leading up to the 2020 elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Y2K-like bug knocks out NYC wireless network system...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/ny-y2k-like-gps-bug-knocks-out-city-wireless-network-20190411-ncscsp2vzvhajbn4km74rbzlaq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Y2K-like bug knocked out the city’s already-troubled wireless network system.The bug, known as the “GPS Rollover,” hit the city’s NYCWiN system on April 6, affecting several tasks including remote monitoring of traffic lights at 13,000 intersections, wireless reading of water meters, and a handful of NYPD license plate readers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graydon Carter: Life After 'VANITY FAIR'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/graydon-carter-life-vanity-fair-embracing-future-1200325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sure, the perks, pleasures and expense accounts of a vanishing print business have been replaced by digital churns and dubious Facebook ads, but the legendary magazine editor — who recently turned down an offer to run Time — retains his zest for journalism with a new newsletter and an occasional trip to the neighborhood newsstand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE UNLEASHED...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/roger-stone-will-vindicated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Narcissist Jack Dorsey extreme dieting, routines...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/04/11/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-eats-only-one-meal-per-day/?_ga=2.84199834.28225014.1554910023-1672167919.1554054498</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He fasts completely on weekends and endures freezing ice baths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside DNC war room...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/dnc-launches-hyper-local-2020-effort-shadow-trump-trail-n993196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party will use local stories to highlight promises it says the president has failed to keep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hitler Would Have Loved Social Media'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/race/bob-iger-calls-civil-discourse-warns-hitler-would-have-loved-social-media-1201201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have to change how we talk to each other," Iger said before suggesting, "Maybe we should just start by reconnecting with those friends and family members that we haven’t spoken to since the 2016 election."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plans For 5G Cell Phone Towers Raise Health Concerns; Demand For Protection From Radiation...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/04/10/plan-5g-cell-phone-towers-health-concern-moraga/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An East Bay neighborhood's fight against 5G is the topic of a town council meeting scheduled for Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper arrested for violent lyrics...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/rapper-threats-lyrics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida rapper has been arrested on a charge of threatening a mass shooting after song lyrics posted on Facebook say he will &amp;quot;catch you at a Gator game and shoot the whole campus up.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naked women lead cops on high-speed chase...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/no-clothes-trio-290765</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 11--Three naked women fresh from the shower at a Florida rest area told cops they were “air drying” in public when spotted by a witness who called 911, precipitating a bizarre chase that resulte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of flying? Dining booths, shops, sports bars coming to planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6907407/Cabin-designer-Ross-Burns-Aim-Altitude-wants-revolutionise-air-travel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline talks to Ross Burns, lead designer of cabin interiors at Bournemouth-based Aim Altitude, the firm behind Virgin Atlantic's bar - and now pushing the design envelope even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of 'splinternet': Web will fragment as govts set own rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6905695/Breaking-internet-new-regulations-imperil-global-network.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans to restrict online content put forward by governments worldwide threaten to fragment the internet, a number of experts in the fields of law, civil rights and censorship have warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E. coli outbreak continues to spread; Sickens nearly 100...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6911847/Mysterious-E-coli-outbreak-continues-spread-sickens-nearly-100-people-five-states.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC says 96 people have fallen ill in Georgia, Kentucky, Ohio, Tennessee and Virginia due to a mysterious E. coli outbreak. Health officials have not yet identified the source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOBLESS CLAIMS LOWEST IN 50 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/04/11/weekly-jobless-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First-time claims for state unemployment benefits were expected to total 211,000 for the most recent week, up from the 202,000 claims reported for the previous week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen Thieves Steal Laptops From Customers Seated Inside STARBUCKS...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/04/10/coffee-shop-criminals-computers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In each case, thieves target seated customers, grabbing their laptops, then running for the door.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGER: EVERYONE STOP THE HATE!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/04/bob-iger-reject-hate-wiesenthal-tribute-jeffrey-katzenberg-jimmy-kimmel-anti-semitism-1202593357/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We must demand more from our government officials,” said Bob Iger tonight at the Simon Wiesenthal Center and Museum of Tolerance tribute dinner. “I want to hear a pitch that isn’t grounded i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First privately funded craft attempts landing on moon...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2019/04/a-private-spacecraft-from-israel-will-attempt-a-moon-landing-thursday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No private company has ever achieved what SpaceIL is trying to do.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
