<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>LANDSLIDE HORROR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9794425/Germanys-flood-death-kills-81-1-300-missing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Several' people have died in a landslide that hit the flood-damaged town of Blessem, western Germany, on Friday as the country's deadliest flooding disaster for decades worsened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds Missing, Scores Dead as Raging Floods Strike Europe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-health-environment-and-nature-floods-9796ab4c2458604ff15203ef630b43f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — At least 100 people have died in devastating floods across parts of western Germany and Belgium, officials said Friday, as rescue operations and the search for hundreds still unaccounted for continued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Considering Intervention in Cuba...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-07-15/biden-considering-us-intervention-in-cuba-as-anti-government-protests-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is exploring whether it has the technology to assist protesters in Cuba suffering from blackouts orchestrated by the government there, Biden said Thursday, among other options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein investigation film gets release date...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/carey-mulligan-she-said-2022-release-date-weinstein-investigation-film</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carey Mulligan and Zoe Kazan's Weinstein investigation film "She Said" gets a November 2022 release date from Universal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Bodies Found in Versace Mansion on Anniversary of His Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3283107/two-dead-versace-mansion-hotel-room/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO men were found dead inside of a hotel room at the former Versace mansion on the eve of the iconic fashion designer’s death. The cops were called to the million-dollar home just before 1.3…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT says group sold tools to expose Windows...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/technology/microsoft-says-israeli-group-sold-tools-hack-windows-2021-07-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Israeli group sold a tool to hack into Microsoft Windows, Microsoft and technology human rights group Citizen Lab said on Thursday, shedding light on the growing business of finding and selling tools to hack widely used software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAITI ASSASSINS WERE PENTAGON TRAINED?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-military-once-trained-colombians-implicated-in-haiti-assassination-plot-pentagon-says/ar-AAMbYph</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The suspects received training while serving in the Colombian military, the Pentagon said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60+ dead, dozens missing as severe floods strike Europe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9790683/Five-dead-50-missing-floods-destroy-buildings-Germany.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Torrential downpours overnight triggered flash flooding across large parts of western Europe on Thursday, with more than 40 people dead and 70 missing - most of them in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House 'flagging' posts for FACEBOOK to censor...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/15/white-house-flagging-posts-for-facebook-to-censor-due-to-covid-19-misinformation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Surgeon General Vivek Murthy had called on social media companies to get rid of problematic posts, Jen Psaki admitted the government’s involvement in looking to take down certain posts …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bourdain Doc Sparks Controversy for 'Creepy' AI Rendering of Voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/new-anthony-bourdain-documentary-sparks-controversy-for-a-i-rendering-of-late-chefs-voice-crosses-an-ethical-line/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roadrunner: A Film About Anthony Bourdain, releasing on July 16th, is raising eyebrows for the practices utilized by the documentary filmmaker Morgan Neville.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo to be questioned in state sex harassment probe...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/15/andrew-cuomo-to-be-questioned-in-state-sexual-harassment-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo is set to be questioned this weekend as part of an independent state probe into allegations he sexually harassed current and former female aides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father-in-law says he pepper-sprayed NFL Sherman...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-sports-football-gun-politics-nfl-71bd220cbb7e18a145f3e417a679eb26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Richard Sherman’s father-in-law armed himself with a handgun and fired pepper-spray at the NFL cornerback to protect his family as Sherman tried to bust in the door of his in-laws’ home, according to a police statement obtained by The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman qualifies Navy's first female special operator...</title>
      <link>https://taskandpurpose.com/news/navy-first-female-special-operator/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;taskandpurpose.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We are incredibly proud of our teammate'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filmmaker to examine whether Angelina Jolie's son 'was STOLEN from birth family'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3190009/angelina-jolie-son-maddox-stolen-from-birth-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A NEW documentary about adoptions in Cambodia will take a fresh look at questions whether Angelina Jolie’s son Maddox may have been stolen from his birth family, The Sun can exclusiv…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Criticized Afghan War. Now Worries About Withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-criticized-the-afghan-war-now-it-worries-about-the-withdrawal/ar-AAMbUQy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese government rarely passes up a chance to accuse the United States of military adventurism and hegemony. In the case of Afghanistan, though, it has changed its tone, warning that Washington now bears the responsibility for the hasty end to its two-decade war there. “The United States, which created the Afghan issue in the first place, should act responsibly to ensure a smooth transition in Afghanistan,” China’s foreign minister, Wang...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Fires Execs for Criticizing Bosses Over SLACK...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/netflix-fires-execs-over-slack-comments-1234982361/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has dismissed three senior film marketing executives — about half its staff at that level — after they were discovered grousing on Slack about management, sources tell The Hollywood Reporte…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE names top DAILY BEAST staffer as new editor in chief...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/15/rolling-stone-names-top-daily-beast-staffer-as-new-editor-in-chief/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rolling Stone magazine named Noah Shachtman, the top editor at the Daily Beast, as its new editor-in-chief, ending a five-month search for a replacement. Shachtman, who will start the new gig in Se…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army scientists developing next tank -- that's no tank...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/07/15/how-army-scientists-are-developing-the-next-tank-thats-not-a-tank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The concepts researched today build the platforms of tomorrow's war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general urges national fight 'against misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-joe-biden-business-coronavirus-pandemic-misinformation-50d081bad2f76f097b6de57356ef8ab0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50+ dead, dozens missing as severe floods strike Europe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-environment-and-nature-germany-floods-44498a9899e1a75929f8de9e3df07874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — More than 50 people have died and dozens were missing Thursday as heavy flooding in Germany and Belgium turned streams and streets into raging torrents that swept away cars and caused houses to collapse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$28 million bidder bails!</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1002652/the-person-who-paid-28-million-to-go-to-space-with-jeff-bezos-cant-make-it-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC sex workers rampant in open-air prostitution market...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/15/prostitution-runs-rampant-in-brooklyn-amid-declining-enforcement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During weekends in East New York, more than a dozen sex workers — many likely trafficking victims — stop cars to entice drivers with their services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie-backed socialist, once inevitable, now in tight race in Dem special election...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/elections/beacon-poll-shows-brown-and-turner-tied-in-ohio-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats Shontel Brown and Nina Turner are neck-in-neck in the special election primary campaign to replace former Rep. Marcia Fudge (D., Ohio), who stepped down to become President Joe Biden’s housing secretary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to Block One of Biggest Porn Sites...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/germany-porn-sites-age-checks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regulators are trying to force adult sites to introduce age checks for users. Now one of the largest in the world faces a total block for refusing to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kids Are Not Alright: Chaos at  College RNC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/news/the-kids-are-not-alright-chaos-at-the-college-republican-national-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College Republican chapters all over the country claim they are being disenfranchised by a president seeking to consolidate power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News Site That Reported Putin May Have Secret Child Barred...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/russia-bars-news-site-that-reported-putin-may-have-secret-child</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia Bars News Site That Reported Putin May Have Secret Child</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Officials Ask Fully Vaccinated To Mask Again...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/07/15/sacramento-county-covid-masks-recommended-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sacramento residents are once again being asked to mask up indoors as the county’s COVID-19 case rate increases and the Delta variant surges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Hackers Targeted U.S. Defense Contractors in 'Sophisticated' FACEBOOK Campaign...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.commsn.com/en-us/news/world/iranian-hackers-targeted-u-s-defense-contractors-in-sophisticated-facebook-campaign/ar-AAMccIc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.commsn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 200  'Long-Hauler' Symptoms Identified...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/200-covid-long-hauler-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new report finds, among COVID long haulers, the likelihood of symptoms lasting longer than eight months is a staggering 91.8 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>amFAR's Big Sponsor This Year is Film Festival from Saudi Arabia, Which Deports People with AIDS and Treats Gays as Criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/15/amfars-big-sponsor-this-year-is-film-festival-from-saudi-arabia-which-deports-people-with-aids-and-treats-gays-as-criminals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, this makes sense. (Just kidding.) amFAR is the organization that raises money for AIDS research. Red Sea International is a foundation owned by the Saudi Royal family to underwrite their inau…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO experts warn more dangerous covid variants could take hold...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/u-s-covid-19-cases-more-than-double-in-two-weeks-as-delta-variant-spreads-fast-and-who-warns-pandemic-nowhere-near-finished-11626360879</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of new cases of COVID-19 in the U.S. has more than doubled in the last two weeks, as the delta variant continues to race across the nation,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porsches, Gucci rings, and billions of robocalls: Inside the PAC operation that raised millions by impersonating Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/15/politics/kfile-pac-trump-robocall-operation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At first glance, "Matte Nox" looks like your typical thirty-something wannabe Internet influencer, flaunting a lavish lifestyle on his public Instagram and TikTok accounts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 45 dead in Germany as storms ravage Europe... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/least-19-dead-germany-storms-082121360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heavy rains and floods lashing western Europe have killed at least 45 people in Germany and left many more missing, as rising waters led several houses to collapse on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLICE DEPLOY COVID-SNIFFING DOGS...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/07/15/bristol-county-sheriff-covid-sniffing-dogs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bristol County Sheriff’s office is adding a new tool to the department – canines trained to sniff out COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Billionaire Behind Bannon's Fake Chinese Embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/eduardo-eurnekian-the-billionaire-behind-steve-bannons-fake-chinese-embassy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mogul’s bulletproof Manhattan mansion shields network of right-wing news and nonprofits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK, TWITTER Struggle to Control Racist Use of Emojis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/soccer/twitter-facebook-struggle-to-control-racist-use-of-emojis/ar-AAMbeGF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wave of online racism aimed at some of England’s Black soccer players has highlighted how social media companies’ content moderation systems are failing to monitor the use of emojis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A private Israeli firm has helped governments hack journalists and human rights advocates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/a-private-israeli-firm-has-helped-governments-hack-journalists-and-human-rights-advocates/ar-AAMbOk0?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The firm has targeted more than 100 victims across the globe, according to Microsoft and Citizen Lab reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE QUIETLY ADMITS INFLATION SURGE COULD LAST YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house-quietly-signals-inflationary-run-could-last-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is sending mixed messages on the United States's post-pandemic inflationary run, with quiet signals suggesting the period might last years longer than administration officials have publicly indicated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel hit with new outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/coronavirus-in-israel-765-new-cases-138-percent-of-tests-return-positive-673898</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The outbreak continued to grow on Thursday as Israel registers some 765 cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth tax proposed for Canada's rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/wealth-tax-proposed-for-canadas-ultra-rich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Democrats would tackle the country's multi-billion deficit through the party's long-standing promise to tax extremely wealthy Canadians and corporations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Vampire' serial killer admits murdering 10 children and sucking one victim's blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/vampire-serial-killer-admits-murdering-24541531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Child serial killer Masten Milimo Wanjala admitted his five-year spree and is now assisting police after two bodies were discovered near Nairobi, shocking Kenyan reports say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTER PELOSI:  Clark ascends as prime candidate for next Speaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/katherine-clark-speaker-house-559b6389-8256-4a18-97e4-91a4fec67602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi has already suggested this is her final term in that job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans tops urban heat ranking...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/how-these-5-cities-became-the-most-intense-urban-heat-islands/981815</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study released Wednesday found that five U.S. cities can heat up between 7 to 9 degrees higher than the surrounding rural areas. It also notes how air conditioning can contribute to the added heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIKIPEDIA co-founder: Nobody should trust the site!</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/thepost/wikipedia-co-founder-i-no-longer-trust-the-website-i-created/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chances are, if you’ve ever been on the internet, you’ve visited Wikipedia. It is the world’s fifth largest website, pulling in an estimated 6.1 billion followers per month and serves as a cheat sheet for almost any topic in the world. So great is the online encyclopaedia’s influence is so great that it is the [...]Read More...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds seek prison term for first felony defendant in Capitol breach; Domestic terror threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-seeks-prison-term-for-first-felony-defendant-to-be-sentenced-in-capitol-breach-citing-domestic-terror-threat/ar-AAMbWba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Dept. urges judge to consider FBI Director Wray’s warning that attack emboldened some homegrown violent extremist actors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hesitancy morphs into hostility...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/vaccine-hesitancy-morphs-into-hostility-as-opposition-to-shots-hardens/ar-AAMbQZO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Red Tide Across Tampa Bay Killing Fish, Scaring Tourists Away...</title>
      <link>https://tampa.cbslocal.com/2021/07/15/red-tide-causes-local-businesses-to-suffer-1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tampa.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One fishing charter employee said because of Red Tide, he’s had several customers cancel their fishing experiences with him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J recall sunscreens over cancer-causing chemical...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/15/jj-recalls-aveeno-neutrogena-sunscreens-over-cancer-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp; Johnson is recalling five of its Neutrogena and Aveeno spray sunscreens after the company found low levels of benzene, a cancer-causing chemical, in some samples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD: Mexican adults crossing border again and again in attempts to reach USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/news/national/mexican-adults-are-crossing-the-border-again-and-again-in-attempts-to-reach-the-united/article_c832ce5a-6c71-53a4-8f1f-39ce1b33c9ea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO — Twenty-four hours a day, adults with scuffed shoes and dusted pant legs file out of the Otay Mesa Port of Entry — sometimes alone and sometimes in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Truth Behind AMAZON Mystery Seeds...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2021/07/unsolicited-seeds-china-brushing/619417/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why did so many Americans receive strange packages they didn’t think they’d ordered?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeopathic doctor sold fake vax cards and 'immunization pellets'...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/homeopathic-doctor-arrested-for-selling-fake-covid-19-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Napa-based naturopathic doctor allegedly sold unapproved vaccines for Covid-19 and childhood illnesses that she falsely claimed would satisfy immunization requirements for California schools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: Cheapest states to live in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/15/these-are-americas-cheapest-states-to-live-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As inflation increases prices on everything from groceries to energy, these are the ten U.S. states where a dollar goes the furthest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illegal pot invades CA deserts, bringing violence, fear, ecological destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/illegal-pot-invades-california-s-deserts-bringing-violence-fear-and-ecological-destruction/article_e9e3ac39-a3d4-5cb4-96a0-dfaca1fb611e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Before his corpse was dumped in a shallow grave 50 miles north of Los Angeles, Mauricio Ismael Gonzalez-Ramirez was held prisoner at one of the hundreds of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than 99% Hospitalized NOT Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/07/15/us-is-losing-time-in-vaccination-race-as-delta-variant-becomes-more-pervasive-expert-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 vaccination rates are down and cases are on the rise, exacerbated by the more transmissible Delta variant -- and an expert says the key to winning the race against the spread is getting more Americans vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna Doc to Debut on PARAMOUNT+...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/madonna-doc-madame-x-to-debut-on-paramount-this-fall-watch-trailer-here-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Movie "captures the pop icon’s rare and rapturous tour performance, hailed by sold out theatrical audiences worldwide"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famed Dutch crime reporter dies after being shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/dutch-crime-reporter-de-vries-dies-after-being-shot-rtl-news-2021-07-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity Dutch crime reporter Peter R. De Vries has died just over a week after being shot in the street, his family and his employer RTL Netherlands news said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beloved Neighborhood Peacock Shot To Death; Ad Sought Hit Job...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/authorities-probe-whether-beloved-peacock-was-shot-to-death-by-someone-hired-through-craigslist-ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Please contact me so we can form a strategy to eliminate this bird, and also to agree on how much you will be compensated," the Craigslist ad said. The bird died from a gunshot wound to the chest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes Screens Bombshell Hong Kong Protest Doc...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/cannes-2021-kong-protest-documentary-1234981760/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cannes Film Festival made a bombshell, last-minute addition to its lineup this week, inviting select members of the international press to attend a “confidential” screening of Revol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men found dead at Versace Mansion on eve of designer death anniversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3283107/two-dead-versace-mansion-hotel-room/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TWO men were found dead inside of a hotel room at the former Versace mansion on the eve of the iconic fashion designer’s death. The cops were called to the million-dollar home just before 1.3…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos in Melbourne as residents resist rules..</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9791503/Covid-Australia-Anti-lockdown-protestors-storm-Melbourne-eve-Victorias-five-day-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of protestors have stormed Melbourne's CBD to rally against the looming five-day lockdown coming into force across Victoria from midnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests hit Athens, Paris over restrictions, jab mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/covid-19-global-updates-protests-hit-athens-and-paris-over-new-coronavirus-restrictions-vaccine-mandates/ar-AAMben3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unrest has underscored the difficulty that some leaders face in weighing public health during a pandemic against policies that appear to encroach on individual freedom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: PUTIN PLOT TO BACK TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/putin-plot-trump-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked documents from the Kremlin obtained by The Guardian reportedly reveal a plot to put Donald Trump in the White House approved by Vladimir Putin in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every Covid patient in L.A. hospital not fully vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/14/health/los-angeles-county-covid-cases/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County is seeing a surge in new Covid-19 coronavirus cases, topping 1,000 for the fifth straight day Wednesday, and though hospitalizations remain low, each infected patient admitted to a county hospital has not had all their vaccine shots, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of palace security held...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/14/americas/haiti-moise-security-head-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of security at Haiti's presidential residence has been placed in police custody, according to a close associate, as authorities continue to investigate the assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama military base 1st to order troops to show proof...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/alabama-military-1st-u-order-054315608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The commanding general of Fort Rucker has announced that the Alabama military base will require service members not wearing face masks "to show proof of vaccination" while on duty to combat rising COVID-19 cases.Why it matters: The order, issued Wednesday, makes Fort Rucker the "first military base in the continental" U.S. to permit leaders to "check the vaccination status of those in uniform," the Washington Post notes.Get market news worthy of your time with Axios Markets. Subscribe for free.D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases surge in Tokyo week before Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-lifestyle-2020-tokyo-olympics-japan-olympic-team-tokyo-47d81e15c1b320bc37b721160a4b7bdc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — New coronavirus cases surged to 1,308 in Tokyo on Thursday, a six-month high, as fears rise of a possible dramatic increase that could flood hospitals during the Olympics that start in eight days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authoritarianism advances as world battles pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-religion-government-and-politics-a127151d7208b79c02767b435355511d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Here’s some of what happened while the world was distracted by the coronavirus: Hungary banned the public depiction of homosexuality. China shut Hong Kong’s last pro-democracy newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On farewell visit to USA, Merkel brings message of stability...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-21fe2acde1b05ca11889636b99e8716b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden welcomes German Chancellor Angela Merkel to the White House for what is likely to be her last official visit and one to which she's bringing a bag full of issues and an overarching message for Berlin's close ally: You've got a friend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL: Two in Three Southern Republicans Want to Secede...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/shock-poll-two-in-three-southern-republicans-want-to-secede-from-the-united-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shocking YouGov poll reveals that 66% of Republicans in southern states want to secede from the United States. The survey looked at the current political climate in America and was done by YouGov in conjunction with BrightLineWatch. The most stunning result looked at support or opposition for the state in which respondents lived in […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI could control when humans sleep, wake...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/next-generation-ai-could-control-24539397</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technology records and tracks snoring levels, and has already been integrated into a new app called Soundsleep. It was created by researchers at the University of Sheffield</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials warn could kill nearly all young endangered salmon...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/energy-environment/563120-officials-warn-heat-wave-could-kill-nearly-all-young-endangered</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California officials are raising concerns that the intense heat waves across the state may cause nearly all young endangered salmon in the Sacramento River to die.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden policy suddenly in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/22573703/biden-cuba-protests-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump-era sanctions are adding to Cuba’s crisis. Biden has to decide whether to keep them in place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEZOS GETS READY: BLUE ORIGIN to make history with unpiloted civilian space flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/aerospace-defense/bezos-blue-origin-make-history-with-unpiloted-civilian-space-flight-2021-07-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos may have been beaten to space by rival Richard Branson, but the billionaire American businessman is poised to make history next week aboard what would be the world's first unpiloted suborbital flight with an all-civilian crew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: After days of hiccups, Brazil's Bolsonaro may need surgery...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/brazil-s-bolsonaro-hospitalized-after-10-days-hiccups-won-t-n1274018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro, 66, was diagnosed with an intestinal obstruction on Wednesday evening after being taken to a hospital in São Paulo, according to state-run news agency Agência Brasil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: ANOTHER heat wave to roast western USA, Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/yet-another-major-heat-wave-is-set-to-roast-the-western-us-and-canada-by-the-weekend/ar-AAM9IZq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fourth punishing heat wave in five weeks could break more records this weekend into early next week, this time focusing in the Rocky Mountains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tougher tactics targeting unvaccinated needed to stop new COVID spike, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/tougher-tactics-for-the-unvaccinated-needed-to-stop-new-rise-in-covid-19-experts-say/ar-AAM9026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Door-to-door outreach and vaccine requirements at work would help curb coronavirus spread, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who bankrolled?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article252765228.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The multinational probe into the brazen, middle-of-the-night assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse broadened Tuesday, with law enforcement in Haiti and South Florida searching for those who provided logistics and arms for the deadly assault — and who bankrolled it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Passport With Bitcoin, Escape Taxes?</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/robertwood/2021/07/14/buy-passport-with-bitcoin-escape-taxes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 5,000 Cubans detained during protests, report says...</title>
      <link>https://www.fltimes.com/news/nation/more-than-5-000-cubans-detained-during-protests-report-says/article_47b9fd54-1e05-591c-a42c-759dac88704d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fltimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAVANA — Thousands of protesters have been detained in Cuba during three days of protests against the government, according to compiled reports. More than 5,000 were detained, including 120 activists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THREATENED TO KILL SELF...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9790181/Richard-Shermans-wife-Ashley-called-911-reporting-threatening-kill-arrest.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Richard Sherman's wife Ashley Moss called 911 reporting her husband had drunk two bottles of liquor and was threatening to kill himself before his arrest on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breyer says hasn't decided retirement plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/15/politics/stephen-breyer-retirement-plans/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Stephen Breyer has not decided when he will retire and is especially gratified with his new role as the senior liberal on the bench, he told CNN in an exclusive interview -- his first public comments amid the incessant speculation of a Supreme Court vacancy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Britney Spears wins right to new lawyer in battle to remove dad...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/britney-spears-conservatorship-new-lawyer-matthew-rosengart-court-hearing-1234793152/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED with Spears reaction following 3:28 PM update: Less than an hour after becoming Britney Spears’ new lawyer, Matthew Rosengart pledged to push the singer’s father off his perch i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami security firm faces questions in Haiti assassination...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-miami-haiti-assassinations-9ee8e2deb6de5be44d8ed82fe3da932d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — For the owner of a small private security company with a history of avoiding paying debts and declaring bankruptcy, it looked like a good opportunity: Find people with military experience for a job in Haiti.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
