<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Japanese space probe arrives at asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://www.popularmechanics.com/space/solar-system/a21967081/japanese-sample-return-spacecraft-reaches-target-asteroid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.popularmechanics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's Hayabusa-2 spacecraft will collect a piece of the asteroid Ryugu and bring it back to Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishment Takes Beating...</title>
      <link>https://www.weeklystandard.com/david-byler/the-democratic-establishment-takes-a-beating</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive leftists got some wins, but they aren't the Democratic Tea Party yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Saudi TV Presenter Flees Country Amid 'Indecent Dress' Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/middle-east-news/female-saudi-tv-presenter-flees-country-amid-indecent-dress-probe-1.6218899</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EX-FOXNEWS BOSS BILL SHINE IN TALKS TO BECOME WHITE HOUSE COMMUNICATIONS DIRECTOR... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/former-fox-news-exec-bill-shine-in-final-talks-to-become-white-house-communications-director/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women dominating Dem primaries...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/latest-news/article213790179.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A half-dozen leading Democratic pollsters explain that it's as much about the nuances of this year's campaigns as it is sweeping cultural forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Jackson dead...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/06/27/joe-jackson-dead-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Jackson dead at 89.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL POPS TO HIGHEST PRICE IN 4 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/crude-rises-as-traders-fret-over-potential-supply-worries-linked-to-iran-2018-06-27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil prices rally Wednesday, with the U.S. benchmark heading toward its highest since 2014 as domestic crude supplies notch their biggest weekly drop of the year so far and traders fret over U.S. threats to sanction countries that don’t stop importing oil from Iran by Nov. 4.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC HOSTS GUSH...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/394374-twitter-fights-with-trump-dont-move-the-nation-forward</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, the political newcomer who vanquished a top-ranking House Democrat in a New York primary, said Wednesday that "getting int</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweltering Europe loses its fizz as C02 shortage hits drinkers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/sweltering-europe-loses-fizz-c02-shortage-hits-drinkers-145438375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's peak season for bars and barbecues in Europe as a summer heatwave coincides with the World Cup on TV. A shortage of industrial carbon dioxide (CO2) is also affecting meat producers and food companies that rely on dry ice as a refrigerant. Ice cream is another item at risk, just as temperatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes curb power of public sector unions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0f83c64b1dd249de9ec89ab85235790a/Supreme-Court-deals-big-setback-to-labor-unions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Supreme Court ruled Wednesday that government workers can't be forced to contribute to labor unions that represent them in collective bargaining, dealing a s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement speculation shadows court's final day...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/regulation/394291-retirement-speculation-shadows-courts-final-day</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court is expected to end its term on Wednesday with one final major case challenging public sector union fees left to decide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI SNAPS; ASKED ABOUT FRESH CANDIDATES...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-pelosi-snaps-reporter-who-asked-about-younger-candidates-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘I am particularly excited that so many women are running across the country’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Dems, Media Figures Glorify Violence Against Trump Supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nw9kyYEwg2A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who is really glorifying violence against people with other political views? Many in the entertainment and news media, as well as many Democrats, have tragic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Orders Family Reunification Within 30 Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration/u-s-judge-orders-migrant-families-to-be-reunited-idUSKBN1JN1WH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. judge has blocked the Trump administration from separating immigrant parents and children at the U.S.-Mexico border, and ordered that those who were separated be reunited within 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The four liberal justices dissented...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-court-unions/supreme-court-delivers-blow-to-organized-labor-in-fees-dispute-idUSKBN1JN0H2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Supreme Court on Wednesday dealt a blow to organized labor, ruling that non-members cannot be forced in certain states to pay fees to unions representing public employees such as teachers and police, shutting off a key union revenue source.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House considers 'largest amnesty bill in history,' adds 2.2 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/house-considers-largest-amnesty-bill-in-history-adds-2-2-million-bigger-than-houston</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The immigration compromise the House plans to vote on Wednesday would provide the biggest amnesty ever, turning 2.2 million undocumented and illegal immigrants into citizens, according to a new analysis of the package from House Speaker Paul Ryan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP APPROVAL 45%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_jun27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK POLL:  44% SEE CIVIL WAR SOON IN USA...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/general_politics/june_2018/31_think_u_s_civil_war_likely_soon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin-Trump summit on agenda as Bolton holds Moscow talks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/National-security-adviser-John-Bolton-Russian-13029669.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - National security adviser John Bolton met with Russian President Vladimir Putin on Wednesday in a prelude to a long-anticipated summit with President Donald Trump that is looking increasingly likely. Putin warmly greeted Bolton in a grand oval meeting hall at the Kremlin, flanked by statues of Russian czars set before lime-painted walls. Putin opened the meeting by repeating to Bolton his frequent contention that U.S.-Russian relations are in a poor state in large part because of the domestic political environment in the United States. "Your visit here to Moscow inspires hope that we will be able to take first steps to restore full-fledged relations between Russia and the United States," Putin said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of hammerhead shark pups found dead in Honolulu...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dozens-hammerhead-shark-pups-found-dead-honolulu-135235439.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Hawaii authorities are investigating after dozens of baby hammerhead sharks were found dead near Keehi Lagoon in Honolulu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BITTER BILL: Clinton says Trump has poured 'poison' down 'America's throat'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/394370-bill-clinton-trump-has-poured-poison-down-americas-throat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Clinton is suggesting that President Trump is at least partly to blame for a lack of civility in politics, saying he has poured “poison" down "America’s throat.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiCaprio, Pitt go back to sixties in first look at Tarantino 'ONCE UPON A TIME IN HOLLYWOOD'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/06/27/leonardo-dicaprio-brad-pitt-go-back-sixties-first-look-upon-time-hollywood-7664974/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We're being spoiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes deal sharp defeat to public employee unions, banning mandatory fees...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-court-unions-fees-20180627-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court frees public employees from having to pay fees to support their union.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Gay Man Running for Mayor of Moscow...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/meet-anton-krasovsky-the-gay-man-running-for-mayor-of-moscow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anton Krasovsky stands alone: the only out LGBTQ person willing to stand for election in Russia. That’s if the authorities allow him to run for mayor of Moscow this September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String of trans murders could be work of serial killer, activists fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/feature/nbc-out/string-transgender-murders-could-be-work-serial-killer-activists-fear-n886801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three trans black women have been fatally shot in Jacksonville, Florida, since the beginning of this year, and local activists fear that the murders are linked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE FOR FOX: COMCAST Hunts for Additional Cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/comcast-seeks-more-cash-in-pursuit-of-21st-century-fox-assets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast Corp. is exploring tie-ups with private-equity investors or strategic partners that could provide additional capital as the cable giant pursues a costly acquisition of 21st Century Fox's entertainment assets, according to people familiar with the situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timothee Chalamet Battles Addiction in 'BEAUTIFUL BOY' Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/timothee-chalamet-beautiful-boy-trailer-steve-carell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 72% say traditional outlets 'report news they know to be fake'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-effect-92-percent-republicans-media-fake-news-9c1bbf70-0054-41dd-b506-0869bb10f08c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trust in the media is heavily influenced by partisanship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pittsburgh officer charged with criminal homicide in teen shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/27/us/michael-rosfeld-charged-criminal-homicide-antwon-rose-east-pittsburgh/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;East Pittsburgh police officer Michael Rosfeld has been charged with criminal homicide in the shooting death of 17-year-old Antwon Rose, court records show. Rosfeld's bail was set at $250,000. A preliminary hearing is set for July 6. The severity of the charge was not immediately clear. Under Pennsylvania law, criminal homicide includes murder, voluntary manslaughter and involuntary manslaughter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JETBLUE flight mistakenly sends hijack alert, triggering huge scare at JFK airport...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/26/jfk-airport-jet-blue-aircraft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plane sent a false alarm to the airport's control tower while it was taxiing to take off, according to the Port Authority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer Americans spending final days in hospital; More dying at home...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/science/sciencenow/la-sci-sn-where-americans-die-20180627-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The American way of dying seems to have become less frantic, desperate and expensive. A new study finds that seniors insured by Medicare who died in 2015 were less likely to do so in a hospital, and more likely to pass away in a home or other community setting, than were those who died in 2000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Man shoots wife he thought was 'possessed'...</title>
      <link>http://bronx.news12.com/story/38514873/authorities-franklin-borough-man-shot-wife-who-he-thought-was-possessed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bronx.news12.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a Sussex County man fatally shot his wife because he believed she was "possessed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tebow suddenly looking like pro baseball player...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/27/tim-tebow-suddenly-looking-like-a-pro-baseball-player/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The jokes have slowed considerably. The playful jabs have begun to subside. Tim Tebow is proving he belongs, and lately he’s doing more than that. He has been performing at a high level this month.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED Flight Diverted After Passenger Dies On Board...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2018/06/27/united-airlines-flight-1888-passenger-dies-houston-boston/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Flight 1888 was diverted to Washington-Dulles because there was a medical emergency on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benicio Del Toro, Hollywood's Instant Antihero, Goes the Distance...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/06/27/movies/benicio-del-toro-sicario-day-of-the-soldado.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The economical actor has burned brightly in all his films, from “The Usual Suspects” to “The Last Jedi.” Now, with an action franchise and a mini-series, he’s learning to linger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Merkel teeters, Austria's Kurz seizes moment as 'rock star of new right'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/As-Merkel-teeters-Austria-s-Kurz-seizes-the-13029682.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIENNA - By 24, Sebastian Kurz was a member of the Austrian Cabinet. By 27, he was his country's foreign minister. And by 31, the debonair university dropout with the slicked-back mane and the Hollywood grin became the world's youngest leader. Now, just six months into his term as chancellor, Kurz is seizing a febrile moment in European politics to make himself into one of the continent's true power players. In the next few weeks alone, he is trying to seal off Europe from asylum seekers arriving by sea, orchestrate a summit between President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin and, critics say, undermine Germany's Angela Merkel, the most consequential European leader of the past decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apocalyptic scenes as fire rages in England...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-saddleworth-moor-fire-now-12799493</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 50 homes have now been evacuated and 100 firefighters are on the scene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fires to clear land lead to near-record loss of tree cover...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180627070031-z4mgl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical forests were lost at a rate equivalent to 40 football fields per minute in 2017, says World Resources Institute</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind in sails, Mexican leftist heads to giant stadium for campaign finale...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-election/wind-in-sails-mexican-leftist-heads-to-giant-stadium-for-campaign-finale-idUSKBN1JN0HD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican presidential favorite Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador is due to wrap up his election campaign on Wednesday in the country's largest soccer stadium, fortified by a new opinion poll showing his already-commanding lead growing even further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Backs Personal Injury Lawsuits in Market With 20% Returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/06/27/soros-backs-personal-injury-lawsuits-in-market-with-20-returns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soros Backs Personal Injury Lawsuits in Market With 20% Returns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Space Race Making Life Difficult For Airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-27/the-billionaire-space-race-is-making-life-difficult-for-airlines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More launches mean more closed airspace, and more delays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model raises ire with nude photo overlooking Western Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/belgian-model-raises-ire-with-nude-photo-overlooking-western-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marisa Papen says photograph with Jewish holy site in the background designed to challenge 'boundaries of religion and politics'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA predicts it will screen more than 28M passengers over holiday...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/transportation/tsa/394330-tsa-predicts-screening-more-than-28-million-passengers-for-july</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The TSA predicts it will screen more than 28 million individuals for holiday travel over the Fourth of July.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flamingo? In Texas? Zoo Fugitive Since '05 Still Surviving in Wild...</title>
      <link>http://abc13.com/pets-animals/fugitive-flamingo-spotted-in-texas-after-escaping-from-zoo-in-kansas--/3658683/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A notorious African flamingo, who escaped from a zoo in Kansas in 2005, was spotted on Texas coast bend Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez? Democratic Giant Slayer...</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/all-about-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-who-beat-crowley-in-ny-dem-primary-2018-6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 28-year-old beat veteran congressman Joe Crowley in New York's Democratic Party congressional primary election on Tuesday night, in what has been perceived as shocking and major upset within the Democratic Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Orders Migrant Family Reunification Within 30 Days...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/27/california-judge-rapid-reunification/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We are a country ... of compassion'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie congratulates progressive candidates on primary wins...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/394328-sanders-congratulates-progressive-candidates-on-primary-wins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) on Tuesday issued a statement congratulating two progressive candidates on their primary wins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY REBOOT!</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2018/06/27/mitt-romney-takes-huge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Orem • Mitt Romney hardly broke a sweat on his way to capturing the Republican nomination in Utah’s U.S. Senate race, according to unofficial results Tuesday, earning 74 percent of early vote tallies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILLENNIAL ROCKS DEM PARTY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/26/politics/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-joe-crowley-new-york-14-primary/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a 28-year-old Latina running her first campaign, ousted 10-term incumbent Rep. Joe Crowley in New York's 14th congressional district on Tuesday, CNN projects, in the most shocking upset of a rollicking political season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military aims for $1B missile defense radar in Hawaii... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-military-aims-1b-missile-defense-radar-hawaii-003417197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — The U.S. military wants to install missile defense radar in Hawaii to identify any ballistic missiles that are fired from North Korea or elsewhere, officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope and Macron hold 'intense' meeting at Vatican...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/pope-receives-french-president-macron-vatican-000325711.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French President Emmanuel Macron held an "intense" meeting with Pope Francis during his first official visit to the Vatican on Tuesday, discussing global issues including the fate of migrants coming to Europe. The tete-a-tete between the Argentine pontiff and Macron in the Vatican's ornate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROMNEY REBOOT?</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mitt-romney-against-state-lawmaker-senate-primary-140955039--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Mitt Romney will learn Tuesday if he'll continue the reboot of his political career as voters were deciding a primary in the race for a Utah Senate seat vacated by Orrin Hatch, who is retiring after more than 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan win sets up prolonged stand-off with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-win-sets-prolonged-stand-off-us-183708775.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington's chilly reaction to Recep Tayyip Erdogan's election victory and consolidation of his presidential powers reflect expectations that no thaw in US-Turkish ties is imminent. Erdogan's position as Turkey's leader remains strong, but his parliamentary majority now depends not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burlesque is back at Atlantic City casino that went bust...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/burlesque-back-atlantic-city-casino-175909703.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTIC CITY, N.J. (AP) — Things are going bust again inside the casino at the northern end of Atlantic City's Boardwalk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On both sides of Atlantic, illegals meet hostile reception...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/austrian-police-army-perform-border-closure-exercise-095213321.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — On both sides of the Atlantic, migrants flooding across borders by the hundreds each day have met a hostile reception and governments unable to agree on how to cope with the arrivals. In Europe, where far-right parties have joined the governments in Italy and Austria and made gains elsewhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested after jumping on plane wing, pounding on windows at Atlanta airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/passengers-escapes-plane-on-tarmac-at-atlanta-airport/777645592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsbtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We've got a reporter at the airport working to learn the latest details for the Channel 2 Action News Nightbeat at 11 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Citing 'Anti-Meat' Sentiment, Butchers Seek Police Protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/citing-anti-meat-sentiment-butchers-seek-police-protection/17656884/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS — French butchers say they’ve had enough. Not only must they confront media coverage of the “vegan way of life,” now they say they are under assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column and contributes to the PostPartisan blog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sotomayor Delivers Fiery Dissent... </title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2018/6/26/17505906/sonia-sotomayor-dissent-travel-ban-muslim-trump-ginsburg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sotomayor read Trump’s tweets too and wants to know why the rest of the Supreme Court didn’t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega-mansions for world's elite compete for most extreme home ever built!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/6627569/most-expensive-mansions-helipad-cinema-extreme-millionaire-man-caves-built/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SWANKY mega-mansion with a rooftop helipad, 40-person cinema and a swimming pool is vying to be crowned the ultimate man cave. Six glamorous homes, which are all on the market for eye-watering su…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE, Obama plan to control news...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenewatlantis.com/publications/googlegov</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenewatlantis.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the quiet alignment between “smart” government and the universal information engine. By Adam J. White, director of the Center for the Study of the Administrative State at George Mason University’s Antonin Scalia Law School</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famed Route 66 put on list of 11 endangered historic places...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/jun/26/route-66-highway-national-endangered-list </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To ensure special protection for famous highway, Congress and the president would have to declare it a national historic trail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out 'climate change' suits against big oil...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/science/article/Judge-throws-out-SF-and-Oakland-climate-change-13025637.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge Monday tossed out two groundbreaking lawsuits by San Francisco and Oakland that sought to hold some of the world’s largest oil companies liable for climate change. In an exhaustive, 16-page ruling that touched on such scientific matters as the ice age and early observations of carbon dioxide, U.S. District Judge William Alsup acknowledged the problem of a warming planet but said it is just too big for the courts to solve. The cities are trying to get five oil and gas giants, including Bay Area-based Chevron, to help cover the costs of dealing with sea-level rise, like picking up the tab for seawalls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protestors Confront McConnell and Wife: 'Leave My Husband Alone!' </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/watch-immigration-protestors-confront-mitch-mcconnell-and-elaine-chao-leave-my-husband-alone/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDakota town could abolish itself to stop white supremacist takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.idahostatesman.com/news/nation-world/national/article213792799.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2013 white supremacist Craig Cobb tried to turn Leith, North Dakota into a white enclave but failed. Now Leith's mayor, Ryan Schock, concerned that two possible Cobb followers were elected to the town council, wants to scrap the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in huge brawl as Pride festival turns into chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/712297/Bikini-women-brawl-San-Francisco-Pride-Parade-festival-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Protection for Sarah Sanders...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/06/26/politics/sarah-sanders-secret-service-protection/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House press secretary Sarah Sanders is expected to receive Secret Service protection as soon as Wednesday, two sources familiar with the decision tell CNN, but they did not specify how long it will last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farmers in America killing selves in staggering numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/american-farmers-rising-suicide-rates-plummeting-incomes/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Farming has by far the highest suicide rate of any occupation in the U.S. -- plummeting incomes may be one reason</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett Chooses New Path for Newspapers After Lamenting Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/2018/06/26/buffett-chooses-new-path-for-newspapers-after-lamenting-decline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway struck a deal for Lee Enterprises to manage its newspapers in 30 markets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank Stocks On Historic Losing Streak...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-26/banks-endure-record-streak-of-losses-as-yield-curve-flattens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bank stocks just hit a record -- a record of losses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONSERVATIVE WIN STREAK AT COURT...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/supreme-court-travel-ban-abortion-conservatives-eaf72fd7-6f1b-44cc-beaf-b71a5c9e811b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anthony Kennedy is still a conservative — mostly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen is your early-morning guide to the vital news in business, politics, tech and media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veteran sets self on fire outside Georgia Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/breaking-emergency-scene-outside-state-capitol/t1EJeInRLqB2fegT9JtLtI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgruntled with the Department of Veterans Affairs, a veteran set himself on fire in protest Tuesd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYLAN BYERS</title>
      <link>https://us11.campaign-archive.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=505046f69e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late Night Hosts Team Up to Take Down Trump...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2018/06/26/stephen-colbert-jimmy-fallon-conan-obrien-video-late-show-trump-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How are the hosts of late night TV responding to President Trump’s vicious attacks? By teaming up… and whimpering a bit. In this jointly produced cold open that will kick off both tonig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA PRIVACY PUSH SPOOKS TECH GIANTS...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2018/06/26/google-and-facebook-are-quietly-fighting-californias-privacy-rights-initiative-emails-reveal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emails show how tech giants are negotiating for a compromise to avoid the prospect of California voters potentially ushering in the strongest privacy rules in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montage: Media Framing Trump Voters as Public Enemy No. 1...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-montage-media-turning-trump-voters-public-enemy-no-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘If you vote for Trump, then you, the voter, you, not Donald Trump, are standing at the border, like Nazis’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Man Clings To Hood Of Speeding MERCEDES On I-95 In FL --  While Talking On Cellphone!</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/06/25/man-seen-on-hood-of-car-on-i-95/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just when you thought you had seen everything on South Florida roadways, along comes something that makes you shake your head.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCRAMBLE TO AVOID BALLOT...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/california-has-48-hours-to-pass-this-privacy-bill-or-el-1827117016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent headlines have suggested that California lawmakers are considering a bill that would give Californians “unprecedented control over their data.” This is true but that is not the whole story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER OF UNREST</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/protesters-disrupt-immigration-agents-encampments-across-u-182118501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small groups of protesters in cities across the United States are camping outside offices used by federal immigration agents, seeking to disrupt deportations in response to U.S. President Donald Trump's tough stance on illegal immigration. The protests, which began last week in Portland, Oregon,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters pushes camera, waves papers, sticks out tongue!</title>
      <link>https://bigleaguepolitics.com/watch-laura-loomer-confronts-maxine-waters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bigleaguepolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High court OKs Trump travel ban, rejects Muslim bias claim...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3a20abe305bd4c989116f82bf535393b/High-court-OKs-Trump's-travel-ban,-rejects-Muslim-bias-claim</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A sharply divided Supreme Court upheld President Donald Trump's ban on travel from several mostly Muslim countries Tuesday, the conservative majority taking his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP NEXT: 1970S-STYLE BOMBINGS, WARNS PROGRESSIVE...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/06/up-next-1970s-style-bombings-warns-progressive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A writer for the popular progressive news website Splinter is warning supporters of President Trump that if they have a problem with the heckling of administration officials in public places, they haven’t seen anything yet. “Do you think that being asked to leave a restaurant, or having your meal interrupted, or being called by the public is […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns left about harassment of his staffers: 'Not on my watch'...</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jun/26/donald-trump-warns-left-about-harassment-his-staff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump says in a fundraising email that Democrats “only care about ‘equal rights’ if you’re a liberal,” citing the left’s harassment of his top advisers and declaring, “not on my watch.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the latest Rolling Stone news with exclusive stories and pictures from Rolling Stone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police: Threat Probes Expand Since Shootings...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/policy/member-event-security-threat-probes-expand-since-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capitol Police has “widened the net” of events off Capitol Hill where the agency has acted to ensure protection for lawmakers since the shooting at a GOP baseball practice last June, Chief Matthew Verderosa told members of the House Administration Committee on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing deficits to push debt to almost 100% of GDP...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/policy/cbo-us-debt-burden-set-to-break-record-in-early-2030s</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Debt as a share of the United States economy is on track to blow through the previous World War II-era record within two decades and keep rising from there, the Congressional Budget Office said in its annual long-term budget report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House immigration bill is expected to get a vote Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NY DAILY NEWS] CONFIDENTIAL</title>
      <link>http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/gossip/confidential</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read celebrity gossip around New York and Hollywood from the New York Daily News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LifeZette's mission is contained in its moniker: Life. Explained. Each day the site captures the wonder, the complexity, the frustration and the joys of life in all its variety. This is media built for the way we live--never in one place or focused on one issue to the exclusion of all others. From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain -- and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sessions LA visit sparks mass protest...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-sessions-downtown-20180626-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of protesters were gathering downtown Tuesday morning to demonstrate a visit by U.S. Atty. Gen. Jeff Sessions to downtown Los Angeles, where he delivered an afternoon speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency influencers hype up coin offerings, making $105,000 a tweet...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-cryptocurrency-ico-influencers-20180626-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the murky world of cryptocurrency bounty campaigns, social media influencers get paid to promote initial coin offerings by the entrepreneurs (and in some cases scammers) behind those offerings. The advice of a YouTuber who is paid to publicize offerings: "You shouldn’t listen to YouTubers."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! US, News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/news/blogs/the_papers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus, Fox Business anchor Trish Regan came to Acosta's defense on her program this afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Machete-wielding woman forces ex-boyfriend to have sex...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/montana-machete-assault-295730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 26--A machete-wielding Montana woman broke into her ex-boyfriend’s home, directed him to disrobe, and then forced him to have sex with her, according to police. As detailed in a criminal complai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising concerns over hackers using satellites to target USA...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/394037-satellites-become-latest-tool-for-hackers-targeting-businesses-consumers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rapidly expanding number of satellites transmitting GPS locations, cellphone signals and other sensitive information is creating new opportunities for hackers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem lawmakers seek distance...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/394266-dem-lawmakers-seek-distance-from-waters-call-for-confrontation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats on Capitol Hill are mad as hell about President Trump’s “zero tolerance” immigration policy, but they’re distancing themselves from Rep. Maxine Waters (D-Calif.) and her calls for public confrontations with administration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/article/declarations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American institutions—and therefore democracy itself—are frailer than we often realize.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin-Trump summit on agenda as Bolton holds Moscow talks...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180626230124-hzyqp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/BOLTON (TV, PIX):Putin-Trump summit on agenda as John Bolton holds Moscow talks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE NEWS</title>
      <link>http://news.google.com/nwshp?hl=en&amp;tab=wn&amp;q=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.google.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comprehensive up-to-date news coverage, aggregated from sources all over the world by Google News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap produces a wide range of news contents and provides print, broadcast media as well as state and private institutions with real-time news products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mob Targets Stephen Miller's Apartment...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/25/protest-outside-white-house-adviser-stephen-millers-apartment-pass-out-wanted-flyers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'defeating fascism and the Trump regime ... '</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC MELTDOWN: Woman screams hysterically, threatens passengers...</title>
      <link>http://abc13.com/womans-outburst-on-spirit-flight-from-houston-stuns-passengers/3654463/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New video shows the woman cursing, making threats involving her brothers, and acting erratically before a plane full of distressed passengers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
