<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Army fires first 'Iron Dome missile interceptor' in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3524780/us-army-iron-dome-missile-interceptor-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US Army successfully fired its first Iron Dome missile interceptor on Monday as fears of World War Three build across the world. The troops this morning completed the first test of the missile …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Couch Potatoes 7 Times More Likely To Suffer Stroke...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/couch-potatoes-stroke-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers add that nearly nine in 10 strokes could be attributed to "modifiable" risk factors such as sitting too much.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Boasts $30 Billion in Payments as Creator Wars Heat Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-08-23/youtube-boasts-30-billion-in-payments-as-creator-wars-heat-up</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media companies have thrown considerable resources and money at online creators in recent years. YouTube would like to remind everyone that it throws the most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam deploys troops to enforce rules...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210823131541-rgvz9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/VIETNAM (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Vietnam deploys troops to enforce COVID lockdown in largest city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand extending stay-at-home as outbreak grows...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/568971-new-zealand-extending-lockdown-as-covid-19-outbreak-grows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand’s government has extended its nationwide lockdown as COVID-19 cases grow around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underground arm-wrestling mania slamming NYC streets...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/23/underground-arm-wrestling-mania-takes-nyc-by-storm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“So much of the world is being taught to shy away from people, that people are dangerous. But we are pack animals — people belong together — and the sport of arm-wrestling teaches you that together…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health worker crunch pressures states battling Delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/08/23/health-worker-crunch-delta-variant-506484</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alarming spread of new cases is draining the pool of available health workers in ways not seen since the pandemic’s winter peak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked footage shows grim conditions in Iran's Evin prison...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-health-religion-iran-prisons-01dfade61d7a706d630bf83d30d8cb02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — The guard in a control room at Iran's notorious Evin prison springs to attention as one by one, monitors in front of him suddenly blink off and display something very different from the surveillance footage he had been watching.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget clash pits moderate Dems against President, Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-c2c1cfd80e7850d32d3387a9e1c05087</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Outnumbered and with their party's most powerful leaders arrayed against them, nine moderate Democrats trying to upend plans for enacting President Joe Biden's multitrillion-dollar domestic program face a House showdown .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborations between Black women sparking golden age for hip-hop...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/Collaborations-between-Black-women-are-sparking-a-16404913.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turn on your car stereo. Or open one of Spotify's top hits playlists. Or peruse your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban warn of 'consequences' if USA extends military presence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/taliban-warned-consequences-us-extends-100037785.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The warning came hours after Biden said the US could extend the withdrawal deadline to help evacuation efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental health online: Police posts of crises may traumatize...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-police-mental-health-41883ccc67210e505e13bdd7aaf4713a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EDITOR’S NOTE — This story includes discussion of suicide. If you or someone you know needs help, please call the National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 1-800-273-8255. The videos are difficult to watch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210823-taiwan-team-says-it-was-told-to-remove-flag-before-le-mans-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan team says it was told to remove flag before Le Mans race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin warns of influx of militants disguised as refugees...</title>
      <link>https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/08/23/putin-warns-of-influx-of-afghan-militants-disguised-as-refugees-a74865</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Who is among these refugees? How can we know?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces crucial moment on Capitol Hill...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/568963-this-week-biden-faces-crucial-moment-on-capitol-hill</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is facing a critical week on Capitol Hill amid Democratic divisions on infrastructure strategy and high-profile criticism over a messy exit in Afghanistan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Topping $50,000 Stirs Forecast of Run Toward Record High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bitcoin-nears-50-000-level-015607040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin topped $50,000 for the first time since May as crypto prices continued an ongoing recovery from a disorderly rout just three months ago.The largest virtual coin advanced 3.8% to $50,272 as of 6:53 a.m. in New York, with other tokens including Ether and Cardano’s ADA also rising. The revival in virtual currencies has excited the animal spirits of the crypto faithful, putting predictions of $100,000 or more for Bitcoin back in vogue. Others see the volatile asset carving out</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY Judges Order Defendants to Get Jab. Can They Do That?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/23/2-new-york-judges-ordered-defendants-to-get-vaccinated-can-they-do-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendant was charged with a number of minor crimes, including drug possession and shoplifting. He was prepared to plead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly firefight erupts at airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/23/deadly-firefight-erupts-at-kabul-airport-as-evacuation-chaos-continues.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The administration is considering extending the deadline for the complete troop withdrawal beyond its original Aug. 31 date, Biden said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds clash in Portland as Proud Boys rally descends into violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/hundreds-clash-portland-proud-boys-055220944.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Colorado River Dries Up, Phoenix Will Have to Survive on Less Water...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/interactive/2021/08/us/colorado-river-water-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado River irrigates farms, powers electric grids and provides drinking water to 40 million people. But as its supply dwindles, a crisis looms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida's peak of delta wave could be days away...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2021/08/22/floridas-peak-of-the-delta-wave-could-be-days-away-university-models-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. — Florida is rapidly approaching the peak of new infections of the delta wave, when the highest single-day counts could come, according to two models created by researchers at Florida…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rev. Jesse Jackson hospitalized with covid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-religion-coronavirus-pandemic-voting-rights-fb8ce99277e00e21189f948b98d15d55</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The Rev. Jesse Jackson, and his wife, Jacqueline, remained under doctors' observation Sunday at a Chicago hospital and were “responding positively to treatments” for COVID-19, their son told The Associated Press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER NFL FAN BRAWL: Woman slaps man in stands, triggering huge fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/3521807/brawl-nfl-game-woman-slaps-man/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DRAMATIC footage shows the moment ANOTHER huge brawl broke out at an NFL match after a woman shouted in a man’s face before slapping him. Chaos erupted in the stands at the Steelers’ pr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four weeks in July: Inside Biden struggle to contain delta...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/four-weeks-in-july-inside-the-biden-administration-e2-80-99s-struggle-to-contain-the-delta-surge/ar-AANA8py?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After declaring ‘independence from a deadly virus’ on July Fourth, Biden and his team were caught flat-footed as the delta crisis spiraled out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump booed at Alabama rally after telling supporters to get vaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/22/trump-booed-at-alabama-rally-after-telling-supporters-to-get-vaccinated.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"But, I recommend take the vaccines," Trump said. "I did it. It's good. Take the vaccines."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon hints at expanded operations in Kabul; Evacuations face new hurdles...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Taliban-co-founder-in-Kabul-for-talks-as-group-16402556.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abdul Ghani Baradar, considered the Taliban's top political leader, arrived in Kabul on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue dogs shot dead in Australia due to restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://www.smh.com.au/national/nsw/rescue-dogs-shot-dead-by-nsw-council-due-to-covid-19-restrictions-20210821-p58ksh.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smh.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several impounded dogs have been shot by a rural council under its interpretation of COVID-19 restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record hour of rainfall in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/tropical-storm-henri-leaving-impressive-rainfall-totals-in-its-wake</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some parts of Central New Jersey could see as much as 10-12 inches of rain as Henri slowly churns its way out of our area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catastrophic...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/catastrophic-flooding-turns-deadly-in-middle-tennessee/1004182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intense and relentless downpours resulted in catastrophic flooding across Middle Tennesse on Saturday, with one location potentially setting a 24-hour rainfall record with more than 17 inches of rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 dead, many missing after 17 inches of rain in Tennessee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/floods-tennessee-d35389e7d661cb1a225ae55af332022e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAVERLY, Tenn. (AP) — At least 22 people were killed and rescue crews searched desperately Sunday amid shattered homes and tangled debris for dozens of people still missing after record-breaking rain sent floodwaters surging through Middle Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov. candidate Allen West 'livid' after wife arrested for suspicion of DWI...</title>
      <link>https://www.wfaa.com/article/news/crime/texas-gov-candidate-allen-west-livid-after-wife-arrested-for-suspicion-of-dwi-denies-she-was-drinking/287-45c46fa3-167b-4a9f-b517-64d628909e26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wfaa.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen West, the former Texas Republican Party chairman, said in an Instagram video Saturday morning that his wife had not been drinking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 dead, 40 missing after extreme floods rock Middle Tennessee...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/08/21/middle-tennessee-nashville-weather-water-rescues-and-flooding/8227162002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens were missing in Middle Tennessee after floods rocked the area including Humphreys, Dickson, Hickman and Houston counties on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RI in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/story/news/local/2021/08/20/emergency-responders-rhode-island-businesses-gird-another-emergency/8211267002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After investing heavily in a summer of relaxed COVID-19 restrictions, officials and business owners prepared for another potential curveball on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Sees Historic Rain...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/national-international/tropical-storm-henri-to-become-hurricane-as-path-tracks-up-east-coast/3229412/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A weakened Tropical Storm Henri made landfall Sunday afternoon along the coast of Rhode Island with maximum sustained winds around 60 mph, though its threats of potentially deadly storm surges and flooding for parts of Long Island and Connecticut remain from over. Henri is expected to slow down and possibly stall near the Connecticut-New York border Sunday night, according to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom could be replaced by candidate with far fewer votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/california-recall-reality-newsom-could-be-replaced-by-candidate-with-far-fewer-votes/ar-AANAV76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal scholars say courts would uphold California's recall law, even if an incumbent were replaced by someone with fewer ballots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban appear to mock Iwo Jima flag raising in latest propaganda push...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2021/08/21/taliban-photo-appears-to-mock-iwo-jima-flag-raising-in-latest-propaganda-push/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban’s media wing has wasted little time releasing droves of new propaganda in the wake of its ascension to power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racehorse bucks jockey, escapes track, takes run in traffic...</title>
      <link>https://www.kentucky.com/sports/horses/article253660718.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kentucky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The riderless horse, Bold and Bossy, could be seen running along a major highway in a video shared on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bombs Gaza in response to violent border clashes...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/middle-east/20210822-israel-bombs-gaza-in-response-to-violent-border-clashes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's military bombed Palestinian militant weapons sites in the Gaza Strip early Sunday in response to a violent demonstration on the perimeter fence that left an Israeli police officer critically…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concert to celebrate end of virus cancelled...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20210822-hurricane-henri-cuts-short-new-york-covid-19-recovery-concert</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This time, Barry Manilow didn’t make it through the rain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Dept hit by cyber attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/state-department-hit-with-cyberattack-in-possible-serious-breach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department is the latest to fall victim to a cyberattack and the notification of a possible serious breach was made by the Department of Defense Cyber Command, a source told Fox News Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot by wife's boyfriend who was secretly living in their home...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox10tv.com/news/mobile_county/creola-man-shot-by-wifes-boyfriend-who-was-secretly-living-in-their-home-deputies-say/article_5e124dbc-ff7a-11eb-98a1-27937bc0160c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox10tv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CREOLA, Ala.--On August 15, 2021 at around 9 p.m., Mobile County Sheriff’s Office responded to a shooting that occurred at home on Skidmore Road in Creola.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprinter Sha'Carri Richardson finishes last in return from substance ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/olympics/story/_/id/32061927/sprinter-shacarri-richardson-finishes-last-100-meters-return-substance-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sha'Carri Richardson ran the 100 meters in 11.14 seconds to finish last and then withdrew from the 200 meters at the Prefontaine Classic. It was her first race since testing positive for a chemical found in marijuana after a win at the Olympic trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half CT could lose power...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/news/article/Hurricane-Henri-powers-toward-Connecticut-but-16403608.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest forecast says Tropical Storm Henri could move west throughout the day and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil Reserve Air Fleet activated; Commercial airlines requested to assist airlift...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/22/biden-administration-activates-civil-reserve-air-fleet.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon on Sunday said it activated the Civil Reserve Air Fleet, ordering U.S. airlines to provide flights for the Afghanistan evacuation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth on escape plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-58297893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The woman went into labour en route to Ramstein Air Base in Germany and gave birth on the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden grapples with twin crises...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/568816-biden-grapples-with-twin-crises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden is grappling with an international crisis involving the fall of the Afghan government and a domestic one in the COVID-19 pandemic, testing the resolve and ability of his young presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm surge threat...</title>
      <link>https://pix11.com/weather/henri-tracking-hurricane-conditions-long-island-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pix11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking update: Tropical Storm Henri made landfall in Rhode Island on Sunday, packing heavy winds and drenching rains as it lashed the northeastern U.S. coastline. Original story: NEW YORK —…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets, subways flood...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/22/hurricane-henri-already-flooding-nyc-streets-subways/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers are starting to feel Hurricane Henri’s impact as cars are left stranded and subway stations flooded ahead of the storm’s arrival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trains, flights canceled...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/21/trains-flights-canceled-as-nyc-braces-for-hurricane-henri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trains were canceled and flights were grounded across the New York City region Saturday as Hurricane Henri made its way up the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside luxurious lives of disgraced, deposed leaders in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/21/inside-the-luxurious-lives-of-disgraced-deposed-leaders-in-dubai/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just days after Ashraf Ghani fled his homeland the former Afghan president emerged in his new safe haven: Dubai, a veritable Disneyland for deposed despots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti faces anger and despair week after quake...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210821140809-dooth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Haiti faces anger and despair a week after quake, fanning security fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakens to tropical storm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tropical-storm-henri-hurricanes-35b9448730d64a02ca81da6cbbd6dc18</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTERLY, R.I. (AP) — Tropical Storm Henri hit the coast of Rhode Island Sunday afternoon, packing high winds that knocked out power to tens of thousands of homes and bands of rain that led to flash flooding from New Jersey to Massachusetts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflicts descend into violence, harassment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-2eba81ebe3bd54b3bcde890b8cf11c70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — The Hawaii lieutenant governor watched in horror as protesters showed up outside his condo, yelled at him through bullhorns and beamed strobe lights into the building to harass him over vaccine requirements.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
