<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brit killed fighting in first UK casualty...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5221967/brit-killed-fighting-russian-troops-ukraine-another-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BRIT has been killed “fighting Russian troops” in Ukraine and another one is missing. It is believed the two soldiers were volunteers to Ukraine’s army although it has not been …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen says more shocks likely to challenge economy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-business-europe-economy-janet-yellen-356153601cd404a0967c26e7a50875ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen said Thursday the global pandemic and Russia’s invasion of Ukraine highlight the possibility of big economic shocks in the future, adding that downturns are “likely to continue to challenge the economy.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women fed up with flagrant sexism could swing Australia's election...</title>
      <link>https://gazette.com/ap/international/women-fed-up-with-flagrant-sexism-could-swing-australia-s-election/article_ace294c9-df69-57a9-add9-f06a1eafa576.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women in Australia have endured more than a year of shocking allegations of misconduct from inside their nation’s parliament revealing a culture that has normalized sexual violence and humiliation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean tweets from inside House? Incivility up among politicians...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mean-tweets-coming-inside-house-130040342.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that tweets by members of Congress have grown more uncivil over the last decade. Researchers attribute the change in part to how Twitter incentivizes mean tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: TESLA stock slide puts Musk's TWITTER deal in jeopardy...</title>
      <link>https://boingboing.net/2022/04/28/tesla-stock-slide-puts-musks-twitter-deal-in-jeopardy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boingboing.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla stock fell 20% in a week, wiping some $125bn from the company’s value as its CEO Elon Musk instead worked on shitposting and his quixotic plan to buy Twitter. As the deal he struck depe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Wall St's stars, Big Tech falls back to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-economy-ea18403e71a0b45a5fdbd22e3c32491f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Trump vs. Cruz in Ohio and Pa. Senate races...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/28/cruz-trump-gop-endorsements-senate-00028381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the former president makes endorsements directly at odds with the Texas senator, there's plenty of GOP intrigue over how that affects those races — and the futures of the once political rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal braces for less water, browner landscape...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cannot-afford-green-lawns-southern-120044900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large portions of Southern California are being told to water outdoors just one day a week. And a total watering ban could be imposed by fall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkinson's Patient First In World To Receive rain Implant That Reverses Symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.braintomorrow.com/2022/04/27/parkinsons-brain-implant-reverses-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.braintomorrow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A British hospital is the first in the world to implant a brain device that reverses the symptoms of Parkinson's disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House proposes plan to sell oligarch yachts for Ukraine aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/white-house-russian-assets-ukraine-aid-1db28a96-c31b-48b9-bf3f-23f034b26884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. has already seized million of dollars in assets from wealthy Russians with close ties to Putin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk criticism of TWITTER staff sparks backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20220428-elon-musk-s-criticism-of-twitter-staff-sparks-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's criticism of Twitter Inc TWTR.N sparked a barrage of abusive tweets against the company's top lawyer on Wednesday, raising questions about his compliance with a non-disparagement agreement…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowden Revealed As Key Participant In Mysterious Ceremony Creating Anonymous Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeldelcastillo/2022/04/27/edward-snowden-revealed-as-key-participant-in-mysterious-ceremony-creating-2-billion-anonymous-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notorious whistle-blower acknowledges he was the sixth person who participated in an elaborate 2016 ceremony that led to the creation of zcash, a leading privacy protecting cryptocurrency now valued at $2 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Faces New Challenge From Anti-Immigration Firebrand...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/erdogan-faces-new-challenge-from-anti-immigration-firebrand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Erdogan Faces New Challenge From Anti-Immigration Firebrand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year after disappearing, informant in Trump probe found dead at high school...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/one-disappearing-federal-informant-found-193441709.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The body of an informant who helped federal authorities investigating Deutsche Bank's dealings with former President Trump is found at an L.A. school.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New plaintiff claims LIBERTY U mishandled sex assault report...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2022-04-27/liberty-university-sexual-assault-lawsuit-5823465.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit claims that the school has a pattern of weaponizing the student code of conduct against victims of sexual assault by leading them to fear that reporting an incident will get them in trouble for violating campus rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports of Kids' Mysterious Liver Ailment Expand in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/reports-of-kids-mysterious-liver-ailment-expand-in-us/ar-AAWEYc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee lawmaker suggests burning banned books...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/state-watch/3469350-tennessee-lawmaker-on-books-he-objects-to-i-would-burn-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Tennessee state lawmaker said he would “burn” books taken out of school libraries during an exchange with another state lawmaker who asked what he proposed doing with the objectionabl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yen's Historic Fall Signals Rewrite of Global Currency Playbook...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/yen-historic-fall-signals-rewrite-074224479.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The yen’s plunge to a 20-year low threatens to leave it significantly weaker for years to come, shaking up global money flows and undermining Japan’s efforts to get its fragile economy back on track.Most Read from BloombergFour European Gas Buyers Made Ruble Payments to RussiaAmazon’s Twitch Seeks to Revamp Creator Pay With Focus on ProfitRussia to Cut Gas to Poland, Bulgaria Until Pay Demands MetA Powerful Dynasty Bankrupted Sri Lanka in Just 30 MonthsRussia to Cut Gas to Poland</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In El Salvador, President Cracks Down on Civil Liberties, and Is Beloved for It...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/28/in-el-salvador-the-president-cracks-down-on-civil-liberties-and-is-beloved-for-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TONACATEPEQUE, El Salvador — It has been four weeks since the shoemaker vanished from his hometown, hauled away in handcuffs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heart-Pounding Supercar Aims to Upend How Vehicles Built...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/28/a-heart-pounding-supercar-aims-to-upend-how-cars-are-built/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Czinger 21C is a decadent supercar designed to get car enthusiasts aflutter on social media. It has serpentine curves,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears Mounting War Will Spill Across Borders...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/27/fears-are-mounting-that-ukraine-war-will-spill-across-borders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — For nine weeks, President Biden and the Western allies have emphasized the need to keep the war for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Swaps Prisoner With Russia in Surprise Sign of Cooperation...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5212550/trevor-reed-exchanged-russian-pilot-konstantin-yaroshenko-prison-swap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORMER US Marine Trevor Reed has been exchanged for Russian pilot Konstantin Yaroshenko in a prison swap. The exchange took place in Turkey on Wednesday, reports say. Reed was arrested in Moscow in…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious attacks in Transnistria add further intrigue to Ukraine war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mysterious-attacks-in-transnistria-add-further-intrigue-to-ukraine-war/ar-AAWG5kY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood and bruises: Welcome to Bangkok's real-life fight club...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-sg/news/world/blood-and-bruises-welcome-to-bangkok-s-real-life-fight-club/ar-AAWFZdB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Musk Still Afford TWITTER After TESLA Wipe Out?</title>
      <link>https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2022-04-26/tesla-loses-126-billion-in-value-amid-musk-twitter-deal-funding-concern</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COKE CEO becomes first target in activist shareholder's busy week: 'Woke-a-Cola'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/coca-cola-ceo-becomes-first-target-in-activist-shareholders-busy-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Activist shareholder group the National Legal and Policy Center is presenting a flurry of resolutions to corporate boards this week. Their first target was Coca-Cola CEO James Quincey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phone Number on GOOGLE? Search Giant Now Takes Removal Demands...</title>
      <link>https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2022-04-27/your-phone-number-on-google-search-giant-now-takes-removal-demands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew STRIPPED of York title after fury over rape case settlement...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5215375/prince-andrew-stripped-of-york-title/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew has been stripped of another honour after the city of York agreed to remove his title as Honorary Freeman. The underfire royal was given the freedom of the city of York in a lavish ce…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's responsible for $2B debt?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10759917/Reedy-Creek-chiefs-meet-time-Ron-DeSantis-stripped-Disney-special-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Wednesday morning, Reedy Creek officials seemed just as confused as everyone else about what will come next. The district's 400 employees could lose their jobs and benefits next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions hit Transnistria: Is war spreading?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-61233095</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mysterious explosions in Transnistria raise fears that the Ukraine conflict may spread to Moldova.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY in dark about Florida move to dissolve self-govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/disney-in-the-dark-about-florida-move-to-dissolve-self-government/ar-AAWFBKE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin Keeps Trying to Call Zelensky Drug Addict...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gpd3/russia-zelenskyy-drug-addict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“If Russians believe lies on Russian TV, why not believe this?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to skip eating portion to limit risk...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3469215-biden-to-skip-eating-portion-of-correspondents-dinner-to-limit-covid-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will take added precautions while at the White House Correspondents’ Association Dinner this weekend amid concerns about exposure to COVID-19, but White House press secretary …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN WARNS HE'LL NUKE WEST</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5213926/putin-warns-nukes-west/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VLADIMIR Putin has warned he will use nuclear weapons against the West if anyone interferes in Ukraine. The threat comes as the Russian leader said the response to counterstrikes will be “lig…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoCal's biggest water supplier limit irrigation to day per week...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/socal-s-biggest-water-supplier-to-limit-outdoor-irrigation-to-one-day-per-week-starting-june-1/ar-AAWEHV0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge knocks down Elon's bid to end SEC consent decree...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/27/judge-knocks-down-elon-musks-bid-to-end-sec-consent-decree.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Lewis J. Liman shot down an argument Musk attorneys made suggesting that the settlement agreement had chilled the CEO's rights to free speech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAYPAL shuttering San Fran office...</title>
      <link>https://techcrunch.com/2022/04/27/paypal-shuttering-its-san-francisco-office/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techcrunch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PayPal is closing its San Francisco office on June 3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBAT DOLPHINS DEPLOYED</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2022/04/27/trained-russian-navy-dolphins-are-protecting-black-sea-naval-base-satellite-photos-show</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has deployed trained dolphins during its invasion of Ukraine to protect a Black Sea naval base, USNI News has learned. The Russian Navy has placed two dolphin pens at the entrance to Sevastopol harbor, sheltered just inside a sea wall. The pens were moved there in February, around the time of the invasion of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Scott to Make First Festival Performance Year After Astroworld...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/travis-scott-to-make-first-festival-performance-one-year-after-astroworld-tragedy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travis Scott has announced his first music festival appearance since last year's Astroworld Festival tragedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: CDC, FDA 'altered' guidance under political pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10759403/CDC-FDA-altered-Covid-guidance-pressure-bombshell-report-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal investigators spoke to more than two dozen top-level directors and managers who worked at the agencies behind the country's public health guidance that aimed to keep Americans safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Champion looter' sends ton of stolen goods home to wife...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/russias-champion-looter-sends-almost-500-kg-of-stolen-goods-home-to-his-wife-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don feared 'dangerous' fruits could be thrown at him by protesters...</title>
      <link>https://africa.businessinsider.com/politics/donald-trump-worried-dangerous-fruits-could-be-thrown-at-him-by-protesters-a-new/z50lnrf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;africa.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump said pineapples, tomatoes, bananas, stuff like that could be thrown at him at protests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  Jared Polis, Most Libertarian Gov in America?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/podcast/2022/04/25/jared-polis-the-most-libertarian-governor-in-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colorado's Jared Polis might be the most libertarian governor in America, at a time when his big-state Democratic colleagues are...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronic Shortages Of Few Items Will Evolve Into Hundreds?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/chronic-shortages-few-items-now-will-evolve-chronic-shortages-hundreds-products-later</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAKING THE PFIZER PILL...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10758917/Kamala-Harris-treated-Pfizers-Paxlovid-pills-testing-positive-COVID.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her press secretary Kirsten Allen said in a statement that Harris - who is fully-vaccinated and double boosted - received positive rapid and PCR test results after returning from a week in California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell Phone Radiation Driving Alzheimer's Spike?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cell-phone-radiation-alzheimers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say excessive cell phone use and even Wi-Fi radiation can lead to increases in intracellular calcium levels in the brain -- another hallmark of the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans give McCarthy standing ovation, brush off tapes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/house/3468729-house-republicans-give-mccarthy-standing-ovation-brush-off-tapes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy (R-Calif.) got a standing ovation in a Wednesday House GOP conference meeting after he addressed leaked recordings of his comments in the aftermath of Jan. 6, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bizarre Prophet Rumored to Have Putin's Ear...</title>
      <link>https://www.thebulwark.com/aleksandr-dugin-putin-brain-russian-prophet-bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thebulwark.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aleksandr Dugin hates America and is obsessed with Nazis, the occult, and the end times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Robbery in Front of FBI HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/thief-armed-robbery-fbi-hq-1701293</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brazen thief carried out an armed robbery right under the FBI's nose — with an audacious hold-up just outside the agency's headquarters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly half of Israelis fear second Holocaust is coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/article-705210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poll, which found that women and the ultra-Orthodox are more worried about another Holocaust, was conducted just days ahead of Holocaust Remembrance Day, starting Wednesday evening, April 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wine-loving nun named world's oldest person!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/worlds-oldest-person-french-nun-sister-andre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sister André, born Lucile Randon, has lived through two world wars, the 1918 influenza pandemic, and even survived a COVID-19 infection last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interstellar Meteor Crashed to Earth. Astronomer Wants to See If Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gpv3/an-interstellar-meteor-crashed-to-earth-this-astronomer-wants-to-see-if-its-aliens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The meteor that crashed into the Pacific was confirmed to be interstellar by secret government data. Harvard astronomer Avi Loeb wants to recover it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  KAMALA COVID 'NO SYMPTOMS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/harris-tests-positive-covid-a3953375-2285-4789-bf7a-3edd035089d2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is fully vaccinated and received a booster dose in October.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
