<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>3-legged dog with cancer jumps into river to save baby otter...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansascity.com/news/nation-world/national/article260719512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansascity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“First time swimming with three legs and he comes out of the water with a baby otter in his mouth.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE PEN DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/marine-le-pen-fighter-suffering-190552478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marine Le Pen, who on Sunday lost the second round of France's presidential election to Emmanuel Macron, had fought hard to make her far-right party electable but in the end failed by a wide margin to win over a majority of voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE BLOWOUT! LE LANDSLIDE!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-le-pen-france-faces-001327854.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (Reuters) -French President Emmanuel Macron defeated his far-right rival Marine Le Pen on Sunday by a comfortable margin, securing a second term and heading off what would have been a political earthquake. European leaders also welcomed the news that pro-European Union Macron and not nationalist eurosceptic Le Pen had won. "I am very relieved - it had looked very close and populism was at our door," 42-year old Alessandro Paleni told Reuters at the Macron rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LE PEN DEFIANT...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/macron-wins-key-quotes-frances-181942066.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Emmanuel Macron triumphed over his far-right rival Marine Le Pen by a comfortable margin in France's election on Sunday, winning a second term and heading off what would have been a political earthquake. Even so, the far right scored its highest ever score in a presidential election. Marine Le Pen, defeated far-right challenger:"Tonight's result is in itself a remarkable victory (for us)."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeological dig in Turkey uncovers massive underground city...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/article-704928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers believe the underground city may be the largest in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ allows cops to smoke pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-legal-cannabis-off-duty-police-officers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey's attorney general says the state's new legal weed law doesn't prohibit cops from using cannabis while off-duty. But the mayor of Jersey City said he will fire any cop who tests positive at any time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN:  'He's a liar and a traitor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/warren-says-kevin-mccarthy-liar-traitor-0b4583d9-5a3e-48cd-a085-75361873be8e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Massachusetts Democrat was asked about audio of the GOP leader saying he planned to urge President Trump to resign over the Jan. 6 riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220424-live-follow-the-results-of-france-s-presidential-election-run-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French voters went to the polls on Sunday for the presidential election run-off pitting incumbent Emmanuel Macron against far-right National Rally candidate Marine Le Pen. FRANCE 24 brings you real-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French presidential finale... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-french-election-voting-results-f5b549e3b99930ee05bed17a9d3870b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — From bucolic villages to humming cities, French voters on Sunday were choosing between two radically different futures for their country, with President Emmanuel Macron offering a centrist pro-European outlook if he is reelected while far-right challenger Marine Le Pen is pledging seismic changes for France and its allies if she becomes the country's first female leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm in Brussels as shock Pen victory would 'spell end of EU'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/18318364/france-election-le-pen-victory-eu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALARM bells are ringing in Brussels over fears a shock victory for Marine Le Pen today in today’s French presidential election could “spell the end of the EU as we know it”. The r…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Royals Selling Homes, Yachts, Art as Crown Prince Cuts Income...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/saudi-royals-are-selling-homes-yachts-and-art-as-crown-prince-cuts-income-11650801706282.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kingdom’s senior princes are trying to raise cash and avoid scrutiny from Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21,800 invading troops 'liquidated'...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1600252/ukraine-live-vladimir-putin-russian-investigation-sas-deployed-russia-war-updates-Zelensky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE'S resistance against Moscow's military had been "strong across all axes" and numerous Russian assaults along the line of contact in Donbas this week have been repelled, according to the latest UK intelligence update.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why more people of color buying guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/guns-firearms-people-of-color-7f2ef104-35cd-4e9e-902e-c910958454f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gun ownership is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Rampage: Knifeman screams 'we must kill Macron' then stabs priest &amp; nun...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1600320/French-election-attack-Nice-church-stabbing-priest-nun-France-Saint-Pierre-d-Ar-ne-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A KNIFEMAN reportedly screamed "we have to kill Macron" as he stabbed a priest and a nun inside a church on election day in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged after allegedly threatening MERRIAM-WEBSTER over gender definitions...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/23/us/jeremy-david-hanson-charged-merriam-webster-threats/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California man was arrested this week after he allegedly sent threatening online messages to the Merriam-Webster company over dictionary definitions containing references to gender identity, according to court documents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Man Married Fictional Character. He'd Like You to Hear Him Out...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/24/this-man-married-a-fictional-character-hed-like-you-to-hear-him-out/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO — In almost every way, Akihiko Kondo is an ordinary Japanese man. He’s pleasant and easy to talk to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic recovery slows to crawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/24/investing/stocks-week-ahead/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors are gearing up for a week of big ticket economic data, including a first look at economic growth between January and March and more inflation numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid increasing abuse, officials flee youth sports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-sports-health-youth-football-5db4156110f035c65bbcf3f5981dc576</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — When one looks at the ugly bruise encircling Kristi Moore's left eye, it's not surprising so many refs and umps are hanging up their stripes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metal Barriers Go Up Around Town...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-china-pandemics-shanghai-2e2a27baef0e6dd2be4d30344b890260</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — Volunteers and low-level government workers in Shanghai have erected metal barriers in multiple districts to block off small streets and entrances to apartment complexes, as China hardens its strict “zero-COVID” approach in the metropolis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK braces for what comes next...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/apr/23/meta-earnings-report-preview-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After losing a record $230bn in market value due to a disappointing earnings report in February, analysts are hoping to see progress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social bans ads that 'contradict science on climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/nation-world/2022/04/23/twitter-bans-ads-that-contradict-science-on-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There was no indication that the change would affect what users post on the social media site, which has been targeted by groups seeking to promote misleading claims about climate change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Chancellor Who Became Putin's Man in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/23/the-former-chancellor-who-became-putins-man-in-germany/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HANOVER, Germany — On the evening of Dec. 9, 2005, 17 days after Gerhard Schröder left office as chancellor of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing anti-sex movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2022/apr/24/eva-wiseman-the-ghost-of-mary-whitehouse-and-the-new-anti-sex-backlash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From Mary Whitehouse to the new ‘puriteens’, there is a growing anti-sex movement gathering pace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felons turned firefighters find new lives on front lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/24/us/felon-firefighters-california/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Reyna peeled off protective gear at the firefighter Ventura Training Center (VTC), and reflected on dark days in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXXON Bans Pride Banner From Flagpoles...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/business/article/Exxon-Bans-Outside-Flags-Like-the-Pride-Banner-17121869.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exxon Mobil will no longer allow banners of outside organizations on its flagpoles,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Husband-Wife MAGA Murder Saga Descended Into Chaos...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/husband-wife-maga-murder-saga-235345919.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast/Chaffee County Sheriff’s Office/GettyFor about 12 months, Colorado law enforcement was steadfast in alleging that Barry Morphew murdered his wife of 26 years after learning she had a torrid extramarital love affair, disposed of her body, and staged a fake bike crash to throw off investigators.Prosecutors last May filed several charges against Morphew, which offered shocking details about how the 53-year-old allegedly planned and covered up Suz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If Highway Could Charge Electric Vehicles?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/highway-could-charge-electric-vehicle-031345605.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Luis G. Rendon/The Daily Beast/GettyPeople avoid buying electric vehicles out of fear. Many worry the charging infrastructure isn’t adequate, that they’ll get stranded between charging stations—a concern known as range anxiety. But now a pilot program in Michigan could ease that tension.Next spring, the nation’s first mile of public road that can charge electric vehicles as they drive over it will go online in Detroit.A joint venture between the Michigan Department of Trans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overdoses, not Covid, drive spike in LA homeless deaths...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-health-pandemics-public-mental-638c602c8d32948f0b008845ae08ec58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Nearly 2,000 homeless people died in Los Angeles County during the first year of the pandemic, an increase of 56% from the previous year, driven mainly by drug overdoses, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commander hints at greater ambitions...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/europe/2022-04-23/commander-hints-at-russian-ambitions-beyond-ukraine-5773317.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian commander said Friday that Moscow wants to take “full control” of eastern and southern Ukraine, in part so it could have a path to neighboring Moldova — raising fears that the nearly two-month war could spill outside of Ukrainian borders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blunders Open Door to Primary Challengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/ma-2657202480/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a report from the Wall Street Journal, Rep. Madison Cawthorn's re-election is no longer a certainty as North Carolina Republican voters who supported him in 2020 are looking elsewhere because he's more interested in grandstanding than he is in serving their needs.While the Republican no...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chippendales stripping down, lobbying up...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/22/chippendales-lobbying-covid-relief-00027202</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The iconic male stripper group has hired a lobby shop for the first time. It wants pandemic relief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVASION ENTERS 3RD MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/24/russia-ukraine-live-updates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine entered its third month on Sunday, a conflict that has killed thousands and led to the worst refugeeÂ crisisÂ Europe has seen sinceÂ World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE BRACES</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220424-live-polls-open-across-france-as-macron-and-le-pen-vie-for-french-presidency </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why U-HAULs all have AZ license plates...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/23/business/uhaul-rental-trucks-license-plates-arizona/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are around 175,000 white and orange U-Haul rental trucks in the United States and Canada for do-it-yourself movers. And they all have something strange in common: Arizona license plates with the word "apportioned" slapped on them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  MACRON IN LEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10747337/Emmanuel-Macron-course-BEAT-far-right-rival-Marine-Le-Pen-French-presidential-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polls predicted a narrow lead for Emmanuel Macron when campaigning ended Friday, with the incumbent ahead of far-right Marine Le Pen by 56.6 per cent to 43.5 per cent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Only 29% hospitalized covid patients fully well one year on...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/world/covid-19-only-29-percent-hospitalised-patients-fully-well-one-year-2643796</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS: Not even one in three people have completely recovered from COVID-19 a full year after being hospitalised with the disease, a United Kingdom study indicated on Sunday (Apr 24), warning that long COVID could become a common condition. The study involving more than 2,300 people als</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC commish slams Tim Cook for hypocrisy over China censorship, human rights...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/22/fccs-brendan-carr-slams-apples-tim-cook-for-china-hypocrisy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FCC Commissioner Brendan Carr detailed his concerns about the tech giant’s activities in China policies in a letter that referenced Cook’s recent keynote address.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Brazil holds first carnival since pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/much-joy-brazil-holds-first-092938463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio de Janeiro's carnival, a glittering, sequin-studded festival of the flesh, exploded back to life Friday with the first famed samba school parades since Covid-19 hit Brazil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp in starring role at defamation trial...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnny-depp-starring-role-defamation-012040969.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testy at times, rambling and poetic at others, Johnny Depp has embraced a familiar role at his defamation trial against his former wife Amber Heard -- the leading man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing warns of 'grim' situation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-covid-death-toll-rises-024240149.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shanghai reported 39 Covid deaths Sunday, official data showed, its highest daily toll since a weeks-long lockdown started, while China's capital Beijing warned of a "grim" situation with rising infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild testimony; Wild cross-examination...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/amber-heard-johnny-depp-entertainment-arts-and-lawsuits-3a82a135d9e019b7bf3865759ce4e05b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For three days, Johnny Depp has been testifying in a libel trial that, at least in theory, is about whether Amber Heard defamed him in a 2018 newspaper op-ed. The trial has turned into a spectacle in which Depp has testified about everything from taking pills as a child to a near mental breakdown in which the actor said he used his severed finger to write on the walls in his own blood to recount his ex-wife’s alleged lies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 suicides among sailors from same ship raises mental health concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/least-five-uss-george-washington-233059478.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least five U.S. sailors who served on the same aircraft carrier in Virginia have died by suicide in the last year, including three who died within a week earlier this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Commander hints at Russian ambitions beyond invasion...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/2022/04/22/russian-ambition-beyond-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The comments from Rustam Minnekayev, deputy commander of Russia’s Central Military District, suggested that the Kremlin wants to conquer wide swaths of its neighbor’s land, and potentially threaten the nations that lie beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Russia social media accounts spread fake Zelensky cocaine video...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/pro-russia-social-media-accounts-fake-zelensky-cocaine-video-1342178/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shallow fake video continues years-long smear against Ukrainian president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House readies for tough probes that would follow a Republican takeover...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-readies-for-tough-probes-that-would-follow-a-gop-takeover/ar-AAWuTnr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Response Shows Trump Republican Stranglehold...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mccarthy-rapid-response-to-audio-shows-trump-s-gop-stranglehold/ar-AAWvRPp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK CLAIM:  World to run out of food in 27 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/domesday-prediction-says-world-run-26781642</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Scientists have issued a terrifying warning and have said the world could be left starving without any food in just over two decades, according to a chilling doomsday countdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Republican headache...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10729375/Fired-Madison-Cawthorn-aide-claims-liquor-water-office-rips-liar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a leaked 16-minute phone call published by an anti-Cawthorn group, the former staffer describes jaw-dropping conditions in the lawmaker's one North Carolina office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Reports Record Daily Deaths in Current Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/china/shanghai-reports-record-daily-covid-deaths-in-current-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shanghai Reports Record Daily Covid Deaths in Current Outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines Substitute Buses for Planes as Pilot Shortage Persists...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/u-s-airline-pilot-shortage-crimping-summer-route-ramp-up-plans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines Substitute Buses for Planes as Pilot Shortage Persists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STREAMING IS BLEEDING:  NETFLIX Becomes Takeover Target...</title>
      <link>https://theankler.com/p/pod-netflix-becomes-a-takeover-target?s=r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theankler.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Listen now (35 min) | Media analyst Rich Greenfield also names a familiar top executive who should join the streamer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion clinic on Tex-Mex border faces unique legal  challenges...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/abortion-clinic-texas-mexico-border-legal-and-cultural-challenges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as Texas has tightened its laws surrounding abortion, Mexico has gone the opposite direction, compelling people to seek potentially less-safe procedures south of the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picture of Depp passed out with ice cream dribbling down his legs shown to court...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5185707/johnny-depp-ice-cream-dribbling-legs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN IMAGE of Johnny Depp “passed out” with ice cream dribbling down his legs has been shown to the court during his defamation trial with Amber Heard. The actor claimed the embarrassing …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe to slap new regulations on Big Tech, beating USA to the punch...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/europe-to-slap-new-regulations-on-big-tech-beating-us-to-the-punch/ar-AAWuRJE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai Reports Record Daily Deaths in Current Outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.ibtimes.com/shanghai-reports-12-new-covid-deaths-frustrations-boil-over-3482682</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ibtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The major financial hub of Shanghai reported 12 new COVID-19 related deaths on April 22, up from 11 the previous day, as frustrations among residents continued to boil over amid a harsh lockdown and strict censorship online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Musk Bids For TWITTER, His Fight to Tweet Freely Hits Snag...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/as-musk-bids-for-twitter-his-fight-to-tweet-freely-hits-snag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mickey's $578 Million Tax Break Left Untouched in Feud...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/disney-578-million-tax-break-170000800.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Florida Governor Ron DeSantis may have put a bull’s-eye on special perks that Walt Disney Co. has enjoyed in his state for more than 50 years, but he’s keeping his hands off hundreds of millions of dollars in tax breaks recently lavished on the entertainment giant.Most Read from BloombergUkraine Latest: Zelenskiy Says Blinken, Austin Will Visit KyivUkraine Latest: UN Chief to Meet Zelenskiy, Putin Next WeekI Modeled For Abercrombie. Netflix’s ‘White Hot’ Doc Is AccurateThe Second</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orrin Hatch dead at 88...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/philanthropy-utah-mitt-romney-confirmation-hearings-clarence-thomas-eb5c864b40e5d3a60de7077a9504b5cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — Orrin G. Hatch, who became the longest-serving Republican senator in history as he represented Utah for more than four decades, died Saturday at age 88. His death was announced in a statement from his foundation, which did not specify a cause.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
