<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brain sensor discovery behind humans getting taller...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/health-59140359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists say they've worked out how the body knows when to grow and start puberty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerusalem tests massive inflatable missile detection system...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-israel-militant-groups-hamas-3dc07c50c9f24582bc0562bbd5cb4e5b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel said Wednesday it has begun testing a massive inflatable missile detection system designed to hover at high altitudes and detect long-range threats. Israel already boasts an array of sophisticated missile defenses, which were used successfully during the 11-day Gaza war this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violent crime continues to surge city...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/violent-crime-continues-to-surge-in-nyc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the NYPD touts a drop in shootings and murders, newly released crime statistics show a continuing growth in other violent crimes including felony assaults and robberies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANKS: Bezos Asked Me To Go To Space Before Shatner -- But Wanted $28 Million!</title>
      <link>https://comicbook.com/movies/news/tom-hanks-jeff-bezos-asked-space-before-william-shatner-28-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;comicbook.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Hanks was offered to go to space with Jeff Bezos, but he didn't want to pay for it. The movie [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers outraged as man caught giving a TATTOO on plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/travel/3989239/passenger-shaming-tattoo-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PASSENGER left travellers stunned after he was caught giving a friend a TATTOO during a flight. The man was caught using a tattoo gun while the plane was landing. The video was posted by Instagra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX toilet leak will force NASA astronauts to wear diapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/spacex-toilet-leak-force-nasa-25368420</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four astronauts could be in for a squelchy ride home due to a leaky toilet onboard SpaceX's Crew Dragon capsule - NASA says they will have to wear special 'undergarments' instead of using the loo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA adds Israeli maker of PEGASUS spyware to 'black list'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/us-blacklists-4-companies-from-israel-russia-singapore-citing-spyware-683917</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Israeli companies, NSO Group - the focus of an international investigation in July - and Candiru, were put on the US's list of companies that engage in harmful activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW Shares Plunge as Investors Digest Home-Flipping Halt...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/zillow-shares-plunge-investors-digest-133814435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Zillow Group Inc. shares plunged on Wednesday as investors digested the news that the company was pulling the plug on its tech-powered home-flipping operation.Most Read from BloombergSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItChina’s Climate Goals Hinge on a $440 Billion Nuclear BuildoutInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’Results on Key Ballot Initiatives, From Policing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquakes haunt tiny SCarolina community. What's causing tremors?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/earthquakes-haunt-tiny-south-carolina-community-whats-causing-the-tremors/ar-AAQgDm0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. — Minor earthquakes that have gently shaken the ground north of Columbia during the past week are occurring in an area where construction of a lake four decades ago is suspected of causing a rash of tremors through the years. Since engineers built Lake Monticello in 1978, geologists have recorded thousands of earthquakes that, for the most part, are too small for people to ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden returns from Europe to turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-returns-from-europe-to-democratic-turmoil-over-virginia-election-loss/ar-AAQgBiI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After hobnobbing with global leaders in Europe, President Biden faces a crush of political challenges upon his return home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin positioning for presidential run?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/579738-is-joe-manchin-positioning-for-a-presidential-run</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West Virginia senator has shown himself to be a strong and fearless advocate for moderate, bipartisan politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cargo thefts spike as backlog of container ships continues to grow...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/03/cargo-thefts-spike-as-container-ship-backlog-continues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thieves made off with more than $5 million worth of goods as a result of so-called supply-chain theft in California during the third quarter of 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine passes nation's 1st 'right to food' amendment...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-2021-maine-right-to-food-605019e60df5b3e32bc70c86dcf957b3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Maine (AP) — Maine voters passed the nation’s first “right to food” constitutional amendment on Tuesday. A statewide referendum asked voters if they favored an amendment to the Maine Constitution “to declare that all individuals have a natural, inherent and unalienable right to grow, raise, harvest, produce and consume the food of their own choosing for their own nourishment, sustenance, bodily health and well-being.” It was an experiment not tried before by any state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Breakups More Emotionally Painful For Men...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/breaking-up-more-pain-men/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers find men were more likely to discuss the heartbreak ending a relationship caused than women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Game-changer' blood test that detects 50 types of cancer set to roll out...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10158341/Game-changer-blood-test-detect-50-different-types-cancer-set-roll-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Galleri test, which can detect 50 types of cancer using only a blood test, will become available in the U.S. soon. The test only requires two vials of blood and get a person results in ten days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Is this really green?' Fight over solar farms in Mojave Desert...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/is-this-really-green-the-fight-over-solar-farms-in-the-mojave-desert/ar-AAQgzTn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mojave Desert is prime real estate for carbon-cutting solar farms. Not all environmentalists are on board.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZILLOW laying off quarter of staff...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/business-a-lobbying/579772-zillow-laying-off-one-quarter-of-its-staff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Real estate website Zillow will lay off nearly one-quarter of its staff as it prepares to stop buying and selling homes, according t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese tennis star's sex allegation against former top leader prompts online blackout...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/china-peng-shuai-zhang-gaoli-metoo/2021/11/03/79c0f308-3c4f-11ec-bd6f-da376f47304e_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Censors have scrubbed mentions of the accusations by Peng Shuai against former vice premier Zhang Gaoli.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Marines force American troops into humiliating surrender just days into training exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10159949/Royal-Marines-commandos-force-troops-humiliating-surrender-training-exercise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American combatants asked for a 'reset' halfway through a five-day simulated war exercise against Royal Marines in southern California.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diana Ross teases first music video in decade...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211103110006-2f0ak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSIC-DIANA ROSS/ (TV, PIX):Singer Diana Ross teases first music video in over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it thwarts U.S. attempt to 'steal' oil in Sea of Oman...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/iranian-state-tv-says-iran-thwarts-us-attempt-steal-oil-sea-oman-2021-11-03/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran's elite Revolutionary Guards foiled an attempt by the United States to "steal" the Islamic Republic's oil in the Sea of Oman, Iranian state TV reported on Wednesday, saying the incident took place recently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to hear biggest gun rights case in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/supreme-court-hear-biggest-gun-rights-case-more-decade-n1282583</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both sides hope the court will clarify how much protection the Second Amendment provides for carrying a gun outside the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Newman Will Tell Own Story, 14 Years After His Death...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/03/paul-newman-will-tell-his-own-story-14-years-after-his-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Decades ago, the actor and philanthropist Paul Newman, frustrated by all the unauthorized biographies and coverage of his life, recorded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta's Braves Win World Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/32522726/world-series-2021-atlanta-baby-braves-all-grown-now-mlb-champions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Baby Braves are all grown up! Here's how Atlanta's young core helped bring home the team's first championship since 1995.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bragg Elected Manhattan's First Black DA, Will Take Over Probe Into Trump...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/02/voters-to-elect-new-manhattan-da-will-be-just-the-4th-person-to-hold-the-office-in-80-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bragg, a civil rights lawyer and former federal prosecutor, defeated Republican Thomas Kenniff to join a growing wave of progressive, reform-minded prosecutors across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both parties win in special election for OH House seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-special-elections/ohio-house-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Governor Race CLOSER than expecteed... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-elections/new-jersey-governor-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER STOCK DOWN FOR YEAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/quotes/TWTR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get Twitter Inc (TWTR:NYSE) real-time stock quotes, news, price and financial information from CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Middle School Teacher's Wild Political Rant Recorded By Student; Goes Off On  Biden, Sex, Vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/01/exclusive-middle-school-teacher-draws-criticism-for-comments-on-hunter-biden-presidential-election-and-vaccines-in-classroom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident occurred two weeks ago and was recorded by an eighth grader in the teacher's classroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Average Child Now Spends 8 Hours Day Looking At Screens!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/childrens-screen-time-doubled/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show adolescents are, on average, looking at screens for recreation for 7.7 hours a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Boosts Quarterly Borrowing Estimate to $1 Trillion...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-treasury-boosts-quarterly-borrowing-190000895.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. Treasury increased its estimate of federal borrowing needs for the three months through December after it ran down its stockpile of cash more than it previously anticipated.Most Read from BloombergInto the Metaverse: Where Crypto, Gaming and Capitalism CollideSupply Chain Crisis Risks Taking the Global Economy Down With ItAtlanta’s Crowded Election Pits Former Mayor Versus ‘Anyone But’Can a New Mayor Fix Seattle’s Downtown?In Minneapolis Election, the Future of Policing I</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEM DOWN IN VA</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/election-day-2021-mcauliffe-youngkin-biden-trump-a84bf1d7f2113c77197bca103fd0e81b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. (AP) — Polls were closing Tuesday night in the nation’s most closely watched off-year election as Virginia voters chose between Democrat Terry McAuliffe and Republican Glenn Youngkin in a campaign that became partly a referendum on President Joe Biden’s first year in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2021-elections/virginia-governor-results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayoral candidate caught illegally parking, driving on sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/nyc-mayoral-candidate-eric-adams-caught-illegally-parking-driving-on-a-sidewalk-and-actually-entering-his-brooklyn-apartment-in-wild-stakeout-by-new-york-magazine-reporters/ar-AAQfnaz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A reporter saw Adams "climb into the car from the passenger side, shimmy into the driver's seat, then drive the car up onto the sidewalk."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jellyfish Keep Attacking Nuke Power Plants...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/epx4mj/jellyfish-keep-attacking-nuclear-power-plants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jellyfish are continuing to clog the cooling pipes of nuclear power plants around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Maskless Voters Turned Away...</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/tipsheet/spencerbrown/2021/11/02/virginia-poll-workers-requiring-masks-to-vote-in-violation-of-election-rules-rep-n2598436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE:Following reporting from Townhall and others that Virginia voters were being required to wear a mask in order to cast a ballot on Tuesday, Virginia Department of Elections Commissioner Chris</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX defends shot, rebukes reporter's 'false claims'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/579696-newsmax-defends-vaccines-in-rebuke-of-its-own-reporters-false-claims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative news network Newsmax issued a pair of statements Tuesday distancing itself from "false claims" about coronavirus vaccines made by one of its correspondents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Radio 'Money Doctor' Sentenced For Bilking Listeners In Ponzi Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/11/01/william-neil-doc-gallagher-sentenced-life-terms-ripping-off-texans-ponzi-scheme/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2020, he pleaded guilty to similar charges in Dallas County and was sentenced to 25 years in prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON Followers Gather in Dallas for Arrival of JFK Jr, Who Died in '99...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/weird/qanon-followers-gather-in-dallas-for-the-arrival-of-jfk-jr-who-died-in-1999/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remember QAnon? Well, apparently there are still people who believe these conspiracies, one of which involves... John F. Kennedy Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers release Israeli LGBTQ dating site details...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211102-hackers-release-israeli-lgbtq-dating-site-details</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's justice ministry said Tuesday Google had blocked sites of a hacking group that leaked user details of an Israeli LGBTQ dating site, an attack some security experts blamed on Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: Not Worried About Armed Conflict With China...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211102193046-snxhy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLIMATE-UN/USA-CHINA (URGENT):Biden says he is not worried about armed conflict occurring with China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Monkey Jizz' Crypto Turns Out to Be Scam...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/n7nw4k/unbelievable-monkey-jizz-cryptocurrency-turns-out-to-be-a-scam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team behind Monkey Jizz was able to make off with nearly $300,000 worth of Binance Coin on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man in Halloween costume randomly attacks pedestrian with ax in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/02/masked-man-randomly-attacks-pedestrian-with-ax-in-nyc-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 51-year-old victim was on Broadway near West 61st Street just after 10 p.m. Monday when the suspect threatened to kill him and struck his arm with the ax without provocation, cops said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage: 'Stupidest Thing I've Ever Heard'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/national-news/articles/2021-11-02/how-the-military-is-handling-troops-who-refuse-coronavirus-vaccines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday marked the military’s first deadline for all Air Force and Space Force troops to receive the coronavirus vaccine. Following months of patience, the punishments now begin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worship and elderly visits on ballots...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-texas-voting-rights-constitutions-5c839f590064ffc1a530d83992e464b9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemic policies were being put to the test Tuesday in several states where ballot measures sought to rebuke or affirm actions taken by officials trying to fight COVID-19. The virus-related measures were among two dozen ballot proposals in six states that also include new constitutional rights for residents to grow their own food or enjoy clean air and water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL STAR INVOLVED IN FATAL CAR ACCIDENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/11/02/las-vegas-raiders-henry-ruggs-involved-in-serious-car-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raiders wide receiver Henry Ruggs III was involved in a serious car accident in Las Vegas early Tuesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighter jet pilots at greater cancer risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2021/11/02/fighter-jet-pilots-at-greater-risk-of-certain-cancers-study-concludes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers recommend that fighter aviators who served during the 35-year span in question talk with their doctor or flight surgeon about the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College costs up 169%. Pay up only 19%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/02/the-gap-in-college-costs-and-earnings-for-young-workers-since-1980.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It is far better to be born rich and white than smart and poor in America," reads a recent report from Georgetown University.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
