<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Race Is on to Save Burning Cargo Ship Full of Luxury Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/news/44351/salvage-crews-racing-to-save-burning-cargo-ship-full-of-porsches-bentleys-and-vws</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 4,000 vehicles are on board as the fire consumes the ship—and the electric cars it’s carrying pose an extra danger for firefighters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 43%  Turn To Food For Pick-Me-Up When Feeling Down...</title>
      <link>https://www.gutnews.com/gut-brain-mental-health-connection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gutnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey reveals that although 90% of adults think about their gut health to some degree, 40% weren't aware that the gut is linked to mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercise boosts brain -- and mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Exercise-boosts-the-brain-and-mental-health-16931993.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mental health disorders such as depression and anxiety aren't easy to treat. Medications...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems hit 30-year high for House retirements...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/594797-democrats-hit-30-year-high-for-house-retirements</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of House Democrats not seeking reelection this year has hit a 30-year high — a bleak benchmark reflecting frustrations with the gridlock on Capitol Hill, the toxicity of relations between the parties and the challenges facing Democrats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once He Kept Russia at Distance. Now He Is Docile Putin Satrap...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/19/once-he-kept-russia-at-a-distance-now-he-is-a-docile-putin-satrap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINSK, Belarus — In a winter military coat trimmed with fur, Aleksandr G. Lukashenko stepped out of his white presidential</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris, Blinken navigate Munich as Europe holds breath...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/harris-blinken-navigate-munich-security-conference-as-europe-holds-its-breath/ar-AAU4iXj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Comes Too Soon for Some...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/unmasking-comes-too-soon-for-some-still-wary-of-covid-s-wiles/ar-AAU29RJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO raises readiness level...</title>
      <link>https://www.anews.com.tr/world/2022/02/18/nato-raises-readiness-level-for-tens-of-thousands-of-troops</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.anews.com.tr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO raises readiness level for tens of thousands of troops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol girding for potential trucker protest at State of Union...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2022/02/18/capitol-potential-freedom-convoy-protest-state-of-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Truck drivers protesting vaccine requirements have snarled the Canadian capital of Ottawa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind China's Olympics, saga of chained woman unfolds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-chained-woman-eileen-gu-fa30a04d74a91f5beff9983442353971</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — The post, on China's Weibo social platform, resembled many others posted by official media during these Olympics — an ode to freestyle skier Eileen Gu, known to Chinese as Gu Ailing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rebels mobilize troops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-europe-moscow-donetsk-4596388ab5f4ee61cee94f4f9a993915</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Separatist leaders in eastern Ukraine ordered a full military mobilization Saturday amid a spike of violence in the war-torn region and fears in the West that Russia might use the strife as a pretext for an invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan woman turning 100 adds another tattoo...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-lifestyle-michigan-st-joseph-tattoos-08f26bfdc667ed4a0625f901e3324d51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. JOSEPH, Mich. (AP) — A Michigan woman soon will celebrate a milestone birthday. How old? Look at her decorative upper arm. Gloria Weberg has “NY NY 1922” tattooed on her left arm, the year and place of her birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican army sends anti-mine squads to cartel turf war zone...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-mexico-caribbean-improvised-explosives-drug-cartels-a49c12cd0539940f165659f211316c42</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NARANJO DE CHILA, Mexico (AP) — Special squads of Mexican army troops equipped with metal detectors and bomb suits have deployed to the western state of Michoacan, where warring drug cartels have planted land mines or improvised explosive devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could artificial intelligence wipe out humanity?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4718282/artificial-intelligence-wipe-out-humanity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANY fear that artificial intelligence will be the end of humankind – here’s the truth according to experts. By now, most people around the world use some sort of AI-utilizing device that is …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men at risk of weak sperm depending on which city live in?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4719840/men-risk-weak-sperm-pollution-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEN are at risk of weaker sperm depending on where they live, a study warns. The fertility of thousands, potentially millions of men, may be experiencing fertility decline without realising. Resear…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Officials Warn of Imminent Russian Invasion of Ukraine With Tanks, Fighter Jets, Cyber...</title>
      <link>https://wsj.com/articles/ukraine-troops-told-to-exercise-restraint-to-avoid-provoking-russian-invasion-11645185631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prospects for averting war appear dim, officials said, even as the Biden administration is working to arrange new talks with Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROKU's Record Stock Collapse Expands List of Fallen Pandemic Favorites...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/roku-record-collapse-expands-list-145434032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Roku Inc. shares tumbled Friday, with the streaming-video platform company the latest example of a one-time pandemic favorite to see a precipitous decline as investors look past an era where consumers are no longer stuck indoors.Most Read from BloombergMorgan Stanley Relationships on Wall Street Snared in ProbeLavrov Agrees to Meet Blinken, U.S. Says: Ukraine UpdateIndia Protests Against Singapore PM’s Comments on LawmakersThe Housing Boom’s Mortgage Rate Threat Is Worse Than It S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden 'Convinced'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-joe-biden-europe-russia-moscow-c2e55b8b2b061b58e2b140d2a6dc1d57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — U.S. President Joe Biden said Friday that he is “convinced” Russian President Vladimir Putin has decided to invade Ukraine, including an assault on the capital, as tensions spiked along the country's militarized line with attacks that the West said could be “false-flag” operations meant to establish a pretext for invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Archives: Classified items taken to Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-mar-a-lago-national-security-9c1f6dca7e3e8073ee029604c8253a5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Classified information was found in the 15 boxes of White House records that were stored at former President Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago residence, the National Archives and Records Administration said Friday in a letter that confirmed the matter has been sent to the Justice Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN WANTS KYIV</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-joe-biden-says-russia-26273949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden says he has reason to believe Russian forces are planning to attack Ukraine in the coming days, with Vladimir Putin attempting to set up a 'false justification' to launch an invasion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: Kendall Jenner's tequila accused of  'blatantly' copying rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/kendall-jenners-tequila-brand-accused-blatantly-copying-tequila-512-la-rcna16744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit alleges that the branding is so similar that an image of Tequila 512 was mistakenly used in Kim Kardashian’s mobile game instead of Jenner’s 818 Tequila.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communist French presidential candidate calls for abolishing homework...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/communist-french-presidential-candidate-calls-for-abolishing-homework-you-will-be-free/ar-AAU30vi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marine reservist charged with fake vax card scam...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-e2233e42b2c99abfe316eb4673a19657</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A Marine Corps reservist who was charged in last year’s riot at the U.S. Capitol also schemed with a nurse to steal, forge and sell hundreds of fake coronavirus vaccination cards and destroy vaccine doses to fake inoculations, federal authorities said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuban tourism flounders as sunseekers look elsewhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/world/cuban-tourism-industry-flounders-as-sunseekers-look-elsewhere/ar-AAU30vw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuban tourism industry flounders as sunseekers look elsewhere</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you be healed by sound frequency?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/can-you-be-healed-by-a-sound-frequency-from-sound-baths-to-tiktok-a-debate-gently-rages/ar-AAU2avN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GETTR Will Ban Users That Question If Guo Is A 'Spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/can-you-call-free-speech-gettrs-backer-guo-wengui-a-spy-on-the-app-we-tested-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some right-wing users have claimed Gettr censors allegations that Guo Wengui, its fugitive Chinese financier, is a CCP “spy.” The Daily Beast tested the claims out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Attractive People Have Stronger Immune Systems...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/attractive-people-immune-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although beauty is often in the eye of the beholder, researchers say there has been a historical link between what societies consider attractive and reproductive success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Violent' attack by protesters at Canadian pipeline worksite...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220218-violent-attack-by-protesters-at-canadian-pipeline-worksite</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian police said Friday they were investigating a "violent confrontation" at a gas pipeline construction site in the western province of British Columbia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Political affiliation drove use of ivermectin, hydroxychloroquine...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/594953-study-shows-political-affiliation-drove-use-of-ivermectin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The use of two unproven COVID-19 treatments was higher in counties with a larger share of Republican voters in late 2020, according to a study released Friday, suggesting stark political differences in medical decis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelenskyy trip to Munich raises alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/us-concerned-zelenskyys-trip-munich-rcna16856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainian president hasn’t made a final decision on the visit as Washington worries Russian President Vladimir Putin could exploit his absence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrest, Assassination Campaign Planned...</title>
      <link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2022/02/18/russia-ukraine-arrest-assassination-invasion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;foreignpolicy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intelligence on possible targets has been shared with Ukraine and other partners in the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom's waning voter approval might've given Republicans shot. But they blew it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/newsom-s-waning-voter-approval-might-ve-given-the-gop-a-shot-but-they-blew-it-in-the-recall/ar-AAU2I9u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  USA allows Mexican avocado imports to resume...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/18/us-government-allows-mexican-avocado-imports-to-resume-after-brief-suspension.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Department of Agriculture announced Friday that imports of Mexican avocados could resume after a brief pause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans fleeing to places where political views match their own...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/02/18/1081295373/the-big-sort-americans-move-to-areas-political-alignment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is growing more geographically polarized — red ZIP codes are getting redder and blue ZIP codes are becoming bluer. People appear to be sorting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Mickelson deal with Saudi 'motherf***ers' to pressure PGA Tour...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/golf/story/_/id/33312893/phil-mickelson-deal-saudis-pressure-pga-tour</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phil Mickelson is willing to deal with Saudi Arabia to put pressure on the PGA Tour, according to a new book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-powered PR firm secretly bought news site to tout itself, bash rivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/media/ronn-torossian-5wpr-secretly-scrubs-industry-news-site-it-operated-tout-itself-bash-rivals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ownership disclosure and removal of fake bylines comes after years of 5WPR founder Ronn Torossian denying he was behind the operation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are so many so rude to each other?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/02/our-age-of-incivility-must-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Narcissistic radicals turn politics into a vacuum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinicians Sent to Clean Things Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-york-city-to-send-clinicians-to-subways-reinforce-ban-on-sleeping-in-stations/ar-AAU2vdh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA bill would allow citizens to enforce weapons ban...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-texas-lawsuits-california-gun-politics-b0a3cd6c9061e1ba37d6c52ae093e6c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — A new bill in California would allow private citizens go after gun makers in the same way Texas lets them target abortion providers. Gov. Gavin Newsom on Friday backed legislation that would let private citizens enforce the state’s ban on assault weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This scientist is the lizard king, and he just found another one from age of dinosaurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/this-scientist-is-the-lizard-king-and-he-just-found-another-one-from-the-age/article_70bbe8df-893b-5ba3-a42a-6eecdddd6f5e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — Aaron Bauer has traveled the world in search of lizards, logging more than 2 million miles in his quest to identify new species and determine how they fit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun erupting non-stop for month; Giant flares incoming, scientists say...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4717589/sun-erupting-non-stop-flares-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SUN has been pretty busy the past few weeks. On Tuesday, our star fired off two enormous explosions from its farside in what has already been a heavy month of solar activity. A magnificent coro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>190,000 troops holding at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/uk/west-high-alert-russian-invasion-ukraine-damian-hinds-boris-johnson-b983234.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin rattled already frayed tensions with the West by announcing plans to stage massive drills of Russia’s nuclear forces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States craft COVID exit strategies...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2022/02/15/states-craft-their-covid-exit-strategies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once ardent supporters of the CDC’s mask advice, Democratic governors move on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary mocks MAGA; Says conspiracy theories getting 'wilder'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/us-elections-government/ny-hillary-clinton-donald-trump-mocked-20220217-h44iyenyvzgarhiintfukf6bcq-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hillary Clinton suggested Thursday that a desperate President Donald Trump hopes to divert attention from his deepening legal trouble by spreading ludicrous lies about her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brooklyn gang members lived large on $4 million in stolen virus unemployment funds...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-brooklyn-gang-members-stole-millions-in-covid-aid-20220218-poe5moloafht3azdzwfticm5xe-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cops caught wind of the fraud when members of the NYPD’s intelligence bureau noticed that members of the Canarsie-based Woo gang were making trips to California, renting houses, buying expensive cars and posing on social media with stacks of cash at the beginning of the COVID pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58% Say Jobs Are Main Source of Mental Health Woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/cio-briefing/2022/02/survey-58-working-americans-say-their-jobs-are-main-source-mental-health-challenges/362128/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 90% of Americans believe being in control of their work schedules, along with performance measures, could improve burnout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahead of expected retirement, Baquet reflects on NYT's unprecedented growth...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/the-new-yorker-interview/dean-baquet-never-wanted-to-be-an-editor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead of his expected retirement, the Times’ executive editor reflects on his newsroom’s unprecedented growth, Twitter’s influence on journalism, and the time he punched a hole in a wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separatists announce civilian evacuation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/east-ukraine-shelling-russian-invasion-fears-putin-pretext-rcna16773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move comes amid a spike in shelling in the area, with tensions rising once again after the West disputed Moscow’s claims of a troop pullback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ to investigate companies exploiting supply chain snafus...</title>
      <link>https://www.murrayledger.com/news/national-world/justice-department-to-investigate-companies-exploiting-supply-chain-snafus/article_33741dac-9056-11ec-a2e1-f3d974f86df9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.murrayledger.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(TNS) The Justice Department announced on Thursday it was launching an initiative to identify companies that are exploiting supply chain disruptions in the U.S. for increased profits in possible violation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Comes Too Soon for Some Still Wary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/unmasking-comes-too-soon-for-some-still-wary-of-covid-s-wiles/ar-AAU29RJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Store employees working to unionize, part of growing worker backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/some-us-apple-store-employees-are-working-to-unionize-part-of-a-growing-worker-backlash/ar-AAU20lZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm Eunice rips roof off London's O2 arena as record-breaking gusts blast UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-storm-eunice-rips-roof-26268649 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storm Eunice has caused serious damage to the O2 Arena's iconic roof, with pieces of panelling seen flying into the Thames amid huge gusts of wind battering the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGALOPOLIS:  Francis Ford Coppola's $100 Million Bet...</title>
      <link>https://www.gq.com/story/francis-ford-coppola-50-years-after-the-godfather</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gq.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fifty years after he gave us "The Godfather," the iconic director is chasing his grandest project yet—and putting up over $100 million of his own money to prove his best work is still ahead of him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITY OF HATE:  Breakdancer stabbed while performing on NYC subway train...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-stabbed-on-l-train-nypd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 22-year-old man was stabbed in the leg on a L train in the New York City subway on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overrun Hong Kong hospitals forced to leave Covid patients outside...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/overrun-hong-kong-hospitals-forced-26269897</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Omicron cases in Hong Kong have surged as the government failed to execute their "Covid zero" plan during the Lunar New Year holiday, with the worst number of daily cases since pandemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAR BOMB:  Putin finally springs his false flag?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10527897/Ukraine-crisis-Pro-Moscow-rebels-start-evacuating-civilians.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large explosion has rocked the separatist-held city of Donetsk in eastern Ukraine with a car bomb detonating near the headquarters of the pro-Moscow government, Russia's state media said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisville activist charged with attempted murder of mayoral candidate released on $100k bail...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2022/02/17/craig-greenberg-others-criticize-quintez-brown-bail-others-support-suspect/6830995001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craig Greenberg was one of many who criticized Thursday the release of shooting suspect Quintez Brown, though others defended his bail payment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR DRUMS:  Shelling intensifies in eastern Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/russia-ukraine-news-shelling-donbas-buildup-latest-us-invasion-pretext-blinken-lavrov/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian-backed separatists accuse Ukraine's forces of planning an imminent attack and announce a massive evacuation of civilians to Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injuries similar to 'Havana Syndrome' cases reported on White House grounds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/havana-syndrome-60-minutes-2022-02-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior national security officials say they were stricken with vertigo, confusion and memory loss both at home in Washington and on the grounds of the White House. 60 Minutes reports, Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-Right Zemmour Real Contender in French Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/far-right-radical-zemmour-is-a-real-contender-in-french-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Far-Right Radical Zemmour Is a Real Contender in French Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  With 'bodies piling up,' contractors clearing backlog at Maryland medical examiner's office...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/health/bs-hs-medical-examiner-office-looks-for-labor-20220217-ut6fihjzqvdqtowutabs6jqsji-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The overburdened medical examiner's office in Maryland is rehiring retired workers to clear the backlog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Americans so rude to each other?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/02/our-age-of-incivility-must-end/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Narcissistic radicals turn politics into a vacuum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mental speed stays high until age 60, research suggests...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/mental-speed-stays-high-until-160000398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study challenges previous assumptions that mental speed peaks at age 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House latest challenge is sour public mood...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/594842-white-houses-latest-challenge-is-sour-public-mood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Biden White House struggling to find any sort of political momentum is facing a stern challenge in trying to shift the sour mood of a public fatigued by the two-year pandemic, annoyed with rising prices and uncertain over conflicts abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Surgeon General Murthy and his family test positive...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-surgeon-general-murthy-family-174100722.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murthy, a leading U.S. government spokesperson on public health, added that he and his wife had mild symptoms. He added that his 4-year-old daughter, who tested positive first over the past weekend, was "doing ok" and her fever was starting to improve. Murthy also stressed the importance of being vaccinated and boosted against the virus and reiterated the efficacy of the COVID-19 vaccine in his tweets on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pretext to invade'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/shelling-breaks-east-ukraine-west-104109489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW/KYIV/DONETSK (Reuters) -Russian-backed separatists packed civilians onto buses out of breakaway regions in eastern Ukraine on Friday, a shock turn in a conflict the West believes Moscow plans to use as justification for all-out invasion of its neighbour. Warning sirens blared in Donetsk after it and the other self-proclaimed region, Luhansk, announced an evacuation to Russia, with women, children and the elderly going first. Most of the several million civilians in the two rebel-held areas of eastern Ukraine are Russian speakers, with many already granted citizenship by Moscow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Now Least Affordable Housing Market In USA...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2022/02/17/miami-now-least-affordable-housing-market-in-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’ve forgotten what a “for sale” sign looks like, you’re not alone. There are fewer and fewer around Miami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Avocado Growers Feeling the Pain of U.S. Ban...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mexico-avocado-growers-feeling-pain-130000668.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Avocado growers in the Mexican state of Michoacan are feeling the pain of the U.S.’s decision to suspend imports of the green fruit due to security concerns. Most Read from BloombergMorgan Stanley Relationships on Wall Street Snared in ProbeLavrov Agrees to Meet Blinken, U.S. Says: Ukraine UpdateIndia Protests Against Singapore PM’s Comments on LawmakersThousands of Cars Including Audis, Porsches Adrift on Burning Cargo ShipElon Musk Ratchets Up Trudeau Criticism With Hitler Compa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Fortress Australia' Has New Message: Come Back...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/18/fortress-australia-has-a-new-message-come-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moments after the Australian government announced that it would reopen the country’s borders to international travelers later this month, Emily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bots and Fake Accounts Push China's Vision of Winter Olympic Wonderland...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/18/bots-and-fake-accounts-push-chinas-vision-of-winter-olympic-wonderland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This article is published with ProPublica, the nonprofit investigative newsroom. BEIJING — Inside the Potemkin village of China’s propaganda, the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship Carrying 1,100 Porsches, Other Luxury Cars Burning and Adrift...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/02/17/ship-carrying-1100-porsches-and-other-luxury-cars-is-burning-and-adrift/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mammoth cargo ship believed to be carrying thousands of vehicles including 1,100 Porsches was on fire and drifting off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions, outages, fear...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-technology-europe-russia-ebba0930160acb98b2e05617f332cec7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KYIV, Ukraine (AP) — Shells struck by the hundreds along the tense front lines in eastern Ukraine , drones monitoring a fragile cease-fire lost their way when the GPS signal they rely on was jammed, and then the cellphone network went dark.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry lawyers say he feels unsafe bringing kids to UK...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-europe-united-states-prince-harry-royalty-23f6175e18a4499bcfbddffda4bde092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Lawyers for Prince Harry told a court hearing on Friday that the British royal is unwilling to bring his children to his homeland because it is not safe. Harry has launched a legal challenge to the U.K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE MOB TAKES THE FIFTH'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bill-cosby-business-new-york-donald-trump-75002cbfb671903a5fe6db3c23517133</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — To plead the Fifth, or not to plead the Fifth? That is the question Donald Trump may face after a New York judge ordered the former president to testify in a long-running state civil investigation into his business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect claimed to be sleepwalking when he burglarized truck...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/sleepwalker-burglary-569034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 18--An accused auto burglar told Louisiana cops that he was sleepwalking when he entered a parked pickup late Wednesday evening, according to an arrest affidavit. Responding to a call about</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
