<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belgian skater placed in severe isolation with no explanation...</title>
      <link>https://www.outsports.com/olympics/2022/2/2/22914779/kim-meylemans-olympic-skeleton-covid-isolation-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olympic organizers forced the out athlete into a detention center despite several negative COVID tests, before outcry got her released.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds' contract with PFIZER has surprises...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/02/01/1075876794/feds-contract-with-pfizer-for-paxlovid-has-some-surprises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NPR has obtained the government's $5.3 billion contract for the first 10 million courses of Paxlovid, an antiviral pill for COVID-19. Here's what's in it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos' new megayacht so big, Dutch to take apart historic bridge to let it pass...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/jeff-bezos-new-megayacht-is-so-big-the-dutch-are-going-to-have-to-take-apart-a-historic-bridge-to-let-it-pass/ar-AATpOyI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suit: Wrong sperm used during fertilization procedure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-lawsuits-cleveland-akron-41da7799c975ea8028f9c09033817ad2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — Jessica Harvey Galloway asked her parents for a DNA genealogical test for Christmas in 2020 hoping to finding distant relatives during a planned trip to Italy with her husband. The test led to a shocking and disturbing discovery, according to a lawsuit filed Wednesday in Akron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Livid', threatening to quit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/02/02/whoopi-goldberg-threatening-to-quit-the-view-source/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whoopi Goldberg is “livid” after she was suspended from “The View” over her claim that the Holocaust was “not about race” — and is telling co-workers she is goin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Animals Understand What It Means to Die?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg57q/do-animals-understand-what-it-means-to-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Primates carry their dead infants; elephants return to where relatives lay dead. To explain these behaviors, scientists have to answer questions that have vexed philosophers for millennia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Hillary tops Joe in hypothetical match-up in FL...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2022/02/01/poll-biden-struggling-florida-2024/9282357002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Suffolk University/USA TODAY Network poll of likely Florida voters says only 39% of respondents approve of the job Biden is doing, while 53% disapprove.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson bats away criticism as party allegations escalate...</title>
      <link>https://www.union-bulletin.com/boris-johnson-bats-away-criticism-as-party-allegations-escalate/article_cad8350f-ff30-5c89-b420-2da7fd22eb90.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.union-bulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson dismissed criticism about the conduct of his government after further reports of parties in Downing Street during lockdown prompted renewed pressure within his ruling Conservative Party for him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Hosts Furious at ABC for Suspending...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/whoopi-goldberg-suspended-from-the-view-for-two-weeks-over-holocaust-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The famed co-host is going off-air for two weeks to “reflect” on her comments, and sources said her on-air colleagues are not pleased with ABC’s decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Tycoon Goes to War With Hawaii Locals Over Beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/crypto-tycoon-jonathan-yantis-goes-to-war-with-hawaii-locals-over-beach</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blockchain mogul Jonathan Yantis wants quiet near his $24 million mansion on Maui. Locals are painting him as an exclusionary rich “a--hole.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans porn star dead at 30...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4593230/porn-star-holly-parker-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORN star Holly Parker has died at the age of 30, according to reports. The transgender adult entertainer, who starred in dozens of movies, passed away on Monday, her close friend Brooke Zanell sai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 In 5 Trust Punxsutawney Phil Over Meteorologists...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/groundhog-day-punxsutawney-phil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 3 in 5 agree that whether or not Punxsutawney Phil sees his shadow on Groundhog Day actually determines if there will be six more weeks of winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Body Fat Linked To Cognitive Decline...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/body-fat-linked-cognitive-decline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Higher levels of body fat are a risk factor for cognitive decline, slower thought processing speed, and memory issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monica Vitti, multifaceted actress who symbolized Italian mystique, dies at 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Monica-Vitti-multifaceted-actress-who-symbolized-16825332.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Vitti, an Italian actress who secured an enduring place in art house drama as the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Protesters block U.S.-Canada border crossing as truckers challenge vax mandates...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/protesters-block-u-s-canada-crossing-as-freedom-convoy-truckers-challenge-vaccine-mandates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vehicles have blocked a border crossing in Alberta since Saturday — reportedly in support of truckers in the Canadian capital protesting a COVID vaccine mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA DRIVERS COMPLAIN OF RANDOM, JOLTING STOPS...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/bulletins/tesla-phantom-braking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phenomenon is called "phantom braking," and it's been an issue since October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed-energy could explain unsolved 'Havana Syndrome' cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/directed-energy-could-explain-unsolved-havana-syndrome-cases-u-s-intelligence-panel-finds/ar-AATputk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEBT HITS $30 TRILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/national-debt-surpasses-30-trillion-for-the-first-time/ar-AATnlcL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army begins discharges...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2022/02/02/army-begins-discharges-for-covid-vaccine-refusing-soldiers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order also applies to cadets, Guard and Reserve troops who are on Title 10 active duty tours of more than 30 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer says 'corroborating evidence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/sports/nfl/miami-dolphins/article257961213.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among the potentially seismic allegations Brian Flores made in his racial-discrimination lawsuit against the NFL and Miami Dolphins on Tuesday, one of the most stunning pieces was an accusation team owner Stephen M. Ross bribed Flores to lose games during the 2019 NFL season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee body stuck in Spanish prison morgue; Fight rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/his-end-is-a-void-of-unknown-john-mcafees-body-is-stuck-in-a-spanish-prison-morgue-as-a-fight-rages-over-his-legacy-11643823665</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than seven months after he died in a Spanish prison, John McAfee’s body remains in a prison morgue freezer somewhere in or near Barcelona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man disrupts pope audience: 'God rejects you'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220202-man-disrupts-pope-audience-shouts-god-rejects-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shouting man denouncing the Church disrupted an audience by Pope Francis at the Vatican Wednesday, before being escorted outside by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-life Atlantis could be ready for residents in eight years...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/tech/news/real-life-atlantis-costing-26-26120527</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambitious Japanese scientists revealed plans to build a gigantic Ocean Spiral City under the sea - it would let us use the deep sea for resources and live next to colossal octopuses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Jackson Musical Kicks Out Reporter for Asking About Sex Abuse Allegations...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/scene/news/mj-michael-jackson-musical-1235169558/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tuesday evening in New York City, “MJ The Musical,” a new biographical musical celebrating the life and work of Michael Jackson, opened on Broadway. “MJ The Musical,” written by two-time Pulitze…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of libertarian movement?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/feature/1009651/the-strange-return-of-the-libertarian-moment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Libertarianism is back, with a new look</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vindman suit accuses Trump Jr., Giuliani of witness intimidation, retaliation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/592438-vindman-lawsuit-accuses-trump-jr-giuliani-of-witness-intimidation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retired Lt. Col.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon: Climate lockdowns?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/592011-coming-soon-climate-lockdowns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proclaimed crisis of climate changes appears ready to become the new COVID.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ketanji Jackson favorite for Biden historic Supreme Court pick...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ketanji-jackson-favorite-bidens-historic-110037123.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Appeals Court Judge Ketanji Jackson, the front-runner for the nomination, graduated with high honors from Harvard and clerked for Justice Breyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 charged in overdose death of actor Michael K. Williams...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/michael-k-williams-overdose-death-charges-d5cae927130c868486331789f876561b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Four men believed to be members of a drug distribution crew have been charged in the overdose death of actor Michael K.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain scrambles jets after detecting unidentfied aircraft...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-defence/britain-scrambles-jets-after-detecting-unidentfied-aircraft-idUSKBN2K7148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain scrambled fighter jets on Wednesday after detecting unidentified aircraft approaching its airspace, the defence ministry said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies unexpectedly cut 301,000 jobs in Jan...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/02/adp-jobs-report-january-2022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls fell by 301,000 for the month vs. the estimate for a 200,000 gain, according to payrolls processing firm ADP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria Starts Criminalizing Vaccine Holdouts in Divisive Gamble...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/austria-makes-covid-vaccines-compulsory-in-new-health-gamble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austria Makes Covid Vaccines Compulsory in New Health Gamble</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shipping giants under fire for record profits, fees as pandemic continues...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/business-a-lobbying/592397-shipping-giants-under-fire-for-record-profits-fees-as-pandemic-continues</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipping giants have come under fire from U.S. business groups and watchdogs for raking in record-breaking profits on the backs of skyrocketing prices driven by unprecedented port congestion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Teen monitoring Musk jet tracking Gates, Bezos, Drake...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2022/feb/02/teen-tracking-elon-musk-jet-bill-gates-jeff-bezos-drake-jack-sweeney-tesla-flight-tracker-bot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Sweeney, who wants Tesla CEO to hand over $50k to remove flight tracker bot, sets sights on other celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA drivers report surge in 'phantom braking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/tesla-drivers-report-a-surge-in-phantom-braking/ar-AAToy5E</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTIFY Rogan Mess Exposes Larger Rift Over Rules, Streaming Revenues...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/spotify-joe-rogan-streaming-revenue-covid-review-1235085384/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Content advisory labels may be beside the point for the streaming giant's flagship podcast series, and other creators may be wary of taking a stand on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bonuses Rain on Wall St Bankers in Biggest Payout in Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/wealth/wall-street-s-big-bonuses-are-back-and-bankers-are-buying-yachts-champagne</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten million dollars, $15 million, $25 million, more: Big money is back on Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's finely crafted web of digital surveillance for Olympics has been years in making...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/winter-olympics/china-e2-80-99s-finely-crafted-web-of-digital-surveillance-for-the-beijing-olympics-has-been-years-in-the-making/ar-AATodn7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Queen Elizabeth II to mark 70 years on throne...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queen-elizabeth-ii-mark-70-030820803.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II on Sunday becomes the first British monarch to reign for 70 years, heralding the start of her Platinum Jubilee year despite her retreat from public view.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump heir? Supporters eye DeSantis as alternative...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-florida-donald-trump-texas-d0fb48fb5ccf444dc7b20590201a05ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONROE, Texas (AP) — There was something different next to the “TRUMP WON!” T-shirts, the “MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN” hats and the “LET’S GO BRANDON” flags for sale at former President Donald Trump’s recent Texas rally: a collection of “DeSantis 2024” bumper stickers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New turning point? More countries easing COVID restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-pandemics-united-nations-ca046d38f7e78ad7150a0a8d95d81433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — Late-night disco partying. Elbow-to-elbow seating in movie theaters. Mask-free baring of faces in public, especially in Europe and North America: Bit by bit, many countries that have been hard-hit by the coronavirus are opening up and easing their tough, and often unpopular, restrictive measures aimed to fight COVID-19 even as the omicron variant — deemed less severe — has caused cases to skyrocket.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli police admit use of spyware without warrant...</title>
      <link>https://www.thevibes.com/articles/world/53367/israeli-cops-appear-to-admit-use-of-spyware-without-warrant</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thevibes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice minister had pledged a full investigation following a media report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sets stage for 2024, saying the quiet part louder and louder...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-sets-stage-2024-saying-205742052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He may have lost the White House and his social media megaphone but Donald Trump is reminding Americans of his ability to dominate the political conversation as he courts controversy on the comeback trail.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian province scraps tax on unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/canadian-province-scraps-tax-covid-201310878.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada's Quebec province announced Tuesday it was scrapping plans for a health tax on those who are not vaccinated against Covid-19, following a public backlash over the proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book banning in Texas schools: Titles pulled off library shelves in record numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/texas-books-race-sexuality-schools-rcna13886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing pressure from parents and threats of criminal charges, some districts have ignored policies meant to prevent censorship. Librarians and students are pushing back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lunar New Year would become the 12th federal holiday under bill before Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/lunar-new-year-would-become-the-12th-federal-holiday-under-a-bill-before-congress/ar-AATnkOS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  Passenger goes into labor on 11-hour flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/passenger-goes-into-labor-on-11-hour-flight-literally-just-witnessed-a-woman-giving-birth/ar-AATnitK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAMOUNT releases first trailer for 'THE GODFATHER' TV series...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/godfather-the-offer-trailer-1235085164/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 10-episode drama from 'The Player' director Michael Tolkin stars Miles Teller and Matthew Goode.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST IN 8 YEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bengals-rams-nfl-playoffs-nfc-afc-championship-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bengals-Chiefs on CBS draws largest audience for early window in 6 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT AGAIN:  Simonn Cowell rushed to hospital after nearly dying following another e-bike smash...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/4591115/simon-cowell-hospital-e-bike-smash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV mogul Simon Cowell was rushed to hospital following another terrifying e-bike smash, The Sun can reveal. Sources said the 62-year-old is lucky to be alive after he was propelled over the handleb…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Fatigue: 70% Just Want to Get on With Lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/covid-fatigue-70-of-americans-say-we-just-need-to-get-on-with-our-lives-according-to-new-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not surprisingly, responses indicate a clear partisan divide with 89% of Republicans agreeing with the statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOOPI SUSPENDED FROM 'VIEW'</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2022/02/01/whoopi-goldberg-suspended-the-view-holocaust-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whoopi Goldberg has been suspended from ABC’s The View for two weeks in light of her controversial comments about the Holocaust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital church membership surges...</title>
      <link>https://fox5ny.com/news/virtual-reality-church-worshipping-in-the-metaverse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Membership in Virtual Reality Church increased dramatically during the COVID shutdown. Worshippers attend using virtual reality headsets and create an avatar. Everything from scripture readings to baptisms can take place in the metaverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMS Win Over 49ERS Tops 50 MILLION Viewers for FOX!</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/02/nfl-la-rams-win-super-bowl-49ers-fox-viewership-1234923211/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most of Sunday’s NFC Championship Game at SoFi Stadium, it looked like the San Francisco 49ers would be heading to Super Bowl LVI in the same venue in two weeks. But looks can be deceiving. Bou…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
