<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bail draws questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/suspect-e2-80-99s-bail-draws-questions-as-investigations-begin-into-wisconsin-parade-tragedy/ar-AAR1Ww2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  WAIT ANOTHER YEAR FOR INFLATION TO COOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.macaubusiness.com/monthly-us-inflation-to-return-to-0-2-0-3-pct-in-second-half-of-2022-yellen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macaubusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Island ER forced to close over lack of vaccinated nurses...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/shortage-of-vaccinated-nurses-prompts-closure-of-er-on-long-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mount Sinai South Nassau said the decision to close the Long Beach Emergency Room came after all options were exhausted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZEN ROBBERS HIT CALI LUXE</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/23/update-shaken-holiday-shoppers-changing-plans-in-wake-of-retail-smash-and-grab-crime-spree/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent smash-and-grab robbery spree targeting retail shops across the Bay Area has shoppers, store employees and business owners on edge at the start the holiday shopping season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMAS SMASH AND GRAB</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/breed-brazen-takeover-robbers-hitting-130021558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;High-end retailers such as Nordstrom and Louis Vuitton have been targeted by brazen robbers in Northern and Southern California, raising alarm among authorities, politicians and retailers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Arrested On Nov. 5 For Punching Woman, Then Running Over Her In Same SUV!</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/waukesha-christmas-parade-darrell-brooks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darrell Brooks, 39, was charged with five counts of murder after he allegedly plowed through a Christmas parade in Waukesha, Wisconsin, on Sunday, killing at least five and injuring dozens more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes of terror recounted...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/waukesha-wisconsin-christmas-parade-crash-what-happened-daee4565c7a36e88029c5fe6393d1be3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours before it started, they were already there — people sitting on lawn chairs or wrapped in blankets, awaiting an event the city's mayor described as straight out of Norman Rockwell. The Waukesha Christmas Parade, a tradition in its Milwaukee suburb for six decades, was to be particularly special this time around after its pandemic-related cancellation last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans Expect To Gain 8 Pounds During Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/holiday-weight-gain-8-pounds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holiday weight gain is inevitable for many of us who can't help but to take a second slice of grandma's pecan pie or another slice of turkey (or three).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Warms to Saudi Money Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/hollywood-saudi-arabia-money-again-1235051906/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn’t too long ago that power brokers rushed to distance themselves from the country after the killing of columnist Jamal Khashoggi. Now it’s hosting a star-studded film festival and backing big-budget features with U.S. talent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable News Hedging on Streaming Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/cnn-fox-msnbc-streaming-plan-1235051688/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While touting new platforms (think: CNN+ or Fox Nation), top broadcast and cable executives are incentivized to protect the linear status quo, given that’s where the money is — even if it’s a rapidly declining business model.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom Deploying Highway Patrol...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/police-smash-and-grab-strategy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stopping the swarm of smash and grabs as holiday shoppers begin their buying spree, local police have a plan to keep criminals out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense after new covid curbs...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123142632-1ol47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-GUADELOUPE (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Gunshots fired at police in France's Martinique, Guadeloupe still tense</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanksgiving challenges airlines as travel nears pre-pandemic levels...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/nov/23/thanksgiving-travel-airports-staffing-cancelations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Travelers fear airport chaos as airlines contend with staffing shortages, which could lead to flight cancelations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOLLAR TREE Gives Up on Buck With $1.25 Price Standard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/dollar-tree-says-dollar125-price-point-to-become-new-standard/ar-AAR2CvB</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last surviving woman born in 19th century dies at 124...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4125578/oldest-ever-human-francisca-susano-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN believed to be the oldest person in world has died at the reported age of 124. Francisca Susano, affectionately known as Lola Iska, died on Monday night at her home in the Philippines. The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President's Low-Key Media Strategy Draws Allies' Concern...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/bidens-low-key-media-strategy-draws-allies-concern/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As president, Donald J. Trump was a media maximalist whose unavoidable-for-comment style helped generate saturation news coverage, for better or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: China Hypersonic Weapon Released Payload And Nobody Knows Why...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43242/chinas-hypersonic-mystery-weapon-released-its-own-payload-and-nobody-knows-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mystery surrounding China's hypersonic vehicle test last summer has deepened after the craft reportedly launched its own projectile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video: Fan Attacks WWE Wrestler At Monday Night Raw...</title>
      <link>https://thespun.com/more/wrestling/video-fan-attacks-wwe-wrestler-seth-rollins-monday-night-raw-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thespun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tonight's WWE “Monday Night Raw” event at Barclays Center in Brooklyn went off the rails when a fan attacked wrestler Seth Rollins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage over 'long, dirty toenails'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/22/us/ahmaud-arbery-trial-toenails-comment-outrage/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sentence uttered by a defense attorney in the trial of those accused in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery brought an audible gasp from people in the courtroom Monday -- and elicited outrage from his family and legal experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NASA probe set for historic asteroid deflection test...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-dart-launch-asteroid-defense-system/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $330 million DART probe will crash head-on into a small asteroid to test the possibility of averting future threats to Earth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUE ORIGIN to launch Michael Strahan, 5 others into space...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/23/bezos-blue-origin-to-launch-michael-strahan-5-others-into-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos’ Blue Origin on Tuesday announced the crew of its Dec. 9 launch, which will carry “Good Morning America” co-anchor and former New York Giant Michael Strahan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Cadets Steal Wrong Goat in Botched Pre-Game Navy Mascot Raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/army-cadets-steal-wrong-goat-in-botched-pre-game-navy-mascot-raid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cadets have stolen the goat mascots, all named Bill, at least 10 times since the first raid in 1953.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors set sights on new Trump target: Widely different valuations on same properties...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/n-y-prosecutors-set-sights-on-new-trump-target-widely-different-valuations-on-the-same-properties/ar-AAQZtcr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC records 200th homicide of  year; Not seen since '04...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dc-records-200th-homicide-of-the-year-a-mark-not-seen-since-2004/ar-AAR2sb1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Lined Up at ER...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/minnesota-covid-bed-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Because we have so many patients in our hospital emergency department waiting to get in the hospital, we have lost the ability and the bed capacity to safely accept many transfers from throughout the region,” Dr. Dan Hoody said. “This is commonly us having to decline five to 50 transfers a day.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Deployed To MN...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/covid-in-minnesota-natl-guard-arrives-as-hospitals-are-overrun-with-covid-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hospitals like Hennepin Healthcare are desperate for people to get vaccinated as Minnesota grapples with one of the worst infection rates in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY to Allow 800,000 Noncitizens to Vote in Local Elections...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/new-york-moves-to-allow-800000-noncitizens-to-vote-in-local-elections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City lawmakers are poised to allow more than 800,000 New Yorkers who are green card holders or have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup host Qatar used ex-CIA officer to spy on FIFA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/soccer-sports-business-migration-middle-east-d9716b62fc69ab88beb3553d402da7d1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The tiny Arab nation of Qatar has for years employed a former CIA officer to help spy on soccer officials as part of a no-expense-spared effort to win and hold on to the 2022 World Cup tournament, an investigation by The Associated Press has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan sparks sell-off...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/turkish-lira-plummets-to-historic-low-after-erdogan-sparks-selloff-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation in Turkey is now near 20%, meaning basic goods for Turks have soared in price and their local currency salaries are severely devalued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA will tap strategic petroleum reserve as gas prices hover at 7-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/23/biden-says-us-will-tap-strategic-petroleum-reserve-as-gas-prices-hover-around-7-hear-high.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. will release 50 millions barrels of oil from the Strategic Petroleum Reserve in an effort to combat climbing gas prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NASA to Launch Mission to Crush Asteroid Heading for Earth...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123115820-dn7bi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPACE-EXPLORATION/ASTEROID (TV):NASA to launch test mission of asteroid-deflecting spacecraft</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghans 'marry off' baby girls for dowries as starvation looms...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211123035757-ylrch</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghanistan's economic meltdown following the Taliban's takeover 100 days ago is pushing destitute families to marry off young daughters - and even baby girls, campaigners say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lira Losses Snowball in Turkey's Worst Streak in 20 Years...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/lira-weakens-past-12-per-104006032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Turkish lira’s freefall is shattering all kinds of records as President Recep Tayyip Erdogan’s renewed campaign for lower interest rates pushes the country deeper into crisis. Most Read from BloombergAsia’s Richest Man Looks to Walton Family Playbook on SuccessionNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsThe Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheries, Hidden Inflation Is Creeping Across JapanMaverick 70-Year-Old CEO Is Determined to Sha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Brands, Blue Brands: Hyper-Partisanship Coming for Corporate America...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/red-brands-and-blue-brands-is-hyper-partisanship-coming-for-corporate-america/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The year is 2041, and Starbucks has real competition. Black Rifle Coffee Company, the java brand favored by conservatives, has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO warns of surge in deaths ahead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-united-nations-denmark-579fe691ceefadd8a205188be52436d7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GENEVA (AP) — The World Health Organization's Europe office says projections show its 53-country region could face another 700,000 deaths in the coronavirus pandemic by next spring, topping 2 million in total.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housework boosts memories?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4123581/housework-keeps-people-better-in-shape/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DOING more housework can boost Brits’ memories and attention span for older people, scientists say. Researchers have found that elderly people who participate in a combination of light housew…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORDSTROM smash-and-grab in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/23/us/los-angeles-the-grove-nordstrom-burglary/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 20 people were involved in a burglary Monday night at the Nordstrom department store at The Grove retail complex in Los Angeles, CNN affiliate KCAL/KCBS reported, citing the Los Angeles Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four-Day Workweek Finally Within Grasp?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/23/is-the-four-day-workweek-finally-within-our-grasp/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In May 2020, as the pandemic sent stress levels through the roof, an online children’s clothes retailer called Primary started</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Was This Ancient Tusk 150 Miles From Land, 10,000 Feet Deep?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/11/22/why-was-this-ancient-tusk-150-miles-from-land-10000-feet-deep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young female mammoth was wandering long ago near what would become the Central Coast of California, when her life</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm X daughter found dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4123852/malcolm-xs-daughter-malikah-shabazz-dead-days-men-exonerated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MALCOLM X’s daughter has been found dead inside her Brooklyn apartment late Monday night. Officers found the late assassinated Black civil rights leader’s daughter Malikah Shabazz dead …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial in Arbery killing nears going to jury...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ahmaud-arbery-georgia-brunswick-a6c84fde31dc86a9b2230f1002ed25af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUNSWICK, Ga. (AP) — Final steps in the trial of three white men charged in the killing of Ahmaud Arbery were scheduled Tuesday before the case of the 25-year-old Black man's death goes to the jury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comfort turned to carnage and fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/at-a-christmas-parade-e2-80-98comfort-and-joy-e2-80-99-turns-to-carnage-and-fear-e2-80-98there-were-bodies-all-over-the-street-e2-80-99/ar-AAR17aj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan hospitals sound alarm over near-record hospitalizations...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/michigan-hospitals-sound-alarm-over-near-record-covid-19-hospitalizations/article_2dade75f-2efc-5dea-8009-537fa4054e67.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT — Michigan's Health and Hospital Association is urging residents to take precautions to reduce the spread of COVID-19 as the state approaches its highest number of hospitalized patients since</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR IN WAUKESHA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/five-dead-dozens-injured-suv-154211471.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man accused of deliberately driving his car into a Christmas parade near Milwaukee, killing five people and injuring dozens, was out on bail from a domestic abuse case and was suspected in another violent altercation earlier that day, officials said on Monday. The suspect, Darrell Brooks, 39, was arrested near the scene of Sunday's vehicular attack in Waukesha, Wisconsin, and faces five counts of first-degree homicide, Waukesha Police Chief Daniel Thompson said. In addition to the five people killed - ranging in age from 52 to 81 - 48 were injured, including six children who remained hospitalized in critical condition on Monday, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE:  NO MORE LOCKDOWNS...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211122224947-dib6x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-WHITEHOUSE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-U.S. not heading toward COVID lockdown, White House says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN KEEPS TRUMP FED CHAIR...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/22/why-biden-picked-powell-523214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the end, President Joe Biden did what many close to him expected: He took a longer-than-anticipated amount of time to arrive at a reasonable, moderate decision that thrilled few but carried limited risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell family files complaint at UN over detention...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/ghislaine-maxwell-family-files-complaint-at-un-say-detention-illegal-2621078</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relatives of Jeffrey Epstein's former lover Ghislaine Maxwell, who goes on trial in the US next week, have complained to the UN that her detention is illegal, lawyers said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YELLEN:  WAIT ANOTHER YEAR FOR INFLATION TO COOL...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/yellen-despite-labor-and-supply-chain-issues-our-recovery-is-on-track/ar-AAR0PSr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  GAGA GAGS IN 'GUCCI'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/22/house-of-gucci-review-lady-gagas-new-movie-is-abysmal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The abysmal “Gucci” would get a better grade, perhaps, if it was a term paper titled “How to Make the Assassination of a Famous Person Boring.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York's French chef Boulud voted world's best...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/yorks-french-chef-daniel-boulud-003852686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French chef Daniel Boulud, who has been living in New York for almost 40 years, was named best restaurateur in the world by Les Grandes Tables du Monde on Monday for his flagship restaurant "Daniel."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 unruly airline passengers face more than $160,000 in fines...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/nationworld/faa-seeks-more-than-160000-in-fines-for-alcohol-related-incidents-on-planes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officials said Monday they are seeking more than $160,000 in fines from eight airline passengers over incidents involving alcohol. The Federal Aviation Administration said the biggest singl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Stock Hits Record High; Big Tech Gets Bigger...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-surges-longest-rally-since-161749125.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Apple Inc. shares closed at a record high on Monday, with the iPhone maker bucking broad-based weakness in the tech sector to rise for a seventh straight session.Most Read from BloombergNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsA Denser City, But at What Cost?The Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheries, Hidden Inflation Is Creeping Across JapanMaverick 70-Year-Old CEO Is Determined to Shake Up Japanese FinanceThe stock rose as much as 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man gets 19 months for urging MAGA to kill lawmakers who backed election results...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/ny-man-gets-19-months-for-urging-trump-supporters-to-kill-lawmakers-who-backed-election-results/ar-AAR0X2b?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUTTIGIEG:  NO vaccine mandate for domestic flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/buttigieg-says-vaccine-mandate-for-us-flights-isn-e2-80-99t-necessary/ar-AAR0Rog?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC agrees to pay some of his legal bills in criminal investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/rnc-agrees-to-pay-some-of-trump-s-legal-bills-in-n-y-criminal-investigation/ar-AAR0FFl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebound as Bad as Last November in Some Spots...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/covid-rebound-in-us-is-as-bad-as-last-november-s-in-some-spots/ar-AAR0BHj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman used obituaries to rob homes during funerals...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bronx-woman-used-obituaries-to-rob-houses-as-people-attended-funerals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She would scan obituaries to find out when people would be attending funerals so she could break into their homes and steal valuables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICTURED: The five dead victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10230857/Nurse-79-Dancing-Grannies-member-one-five-killed-Waukesha-tragedy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victims have been identified as Virginia Sorenson, 79, Leanna Owens, 71, Tamara Durand, 52, Jane Kulich, 52, and Wilhelm Hospel, 82.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Vaccines Wane Against Infections...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/coronavirus/vaccines-ward-off-severe-covid-in-u-s-wane-against-infections</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 vaccines remain highly effective at keeping people alive and out of the hospital, but new U.S. data add further support to the argument that the shots aren’t preventing infections as much as they once did.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waukesha parade suspect wrote anti-Trump rap and declared 'f*** the pigs' before rampage...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4121813/waukesha-parade-darrell-brooks-anti-trump-rap/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect in the Christmas parade rampage that killed five revelers wrote an anti-Donald Trump rap and declared “f*** the pigs”, according to songs posted online. Aspiring rapper Darr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.: Fauci, Bill Gates Should Be Criminally Prosecuted For Profiting Off Virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2021/11/22/rfk_jr_fauci_and_bill_gates_should_be_criminally_prosecuted_for_gross_negligence_and_profiting_off_covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said Big Pharma and the media have divided the political parties and created racial animus so nobody will notice they are making billions to "execute the controlled demolition of American constitutional democracy." In an interview with Michael Cohen on his podcast, RFK Jr. argued you are no longer allowed to criticize government policies or you will be removed from YouTube. RFK Jr. said Dr. Anthony Fauci and Bill Gates should be criminally prosecuted for gross negligence and profiting off of the COVID-19 pandemic. MICHAEL COHEN, HOST: Does it concern you then that your book and its views are being given the most prominent airtime from people like Tucker Carlson who believe that the January 6th insurrection was an inside job created to crack down on the far right? ROBERT F. KENNEDY JR.: I'll talk to anybody. I'll talk to the biggest idiot in the world and I'll talk to criminals if their the only way that I can get my message out, you know, Anderson Cooper's not going to put me on CNN because CNN is run by pharmaceutical companies that gives, you know, 70% of revenues the evening news are coming from, from NPR is, you know, Bill Gates giving $319 million to the public television and, and the so-called independent news. Anybody who wants to criticize pharmaceutical products or government or question government policies cannot do that on a normal network TV, social media. They're thrown off. If you're a person who has suffered a vaccine injury, and you talk about that on Facebook, you will be evicted. You're not, you will never get on a TV program to talk about that.  When Ron Johnson, Senator from Wisconsin, had a group of people, of physicians and people who've been injured -- clearly injured by vaccines, including people who were part of clinical trial, ended up public hearing in front of the United States Senate committee last week and recorded their sworn testimony. And all of that was removed from YouTube.  Cause you are no longer are allowed to criticize government policies. Oh yeah. I will go to places that, you know, people -- I've always done that. I've always been willing to talk to people who don't agree with me on virtually anything. I've been on Hannity probably a dozen times. Hannity and I agree on literally zero. I think democracy is about building bridges to people with whom you don't agree. With creating, you know, finding where there is common ground with other human beings. The biggest thing. The most important productive strategy or the big talk around the oligarchs and the intelligence agencies and the pharmaceutical companies who are trying to impoverish us and, you know, and, and dramatically, and, and obliterate democracy, their strategy is to create fear and division. So orchestrated fear and divide Republicans from Democrats and blacks from whites and get a lot of infighting so nobody notices that they are making themselves billions and billions, and while they impoverish the rest of us and, and, and execute the controlled demolition of American constitutional democracy. And we need to talk, I probably agree with you on almost nothing. I came on here because I'm willing to talk to anybody who is willing to listen about this. Uh, you know, I think we need to start talking to each other even about with people we don't agree. My father told me that partisanship is poison and it's intellectually dishonest. It's tribalism. It's bad for democracy.  Now we need to start talking to people as human beings, not as Republicans and Democrats. Now I don't have to agree with Tucker Carlson on, on anything. If he invites me on a show, I'm going to go on it. Because he has a big audience. And I don't. have to agree with you, Michael. I appreciate you letting me talk to your audience. It does not mean I am endorsing your views. [...] COHEN: Based on your findings, do you believe that Dr. Fauci and Bill Gates should be investigated for criminal wrongdoing? RFK JR.: Yes. COHEN: Plain and simple? RFK JR.: Of course. I mean, I think Fauci's policies -- 80% of the people who died from COVID should not have died. We should've been doing early treatment like the Chinese did. The Chinese put early treatment protocols with chloroquine, which is hydroxy -- the cousin of the hydroxychloroquine. In April, they had protocols with all the drugs we know are effective, anti-coagulants, anti-inflammatory steroids, hydroxychloroquine or chloroquine, and then vitamins, Vitamin D... they had dozens and dozens of Chinese herbs on their protocol that they published. And guess what? They obliterated the pandemic after a month and a half using early treatment, the Chinese had three deaths per million population, you know, but Tony Fauci, had 2,200 Americans. We have the biggest body count in the world because of his policies. We have, we have 4.2% of the global population. We had 14.5% of the casualty COVID casualties. Why is that a success? Right. Of course he should be criminally prosecuted because what he did was clearly, clearly demonstrably purposeful. And I can prove that in front of a jury. We know. And if you, if you read my book, just the first chapter, you will see that indictment laid out clear as day. He deliberately sabotaged by using fraudulent methodologies, ivermectin, hydroxy chloroquine, and promoted a drug that he knew was deadly, Remdesivir. RFK Jr. in the aforementioned interview with Tucker Carlson on the threat of Anthony Fauci and Bill Gates:  RFK Jr. speaks at the Friday, November 12, 2021, protest against abusive health measures in Bern, Switzerland:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germans will be 'vaccinated, cured or dead' by spring, declares health minister...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/jens-spahn-germany-biontech-pfizer-covid-19-vaccination/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jens Spahn rushes out extra doses of BioNTech/Pfizer shot, calls Moderna the ‘Rolls Royce’ of vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones, Roger Stone subpoenaed by Jan. 6 committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/jan-6-committee-subpoenas-alex-jones-roger-stone-other-trump-n1284389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The committee's new batch of subpoenas is in connection with a rally held near the Capitol shortly before a pro-Trump mob stormed the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDEA:  Democracy slipping away at record rate, intergovernmental body warns...</title>
      <link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/rest-of-world/democracy-slipping-away-at-record-rate-intergovernmental-body-warns/articleshow/87840374.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofindia.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rest of World News: A greater number of countries are sliding towards authoritarianism, the International Institute for Democracy and Electoral Assistance said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'40 To 50 Wielding Hammers'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/smash-grab-thieves-target-hayward-mall-lululemon-store-san-jose-robbed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looters targeting Bay Area businesses struck again Sunday evening, with smash-and-grab thieves hitting the Southland Mall in Hayward and suspects taking merchandise from a Lululemon store in San Jose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Economic Concerns Hit Pandemic High...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/357617/economic-concerns-hit-pandemic-high-low-historically.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mentions of economic issues as the most important problem facing the U.S. are at a pandemic high, but remain well below historical norms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron suspended for altercation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lebron-james-isaiah-stewart-suspended-2229c936a38c32df10c3f6c544bae0cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James of the Los Angeles Lakers has been suspended for one game and Detroit's Isaiah Stewart was suspended two games for their roles in an ugly incident during Sunday's Lakers-Pistons game. The NBA announced the suspensions Monday, and both will affect games on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple busted for sex in rear of police car...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/sex/tryst-in-fhp-car-902561</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVEMBER 22--While seated in the rear of a Florida Highway Patrol cruiser, Summer Watkins had a brilliant idea. “Baby, we should record an OnlyFans video back here,” the 24-year-old yelled to her ma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel Warns New Covid Spike 'Worse Than Anything Seen'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/merkel-says-german-covid-spike-120052541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Chancellor Angela Merkel said the latest surge in Covid-19 infections is worse than anything Germany has experienced so far and called for tighter restrictions to help check the spread.Most Read from BloombergNew York City Is Building a Wall of Oysters to Fend Off FloodsA Denser City, But at What Cost?The Women Behind Historic House DesignsFrom Bathhouses to Fisheries, Hidden Inflation Is Creeping Across JapanMaverick 70-Year-Old CEO Is Determined to Shake Up Japanese FinanceMerke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHY?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/waukesha-wisconsin-christmas-parade-crash-388eec09cc3543874d30352e197168ca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAUKESHA, Wis. (AP) — The SUV driver who plowed into a Christmas parade in suburban Milwaukee, killing at least five people and injuring 48, was leaving the scene of a domestic dispute that had taken place just minutes earlier, Waukesha’s police chief said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones, Roger Stone subpoenaed by House Jan. 6 committee...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-roger-stone-capitol-siege-subpoenas-alex-jones-eed9f4013bef0100117c4ec004d6828e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A committee investigating the Jan. 6 U.S. Capitol insurrection issued subpoenas Monday to five more individuals, including former President Donald Trump’s ally Roger Stone and conspiracy theorist Alex Jones, as lawmakers deepened their probe of the rallies that preceded the deadly attack.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto community tried to buy Constitution. Now it has $40 million mess...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjb8av/constitutiondao-aftermath-everyone-very-mad-confused-losing-lots-of-money-fighting-crying-etc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ConstitutionDAO tried to buy the Constitution. Now it has a $40 million mess on its hands and entire refunds are being wiped out by high fees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops kick grandma out of hotel after bad online review...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10230523/Granny-63-granddaughter-6-kicked-hotel-POLICE-gave-bad-review.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Susan Leger, 63, was on the first of her three-night stay at the Baymont Inn &amp; Suites in the mountain town of Helen, Georgia when she got a call from the hotel manager telling her she had to leave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate Warrior Warns: 'Pipelines will be blown up'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/pipelines-will-be-blown-up-says-david-suzuki-if-leaders-dont-act-on-climate-change</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why people with mental illness are at higher risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/11/22/1057258797/why-people-with-mental-illness-are-at-higher-risk-of-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal health officials have been urging adults with psychiatric conditions to get a booster shot to increase their COVID protection. It turns out being mentally ill puts you at higher risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos donates $100M to Obama Foundation...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jeff-bezos-donation-obama-foundation-196365ec-4dd4-4782-b614-b80522638b34.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the largest individual donation the Obama Foundation has received to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch PM lashes out at 'idiots' after 3rd night of violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.news24.com/news24/world/news/dutch-pm-lashes-out-at-idiots-after-third-night-of-violence-20211122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch Prime Minister Mark Rutte lashed out at "idiot" rioters who rampaged through cities across the Netherlands this weekend when protests against coronavirus policies turned violent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEARTLAND TERROR: RAPPER KILLS 5</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4119750/criminal-history-darrell-brooks-bailed-waukesha-rittenhouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE suspect in the Christmas parade rampage that left five dead had fled a domestic dispute moments before the horror crash and had been bailed just days before the frenzied attack, police said on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cohen Suggests More Legal Pressure Coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/michael-cohen-suggests-more-trumpworld-prosecutions-are-coming-in-first-tv-interview-after-release-from-house-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump lawyer Michael Cohen not-so-subtly suggested on Monday that more people in former President Donald Trump's orbit will be prosecuted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT ON 'INAPPROPRIATELY LOW' BOND</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/22/waukesha-suspect-darrell-brooks-bond-was-inappropriately-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Milwaukee District Attorney’s office admitted to setting an “inappropriately low” bond earlier this month for Darrell Brooks, the man allegedly behind the Christmas parade cra…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITTENHOUSE:  I SUPPORT BLACK LIVES MATTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/kyle-rittenhouse-tells-tucker-carlson-hes-not-a-racist-person-and-supports-blm-this-case-has-nothing-to-do-with-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyle Rittenhouse was interviewed by Fox News’ Tucker Carlson, his first media appearance since he was found not guilty of all five charges against him in his murder trial. In a clip from that interview released by Fox News, Rittenhouse insisted that his actions “had nothing to do with race,” and expressed support for the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black militia rally outside courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10230209/Prosecution-argues-Ahmaud-Arbery-defenseless-attacked-killed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense attorney Jason Sheffield tried to refute the prosecution's allegation that Arbery was defenseless. He said Travis McMichael believed Arbery, who was 'armed with his fists,' was a threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5% of Federal Workers Not Complying With Biden Mandate?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10230391/Biden-reveals-95-federal-employees-vaccinated-ahead-Monday-deadline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 95% of federal workers received at least one dose of a COVID-19 vaccine by Monday's deadline set by President Joe Biden, the White House said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental chewing gum may reduce virus spread...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211122182257-pyqb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/SCIENCE (GRAPHIC):COVID SCIENCE-Experimental chewing gum may reduce virus spread; Booster shot protection may be longer lasting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOUIS VUITTON, SAKS Storefronts Smashed in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/21/storefront-windows-of-louis-vuitton-saks-fifth-avenue-on-rodeo-drive-damaged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities on Sunday were investigating the circumstances surrounding two incidences in Beverly Hills that resulted in windows to two stores being smashed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX employee at center of Chappelle protest resigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/netflix-employee-center-dave-chappelle-protest-resigns-rcna6362</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terra Field, a Netflix employee at the center of worker-led protests against Dave Chappelle, is resigning from the company, she said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area hit by THIRD consecutive day of looting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10230017/Bay-Area-hit-consecutive-day-brazen-looting-gang-mall-jewelry-store.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco Bay Area faced a third consecutive day of brazen shoplifting on Sunday when a jewelry store in Hayward was raided as was a Lululemon in San Jose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER starts delivering pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211122-uber-starts-taking-cannabis-orders-in-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber is riding high in Canada, announcing Monday it was starting to take orders for recreational cannabis -- along with munchies -- through its Eats service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Cop Given No Jail Time For Rape Conviction...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/11/22/baltimore-county-officer-sentenced-to-home-detention-for-rape-of-22-year-old-woman/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge determined that Westerman should be released on home detention pending the appeal of his convictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black population continues to drop in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-the-black-population-continues-to-drop-in-chicago-and-illinois-few-regret-their-move-i-have-peace/ar-AAQZGhN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Cases Tick Upward Once More...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/as-thanksgiving-approaches-us-virus-cases-tick-upward-once-more/ar-AAQZ51l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi's Ex-Fixer Testifies PM Spent as Much Time on His Own Image as National Security...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bibi-s-former-fixer-testifies-that-vain-pm-spent-as-much-time-on-his-own-image-as-national-security/ar-AAR0aYQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Hedge fund ALDEN in hunt for another big newspaper chain...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-media-newspapers-6800a21e2d46869249a152f61ef32b9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hedge fund Alden Global Capital, one of the country's largest newspaper owners with a reputation for intense cost cuts and layoffs, has offered to buy the local newspaper chain Lee Enterprises for about $141 million.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
