<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday chaos sweeps world with fights, stampedes, gun scares...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10448541/black-friday-brawl-forever-21-pennsylvania-bargain-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Black Friday sales have seen chaos break out around the world, with fights, stampedes and a gun scare at shops in the US, Brazil, and South Africa. Security guards were filmed fighting to stem …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richest Counties Getting Even Richer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/richest-u-s-counties-getting-wealthier-from-pitkin-to-teton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Richest U.S. Counties Are Getting Even Richer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog pee TD celebration costs Ole Miss in chaotic finish...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/dog-pee-td-celebration-costs-ole-miss-in-chaotic-egg-bowl-finish-041056371.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ole Miss receiver Elijah Moore got a little too frisky when celebrating a touchdown with four seconds remaining.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists Ruined Venice. Now Floods Making It Uninhabitable...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/venice-fraught-future-caught-between-083734735.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Two weeks after high tides and fierce winds produced the worst flooding in Venice in more than half a century, sirens sound about 6:30 a.m. to warn the fragile lagoon city’s weary residents that “acqua alta” is arriving again.Less than two hours later, temporary wooden platforms are in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire's Presidential Legacy Swept Away by Tide of Unrest...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/billionaire-presidential-legacy-swept-away-090000562.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As rioting broke out across Chile in October, President Sebastian Pinera watched his political agenda go up in smoke.Just 18 months after taking office on promises to expand the private pension system, cut taxes for the rich and clamp down on crime, Pinera saw his legislative plans swept</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq PM announces he'll resign amid worsening crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/14bcd26984de4de2a2c039cb3505e3f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — Iraqi Prime Minister Adel Abdul-Mahdi said Friday he would submit his resignation to parliament, a day after more than 40 people were killed by security forces and following calls...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris to Trump: Keep out of it...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129122638-hyaev</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/JOHNSON (UPDATE 2, TV, PIX):UPDATE 2-British PM Johnson to Trump: keep out of UK election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China seeks to root out deepfakes with new online content rules...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191129084514-jkgl3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-TECHNOLOGY/:China seeks to root out fake news and deepfakes with new online content rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans travellers face 'invasive' airport security...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128165827-azkun</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Discrimination concerns are mounting with the growing use of technology by police, security and immigration services that fails to recognise trans and nonbinary people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exotic animals perish in fire at Ohio African Safari Wildlife Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.toledoblade.com/local/animals/2019/11/28/sheriff-crews-battling-fire-at-African-Safari-Wildlife-Park/stories/20191128125</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.toledoblade.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT CLINTON — A blaze killed 10 exotic animals Thursday that were inside a barn at African Safari Wildlife Park in Danbury Township.     Video ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stampede sees shopper carried out on stretcher...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/black-friday-stampede-sees-shopper-20987136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stores across the world have slashed prices on their products Black Friday today. But the excitement spilt over into violence when a stampede was caused at one store</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City traffic chaos a matter of life or death...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-city-traffic-chaos-matter-life-death-014853340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a peculiar scene: in the middle of a busy Mexico City intersection, police officers earnestly blow their whistles, instructing oncoming traffic to stop -- as indifferent drivers speed past them by the dozens. "Nobody stops for anybody," adds her friend Ruben Esposito. The police</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese restaurants rocket to top of best in world list...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/japanese-restaurants-rocket-top-best-world-list-103333130.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Japanese restaurants have shot to the top of the La Liste ranking of best places to eat in the world, with a third one getting the second highest mark from the authoritative "guide of guides". Yosuke Suga's tiny Tokyo restaurant Sugalabo, which has only 20 tables, does not have a Michelin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctica tourism: Quest for Earth's vulnerable extremes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/antarctica-tourism-quest-earths-vulnerable-extremes-042940561.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antarctica, a vast territory belonging to no one nation, is a continent of extremes: the coldest place on Earth, the windiest, the driest, the most desolate and the most inhospitable. On this strip of land, that juts out of the Antarctic Polar and towards South America, visitors can see wildlife normally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI issues warning about smart TVs...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/black-friday-smart-tv-buyers-should-take-this-fbi-cybersecurity-advice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI is offering cybersecurity advice to people who purchase new smart TVs on Black Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian Police Discover a Plot to Create a New Nazi Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-italy-nazi/italy-uncovers-plot-to-create-new-nazi-party-idUSKBN1Y21O1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian police said on Thursday they uncovered a plot to form a new Nazi party a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI issues warning about smart TVs...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/black-friday-smart-tv-buyers-should-take-this-fbi-cybersecurity-advic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record breaking climber dies after plummeting 600ft down mountain in Mexico... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7736067/Brad-Gobright-31-dies-Mexico-rappelling-accident-partner-dropped-end-shared-rope.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brad Gobright, 31, was simul-rappelling on Wednesday in Mexico with Aiden Jacobson, 26. The pair, who met on the day of their climb, hadn't tied knots in their rope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nutcracker sways violently in the wind and pummels marcher... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7735443/The-balloons-fly-Macys-Thanksgiving-day-parade.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of people lined the streets of New York to watch the 2019 Macy's Thanksgiving Parade, featuring a dazzling display of giant balloons, which flew despite concerns over the wind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London police defend decision to drop Epstein investigation... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/nov/28/london-police-defend-decision-to-drop-jeffrey-epstein-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Giuffre says Met did not act after she alleged she had been forced to sleep with Prince Andrew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA aims to reset standards for plane seats, but tests are disputed...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/FAA-aims-to-reset-standards-for-planes-seats-14869499.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a special center in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, researchers from the Federal Aviation Administration are running a series of drills that could affect the comfort and safety of millions of airplane passengers.  More than 700 residents have been recruited to help determine whether the space between airplane seats or the size of the seats affects their ability to evacuate an aircraft.  The drills mark the first time the FAA is examining whether the trend toward smaller seats and less personal space on today's planes poses safety risks to those aboard in the event of an emergency.  But consumer advocates and lawmakers are worried that the results of the tests are flawed, because the people the agency recruited don't reflect the demographics of today's flying public.  The FAA said the pool of volunteers includes adults between 18 and 60. Lawmakers and consumer advocates note that there are no children or travelers with disabilities. The pool also does not include animals, which are a growing presence in today's cabins, said Rep. Steve Cohen, D-Tenn.  "You've got to have a representative sample," Cohen said. "This is supposed to be a scientific study, but it's flawed from the get-go."  An FAA spokesman declined to address concerns about the demographics of the test pool.  The issue is of keen interest for Cohen, a frequent traveler. He, along with Rep. Adam Kinzinger, R-Ill., co-wrote the provision in the 2018 FAA reauthorization bill that required the agency conduct these exercises as part of the push to set minimum standards for seat size and pitch.  There are no federal rules regarding seat size. Manufacturers, however, must demonstrate that there is enough space to allow passengers to evacuate the aircraft in 90 seconds or less.  "The testing is a research project, following...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLACK FRIDAY FLAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7737071/Black-Friday-panic-Stores-slash-prices-80-cent-win-shoppers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stores are slashing prices by up to 80 per cent for Black Friday to win over shoppers who have grown suspicious of cut-price deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busted MCDONALD'S balloon dragged from Thanksgiving Day Parade...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/28/ronald-mcdonald-balloon-partially-deflates-at-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He wasn’t lovin’ it. A limp Ronald McDonald balloon was dragged from the Thanksgiving Day parade Thursday after it was allowed to fly despite a 3-inch gash in his leg that only grew larger as gusts…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE:  As flu sacks eight Patriots, kicker Nick Folk is out after appendectomy...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/news/article/As-flu-sacks-eight-Patriots-kicker-Nick-Folk-is-14869306.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New England Patriots were scrambling, losing their kicker and picking up a little something besides a victory in the chilly rain last week as they prepared for a prime time game Sunday. Kicker Nick Folk will miss the game after having an appendectomy Thursday morning and eight players - five of whom are starters - missed practice Wednesday because of "flulike symptoms." Missing were defensive starters Patrick Chung, Stephon Gilmore, Dont'a Hightower and Jamie Collins Sr., and offensive lineman Isaiah Wynn. Also out were cornerback Joejuan Williams, running back Damien Harris and tight end Ryan Izzo. Offensive tackle Marcus Cannon was limited after being sick last week. "This is probably, for me, in my 10 years here, the most guys I've seen just be gone from being sick," safety Devin McCourty said, according to the Boston Herald. "No injuries or anything, we just had guys come in and you look in their eyes and you could just tell they were just out of it. Hopefully a day at home and meds and rest can help guys out." The bug's origin isn't clear. In the days leading up to last week game, which the Patriots won, 13-9, on a rainy, windy and chilly night, the Cowboys were battling a flu bug and Cannon had been ailing for 48 hours before that game. "We're all working together on this - the player, the medical staff and the coaching staff. Unless the player is cleared medically, there's no conversation to be had," Coach Bill Belichick said. "If the player is cleared medically, then it enters into some element of a coaching, player conversation. As I said, each one is different, and we just try to do the best we can." The Patriots planned to practice Thursday and again Friday before flying to Houston on Saturday. "It's going around, but we've just got to live a healthy lifestyle," wide receiver Phillip Dorsett said....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nixon went quietly. Would Trump? </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Nixon-went-quietly-Would-Trump-14869452.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fervent anti-Trumpers recall the scene the way the faithful venerate The Annunciation.  On Aug. 7, 1974, Sen. Barry Goldwater of Arizona led a small delegation of GOP congressional leaders to the Oval Office to tell President Richard Nixon that he no longer had enough support to survive an impeachment trial in the Senate. Multiple books have replayed the storied moment: the curmudgeonly Goldwater sitting opposite the president's desk; House Republican leader John Rhodes sitting to one side; Senate Minority Leader Hugh Scott to the other. It became received wisdom that the trio's visitation altered history. After all, Nixon announced his resignation the next day.  In reality, Nixon didn't need to be persuaded. When he met with Goldwater and Co., Nixon had already decided to resign (he was a good vote counter). The senators, as it turned out, never actually used the word "resign." Instead, they told the president, he had lost his party's support. It's true what they say about the Oval Office; not even giant killers speak their minds in that haunted room.  Nonetheless, we can wonder what it would take to make history, in effect, repeat itself. What would compel President Donald Trump's own party to show him the door?  The answer, it appears, is nothing. The Republicans are even more dug in on Trump than they were on Nixon. It could happen - but only if congressional leaders are willing to risk a true constitutional crisis.  Right now, Democratic leaders seem intent on a quick process: impeachment in the House before Christmas and a trial in the Senate sometime in the next few months. House leaders believe they have enough evidence to impeach the president. Finding enough Republicans to convict him in the Senate by a two-thirds vote looks impossible.  Or so it appears with the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'ET' PHONES COMCAST...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/11/et-phone-home-again-reunion-short-film-premiere-nbc-and-syfy-universal-steven-spielberg-1202796382/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A short film reuniting the creature from E.T. The Extra-Terrestrial and Henry Thomas, who played Elliott in the 1982 Steven Spielberg film, is premiering Thursday on NBC, Syfy and on the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replaced by ice block in TV debate...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128194912-ica6g</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/CHANNEL4 (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-UK's Johnson replaced by ice block in TV debate, Conservatives cry foul</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poll shows biggest since Thatcher...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/boris-johnson-set-68-seat-235909113.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up to our Brexit Bulletin, follow us @Brexit and subscribe to our podcast.Boris Johnson’s Conservative Party is on track to win its biggest majority in more than three decades, according to the most hotly anticipated poll of the general election campaign.The Tories will win a majority</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump makes surprise visit to troops in Afghanistan... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/president-trump-makes-surprise-thanksgiving-visit-to-afghanistan-today/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President shows up in Afghanistan on Thursday for a surprise Thanksgiving visit with troops engaged in America's longest-ever military conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ilhan Omar challenger suspended from TWITTER for posting lynching threats...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/nov/27/ilhan-omar-challenger-permanently-suspended-from-t/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Danielle Stella, a Republican seeking to unseat Rep. Ilhan Omar, Minnesota Democrat, was suspended from Twitter after her account posted Tuesday about lynching the congresswoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA CANCELS MORE DATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/28/madonna-remember-shes-still-on-tour-skips-her-boston-dates-to-cancel-is-a-kind-of-punishment-for-me-but-the-pain-im-in-right-now-is-overwhelming</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Madonna is like a sturgeon this Thanksgiving. She’s cancelled her Boston dates– three shows– due to physical injury. She writes on Instagram: “Please forgive this unexpected…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Frees Some Detained Writers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/saudi-arabia-frees-some-bloggers-writers-held-last-week/ar-BBXszwI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen on the brink: Retirement plan could see King Charles in two years...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/royal/1209789/royal-family-news-queen-elizabeth-ii-prince-charles-prince-andrew-royal-succession</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUEEN ELIZABETH II is supposedly giving serious thought of stepping down and handing over the reign to Prince Charles, when she turns 95 in two years time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCUSED OF POACHING 'GOD CONTROL'...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/fischerspooners-casey-spooner-says-madonna-didnt-pay-or-credit-him-for-madame-x-song/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spooner on not being compensated or credited for â€œGod Controlâ€�: â€œI HAVE HAD ENOUGHâ€�</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's drone industry becomes global force...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israels-drone-industry-becomes-global-force-050802515.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a fierce battle for market share against world superpowers China and the United States, Israel's drone industry likes to say it has a secret weapon -- military experience. Unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) are used daily by Israel's military in and around its borders, whether dropping tear-gas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 Iraqi protesters shot dead in 24 hours, violence spirals...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128122259-ohy6p</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAQ-PROTESTS/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Iraqi forces kill 28 protesters after Iranian consulate torched</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKOREA POPS OFF</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128111049-zt1dx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-MISSILES/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-N.Korea test fires rockets in Thanksgiving reminder of year-end deadline for U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blogger tests Singapore's 'fake news' law by rebuffing correction order...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128085505-2hlj1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE-FAKENEWS/:Blogger tests Singapore's fake news law by rebuffing correction order</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not enough babies being born to replace population; Birth rate plunges to 30-year low...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10439803/babies-born-30-year-low-america-fertility/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING statistics reveal that not enough babies are being born to replace the US population – as birth rates plunge to a 30 year low. The report revealed that the fertility rate dropped to …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fury as tourists carve initials into ancient Mayan temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/two-tourists-caught-carving-initials-20979987  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The men scratched 'A&amp;P' into the wall of a temple in Tikal National Park, which was declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1979 to preserve pre-colonial culture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump banker Dies by Suicide in Malibu...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/citythinkblog/deutsche-bank-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Bowers, who worked above Trump's personal banker, was 55</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Iraqi protesters shot dead in 24 hours, violence spirals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/de6d09e824b54091a070d5a815e93a2a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — Security forces in Iraq shot dead 20 protesters in a 24-hour period amid spiraling violence in the capital and the country’s south, as Iran condemned the burning of its...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KIM UNTHANKFUL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/773e2ffd5e5c461f99993c274181bfee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — North Korea on Thursday fired two short-range projectiles, likely from a “super-large” multiple rocket launcher, South Korea’s military said, adding to tensions three...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opponents attack Johnson's character as UK election looms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/65a55502bbc4458ba46041e91434f29e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Britain’s opposition parties intensified attacks on Prime Minister Boris Johnson on Thursday with two weeks to go until election day, with polls suggesting the U.K. leader’s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks in Congo kill Ebola responders...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/444a95f488fd4103a7a72cb2db96645d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BENI, Congo (AP) — Rebels have killed four Ebola response workers in eastern Congo, the World Health Organization said Thursday, an alarming development that could cause the waning outbreak to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France to ban Black Friday sales?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3540afdb15584461b71aff7dbd29dd6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — Some French lawmakers want to ban Black Friday, the post-Thanksgiving sales event that has morphed into a global phenomenon. A legislative committee passed an amendment Monday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summons ambassador... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/30458ce0af5b4c8e8e8a19c8621a25fd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China reacted furiously Thursday to President Donald Trump’s signing two bills aimed at supporting human rights in Hong Kong, summoning the U.S. ambassador to protest and warning...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cats to be put on leashes to protect wildlife? EU says No...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ea2d3edea304defa0375a7dbedc35ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Put domestic cats on a leash to better protect threatened birds and the environment? The European Union says that would deny mankind’s furry friend its unalienable right to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam jails three more activists in crackdown on FACEBOOK posts...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191128114423-u7iyy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VIETNAM-SECURITY/TRIALS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Vietnam jails three more activists in crackdown on Facebook posts</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
