<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Longtime FOXNEWS correspondent Wendell Goler dead at 70...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/wendell-goler-longtime-fox-news-white-house-correspondent-dead-at-70</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Longtime Fox News White House correspondent Wendell Goler died this week at age 70.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venture firm SEQUOIA sounds alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/sequoia-capital-alerts-companies-about-coronavirus-economic-fallout.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sequoia Capital sent out a memo to founders and CEOs of its portfolio companies about the worsening economic situation on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishing staff walks out over Woody Allen memoir...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/03/05/litlte-brown-staff-stages-walkout-in-support-of-ronan-and-dylan-farrow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff at Little, Brown publishers have staged a walkout in support of Ronan Farrow and his sister Dylan Farrow, following its parent company’s plans to publish Woody Allen’s memoir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Do Such Elderly People Run America?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/03/why-are-these-people-so-freaking-old/607492/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders is too old. So is Biden. Trump too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney could derail Republican subpoena targeting Bidens...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/05/hunter-biden-subpoena-mitt-romney-122207</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Utah Republican is concerned the push appears intended to undermine a Trump rival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE Agents Ignore Sanctuary Law, Make Arrest In Front Of San Fran Courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/05/ice-agents-ignore-sanctuary-law-san-francisco-courthouse-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local officials were irate Thursday over the arrest by federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents of an individual as he entered San Francisco courthouse for a hearing in violation of the city's sanctuary law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN plotting dream 'MONDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL' booth: Michaels, Manning...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/05/espn-plotting-dream-monday-night-football-booth-al-michaels-and-peyton-manning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thinking large and outside the box, ESPN plans to attempt to acquire Al Michaels from NBC Sports for “Monday Night Football,” The Post has learned. ESPN would like to team Michaels with…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's First Cloned Cat Passes Away At 18...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2020/03/04/worlds-first-cloned-cat-cc-lived-long-normal-happy-life-before-her-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first cloned cat named "Copy Cat" or "CC" for short, has passed away at the age of 18 after veterinarians diagnosed her with kidney failure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How blood plasma from recovered patients could help treat...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2020/03/05/how-blood-plasma-from-recovered-patients-could-help-treat-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The approach is based on the idea that antibodies developed by recovered patients might strengthen the immune system of new patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House sidelines health secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/05/white-house-alex-azar-coronavirus-122250</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HHS Secretary Alex Azar has gone from the face of President Donald Trump's virus team to a supporting character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton blames Lewinsky affair on job pressures...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8078733/Bill-Clinton-says-having-sex-Monica-Lewinsky-manage-anxieties.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former President makes the explosive claims in an interview featured in a new documentary series about his wife Hillary Clinton, called 'Hillary', out on Hulu Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans see Joe wins as setback...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/486042-republicans-rooting-for-sanders-see-biden-wins-as-setback</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican lawmakers are surprised and disappointed by the results of Super Tuesday, which firmly re-established former Vice President Joe Biden as the front-runner for the Democratic presidential nomination and dealt Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to take questions at 1st TV town hall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c03cd0c8f2a41ad0300092fff48ee4f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump will field questions at his first TV town hall of the 2020 election cycle Thursday in the city that helped to shape a would-be rival, former Vice President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein being moved to Rikers despite bid to stay at hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/harvey-weinstein-being-moved-to-rikers-despite-bid-to-stay-at-bellevue-sources-say/2313943/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sources confirm Weinstein is being moved to the Rikers North Infirmary Unit from Bellevue. Those sources believe he will be put in protective custody in a “dorm cell” setting with round-the-clock supervision and medical supervision as needed. Weinstein’s team pushed hard to have him remain at Bellevue until sentencing, arguing he needed ongoing medical care connected to a hospital….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EASTER FEAR 2020...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c57bc457c0c1c02a910c1564d8f76715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BETHLEHEM, West Bank (AP) — Palestinian officials on Thursday closed the storied Church of the Nativity in the biblical city of Bethlehem indefinitely over fears of the new coronavirus, weeks...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAVE TO THE APPLE:  Gadgets for tech giants made with coerced Uighur labor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3f9a92b8dfd3cae379b57622dd801dd5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NANCHANG, China (AP) — In a lively Muslim quarter of Nanchang city, a sprawling Chinese factory turns out computer screens, cameras and fingerprint scanners for a supplier to international tech...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea tests hundreds of thousands...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/south-korea-tests-hundreds-thousands-210000450.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Highly contagious and manifesting in some with little or no symptoms, the coronavirus has the world struggling to keep up. But when it comes to containing the epidemic, one country may be cracking the code -- by doubling down on testing.South Korea is experiencing the largest virus epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS bans personal cups...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/starbucks-bans-personal-cups-over-coronavirus-161236531.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reusable cups are in vogue for reducing waste but are no longer welcome at Starbucks cafes over fears of the coronavirus, the coffee chain announced. "We are pausing the use of personal cups and 'for here' ware in our stores," Rossann Williams, an executive vice president, said in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore:  Lying about where you've been gets 6 months of jail... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/singapore-working-round-clock-coronavirus-153100020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The system relies on surveillance footage, police, and a dedicated team of contact tracers, who map out where patients went before they got COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi empties Islam's holiest site... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-empties-islams-holiest-sterilisation-161118787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia on Thursday emptied Islam's holiest site for sterilisation over fears of the new coronavirus, an unprecedented move after the kingdom suspended the year-round umrah pilgrimage. State television relayed stunning images of an empty white-tiled area surrounding the Kaaba -– a large black</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REGRET...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305151143-v7hi5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/SCHUMER (URGENT):Democratic U.S. Senator Schumer expresses regret for Supreme Court comments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christ's birthplace in Bethlehem quarantined...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305112530-ck0oy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/PALESTINIANS-CHURCH (URGENT):Bethlehem's Church of the Nativity ordered closed over coronavirus fears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More worry in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/2-more-covid-19-cases-in-ny-brings-total-to-13-community-spread-eyed-in-possible-nj-case-as-state-awaits-tests/2313298/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the announcement, the patient is a man in his 30s who is hospitalized in Bergen County. He has been in the hospital since March 3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christ's birthplace in Bethlehem quarantined...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/jesus-christs-birthplace-bethlehem-quarantined-21639198</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Church of the Nativity in the occupied West Bank has been shut down “indefinitely” due to the global epidemic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious black rain falls on Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mysterious-black-rain-falls-japanese-21638038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A social media user asked "are they secretly burning bodies of coronavirus victims?" after the dark-coloured rain fell overnight just north of the Japanese capital Tokyo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Citizen patrols ward off 'invasion' on Greek-Turkish border...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/citizen-patrols-ward-off-invasion-greek-turkish-border-151945679.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tranquil the site may look but it has become a favoured entry point for migrants, as locals know only too well, prompting some to join so-called citizens patrols. Despite the late hour, farm worker Sakis, clad in military fatigues, is wide awake, as he patrols along the river Evros, right on the Turkish</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Idaho turning a little blue? Primary might provide clues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/45486c6b90f7cae1b237248fef3f05bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOISE, Idaho (AP) — Idaho last year was the fastest-growing state in the nation, with close to 37,000 new residents boosting its population to nearly 1.8 million. In the past decade,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Orders Tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/us-factory-orders-tumble-january-sixth-straight-month-yoy-contraction</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Double Downer' Predicts More Pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/etfs-and-funds/sectors/sp500-double-downer-warning-foretells-more-stock-pain-this-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St Wild Ride Continues...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/us-markets-dow-futures-indicate-opening-drop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday's slump comes after days of wild swings on Wall Street, which saw the Dow moving 1,000 points or higher twice in three days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruise Ship With Sick Passengers Stuck In Limbo Off California...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/05/coronavirus-fears-keeps-grand-princess-in-limbo-off-california-coast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Grand Princess remained hovering off the California coast early Thursday, banned by Gov. Gavin Newsom from docking in San Francisco and any other California port until 21 passengers and crew members suffering from flu-like symptoms were tested for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World braces for months of trouble as virus pushes west...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/435cb3786f0d6692c8143a07e29c3e79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — People around the world braced for months of disruptions from the new virus Thursday as its unrelenting spread brought ballooning infections, economic fallout and sweeping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mortgage Rates All-time Low...</title>
      <link>http://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2020/03/05/1995969/0/en/Mortgage-Rates-Hit-All-time-Low.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.globenewswire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MCLEAN, Va., March 05, 2020 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Freddie Mac (OTCQB: FMCC) today released the results of its Primary Mortgage Market Survey® (PMMS®),...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through apps, not warrants, 'Locate X' allows federal law enforcement to track phones...</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/government-buying-location-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal agencies have big contracts with Virginia-based Babel Street. Depending on where you've traveled, your movements may be in the company's data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 'gay, atheist, leftist' is taking on Poland's right-wing govt -- by running for president...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-03-05/poland-presidential-candidate-robert-biedron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Poland, where the conservative Catholic Church has a deep hold, an atheist, Robert Biedron, is the first gay man in history to run for president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disturbing' black rain falling over Japan...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8077787/Disturbing-black-rain-reported-falling-parts-Japan.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soot-coloured rainwater was reported falling on several wards in Saitama Prefecture in Japan, on 2 March. Many fearful citizens took to Twitter using #blackrain to discover the reason.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA Prepping 'Surge Tents'...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/03/04/coronavirus-san-jose-good-samaritan-hospital-surge-tents-influx-cases-covid19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good Samaritan Hospital in San Jose is prepping “surge tents” to handle a possible influx of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bigger and bigger SUVs, pickups outgrowing garages, parking spaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2020/03/05/suvs-pickups-trucks-garages-parking/4904811002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUVs and pickups are getting so big that they’re starting to have trouble fitting into some home garages, parking garages and public parking spaces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Session In Sauna Works Out Heart Just As Much As Exercise..</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/study-a-session-in-the-sauna-works-out-the-heart-just-as-much-as-exercise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research shows that a short sauna session causes an increase in heart rate and blood pressure comparable to the increase seen from a brief, moderate intensity workout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hysterical pet owners 'asking vets to euthanize their dogs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/hysterical-pet-owners-fearing-coronavirus-21636892</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A vet clinic in Sydney, Australia says it has been getting calls from clients worried their pets could give them coronavirus, and want them put down - but vet Dr Sam Kovac has refused</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey deploys 1,000 police at Greek border to stem push-back of migrants...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305095415-o5dbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYRIA-SECURITY/TURKEY-GREECE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Turkey deploys 1,000 police at Greek border to stem push-back of migrants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How risky is that virus? Your mind may mislead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/580923fa5e2200f98c0a42b5c0d7b236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Anna Alexander, a property manager in Virginia Beach, Virginia, started the day Monday thinking that she might avoid shaking hands because of the coronavirus outbreak. Then...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSBC evacuates London offices after 'worker tests positive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11104026/coronavirus-hsbc-evacuates-london-office-canary-wharf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HSBC has evacuated parts of its Canary Wharf headquarters after a worker tested positive for coronavirus. The bank’s research department was cleared this morning and will now undergo a deep c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airlines could lose up to $113 billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/05/coronavirus-iata-warns-passenger-revenue-could-fall.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airlines could lose $63 billion to $113 billion in revenue for passenger traffic globally in 2020, depending on how the coronavirus spreads, International Air Transport Association (IATA) said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego faces critical quake danger from fault long thought inactive...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/earthquakes/san-diego-area-faces-critical-earthquake-danger-from-fault-long-thought-inactive-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conventional thinking has long been that the San Diego region faces less danger from a devastating earthquake than the Los Angeles or San Francisco areas. But a new landmark study shows just ho…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware attacks prompt tough question for local officials: To pay or not to pay?</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2020/03/03/ransomware-attacks-prompt-tough-question-for-local-officials-to-pay-or-not-to-pay</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touching your face. Here is how to stop doing it...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/a-coronavirus-danger-touching-your-face-here-is-how-to-stop-doing-it/ar-BB10JGKl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel severely restricts entry from Europe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israel-severely-restricts-entry-europe-due-virus-204340338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel on Wednesday imposed tough new travel restrictions on five European nations due to fears of coronavirus, barring entry to almost all non-residents of the Jewish state arriving from these affected countries. Israel had earlier in the day ordered all citizens and residents returning from the five</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus controls increase surveillance danger...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200305002314-damsj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TECH (ANALYSIS):ANALYSIS-Coronavirus controls increase surveillance 'danger'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower says DC cops ordered to downgrade serious crimes to make city seem safer...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/crime/mpd-crime-underreporting-whistleblower-first-interview/65-c242223e-6d71-4741-92c5-f4ba2a1f9a76</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sgt. Charlotte Djossou says she faced retaliation for reporting downgrading of crimes to supervisors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN CAN FINISH BERNIE IN MICHIGAN</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/03/04/joe-biden-bernie-sanders-michigan-121160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next big state on the primary calendar is looking dicey for Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULTRA festival canceled in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/miami-dade/downtown-miami/article240878956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Rips FOXNEWS  -- on FOXNEWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-complains-about-fox-news-on-hannity-i-think-theyre-trying-to-be-very-politically-correct/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump ripped into Fox News in an interview Wednesday night with Fox News primetime host Sean Hannity — citing "difficulties" with the cable news giant. Early on in the 45-mi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty stores, quarantined firefighters: Washington city at virus epicenter reels as death toll rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-03-04/kirkland-washington-coronavirus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kirkland, Wash., was once known for its folksy downtown and spectacular lakefront views. Now it is the U.S. epicenter of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: HOMELESS MAN EATS OWN FECES AT SAN FRAN BUS STOP...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/horror-homeless-man-eats-own-feces-at-san-fran-bus-stop/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgusting video depicts realtime collapse of California city into third world hellhole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State warns voters they shouldn't lick mail-in ballots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/04/us/washington-state-coronavirus-voting-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone knows how to seal a ballot return envelope, right? You lick it shut? Wrong, says Washington's Secretary of State and Department of Health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jagger movie star again in 'BURNT ORANGE HERESY'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/04/mick-jagger-is-a-movie-star-again-in-the-burnt-orange-heresy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Please allow me to introduce myself/I’m a man of wealth and taste.” So sings Mick Jagger at the beginning of the Rolling Stones classic “Sympathy for the Devil.” But when that “man of wealth and t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Thirdhand' smoke poses health risks, say scientists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/thirdhand-smoke-poses-health-risks-us-scientists-222328118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study by scientists at Yale University has found that compounds from tobacco smoke can infiltrate well-ventilated rooms by hitching a ride on peoples' clothes, skin, and hair and then evaporating slowly over time in a process called "off-gassing." Secondhand smoke has been studied</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon downplays new Taliban attacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-downplays-taliban-attacks-235700936.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon on Wednesday played down the gravity of new Taliban attack in Afghanistan that cast doubts on a four-day old peace deal between the insurgent group and the United States. Since the signing in Doha on Saturday, the militants have ramped up violence against Afghan forces, ending a partial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF chief calls for all-out offensive to counteract epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/imf-chief-calls-offensive-counteract-epidemic-163131029.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IMF chief Kristalina Georgieva on Wednesday called for an all-out, "no regrets" response to the new coronavirus epidemic which poses a "serious threat" to the global economy. "At a time of uncertainty... it is better to do more than to do not enough," she said, warning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil economy slows in Bolsonaro's first year...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-economy-slows-bolsonaros-first-135820943.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brazilian economy slowed in President Jair Bolsonaro's first year in office, according to official data released Wednesday, disappointing news for markets that bet on the far-right leader to engineer an economic take-off. Brazil's economy grew 1.1 percent in 2019, down from 1.3 percent in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Married 58 years, victims died side by side...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/local/wilson/2020/03/04/mt-juliet-tennessee-tornado-victims-james-and-donna-eaton-were-married-58-years/4948176002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mt. Juliet tornado victims James and Donna Eaton were about as close as a couple could be in life and death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Kardashian makes another White House visit to talk criminal justice reform...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/04/politics/trump-kim-kardashian-west-white-house/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump will welcome Kim Kardashian West to the White House on Wednesday to discuss criminal justice reform issues and meet three women whose sentences he commuted last month, a source familiar with the matter confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks with Sanders about next steps...</title>
      <link>https://www.boston.com/news/politics/2020/03/04/bernie-sanders-elizabeth-warren-super-tuesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"She will make her own decision in her own time."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman 'mocks'?</title>
      <link>https://www.rawstory.com/2020/03/matt-gaetz-mocks-essential-coronavirus-funding-by-strapping-on-a-gas-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rawstory.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While many have joked that the coronavirus is the beginning of a zombie apocalypse, the truth is that it’s a highly contagious disease that has a higher than normal fatality rate. After debates over how much money would be needed to ensure American safety, Democrats and Republicans finally agreed on a funding package that passed […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBERTS SLAMS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/rare-rebuke-chief-justice-roberts-slams-schumer-threatening-comments-n1150036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You have released the whirlwind and you will pay the price," Schumer said of Trump appointees as the justices were hearing a case on abortion rights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical screener at LAX tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/medical-screener-lax-airport-tests-positive-coronavirus-n1149986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The person was among screeners who are assigned to the airport's in-transit lounge and also "support jetway screening on direct flights from China."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Brady, Belichick Phone Call 'Didn't Go Well'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-and-bill-belichicks-recent-phone-call-about-upcoming-free-agency-didnt-go-well-per-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady and the Patriots appear to be far apart on a deal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED slashing flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/airline-news/2020/03/04/coronavirus-flight-fallout-united-cutting-international-us-service/4954094002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United's moves to cut service are the most aggressive by a U.S. airline since the coronavirus outbreak began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu election lead shrinks, raising prospect of another Israel vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election/netanyahu-election-lead-shrinks-raising-prospect-of-another-israel-vote-idUSKBN20R1JJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel appeared headed into another political stalemate on Wednesday after nearl...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: NASA exec kills neighbor after years long fight over dog poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcwashington.com/news/local/man-killed-in-west-springfield-after-yearslong-fight-between-neighbors-victims-mother/2231021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcwashington.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 24-year-old man was shot and killed Tuesday evening in West Springfield, Virginia, and a man is charged in his murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy deploys emergency field hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/italy-deploys-emergency-field-hospitals-fight-virus-205745872.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A blue tent packed with masked medics in nylon overalls and rubber gloves greets patients outside an Italian hospital at the European epicentre of the new coronavirus epidemic. Welcome to the "sorting" room: an urgently deployed army-style field hospital where people running a fever or showing</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
