<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Why Brain, Memories Have Such Strong Link To Smell...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/brain-memories-link-to-smell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brain cells in the olfactory cortex - the area of the brain that controls smell - make the link between specific scents and places.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax podcaster hospitalized on ventilator...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/an-anti-vax-podcaster-has-reportedly-contracted-covid-19-and-now-is-hospitalized-on-a-ventilator/ar-AAS9LQL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Magic' Weight-Loss Pills, Covid Cures: Dr. Oz Under the Microscope...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/12/26/magic-weight-loss-pills-and-covid-cures-dr-oz-under-the-microscope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wealth of evidence now shows that the malaria drugs hydroxychloroquine and chloroquine were not effective at treating Covid-19 and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin to mull options if West refuses guarantees...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-moscow-1f80249ac893d533fb6fcfdecb3d1ad3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin said Sunday he would ponder a slew of options if the West fails to meet his push for security guarantees precluding NATO's expansion to Ukraine. Earlier this month, Moscow submitted draft security documents demanding that NATO deny membership to Ukraine and other former Soviet countries and roll back its military deployments in Central and Eastern Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon, Mars and asteroid missions are top space goals for '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/space-science-missions-2022-15b89d24-fd17-4067-ade2-da8255878ddf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new year will see more Mars rovers, plus a space probe crashing into an asteroid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to expect from pandemic's third year...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/america-third-year-covid-c779feaa-b257-4544-968d-d2f1b9be862c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a devastating Omicron surge, life may finally be able to resemble normal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMICRON PUSHING USA INTO SOFT LOCKDOWN</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/omicron-is-pushing-america-into-soft-lockdown/ar-AAS9zNl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rodgers breaks Favre's touchdown record...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-cleveland-browns-green-bay-baker-mayfield-f76a41f10f29941c8e9bd026dfe57e4b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GREEN BAY, Wis. (AP) — Rasul Douglas and the Green Bay Packers’ pass defense didn't let the Cleveland Browns spoil Aaron Rodgers’ milestone day. Rodgers surpassed Brett Favre to become Green Bay’s all-time leader in touchdown passes, and the Packers intercepted Baker Mayfield four times in a 24-22 victory over the Cleveland Browns on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tech's Next Monopoly Game: Building Car of Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/12/27/self-driving-car-big-tech-monopoly-525867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From self-driving technology to entertainment and search, Google, Apple and Amazon are trying to gain exclusive access to your vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel PM enters isolation after daughter tests positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-689794</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris charts own course as VP amid intense scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/dec/26/kamala-harris-vice-president-first-year-scrutiny-joe-biden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris is navigating a position that comes with great influence but few formal responsibilities – and the stakes are even higher for her compared to past vice-presidents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buff Bezos shows off physique...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344573/Jeff-Bezos-57-shows-buff-body-St-Barts-girlfriend-Lauren-Sanchez.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buff billionaire Jeff Bezos, 57, lounged on a boat in St. Barts on Friday with his girlfriend Lauren Sanchez, 51. The pair looked loved up in the 81-degree heat as they celebrated the holiday with friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desmond Tutu dead at 90...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/26/africa/desmond-tutu-death-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archbishop Desmond Tutu, the Nobel Peace Prize-winning Anglican cleric whose good humor, inspiring message and conscientious work for civil and human rights made him a revered leader during the struggle to end apartheid in his native South Africa, has died. He was 90.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dad claims 'Let's go Brandon' call with president was joke...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/25/oregon-dad-claims-lets-go-brandon-during-norad-call-was-a-joke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oregon dad who told President Biden “Let’s go Brandon” during the annual White House NORAD Santa-tracking phone call claims he used the coded vulgarity as “a joke,”…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robed in secrecy: How judges accused of misconduct dodge public scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/robed-secrecy-judges-accused-misconduct-can-dodge-public-scrutiny-rcna7638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public’s ability to scrutinize judicial conduct is crucial for transparency’s sake, and is as important as policing and prosecutorial overhauls, judicial ethics experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Texted Boyfriend To Kill Himself Before Suicide. Guilty Of Manslaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/paigeskinner/boston-suicide-texts-you-urtula</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a plea agreement, Inyoung You accepted responsibility that her abusive text messages played a role in Alexander Urtula's suicide, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxing Day Havoc Continues...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/26/hundreds-of-more-flights-canceled-as-omicron-surge-wreaks-havoc-on-christmas-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flights continued to be canceled by the hundreds across the country on Christmas as airline workers come down with the highly contagious COVID-19 Omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's NYC restaurant turns away anti-vaxxers!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4340884/trump-tower-nyc-anti-vaxxers-proof-turned-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump’s NYC restaurant turned away a group of anti-vaxxers on Thursday for refusing to show proof of vaccination. The diners tried entering Trump Grill, located within the former president’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Personality Traits Explain Why People Binge-Watch TV Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/personality-binge-watching-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It turns out that binge watching may lead to a multitude of health issues stemming from behavioral addictions, according to a recent study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES: Airlines scrap nearly 1,000 on Christmas Day!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-airlines-scrap-hundreds-christmas-165427350.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) -U.S. airlines scrapped nearly 1,000 flights on Saturday, the second straight day of massive cancellations as surging COVID-19 infections have sidelined some pilots and other crew members, upending plans for tens of thousands of holiday travelers over the Christmas weekend. A total of 957 Christmas Day flights, including domestic flights and those into or out of the country, were canceled, up from 690 on Christmas Eve, according to a running tally on flight-tracking website FlightAware.com. At least one airline said that it expects hundreds more cancellations on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Elizabeth II, '21 brought sorrow and scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/for-queen-elizabeth-ii-2021-brought-sorrow-and-scandal-to-the-royal-family/ar-AAS71B7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruises once again facing disruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/cruise-ships-covid-19-disruption/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least four ocean cruise ships were turned away from ports of call or were prohibited from letting passengers disembark in the Americas this week because of Covid-19 cases aboard.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
