<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>New pro football leagues may disrupt NFL, college...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2019/02/08/pro-football-new-leagues-aaf-xfl-change-nfl-college-game/2800945002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alternative pro football leagues have failed before, but investors are betting time is right for leagues like AAF and XFL to succeed in shadow of NFL.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harrison Ford delivers apocalyptic climate warning; 'Worldwide destruction'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenational.ae/uae/harrison-ford-delivers-apocalyptic-climate-change-warning-1.823568</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenational.ae&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor spoke out ahead of Dubai's World Government Summit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINDA RONSTADT: Country songs now what I call Midwest mall-crawler music...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-country/linda-ronstadt-interview-live-album-parkinsons-791219/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singer, who retired in 2009, has released the new ‘Live in Hollywood,’ recorded in 1980</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD OF ILLEGALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/After-holiday-lull-Central-American-family-13602434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. border officials said Friday they saw an abrupt drop-off in illegal crossings during the holiday season, but the number of Central Americans arriving in family groups has returned to record levels since then. The lull in unauthorized crossings suggests some Central American migrants - and the smuggling organizations that deliver them to the border - may have taken a break or deferred the journey north until after the holidays. During the first week of January, when the extended Christmas season was still being celebrated in Mexico and Central America, the number of migrant family members taken into custody by U.S. agents fell to as low as 200 on some days, according to preliminary data from U.S. Customs and Border Protection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Bundy's deadly charm still polarizes, 40 years later...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cd9e9b2f3e504338a280d3a39ba0e279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CINCINNATI (AP) — She kept her eyes on the dapper, wavy haired man who smiled, winked and exuded self-confidence as the courtroom proceedings moved along. "I don't know what it is he has, but he's fascinating," the teenage spectator explained to me at the time. "He's impressive. He just has a kind of magnetism." It was that beguiling magnetism that investigators said helped make the object of her interest — Ted Bundy — one of the nation's most prolific serial killers, with at least 30 women and girls' deaths linked to him in a multiple-state spree that spanned the late 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extra! Designer makes news (literally) on runway...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3bd73357d5744557bc7271a6d699c116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — CHAOS! HORROR! PANIC! BABY, IT'S HOT! Designer Jeremy Scott has always liked to make news, but with his latest collection he did it literally, drawing design inspiration from New York's tabloid headlines. Chromatically speaking, Scott's runway show Friday evening at New York Fashion Week was a very disciplined collection in all black and white; Scott usually uses a riot of bright colors and large cartoon graphics in his clothes. Here, garments were emblazoned with an artist's versions of the New York Post and the Daily News — on dresses, trousers, jackets, jumpsuits and much more. Some of the most striking items: dainty, elegant chiffon party dresses printed with tabloid headlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer allegations hurt 'BOHEMIAN' Oscar chances?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/16f6675df584439cb9a5714c0be798e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Director Bryan Singer hasn't been involved with the Queen biopic "Bohemian Rhapsody" for over a year, but with a fresh exposé alleging that he sexually assaulted minors and the British Academy of Film and Television Arts "suspending" his nomination, will he be the film's Oscars Achilles heel?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Doomsday Bunker 26-Feet Beneath Vegas Hits Market...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/02/08/las-vegas-bunker/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A house like no other is for sale in Las Vegas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX shows successful? Who knows?</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/are-netflix-shows-successful-who-knows/505567322/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streaming company refuses to release viewership figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealth concentration near 'levels seen during Roaring Twenties'...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/wealth-concentration-near-levels-last-seen-during-the-roaring-twenties-study-finds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shift is eroding security from families in the lower and middle classes, who rely on their small stores to finance retirement and to smooth over shocks like the loss of a job. And it's consolidating power in the hands...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House hunts for schedule leaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/08/trump-executive-time-schedule-1160691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An exasperated Trump is aware of the search, which is making use of the White House IT office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggressive polar bears invade Russian Arctic islands; Emergency declared...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/russian-arctic-islands-sound-emergency-over-invasion-by-polar-bears-1990975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian Arctic archipelago on Saturday declared an emergency situation over an "invasion" of dozens of aggressive polar bears that have entered homes and public buildings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boom in AI-generated art?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/ai-art-from-mario-klingemann-memories-of-passersby-to-sell</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This Art Has Been Created by AI. Will Collectors Want It?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Brazil, Cat's Away and Mice Just Aren't Playing Nice...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/in-brazil-the-cat-s-away-and-the-mice-just-aren-t-playing-nice</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Brazil, the Cat's Away and the Mice Just Aren't Playing Nice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona considers declaring porn public health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/politics/legislature/2019/02/07/arizona-legislature-considers-declaring-porn-public-health-crisis/2802281002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona ranksÂ fourth-lowest in the country forÂ offering comprehensive sex education in middle school, according to the CDC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could women in white sway soldiers blocking aid? </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/could-women-white-sway-venezuelan-soldiers-blocking-aid-021353085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soldiers blocking humanitarian aid from entering Venezuela look unlikely to give any ground, but Maria Acevedo thinks she knows how to make them let the shipments through. Acevedo, 26, wants to join together with fellow Venezuelan women and escort the food and medicine across the border from Colombia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto to headline counter-Trump rally at border...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/429232-orourke-to-headline-counter-trump-rally-at-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O’Rourke (D-Texas) will headline a rally on Monday in El Paso at the same time that President Trump is set to hold a rally there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO Stands by Michael Jackson Doc 'LEAVING NEVERLAND,' Won't Edit...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/hbo-wont-edit-michael-jackson-doc-leaving-neverland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HBO boss Casey Bloys told TheWrap there is "nothing to" a Friday report that HBO is reconsidering its splashy "Leaving Neverland" documentary acquisition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Moonves Sets Up Shop in Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/08/business/media/les-moonves-moonrise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ousted chief executive of CBS is occupying an office on Hollywood’s Sunset Strip that, per his exit agreement, is being paid for by the network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasty surprise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/07/failed-to-withhold-enough-tax-in-2018-the-irs-has-a-nasty-surprise-for-you.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some early-bird tax filers are getting a nasty surprise from the IRS: a shrunken tax refund or a bill for amounts owed. Here's what you should know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  VICE FOUNDER UNLOADS HOMES IN LA, NY...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/dirt/real-estalker/shane-smith-los-angeles-manhattan-1203133371/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian gonzo journalist turned alt-media tycoon Shane Smith, co-founder and Executive Chairman of the millennially focused Vice Media empire, has listed the smaller of his two multi-million dolla…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial biometrics catches woman from Mexico at JFK...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/biometrics-catches-impostor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal authorities say a 26-year-old woman who arrived at John F. Kennedy Airport in New York City was caught using a passport that didn&amp;#39;t belong to her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND WOMAN ACCUSES LT. GOV. OF RAPE...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6684537/Second-woman-accuses-Lieutenant-Governor-Virginia-Justin-Fairfax-rape.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meredith Watson has accused Lieutenant Governor Justin Fairfax of sexually assaulting her in 2000 - when they were both students at Duke University, her attorney said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I see you watching.' Rise of digital home invasions via smart device hacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/business/ct-biz-nest-cameras-hacked-20190204-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As connected devices increasingly populate the home, replacing regular refrigerators, doorbells and more with versions that can be connected to the internet and controlled via smartphone, experts say hacking incidents of the unassuming household objects are on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dubbed a troll, viral videomaker faces 21 charges: Harassment, trespassing...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-marquel-carter-20190207-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore man with the online persona "Plainpotatoess" has been charged with more than 20 counts of harassment and trespassing stemming from incidents that allegedly occurred while he was filming videos to go on his viral social media accounts, according to police and city officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo freaks, Senator touts 'bad, secret deal consequences'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsday.com/long-island/amazon-reconsider-new-york-city-campus-1.27064592</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In response, an Amazon critic faults the governor for making a "secret" and "bad" giveaway deal with the internet giant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space stations to be built INSIDE asteroids?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6683841/Scientists-want-build-space-station-INSIDE-asteroid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Maindl from the University of Vienna in Austria say there are twofold benefits to the plan. It would allow avoid damage from radiation as well as enabling mining to take place.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe calls for VA Lt. Gov to resign after rape accusation...</title>
      <link>https://wtvr.com/2019/02/08/former-gov-mcauliffe-on-second-fairfax-accusation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtvr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Virginia Governor Terry McAuliffe is calling for Lt. Governor Justin Fairfax’s resignation after a second sexual assault accusation in the last week, calling the claims “serious and credible.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREENWALD: Bezos Suffers Grotesque Privacy Threat While Building Surveillance State...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2019/02/08/jeff-bezos-protests-the-invasion-of-his-privacy-as-amazon-builds-a-sprawling-surveillance-state-for-everyone-else/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world's greatest privacy invaders just had his privacy invaded.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ghost apples' at Michigan orchard...</title>
      <link>https://www.woodtv.com/news/kent-county/icy-rain-creates-ghost-apples-in-kent-county/1762758353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.woodtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The freezing rain created an unusual phenomenon in the Fruit Ridge area of Kent County: "ghost apples."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE Host Saudi Govt App That Tracks Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.thisisinsider.com/apple-google-criticised-for-saudi-government-app-activists-say-fuel-discrimination-2019-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thisisinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Absher, an app which Saudi men use to monitor women's travel and stop them leaving, is available for download on iTunes and the Google Play store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Buckingham Emergency Heart Surgery; Vocal Cord Damage...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/lindsay-buckingham-heart-surgery-fleetwood-mac-792212/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fleetwood Mac guitarist recuperating at home after open heart surgery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governments tighten social media control in name of 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world/asia/la-fg-asia-fake-news-20190130-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan is one of several east Asian countries enacting or considering laws to gain access to information on internet users who post reports they call false.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of thousands of cows drown in Oz floods...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/australasia/australia-floods-cows-drown-queensland-townsville-rain-cattle-farmers-outback-a8769541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Stone argues against gag, says no Kardashian...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/08/politics/roger-stone-gag-order-filing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Stone is trying a new tactic in arguing against a federal judge who may restrict what he says in public: He's claiming he's not much of a celebrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax filers seeing smaller average refunds...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/early-data-show-slower-start-to-tax-season-11549653138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first tax-filing season under the new tax law got off to a slower start than last year and filers so far are seeing smaller average refunds, according to early Internal Revenue Service data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NYT editor on plagiarism charges: 'Made mistakes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/2019/2/8/18206892/jill-abramson-plagiarism-book-merchants-of-truth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"What we’re talking about here are sets of facts that I borrowed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Progressive Assault on Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/02/08/opinion/sunday/israel-progressive-anti-semitism.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A movement that can detect a racist dog-whistle from miles away is strangely deaf when it comes to some of the barking on its own side of the fence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klobuchar Under Fire For Hitting Aide With Binder...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/mollyhensleyclancy/amy-klobuchar-staff-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It’s hard to explain the anxiety that permeates the office," a former Amy Klobuchar staffer told BuzzFeed News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wood Skyscrapers Making Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-08/skyscrapers-made-of-timber-make-comeback-nudged-by-google-unit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGOLAND:  Thousands Wake Up To Missing Cars...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/02/08/morning-insiders-missing-cars-chicago/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Imagine coming out of your house to go to work, but your car is nowhere to be seen. Thousands of Chicagoans have found themselves in this position over the last few months, but it’s not because they were parked illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Sought VICE's Help to Build Media Empire...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/saudi-arabia-sought-vices-help-to-build-a-media-empire-11549621800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia is seeking to build an international media empire to combat the kingdom’s rivals and remake its image in the West, and it sought a partnership with Vice Media as part of the project, according to people familiar with the efforts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coloradans report seeing 'fireball in sky'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedenverchannel.com/news/trending/coloradans-report-seeing-fireball-in-the-sky-over-i-70-thursday-evening</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedenverchannel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you weren’t looking up, you probably missed getting a glimpse of a meteor falling across the Colorado sky Thursday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis C.K. Taking Up Audience Phones Before Performing...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6683077/Louis-CK-performs-SIX-sold-shows-Tampa-no-phones-allowed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Louis CK performed at the Side Splitters Comedy Club in Tampa on Wednesday, the first of six sold out shows at the club. No phones were allowed inside and uniformed cops were present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels using caravans to sneak drugs into USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/8/cartels-using-mini-migrant-caravans-sneak-drugs-us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Illegal immigration ticked down at the border in January, but officials said Friday the trends are still worrisome, with the number of families trying to sneak into the U.S. still near all-time highs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Christianity and Confucianism can explain US-China rivalry...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/comment/insight-opinion/united-states/article/2185298/are-confucian-china-and-christian-west</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter T. C. Chang says China’s Confucian heritage means it can tolerate multiple belief systems ‘under heaven’, but the US’ insistence on liberal democracy has echoes of Christian exclusivism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'New Normal': 200 illegals arrested in NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/politics-government/article225944480.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Immigration and Customs Enforcement, ICE, agents have arrested 200 undocumented immigrants in Charlotte and North Carolina in a large scale operation after sheriffs stopped participation in 287.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Supreme Leader Wishes Death on Trump, Bolton, Pompeo...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-supreme-leader-wishes-death-on-trump-bolton-pompeo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei wished death upon President Donald Trump and senior cabinet officials in a series of Tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PROBE</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/jeff-bezos-ami-responds-national-enquirer-investigate-blackmail-david-pecker-1202552571/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 10:05 AM: The owners of the National Enquirer now have a bigger problem than a pissed off and fighting back Jeff Bezos – the feds. Just a day after the Amazon founder published a detailed o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Strikes Deal With Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c11e7a0ab049432483dc3cd3d20a2bbb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian news reports say that Google has agreed with national authorities to delete links to websites banned in Russia. The daily Vedomosti reported Thursday that Google has reached an agreement with the Russian state media oversight agency, Roskomnadzor, to regularly receive updated lists of banned sites and delete links to them upon review. The newspaper says Google has already removed about 70 percent of the banned websites from its search results. The RIA Novosti news agency quoted Roskomnadzor as saying it has established a "constructive dialogue" with Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leopard cub discovered in checked luggage...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/02/08/leopard-cub-passengers-checked-bag-india-chennai-airport/2810859002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Customs officials in India intercepted a passenger trying to smuggle a one-month-old leopard cub at Chennai International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS PROBE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/08/jeff-bezos-reportedly-gives-info-to-federal-prosecutors-related-to-national-enquirer-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American Media, the tabloid's parent company, was granted immunity last year in connection with its assistance in an investigation into Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former lawyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON reconsidering NYC HQ due to local opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/08/amazon-is-reconsidering-ny-headquarters-site-because-of-local-opposition-washington-post-reports.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon's announcement was met almost immediately with protest by some New York officials and residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman 'eaten alive' by pigs after collapsing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/08/woman-eaten-alive-by-pigs-after-collapsing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian farmer who reportedly collapsed into her pig pen after having a suspected epileptic seizure was then eaten by the animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men's makeup goes mainstream...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/culture/story/20190206-is-mens-make-up-going-mainstream</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The male-grooming business is exploding – and even David Beckham is wearing eyeshadow. Bel Jacobs investigates the boom in men's cosmetics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie ready to rumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/02/bernie-sanders-close-announcing-presidential-campaign/582328/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator from Vermont thinks he can prevail against the crowded Democratic field and then beat Trump for president in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. Study of Human Genome Finds Unknown Human Ancestor...</title>
      <link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/artificial-intelligence-study-human-genome-finds-unknown-human-ancestor-species-180971436/#ppY5jy9gT2zYRh6U.99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.smithsonianmag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The genetic footprint of a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grandparents sold gay porn for decades and almost went to prison. Now, they are calling it quits...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-west-hollywood-porn-shop-circus-of-books-20190208-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Circus of Books, purveyor of gay pornography, is closing after nearly four decades. Owners Karen and Barry Mason have survived lawsuits and other threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT 'NewsGuard' Defends NYT After Botched 'Blackface' Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/02/07/newsguard-defends-new-york-times-stealth-edit-of-blackface-story-not-all-changes-necessarily-corrections/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NewsGuard cautioned critics of the New York Times' altering of a headline about Mark Herring admitting to wearing blackface without notifying readers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eight Guatemalans Rescued from Atop CA Wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2019/02/08/eight-guatemalans-rescued-from-border-wall-in-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight Guatemalan migrants were rescued from the top of a border wall near Mexicali after they attempted to scale the barrier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Good genes' President undergoes annual medical exam... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/good-genes-trump-undergoes-annual-medical-exam-152844922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump, who delights in confounding health experts with his junk food cravings and disinclination to exercise, will undergo an annual medical checkup Friday. The Marine One helicopter will take him to the Walter Reed National Military Medical Center in the Washington suburb of Bethesda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroic Pit Bull Breaks Out Of House, Leads Police To Save Owner From Gas Leak...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/02/07/hero-dog-save-owner-gas-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At first police thought she was a dog on the loose, but then realized the pit bull was on a mission to get help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Shutdown?</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/02/08/white-house-another-government-shutdown-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We'll see what happens'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago plans $1,000/month handouts, no strings attached...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/5127392/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Chicago families could start collecting a $1,000 check every month with no strings attached.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress closes in on border deal... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/congress-close-to-a-deal-on-border-fencing-and-trump-might-take-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House and Senate negotiators are closing in on a possible border security agreement that would fund new technology, additional border patrol agents, and likely some kind of fencing in certain areas along the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCabe Seeks Revenge With Book...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/feb/08/rosenstein-did-not-want-to-write-memo-justifying-comey-firing-new-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deputy attorney general privately complained about Trump’s order, according to Comey’s former deputy Andrew McCabe</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
