<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors want to question US intel agents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/russian-prosecutors-question-us-intel-agents-56640996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian prosecutors are pushing to question U.S. intelligence agents and a former ambassador to Moscow in their investigation of an influential foe of Vladimir Putin. The general prosecutor's office made the announcement Tuesday in the wake of Putin's summit Monday with U.S. President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$300 SNAKE Massage...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/07/16/snake-massage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cultures revere the serpents while others simply keep them as pets. Now, you can even get a snake massage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daycare worker who hanged toddler gets probation...</title>
      <link>https://www.kare11.com/article/news/day-care-provider-who-hanged-toddler-sentenced-to-probation/89-574401488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kare11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nataliia Karia received 10 years probation on Monday for hanging a toddler in her daycare and running over two men with her minivan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Gets Book Deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/book-rising-democratic-star-kamala-harris-coming-2019-170908704--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sen. Kamala Harris, a rising star in the Democratic Party who is sometimes cited as a possible presidential contender in 2020, has a book deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbian 'BATWOMAN' TV Series in Works...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/batwoman-tv-series-works-at-cw-1127574?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greg Berlanti and Caroline Dries are developing the drama ahead of the lesbian character's debut in the network's DC crossover event in December.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Blair calls for second vote to fix Brexit 'mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/tony-blair-calls-second-vote-fix-brexit-mess-144915246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;London (AFP) - "It's a total and complete mess": Former prime minister Tony Blair does not hold back when asked in an interview with AFP what he makes of the British government's approach to Brexit. Blair, who held the office for 10 years, said he sympathises with Prime Minister Theresa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines heaviest drinkers military...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/07/16/survey-military-binge-drinking-drops-but-this-service-stood-out-in-a-bad-way/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binge drinking, vaping.... these are just a few of the problems brewing in the military, according to a just-released study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Announces Series About 12-Year-Old Boy Reincarnated as Jesus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/netflix-mark-millar-tv-series-films-millarworld-american-jesus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix announced Tuesday its first slate of films and series based on the stories of "Kick-Ass" and "Kingsman" comic book creator Mark Millar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP UNDER PRESSURE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/back-washington-trump-under-pressure-reverse-course-russia-150202135.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump found himself isolated and under pressure to reverse course Tuesday after publicly challenging the US intelligence conclusion that Russia meddled in the 2016 election during his face-to-face with Vladimir Putin. At his inaugural summit with the Russian president in Finland, Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAKE NEWS GOING CRAZY'</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/17/politics/white-house-mood-donald-trump-vladimir-putin-news-conference/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump was upbeat immediately after his news conference with Vladimir Putin in Finland, but by the time he returned stateside on Monday evening, his mood had soured considerably amid sustained fury at his extraordinary embrace of the Russian leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lashes out at Palin...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/tv/2018/07/16/showtime-defends-sacha-baron-cohen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime has issued a statement slamming critics of Sacha Baron Cohen as spreading fake— um, "widespread misinformation." In an unusual…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED:  Economy growing 'considerably stronger'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/17/powell-backs-more-rate-hikes-as-economy-growing-considerably-stronger.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. economy is running at a fast enough pace to justify continued interest rate increases, Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam withdraws license of news site, issues fine...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/vietnam-withdraws-licence-news-issues-fine-072801197.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A popular Vietnamese news website has been suspended and fined about $10,000 after it was accused of publishing false information, as the communist government quashes any perceived criticism. The Ministry of Information and Communication said in an announcement Monday that the state-owned Tuoi Tre Online</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strikes in Europe on AMAZON Prime Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/strikes-europe-amazons-prime-day-001110901.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers in Spain, Germany and Poland plan to walk off the job on Tuesday as online retailing giant Amazon carries out its major summer sales event called Prime Day. The walkout at the Amazon packing and distribution centre in San Fernando de Henares, near Madrid, kicked off on Monday and was scheduled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelly out as Chief of Staff?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/more-predictions-that-trump-white-house-chief-john-kelly-is-leaving</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’ve heard them for months, the rumors that overworked White House Chief of Staff John Kelly is going to step aside, maybe to be replaced by budget boss Mick Mulvaney.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAZILE:  WHY IS HE ACTING LIKE PUPPET?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/opinion/2018/07/16/donald-trump-stop-being-putins-puppet-protect-voting-democracy-column/786765002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump fears that if he acknowledges what the Russians did, he'll be an illegitimate president. By acting like Putin's puppet, he already seems like one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nazis in their 90s: Germany intensifies hunt for war criminals...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2018/07/17/germany-nazi-killers-einsatzgruppen/768938002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German prosecutors are intensifying their hunt for aging Nazi war criminals still at large by expanding investigations into death squads known as the "Einsatzgruppen," which were responsible for more than 1 million murders. Three suspected members have come under investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Mary statue appears to 'weep' olive oil tears...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/07/17/virgin-mary-statue-crying-olive-oil/791124002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Catholic Diocese of Las Cruces is investigating a Virgin Mary statue that appears to be weeping in a Las Cruces, New Mexico, church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawsuit Arising From Bill Maher's Use of N-Word Moves Forward...</title>
      <link>https://www.tvweek.com/tvbizwire/2018/07/lawsuit-arising-from-bill-mahers-use-of-the-n-word-moves-forward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tvweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Male Film Critics Outnumber Women 2 to 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/study-female-film-critics-outnumbered-hurts-female-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Male critics outnumber female critics by 2 to 1, study conducted by San Diego State University's Center for the Study of Women in TV and Film says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHILD'S PLAY:  FACEBOOK TURNS BLIND EYE TO UNDERAGE USERS; EXTREME CONTENT REMAINS ON PLATFORM...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6795979/facebook-underage-users-report-dispatches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK ignores underage users and knowingly allows extreme material to remain its site, according to a new Channel 4 investigation. An undercover probe by the broadcaster’s Dispatches programme w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMO babies given go-ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/jul/17/genetically-modified-babies-given-go-ahead-by-uk-ethics-body</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nuffield Council on Bioethics says changing the DNA of a human embryo could be ‘morally permissable’ if it is in the child’s best interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad marriage can seriously damage health...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2018/jul/16/a-bad-marriage-is-as-unhealthy-as-smoking-or-drinking-say-scientists </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychologists monitored 373 couples over 16 years and found that couples who continuously disagree have poorer health</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGM sues victims from Vegas mass shooting, denying any liability...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/homicides/lawsuits-claim-mgm-has-no-liability-to-las-vegas-shooting-victims/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MGM Resorts International has filed federal lawsuits against more than 1,000 Las Vegas mass shooting victims in an effort to avoid liability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Bet Big on Liberal Democracy. Now Fears He Is Losing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/07/17/magazine/george-soros-democrat-open-society.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His enemies paint him as all-powerful, but the billionaire philanthropist believes that his political legacy has never been in greater jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Montage:  Cable News Sees Apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/bill-dagostino/2018/07/16/video-montage-cable-news-sees-apocalypse-trumpputin-summit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Within mere hours of President Trump’s press conference with Vladimir Putin concluding, cable news had worked themselves into a frenzy that suggested the sky itself must be falling. While criticism of Trump’s foreign policy decisions – especially those pertaining to Russia – has been bipatisan, the sheer meoldrama of the liberal media’s comments suggested they had lost sight of what they were even covering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD PRESS MOCKS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/donald-trump-branded-traitor-putin-12932473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem heads to Cuba on campaign trail...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article214940325.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State Rep. David Richardson is paying a two-day visit to Cuba this week as he runs for the Democratic nomination to replace U.S. Rep. Ileana Ros-Lehtinen in Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADDOW: Worst Case Scenario...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/rachel-maddow-its-time-for-americans-to-face-worst-case-scenario-on-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC:  'Pearl Harbor!' and 'Kristallnacht!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/msnbc-contributor-trumps-performance-will-live-in-infamy-as-much-as-pearl-harbor-or-kristallnacht/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new AIRBUS plane for 'FAT fliers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716994/Airbus-A220-plane-Air-Baltic-Swiss-Bombardier-C-Series-Farnborough-Airshow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia celebrates: 'West has failed'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/716992/russia-news-vladimir-putin-donald-trump-helsinki-celebrate-cold-war-media-moscow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA to Make More Drugs Easily Available, Cutting Role Docs Play...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/17/u-s-to-make-more-drugs-easily-available-cutting-role-docs-play</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. to Make More Drugs Easily Available, Cutting Role Docs Play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Ushers in New Era as Solomon Takes Reins From Blankfein...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/07/17/goldman-says-solomon-will-succeed-blankfein-as-ceo-in-october</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Solomon finally has a start date for his reign atop Goldman Sachs Group Inc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Voting Machine Vendor Admits It Installed Remote-Access Software...</title>
      <link>https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/mb4ezy/top-voting-machine-vendor-admits-it-installed-remote-access-software-on-systems-sold-to-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;motherboard.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remote-access software and modems on election equipment 'is the worst decision for security short of leaving ballot boxes on a Moscow street corner.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists find quadrillion tons of diamonds in ground...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/07/16/scientists-just-found-150000000000000000000000000-diamonds-ground-7722550/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shhh, no one tell the Hatton Garden gang</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza's Latest Weapon? Arson Bird...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/gaza-latest-weapon-arson-bird-122609768.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians in the Gaza Strip have used kites, balloons and flaming condoms to try to start wildfires across the border in Israel -- and now a bird, according to Israeli authorities. A falcon, outfitted with a harness tied to a steel wire with flammable material at the end, was found hanging in a tree</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record-breaking fine could put GOOGLE business model at stake...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2018/07/16/google-antitrust-fine-this-week-will-break-record/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European regulators are expected to hit Google with a multibillion fine on Tuesday or Wednesday, an announcement that’s being closely watched not because of the anticipated size of the penalt…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump returns from summit in HEL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf62711854b6482c88a611391db05a7d/Trump-returns-from-summit-with-Putin-to-forceful-criticism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — In an extraordinary embrace of a longtime U.S. enemy, President Donald Trump openly questioned his own intelligence agencies' firm finding that Russia meddled in t</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama delivers Mandela address on 'values' in rebuke to Trump...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9c415f558c874ddba99ef23f2cd040f5/Obama-delivers-Mandela-address-on-values-in-rebuke-to-Trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHANNESBURG (AP) — Without ever mentioning President Donald Trump by name, former U.S. President Barack Obama on Tuesday took aim at "strongman politics" in his highest-profile s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston Police Warn of 'Possible Serial Killer'...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/serial-killer-wanted-connection-murder-spree-police/story?id=56632731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A parolee who cut off his ankle monitor is now suspected in connection to a series of murders in the Houston area has been arrested, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Worst ever cable-news hatred of president...</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/2018/07/trump-calls-off-cold-war-ii/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beginning his joint press conference with Vladimir Putin, President Trump declared that U.S. relations with Russia have “never been worse.” He then added pointedly, that just changed “about four hours ago.” It certainly did. With his remarks in Helsinki and at the NATO summit in Brussels, Trump has signaled a historic shift in U.S. foreign […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daughter accused in fatal beating of 85-year-old mom who left her out of will...</title>
      <link>http://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/fort-lauderdale/fl-sb-lauderdale-fatal-mom-beating-20180716-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fort Lauderdale woman is accused of killing her 85-year-old mother after an ongoing fight about the older woman's will, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen Scores 327,000 Viewers...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com/2018/07/17/sacha-baron-cohens-scathing-satire-who-is-america-scores-just-327000-viewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Showtime didn’t do much to promote Sacha Baron Cohen’s new show “Who is America?” And it shows. Just 327,000 people watched it on Sunday night. The only real publicity the s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Bit Off, Swallowed Chunk Of Victim's Nose...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/bizarre/texas-nose-bite-attack-249370</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 16--A Texas woman is facing an assault charge after allegedly biting off and swallowing a large chunk of the nose of a female victim, according to investigators. Jessica Collins, 41, was arreste</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHWARZENEGGER: Looked like 'little wet noodle'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/news/397328-schwarzenegger-trump-looked-like-a-little-wet-noodle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former California Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger (R) tore into President Trump on Monday, saying he acted like a “fan boy” of Russian President Vladimir President in their "embarrassing" press conference earlier in the day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas power demand breaking records during heat wave...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180717130806-925xz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEXAS-POWER/DEMAND:Texas power demand breaking records during heat wave -ERCOT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER DRIVER JOINS  'RESISTANCE'; DUMPS TRUMP SUPPORTERS...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/07/16/exclusive-young-republicans-dumped-at-a-random-gas-station-by-anti-trump-uber-driver-speak-out/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He drove off and said 'welcome to the resistance'</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
