<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Trans runner ruled ineligible for Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/24/why-is-transgender-runner-cece-telfer-ineligible-for-the-olympic-trials/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender runner CeCe Telfer’s Olympic dreams have been put on hold. She has been ruled ineligible to compete in the women’s 400-meter hurdles – her signature event – at the U.S. Olym…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Priest charged over acid attack on 7 bishops...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/greece-middle-east-europe-religion-440eca0f2ca15070be9344831b0e631c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — A defrocked Greek Orthodox priest was charged Thursday with multiple counts of causing grievous bodily harm over an acid attack that injured seven senior bishops and three other people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  First cases likely occurred weeks earlier than reported...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2021/06/24/covid-19-pandemic-started-earlier-study/5241624552499/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first case of COVID-19 likely arose in China between early October and mid-November of 2019, according to an analysis published Thursday by the journal PLOS Pathogens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Law to put Supreme Court hearings on camera?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/24/senate-supreme-court-hearings-on-camera-496067</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the first time such legislation has cleared the Senate committee in more than a decade, according to Fix the Court, a group advocating for more transparency in the judicial system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New prehistoric human unknown to science discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/new-prehistoric-human-unknown-to-science-discovered-in-israel-671949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hebrew U and Tel Aviv University researchers found remains of a new type of ‘Homo’ who lived in the region some 130,000 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX power grid faces summer having changed little from Feb. freeze...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/energy/texas-power-grid-faces-summer-having-changed-little-february-freeze-2021-06-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas's grid operator frightened residents last week when it said it had very little reserves to cover demand spiking as temperatures soared. This summer could produce more scary times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He tried to commemorate erased history. Beijing detained him, then erased that too...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/tried-commemorate-erased-history-china-100038861.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Communist Party's centennial nears, China is erasing official wrongs and party history to create a triumphalist story for a young generation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Exempt From Antitrust Bill Following Donation to Top Dem...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/democrats/microsoft-exemption-from-antitrust-bill-followed-company-donation-to-top-democrat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. David Cicilline (D., R.I.) exempted Microsoft from a bill he sponsored to regulate big tech three months after he received $5,800 in donations from Microsoft president Brad Smith, FEC filings show. Cicilline's decision to accept the money marked an about-face for the Rhode Island congressman, who swore off big tech money in 2019. Cicilline […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$950 BILLION:  White House, lawmakers strike deal on infrastructure...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/24/biden-meeting-senate-bipartisan-infrastructure-talks-495941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have a deal," the president said at the White House alongside senators from both parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White farmer wins halt to program for Black counterparts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/white-farmer-wins-temporary-halt-program-black-counterparts-n1272258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge ordered the USDA not to issue payments under the program for 'socially disadvantaged' farmers until she can rule on the merits of the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portugal imposes stricter rules as surge threatens summer tourism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/lisbon-imposes-early-weekend-closures-142746535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LISBON (Reuters) -Stricter COVID-19 rules will be imposed across the Lisbon region and Algarve tourism magnet Albufeira as Portuguese authorities try to control a rise in infections that threatens the country's summer holiday season. "We are in a fight against time between the progression of the disease and the process of vaccination," Cabinet Minister Mariana Vieira da Silva told a news conference on Thursday. Portugal was still "far from its red lines but on the increase," she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSTAGRAM posts 'Q' pic AFTER death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3150844/john-mcafee-dead-suicide-instagram-removed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee’s Instagram was deleted after the account posted a cryptic “Q” in the wake of his reported jail suicide. The antivirus pioneer reportedly hanged himself ahead of his e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Demonstrably false and misleading statements to courts'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/giuliani-suspended-practicing-law-new-york-over-bogus-election-fraud-n1272266</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We conclude that respondent’s conduct immediately threatens the public interest and warrants interim suspension from the practice of law, pending further proceedings," the state appeals court wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indigenous tribes target Bolsonaro, say Amazon close to irreversible destruction...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/bolsonaro-should-be-tried-crimes-against-humanity-indigenous-leaders-say-n1272193</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indigenous leaders and human rights groups say the Brazilian president's policies threaten tribal communities and constitutes what should be a new crime: ecocide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46%  Invested Stimulus Checks; New Stock Traders...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90648372/should-i-invest-my-irs-stimulus-check-a-lot-more-people-did-the-third-time-around</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you put your stimmy in stocks, you’re part of a growing crowd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacker reveals smart meters spilling secrets in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/hacker-smart-meter-texas-snowstorm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hacker found that smart meters could determine what infrastructure may have been protected from blackouts during the Texas snowstorm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Chocolate After Waking Up Helps?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/chocolate-waking-up-burn-fat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In news that will have chocolate fans jumping for joy, results show morning and nighttime chocolate eating did not lead to weight gain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI LAW LICENSE SUSPENDED... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/breaking-rudy-giulianis-law-license-suspended/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudy Giuliani’s law license has been suspended. In a ruling handed down by the New York State Supreme Court Thursday, the state’s Attorney Grievance Committee successfully moved to have the former New York mayor’s license suspended. Specifically, Giuliani’s actions related to his defense of former President Donald Trump were to blame, according to the court. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL: Biden approval rises to 56%...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/joe-biden/1001908/bidens-approval-rating-rises-to-56-percent-in-fox-news-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thiel $5 Billion Roth IRA?</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/lord-of-the-roths-how-tech-mogul-peter-thiel-turned-a-retirement-account-for-the-middle-class-into-a-5-billion-dollar-tax-free-piggy-bank</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roth IRAs were intended to help average working Americans save, but IRS records show Thiel and other ultrawealthy investors have used them to amass vast untaxed fortunes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study finds correlation between high-fat Western diet and pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/study-finds-correlation-between-high-fat-western-diet-and-pain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diabetes, autoimmune disorders and cardiovascular diseases are known to be affected by nutritional choices. “Generally, unhealthy foods high in omega-6 fats include processed snacks, fast foods, cakes, and fatty and cured meats, among others.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have Gates Foundation efforts to vaccinate world helped -- or hindered?</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/have-gates-foundation-efforts-to-vaccinate-the-world-against-covid-19-helped-or-hindered/article_3ecb6f0f-a9fd-5e28-aa6e-e64ebc493124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE — As a dangerous new virus began spreading around the globe in early 2020, the Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates Foundation turned to a tried-and-true playbook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns Britain it will bomb ships next time...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210624130312-svpq2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-BRITAIN/NAVY (UPDATE 7, TV, PIX):UPDATE 7-Russia warns Britain it will bomb ships next time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan emperor 'worried' about Olympics amid pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/japan-emperor-naruhito-worried-tokyo-olympics-covid-0ae94ec8172e465d1ba85616031c706a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Japan’s Emperor Naruhito is “extremely worried” that the Tokyo Olympics and Paralympics could accelerate the spread of the coronavirus, the head of the Imperial Palace said Thursday with the games opening in one month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guitarist quits MUMFORD &amp; SONS to 'speak freely' on politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-fd8c24396fb818558a9c95c7724d12bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Winston Marshall, a founding member of folk-rock group Mumford &amp;amp; Sons, announced Thursday that is leaving the band so that he can “speak freely” about political issues. Marshall took a break from the band in March after sparking a social media storm by tweeting admiration for “Unmasked,” a book by right-wing writer-activist Andy Ngo that attacked far-left militant groups collectively known as antifa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED to go public...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/24/buzzfeed-announces-plans-to-go-public-via-spac.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed, a 15-year-old digital media company, announced Thursday it plans to go public via a merger with a publicly traded special purpose acquisition company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon has clear pic of 'Black Triangle UFO' rising out of ocean?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3148634/pentagon-black-triangle-ufo-photo-fighter-pilot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE PENTAGON allegedly has in its possession an incredible clear photo of a “Black Triangle” UFO spectacularly rising out of the ocean. Ever since the photo’s alleged existence wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drought Indicators in West Flash Warnings of 'Big One'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/drought-indicators-western-u-flash-100018383.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sarah Brunner opened the irrigation spigots on her farm in March, three months early. The rain should have still been falling in California. Now that summer is taking hold, she and her husband are considering shifting their meager water supplies into pastures so their animals will have enough to eat.Brunner’s worries don’t stop at the barnyard. The family’s fields of shallots, garlic and goats are surrounded by thick Northern California forests, dried out and primed to burn. An ea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copenhagen tops list of best cities for quality of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/copenhagen-tops-monocles-list-best-cities-quality-life-2021-06-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Copenhagen has topped media outlet Monocle's list of the world's best cities for quality of life, the fourth time Denmark's capital has won the honour since the survey began in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney enters 'scariest' phase of pandemic as delta variant spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/sydney-enters-e2-80-98scariest-e2-80-99-phase-of-pandemic-as-delta-variant-spreads-leader-says/ar-AALnD02</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spread of the contagious delta variant has residents grappling with reinstated restrictions just as the United States and Europe open up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury in clouds: Shanghai opens world's highest hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210624-luxury-in-the-clouds-shanghai-opens-world-s-highest-hotel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury in the clouds: Shanghai opens world's highest hotel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: ASSANGE COULD BE NEXT...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/world/202106241083231542-snowden-says-after-mcafees-death-by-suicide-that-assange-could-be-next/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (Sputnik) - US whistleblower Edward Snowden said commenting on the death of US antivirus software developer McAfee, John McAfee, who reportedly committed suicide...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Stick Shifts Fade Into Obscurity, Collectors See Opportunity...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/24/as-stick-shifts-fade-into-obscurity-collectors-see-opportunity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They’re not extinct yet, but the end is coming for stick-shift cars. For the 1980 model year, 35 percent of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns Britain: Do not provoke us again in Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210624091845-fsna2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-BRITAIN/NAVY (UPDATE 4, TV, PIX):UPDATE 4-Russia warns Britain: do not provoke us again in Black Sea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals horror film that is her life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/23/britney-spears-reveals-the-horror-film-that-is-her-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was heartbreaking to hear Britney Spears plead her case before a Los Angeles judge Wednesday, saying simply, “I just want my life back.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban junk food advertising online...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/jun/23/uk-to-ban-junk-food-advertising-online-and-before-9pm-on-tv-from-2023</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prohibition of adverts for products high in fat, salt and sugar could cost broadcasters more than £200m annually in revenue</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I WAS WHACKD'</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3145281/john-mcafee-suicide-whackd-tattoo-didnt-kill-himself-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee had a “Whackd” tattoo and once claimed that if he was ever found dead by suicide that he did not kill himself. He posted a picture of the tattoo in a 2019 tweet in which he …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation into deaths of girls found in Florida canal focuses on woman with Bible...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/investigation-into-deaths-of-girls-found-in-florida-canal-focuses-on-woman-with-bible/ar-AALmEJ5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAUDERHILL, Fla. — The day after two girls’ bodies were discovered in a canal, police canvassed the Lauderhill neighborhood across the water asking for information about a woman whose behavior was so alarming, she was detained by officers and sent away in an ambulance. The woman appears to be at the center of the investigation Wednesday. According to neighbors interviewed by the South Florida ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All UK arrivals in EU should be quarantined, says Merkel...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1453728/Angela-Merkel-news-Covid-quarantine-UK-EU-arrivals-travel-latest-Germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANGELA MERKEL has cracked down on Britain and insisted visitors from the UK arriving in the European Union should isolate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAX EVASION;  CRYPTO FRAUD</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/john-mcafee-found-dead-after-spanish-court-oks-extradition-for-tax-crimes-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antivirus software company founder John McAfee was found dead in a Spanish jail Wednesday after a court approved his extradition to the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC FINDS MORE HEART INFLAMMATION AFTER VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/cdc-reports-more-than-1200-cases-of-rare-heart-inflammation-after-covid-vaccine-shots.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is still a rare event," Dr. Tom Shimabukuro said at the meeting. For both vaccines combined, there were 12.6 heart inflammation cases per million doses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second 'Oath Keepers' pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/06/23/nation/second-alleged-oath-keepers-member-us-capitol-during-insurrection-pleads-guilty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Graydon Young’s plea was one of three on Wednesday by defendants charged in the Capitol breach as prosecutors seek to build momentum on nearly 500 federal cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPANISH PRISON 'SUICIDE'</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/23/john-mcafee-dies-by-suicide-inside-prison-in-barcelona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAfee, the founder of a antivirus software company, was arrested in October of last year and awaiting extradition when he was found dead, police sources told the newspaper El Pais.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes rule for foul-mouthed cheerleader in student free speech case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/supreme-court-cursing-cheerleader-first-amendment-981374cd3adc0e73274d7d33c29a9e0e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In the case of the cursing cheerleader, the Supreme Court notched a victory for the free speech rights of students Wednesday, siding with a high school student whose vulgar social media post got her kicked off the junior varsity squad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCAFEE DEAD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/john-mcafee-dead-spain-prison-extradition-c39cc0f375a975946fb83b60cc2bf3d3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — John McAfee, the creator of McAfee antivirus software, was found dead in his jail cell near Barcelona in an apparent suicide Wednesday, hours after a Spanish court approved his extradition to the United States to face tax charges punishable by decades in prison, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAfee's INSTAGRAM posts 'Q' pic AFTER his death...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3146043/john-mcafee-death-qanon-conspiracy-instagram/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHN McAfee’s Instagram account posted a mysterious “Q” just minutes after his jail “suicide” death was reported. The antivirus pioneer reportedly killed himself after…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famity 'won't let her get married or have babies'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3145981/britney-spears-wants-marry-have-baby-blocked-abusive-conservatorship/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears said she wants to marry and take out her IUD to have another baby. However, the 39-year-old claimed she is unable to grow her family because her “conservator won’t let he…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 1% of Americans have 16 times more wealth than bottom 50%!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/how-much-wealth-top-1percent-of-americans-have.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The top 1% of Americans control $41.52 trillion, according to the Federal Reserve. That's roughly 16 times more wealth than the bottom 50%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY DEMANDS FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/britney-spears-speaks-court-hearing-conservatorship-los-angeles-1234780358/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I would honestly like to be able to sue my family,” Britney Spears said Wednesday via telephone to a downtown Los Angeles courtroom during a hearing over her on her longtime and restrictive conser…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaks Her Silence During Hearing: 'Want to Sue My Family'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usmagazine.com/celebrity-news/news/britney-spears-speaks-out-at-conservatorship-hearing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usmagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears finally spoke out about her conservatorship during a Wednesday, June 23, hearing — read more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This conservatorship is abusive'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-britney-spears-slams-conservatorship-at-hearing-20210623-vheianzm3bfi5frhr4yzx5w5pu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britney Spears slammed her conservatorship during an emotional and unprecedented court hearing Wednesday, telling her judge she feels “enslaved” by the stringent structure and wants to get married and have a baby with her boyfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITNEY ASKS FOR FREEDOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Spears-set-to-make-rare-remarks-to-16266946.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Britney Spears asked a judge Wednesday to end court conservatorship...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No jail time in 1st riot sentence; Oath Keeper pleads guilty...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-capitol-siege-government-and-politics-87122373383f8d3f3c9f0b2ba3fa57d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indiana woman on Wednesday became the first defendant to be sentenced in the Jan. 6 insurrection at the U.S. Capitol and avoided time behind bars, while a member of the Oath Keepers extremist group pleaded guilty in a conspiracy case and agreed to cooperate with prosecutors in a major step forward for the massive investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE CHINESE PROPAGANDA CAMPAIGN...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/how-china-uses-youtube-and-twitter-to-spread-its-propaganda-version-of-life-for-uyghurs-in-xinjiang</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of videos of Uyghurs denying abuses against their community are showing up on Twitter and YouTube. They’re part of an elaborate influence campaign by Chinese officials to counter reports of human rights violations in Xinjiang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE legal worries grow as long-dormant French case moves ahead...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/france-legal-action-case-apple-app-store-developers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of French startups joins a case that could change the way the tech giant runs its App Store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX POLL: McConaughey 'most favorable'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/politics/1001887/matthew-mcconaughey-has-the-best-favorability-numbers-of-any-potential-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-NRA President Duped Into Delivering Fake Graduation Speech to Empty Chairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-former-nra-president-duped-by-parkland-parents-into-delivering-fake-graduation-speech-to-empty-chairs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former NRA president David Keene accepted an invitation to address what he thought was going to be its graduating class of 2021</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans form group on 'climate change'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-business-climate-climate-change-e1f0f572a7b5841bb6141456776bafec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Utah Rep. John Curtis says he's tired of hearing that Republicans — his party colleagues — don't care about climate change or slowing global warming. A former Provo mayor who has served in Congress since 2017, Curtis says Republicans can push for serious climate solutions while holding fast to conservative values.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhunt for escaped con captivates Brazil, terrifies town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/manhunt-for-escaped-con-captivates-brazil-terrifies-town/ar-AALmx2J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like a scene straight out of Hollywood: hundreds of police sweep the countryside looking in vain for an escaped convict, search dogs scampering as helicopters and drones hover overhead. But the massive manhunt under way for Lazaro Barbosa, a twice-escaped inmate and suspect in a quadruple murder, is all too real for the small Brazilian town of Cocalzinho de Goias. Barbosa, 32, has become the most-wanted criminal in Brazil since June 9,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY confirms 'god of mischief' bisexual...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/news/1001883/loki-director-says-it-was-very-important-to-confirm-the-character-is-bisexual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COURT APPROVED EXTRADITION TO USA</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9718567/Antivirus-pioneer-John-McAfee-dies-bars-suspected-suicide.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;McAfee was found dead this afternoon in his cell in Brians 2 Prison in Barcelona, with officials saying that the early investigation points to a suicide, Spanish newspapers reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Greek bishops doused with acid in 'act of revenge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3144454/seven-greek-bishops-acid-revenge-priest-kicked-out-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A PRIEST has been arrested after throwing acid on seven bishops who were attending a disciplinary hearing against him. The shocking attack that took place at an Athens monastery has left three of t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOPPING: COMCAST EYES VIACOMCBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/23/viacomcbs-roku-shares-jump-on-report-that-comcast-is-considering-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast chief Brian Roberts is exploring new options for the company's push into streaming, according to The Wall Street Journal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
