<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Isn't Buying Leon Black's Epstein Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/01/wall-street-isnt-buying-leon-blacks-epstein-story</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dechert’s report on the Apollo cofounder’s decades-long dealings with the late convicted sex offender, including payments of $158 million, is raising eyebrows—and more questions—on Wall Street. One lawyer dismissed it as a “whitewash.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pot Use In Teens Linked To Lower IQ In Adulthood...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/teen-marijuana-use-drops-iq-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have discovered that regular pot smokers suffer a decline of two IQ points over time compared to those who did not use cannabis as an adolescent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD still severely limiting trading...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/robinhood-is-still-severely-limiting-trading-gamestop-holders-can-only-buy-one-additional-share.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robinhood customers can buy one share and up to five options contracts of GameStop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dave Ramsey's empire 'best place to work in America'? Say no and you're out...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/money/2021/01/29/is-dave-ramseys-empire-best-place-work-america/4281535001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, Dave Ramsey has boasted that his company is the best place to work in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Endorsed Political Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2021/01/marjorie-taylor-greene-endorsed-political-violence-video-guns-elections-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Republican said in a broadcast with a gun activist that defending freedom could require “the price of blood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem Rep. moving office away 'for my team's safety'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/democratic-rep-moving-office-away-marjorie-taylor-greene-my-team-n1256185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Cori Bush says Greene and her staff “berated” her in a hallway. It’s unclear when the incident occurred or what was said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelmed, America's largest cemetery refrigerates bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/29/us/cemetery-delays-california-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of Covid-19-related deaths since the holidays have so challenged its capacity that grieving families are having to wait a month for funeral services -- and the cemetery has had to order refrigeration units to hold the bodies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain bans flights from Dubai -- as influencers, TV stars rush to get home...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/coronavirus/ga-health-officials-wont-say-where-the-uk-variant-strain-has-surfaced/RKS27V3GPNGP3JMG5NPS6RFZKQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia has six confirmed cases of the variant coronavirus strain from U.K., but the Georgia Department of Public Health won't disclose where in the state those cases are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the NRA's Strategy to Escape Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/courts/inside-the-nras-strategy-to-escape-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association's bankruptcy in Texas may throw a wrench into New York attorney general Letitia James's (D.) push to shut down the group and seize its assets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline pilots making in-flight errors say they're 'rusty' because of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/airline-pilots-making-flight-errors-130044410.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pilots have attributed mistakes to being out of practice because the COVID-19 pandemic, which slashed air travel demand, had kept them away from flying for a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR FORCE Fleet Oldest, Smallest in its History...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/davedeptula/2021/01/28/air-force-dont-buy-old-combat-aircraft/?sh=2e5e57873409</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force’s business case must be driven by what it costs to achieve a mission objective, or “cost-per-effect,” rather than the lowest lifecycle cost of individual aircraft absent operational realities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Fort Bliss soldiers ill after ingesting substance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-texas-68e5712382b902b14c93925ad3cc4a97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT BLISS, Texas (AP) — Eleven soldiers were sickened — including two who were in critical condition — after ingesting an unauthorized substance during a field training exercise at Fort Bliss in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI: Pipe bombs at RNC, DNC were planted night before riot'...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2021/01/fbi-pipe-bombs-at-rnc-dnc-were-planted-night-before-riot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI said the investigation had revealed new information about when the pipe bombs were planted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI: May start dosing children by summer...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-united-nations-health-coronavirus-pandemic-coronavirus-vaccine-50c1f79fca97a6c2e46f7eaf8fd7afc0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Dr. Anthony Fauci says the Biden administration hopes to begin vaccinating younger children by late spring or early summer. The government’s top public health expert says...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurrection aftermath: Staffers struggle with trauma, guilt and fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/01/28/insurrection-aftermath-staffers-struggle-with-trauma-guilt-and-fear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the aftermath of the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol, staffers are looking for ways to cope in a highly decentralized workplace.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: ABCNEWS president announces departure, joining exodus from newsrooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/news/abc-news-president-announces-departure-joining-exodus-from-us-newsrooms/ar-BB1dbKkv?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Goldston will leave ABC News at the end of March and will help find a successor in the meantime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millionaires' tax for virus relief takes effect in Argentina...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/millionaires-tax-for-virus-relief-takes-effect-in-argentina/ar-BB1ddkqC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A one-off tax on Argentina's richest people to help pay for medical supplies and relief for small businesses battered by the global coronavirus pandemic entered into force on Friday. The proceeds will be used to buy medical supplies, aid small and medium enterprises, fund social aid, and to provide natural gas to people off the energy grid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge gaps in data make it impossible to know who got shots...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/huge-gaps-in-vaccine-data-make-it-next-to-impossible-to-know-who-got-the-shots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details about race, ethnicity and occupation are often missing as data collected nationally is scattered across scores of digital systems that don’t connect. And the CDC doesn’t require vaccinators…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Orthodox unrest threatens Netanyahu reelection hopes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-pandemics-israel-coronavirus-pandemic-benjamin-netanyahu-2e87c8f56dc64ed6876a623ef9f7f352</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — As he seeks reelection, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has turned to a straightforward strategy: Count on the rock-solid support of his ultra-Orthodox political allies...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN chief calls for regulating social media companies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-media-social-media-antonio-guterres-united-nations-b6ed291f3008f935eeda5c1ae4b16d78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — The United Nations chief called Thursday for global rules to regulate powerful social media companies like Twitter and Facebook. Secretary-General Antonio Guterres said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow cultivating Trump as asset for 40 years, says former KGB spy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/jan/29/trump-russia-asset-claims-former-kgb-spy-new-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The KGB ‘played the game as if they were immensely impressed by his personality’, Yuri Shvets, a key source for a new book, tells the Guardian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug treatment clinic owner accused of drug trafficking...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/drug-treatment-clinic-owner-accused-of-drug-trafficking</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The operator of a Kansas drug treatment clinic has been indicted in Kansas City, Missouri, on federal charges of drug trafficking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: AI-powered sex robot declares herself 'more than a machine'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-learning-ai-proclaims-23408140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Nova, created by sex robot manufacturer RealDoll, was quizzed on religion, psychology, and ethics – and was able to provide detailed answers to nearly every question</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Parisians, taxis are ticket to freedom...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129105906-4m1vq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-CURFEW-TAXI (TV):For locked-down Parisians, taxis are a ticket to freedom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada to quarantine all travelers in hotels --  at their own expense!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-justin-trudeau-canada-coronavirus-pandemic-21d1685b076a62025326b0eb4441cd9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — An official familiar with the matter says Prime Minister Justin Trudeau will announce stricter restrictions on travelers response to new, likely more contagious variants of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man caught directing flight traffic with radio...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/arrests-berlin-f56833f73c7ecfa34a5ed5e6461669bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — A man has been arrested in Berlin on allegations he made radio contact with air traffic, including police helicopters, and gave fake flight orders while impersonating an aviation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED:  Covid map hidden by Trump reveals worst hotspots...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2231507/covid-map-hidden-by-trump-published-virus-hotspots-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID data which Democrats claim was “hidden” by the Trump administration has been published for the first time, revealing the worst virus hotspots. Donald Trump had allegedly told stat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro Says Bug Will Last Forever, Isolation Leads Nowhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bolsonaro-says-covid-will-last-forever-isolation-leads-nowhere/ar-BB1dbKac?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDDIT FENZY PUMPS UP DOGECOIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/dogecoin-cryptocurrency-rises-over-400percent-after-reddit-group-talks-it-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dogecoin added about $7.17 billion to its market capitalization in 24 hours, thanks to the SatoshiStreetBets Reddit group talking it up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus consequence: World without cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/consumers-abandon-cash-altogether-because-of-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of the coronavirus pandemic, Americans are finally embracing touch-free payments. And they may never go back to paper currency again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210129-france-s-le-pen-at-record-high-in-polls-proposes-hijab-ban</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France's Le Pen, at record high in polls, proposes hijab ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEC probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/29/sec-reviewing-recent-trading-volatility-amid-gamestop-frenzy-vows-to-protect-retail-investors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The SEC said it will work to protect investors by reviewing the recent volatility that has fueled a meteoric rise in stocks like GameStop and AMC Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Antipope of Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2021/01/29/trump-antipope-president-mar-a-lago-463238</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What a medieval religious schism can teach us about Donald Trump’s unprecedented and radically antagonistic approach to the ex-presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luxury house listings grow as wealthy flee tax-heavy states...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/lifestyle/luxury-house-listings-grow-as-wealthy-flee-high-tax-states</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the world’s most expensive homes, Villa Firenze, comes on the market as a growing number of high-priced homes are up for sale, especially as celebrities and wealthy individuals are fleeing high-tax states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-zero rally...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129130354-m7zs0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-YAKUTSK (PIX):Some Russians gear up for sub-zero rally for Kremlin critic Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China derecognizes British National Overseas passport...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-beijing-hong-kong-immigration-china-9eff79173444f227c67c838fd86a45aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China said Friday it will no longer recognize the British National Overseas passport as a valid travel document or form of identification amid a bitter feud with London over a plan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELESTE: Modern soul hero comes good on the hype...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/en_asia/reviews/album/celeste-not-your-muse-review-2867890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She topped every tipster's poll as once to watch for 2020 and the London star has proved herself a generational talent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Moscow cultivating Trump as asset for 40 years, says former KGB spy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-cultivating-trump-asset-40-122505054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yuri Shvets told the Guardian that the KGB had identified Trump as a potential asset as far back as the 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamlet absorbs charges of  unknowing role in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-columbus-media-social-media-ohio-b033c3b44e9a260a26dc10172dc7e7cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WOODSTOCK, Ohio (AP) — In this don't blink-or-you'll-miss-it, one-stoplight town, dozens of residents still fly “Trump 2020” and “Make America Great Again” flags. But it's a now-shuttered...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Black man denied spot in 'Whites-only' cemetery in Louisiana, graveyard apologized...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/after-a-black-man-was-denied-a-spot-in-a-e2-80-98whites-only-e2-80-99-cemetery-in-louisiana-the-graveyard-has-apologized/ar-BB1dcXLe?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oaklin Springs Cemetery in Oberlin, La., has since amended a provision that says only White people could be buried there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous Liaison: New Zealand quarantine flaw exposed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-coronavirus-pandemic-new-zealand-4e0c3e83080ba770f6e3a9241827618f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — The woman who took a flight back to New Zealand was supposed to avoid all physical contact with others for 14 days as she went into mandatory quarantine. The man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain bans flights from Dubai -- as influencers, TV stars rush to get home...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/britain-bans-flights-from-dubai-as-influencers-and-tv-stars-who-flocked-to-the-city-rush-to-get-home/ar-BB1db5Xa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Influencers and reality TV stars have been branded insensitive for jetting off to sunny destinations amid the global health crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart shopping carts on rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/smart-shopping-carts-on-the-rise-as-stores-adapt-to-pandemic-era/ar-BB1dcPed?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kroger is introducing smart shopping carts as a way to encourage social distancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire blasts 'Robinhood market' as Jon Stewart, others herald rebellion...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Billionaire-blasts-Robinhood-market-as-Jon-15907694.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unlikely rise of GameStop stock was already seen by someas a populist war against...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak rattles crew of Navy warship...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2021/01/29/people-are-scared-covid-19-outbreak-rattles-crew-of-the-warship-chafee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. 3rd Fleet officials confirmed that some personnel had tested positive for the coronavirus on the guided-missile destroyer, but declined to say how many cases had emerged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's Most Inoculated Nation Struggles With Strains...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/worlds-most-vaccinated-nation-struggles-with-virus-variants/ar-BB1dcbHR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With more than 30% of its population vaccinated, Israel leads the fight against Covid-19. Yet the emergence of more infectious variants is overwhelming its hospitals, showing the long road ahead for the rest of the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Investors May Lose Everything, Central Banker Warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/bitcoin-investors-may-lose-everything-central-banker-warns/ar-BB1dcO4H</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin investors need to be prepared to “lose all their money,” European Central Bank governing council member Gabriel Makhlouf said, the latest warning from a central banker on the cryptocurrency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baquet home purchase reignites retirement, LA TIMES chatter...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/28/dean-baquets-la-home-purchase-reignites-retirement-la-times-chatter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News that New York Times executive editor Dean Baquet just purchased a $2.1 million home in a tony neighborhood near Los Angeles has renewed speculation about whether he might take over the top job…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic-weary Ecuadoreans lean toward return to socialism...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210129050242-mroaq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ECUADOR-POLITICS/ (PIX):As election nears, pandemic-weary Ecuadoreans lean toward return to socialism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA lawmaker's white privilege teaching inquiry sparks anger, support...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/education/ga-lawmakers-white-privilege-teaching-inquiry-sparks-anger-support/HCUEVLVXZFGEFOXLYMALH3GG5M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white Georgia state representative is drawing outrage from several educators and support from some students after requesting information to determine whether professors are teaching materials that say white people are privileged and oppressive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Ties to Extremist Groups Under Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/29/republican-ties-to-extremist-groups-are-under-scrutiny/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The video’s title was posed as a question, but it left little doubt about where the men who</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us in Miami! Love, Masters of Universe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/01/29/join-us-in-miami-love-masters-of-the-universe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — America’s business leaders, freed from the office, looked around the country, taking note of its coronavirus lockdowns, taxes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic Has Erased Entire Categories of Friendship...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/entertainment/news/the-pandemic-has-erased-entire-categories-of-friendship/ar-BB1d8ZIr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a reason you miss the people you didn’t even know that well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon evaluating request for help...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210128164554-70rxe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-PENTAGON (URGENT):Pentagon evaluating request for help in administering COVID-19 vaccines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London Oxford Street Faces 'Boarded Up' Future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/londons-oxford-street-faces-boarded-up-future-retailers-warn/ar-BB1dbNie?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinic in Ecuador that gave fake jabs to 70,000 patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9199033/Authorities-shut-clandestine-clinic-Ecuador-offered-FAKE-COVID-19-vaccine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quito security chief César Díaz told reporters that the bogus facility had treated at least 70,000 patients who were charged $15 for each of the three doses they were required to take.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will vaccines keep up?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/01/27/covid-vaccines-new-strains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race is on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazonian city that hatched Brazil variant has been crushed by it...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/the-amazonian-city-that-hatched-the-brazil-variant-has-been-crushed-by-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another surge was coming. This time, Uildéia Galvão thought they were prepared. Galvão, the lead physician in the coronavirus ward at a public hospital in the Brazilian city of Manaus, had been haunted by the wave that crashed last spring....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How minnows sank the sharks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9199783/How-minnows-sank-Wall-Street-sharks-astonishing-financial-story-years.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOM LEONARD: Most City share-tippers would be unlikely to recommend putting money on a chain of video game shops. Yet if you'd taken a punt on GameStop you would have made serious money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter Threatened With Arrest After Asking Her Question...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/01/28/georgia-news-crew-marjorie-taylor-greene-town-hall-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A local Georgia news crew was removed from a town hall hosted by Representative Marjorie Taylor Greene on Jan. 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep me in handcuffs': Navalny denounces criminal proceedings...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/28/alexei-navalny-release-bid-fails-and-senior-aides-charged-over-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kremlin critic will remain in jail until parole hearing next week where he could be sent to penal colony</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICELY TYSON DEAD</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/01/28/rip-the-amazing-cicely-tyson-age-96-award-winning-actress-activist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I have managed Miss Tyson’s career for over 40 years, and each year was a privilege and blessing,” her manager, Larry Thompson, said in a statement. “Cicely thought of her new memoir as a Christma…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene faces mounting calls for repercussions over her words, actions...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/01/28/greene-faces-mounting-calls-for-repercussions-over-her-words-actions-and-social-media-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia Republican Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene has called a Parkland shooting survivor a “coward” and sympathized with QAnon conspiracy theories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS ON STREET:  Stocks targeted by REDDIT users plummet...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/GameStop-shares-whipsaw-as-other-stocks-targeted-15905279.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shares of GameStop and other companies plummeted in regular trading Thursday even as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET:  APP STORE...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/facebook-out-to-loosen-apple-s-grip-on-app-store-report-01611864310</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook is readying a lawsuit aimed at loosening Apple's grip on the App Store that serves as an exclusive gateway onto iPhones, a tech news outlet reported on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren calls CNBC reporter's 'bluff' on rich leaving USA over wealth tax...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/536404-warren-calls-cnbc-reporters-bluff-on-rich-leaving-us-over-wealth-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) called a CNBC reporter’s “bluff” after the reporter suggested that wealthy Americans would leave the U.S. over a new tax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House press briefing is nearly ALL women...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/536363-white-house-press-briefing-is-nearly-all-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thursday's White House press briefing was a woman-dominated event, Twitter users were quick to note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Trump bromance, Biden quickly shifts cold on Putin...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-bromance-biden-quickly-shifts-204701609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Donald Trump's four-year flirtation with Russian President Vladimir Putin, Joe Biden is setting a new, colder tone -- unhesitant criticism, despite openness on arms control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic caused worst year for US economy since 1946...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-caused-worst-us-economy-151711603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States saw its sharpest contraction in growth since 1946 as the coronavirus pandemic hammered the economy last year, but while the country may be set for a recovery, it hasn't arrived yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg 'supreme court' overturns four content-removal rulings...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/facebook-review-board-first-action-155534110.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook's newly-launched 'supreme court' issued its first rulings on Thursday, overturning four of five decisions to remove controversial posts from the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIONEERING HOLLYWOOD ICON</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/cicely-tyson-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cicely Tyson, the iconic and incomparable screen and stage actress and Black American trailblazer, died on Thursday. She was 96.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel leads world time spent with lockdowns...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/israel-leads-the-world-in-time-spent-in-coronavirus-lockdowns-657028</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the beginning of the pandemic, Israel has been in lockdown for 139 days, longer than any other country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's holding up next test of SPACEX Starship? Musk blames FAA...</title>
      <link>https://www.investors.com/news/spacex-starship-sn9-high-altitude-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.investors.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM plans electric-only vehicles by 2035!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gm-sets-goal-of-all-electric-by-2035-going-carbon-neutral-by-2040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Motors announced Thursday it wants to eliminate non-electric light-duty vehicles by 2035 in a goal to go carbon neutral by 2040.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College uses dead teacher for online class...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/concordia-university-says-lectures-from-dead-professor-were-teaching-tool</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concordia University says there should have been no confusion about who was teaching an online class after a student said he was surprised to discover the professor delivering the video lectures had died in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CICELY TYSON DEAD</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/tv/news/cicely-tyson-dead-dies-1234895188/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmy- and Tony-winning actress Cicely Tyson, who distinguished herself in theater, film and television, died on Thursday afternoon. She was 96. “I have managed Miss Tyson’s career for o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowy Owl Spotted In Central Park For First Time In More Than Century...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/01/27/snowy-owl-central-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say the last recorded sighting of a snowy owl in Central Park was back in 1890.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Starved Hollywood Starts To Lose Its 'Marbles' With New Reality Show...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/01/john-de-mol-marble-mania-us-format-talpa-1234681128/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after launching his latest company, John de Mol is taking out what he hopes to be a successful global format with Marble Mania on the heels of a promising launch for the celebrity marble rac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept investigating Musk's SPACEX following complaint of hiring discrimination...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/doj-investigating-spacex-after-hiring-discrimination-complaint-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The DOJ is investigating Elon Musk's SpaceX over whether the company "engages in any pattern or practice of discrimination" in its hiring, court filings say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus variant from South Africa detected in USA for 1st time...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-variant-south-africa-us-2bc397370cdd44afe916ddd6edbaf870</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — A new variant of the coronavirus emerged Thursday in the United States, posing yet another public health challenge in a country already losing more than 3,000 people to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star NYTIMES Reporter Accused of Using 'N-Word'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/star-new-york-times-reporter-donald-mcneil-accused-of-using-n-word-making-other-racist-comments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The paper’s top COVID reporter joined a group of students on a trip to Peru in 2019. Participants alleged he repeatedly made racist comments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BULLSH*T!' Hedge Fund Billionaire Rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/bullsht-hedge-fund-billionaire-leon-cooperman-rages-over-gamestop-surge-rips-small-investors-for-having-no-idea-what-theyre-doing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hedge fund titan is lashing out at the small-time investors who have banded together to disrupt Wall Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Found Biblical 'royal purple' offers look at King David wardrobe...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/archaeology/biblical-royal-purple-found-at-timna-offers-look-at-king-david-wardrobe-657082</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The color, a bright shade of purple, was extracted from mollusks fished in the Mediterranean Sea through a very expensive process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBINHOOD will NOW allow limited buying of restricted securities...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/01/28/robinhood-will-allow-limited-buying-of-restricted-securities-friday-gamestop-jumps-after-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Medical Center Gave Shots To Donors, Relatives Of Top Execs...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2021/01/28/hunterdon-medical-center-gave-covid-19-vaccine-to-donors-relatives-of-top-hospital-executives-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shots were administered by Hunterdon Medical Center in December and early January, at a time when only front-line health care workers and residents of long-term care facilities were eligible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUIT: SUBWAY's tuna sandwich doesn't have tuna in it...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/01/28/subways-tuna-doesnt-actually-have-tuna-in-it-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two California women claim Subway’s tuna sandwich actually contains not a “scintilla” of the fish — and that they were duped by the fast-food joint’s claims, a new $5 …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Falls Into Coma After Getting Vaccine, Dies 4 Days Later...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/01/27/pfizer-vaccine-orange-county-moderna/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 60-year-old Orange County man died after receiving a second dose of the coronavirus vaccine. Now investigators are trying to determine if the vaccination played any role in his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checked by reality, some QAnon supporters seek way out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-us-news-media-social-media-4ea47c2966a41b30ae678e5f471f6070</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROVIDENCE, R.I. (AP) — Ceally Smith spent a year down the rabbit hole of QAnon, spending more and more time researching and discussing the conspiracy theory online. Eventually it consumed her,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
