<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: CIA says 'Havana Syndrome' not foreign power campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/CIA-finds-no-worldwide-campaign-by-any-foreign-16789999.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Central Intelligence Agency has determined that a foreign country is probably not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Pope Benedict XVI 'failed to act' in child abuse cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/ex-pope-benedict-xvi-failed-to-act-in-child-abuse-cases-report/a-60494714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benedict served as the head of the Catholic Church before stepping down in 2013. The child abuse cases occurred during his time as archbishop of Munich and Freising from 1977 to 1982.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe considers new strategy: Accepting virus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-boris-johnson-health-europe-spain-1ab95ea43fa30bcb36f068c9a8664d12</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADRID (AP) — When the coronavirus pandemic was first declared, Spaniards were ordered to stay home for more than three months. For weeks, they were not allowed outside even for exercise .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT bigger than GOOGLE, AMAZON, FACEBOOK. But lawmakers treat like ally in antitrust battles...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/microsoft-is-bigger-than-google-amazon-and-facebook-but-now-lawmakers-treat-it-like-an-ally-in-antitrust-battles/ar-AASX2hz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFIANT BIDEN TOUTS FIRST YEAR</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-10420859/Defiant-Biden-touts-year-vows-reconnect-voters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden sought to reset his presidency in a marathon first year press conference Wednesday, vowing to reconnect with voters and touting successes, while...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico Cases Rise by Record That Doubles Previous Wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/mexico-covid-cases-rise-by-record-that-doubles-previous-wave-1.1710221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico registered a record number of new Covid-19 cases Wednesday -- more than double the amount seen in previous waves -- as the omicron variant extends its spread through the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS REMAINS...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/boris-johnson-tells-rebels-bring-it-on-as-he-vows-to-fight-for-his-job-12520446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM's supporters claim he has bought himself some time, with some of his would-be assassins being persuaded to grant him a reprieve until the Whitehall "partygate" report is published.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arians fined for striking his own player...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/nfl-fines-buccaneers-e2-80-99-bruce-arians-for-striking-his-own-player/ar-AASWCAl?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO-HOUR PRESS CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/biden-s-first-year-struggles-punctuated-by-wayward-russia-remark</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s First-Year Struggles Punctuated by Wayward Russia Remark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A woman's French bulldog was snatched in West Hollywood. She found him in Philadelphia!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/womans-french-bulldog-snatched-west-044537124.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the dog was taken by men in an SUV, detectives tracked the rental car to a man in Philadelphia, and the dog's owner flew out to get him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid doc: We are 'burned out'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-covid-doc-burned-011126118.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exhausted and overwhelmed by the influx of mostly unvaccinated Covid patients, Dr James Samuel Pope, an intensive care physician at Hartford Hospital in the US state of Connecticut, hopes the Omicron wave of the pandemic will be the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HBO MAXXX:  'SEX AND CITY' GOES FULL FRONTAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/19/hbo-maxxx-sex-and-the-city-goes-full-frontal-for-no-reason-miranda-throws-steve-under-a-bus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflated property values, wealth statements...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ny-attorney-general-alleges-trump-e2-80-99s-business-inflated-property-values-wealth-statements/ar-AASVaL0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRNA Boosters DO NOT Block Omicron, Study Shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/mrna-boosters-don-t-block-omicron-south-african-study-shows</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Booster shots with mRNA vaccines such as Pfizer and BioNTech failed to block omicron, a study revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Significant evidence' of  Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/19/n-y-attorney-general-outlines-pattern-of-possible-fraud-at-trump-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State attorney general, Letitia James, accused Donald J. Trump’s family business late Tuesday of repeatedly misrepresenting the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC will not send announcers to Beijing for Winter Games...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/winter-olympics-coronavirus-pandemic-sports-entertainment-health-027549305fa53617fa631caf5210be25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC will not be sending its announcers and most hosts to the Beijing Olympics due to continued concerns about rising COVID-19 cases worldwide and China's strict policy about those who test positive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes allows Jan. 6 committee to get Trump docs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-supreme-court-congress-donald-trump-30d5d01db49f0591d641d9e92d4092a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a rebuff to former President Donald Trump, the Supreme Court is allowing the release of presidential documents sought by the congressional committee investigating the Jan. 6 insurrection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  NFL wild-card TV ratings up big...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-entertainment-dallas-cowboys-las-vegas-5f9a76f463249e31bfe37c6d7e102e73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TV ratings for the NFL's wild-card round increased 21% over last year despite most of the games not being in doubt going into the fourth quarter. The six games averaged 30.5 million viewers, making it the second-highest average for the postseason's opening weekend over the past six seasons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico asks Guard to sub for sick teachers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-mexico-michelle-lujan-grisham-teaching-eaa5e804bc4f3c98efc0c8b14f2fb94e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. (AP) — New Mexico is the first state in the nation to ask National Guard troops to serve as substitute teachers as preschools and K-12 public schools struggle to keep classrooms open amid surging COVID-19 infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG claims company misled banks, tax officials...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-trump-investigations-donald-trump-new-york-b4895a63c5aee3991a2ffc42becfb564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York attorney general says her investigators have uncovered evidence that former President Donald Trump’s company used “fraudulent or misleading” valuations of its golf clubs, skyscrapers and other property to get loans and tax benefits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case NOT a slam dunk, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-donald-trump-new-york-d010518dae5b8305b9bc9be2a3ad7ced</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For years, Donald Trump punctuated his reality TV spiels and presidential speeches with claims that his business and his many gold-plated properties were “huge,” “amazing,” the biggest and the best.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN WARNS PUTIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/antony-blinken-jen-psaki-vladimir-putin-sergey-lavrov-congress-1df536e9a832830dc3bae2e89aef4116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden said Wednesday he thinks Russia will invade Ukraine and warned President Vladimir Putin that his country would pay a “dear price” in lives lost and a possible cutoff from the global banking system if it does.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic in talks to SUE Australia!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4498314/novak-djokovic-sue-australian-government-talks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVAK Djokovic is in talks with lawyers about suing the Australian government for £3.2million for “ill treatment”. The unvaccinated tennis ace, 34, claimed he had a visa exemption but was deported …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britney Spears goes on ANOTHER rant against sister: 'F**king hateful'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4497848/britney-spears-slammed-jamie-lynn-hateful-selfish-feud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITNEY Spears continued her feud with sister Jamie Lynn with a new post claiming she “shut her out when she needed her most.” The pop singer took down her photo of a couple of chocolate drinks alo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laughs Off Idea Legislative Agenda Failing...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/biden-laughs-off-idea-his-legislative-agenda-is-failing-i-got-two-real-big-ones-done-bigger-than-any-president-in-first-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden laughed off a question during his first press conference of 2022 when pushed on whether or not his legislative agenda is failing. ABC’s Mary Bruce asked Biden if his legislative agenda was too ambitious and if that is why he was having trouble getting Congress to pass his major agenda items. Biden […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he didn't 'overpromise'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/590474-biden-says-he-didnt-overpromise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden insisted Wednesday that he did not overpromise on his agenda amid a series of setbacks at the one-year mark of his presidency, making the case that his administration has made progress in fighting the COVID-19 pandemic and on other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret planet size of Jupiter found by citizen scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4496015/secret-planet-jupiter-nasa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TEAM of citizen scientists and astronomers has found a planet the size of Jupiter that NASA missed. The team announced the discovery of the exoplanet, which floats outside of our solar system, la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PREDICTS INCURSION</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/pmn/news-pmn/biden-predicts-putin-will-launch-incursion-into-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX synagogue terrorist ranted about 'f***ing Jews' in call during siege to family...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejc.com/news/world/exclusive-texas-synagogue-terrorist-ranted-about-fing-jews-in-last-call-to-family-made-during-siege-2Y5rmNYVAwKPfoV3fMv8i6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How landlocked state of Nebraska got own navy...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2022/01/19/how-the-landlocked-state-of-nebraska-got-its-own-navy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nebraska admirals are in charge of the tadpoles and the goldfish.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI tool to detect when patients will recover...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10419907/Machine-learning-process-predict-Covid-patients-recover-disease.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A German research team has developed an AI tool that can predict whether a person will survive their Covid bout with just a blood sample - at near 100 percent accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Declassified drone footage shows botched strike that killed 10 Afghans...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/declassified-drone-footage-shows-botched-strike-that-killed-10-afghans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon released footage showing the final moments before 10 innocent Afghans, including seven children, were killed in an errant drone strike during the final days of the US pullout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legislator dies using medical suicide law he helped pass...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-vermont-211fb12ef7ffc5ae3dd5ca4f0476009d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former Vermont legislator and House majority leader has died with the help of a law he himself helped pass that allows the terminally ill to end their own lives, his wife said. Willem Jewett died Jan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark ruling: Smoking ban on balcony...</title>
      <link>https://www.realestate.com.au/news/unit-owner-barred-from-smoking-on-their-balcony-and-the-decision-that-will-reverberate-through-qld-experts-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realestate.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark ruling against a unit owner, barring them from smoking on their own balcony is a game-changer for strata title complexes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coal town grapples with future as plant shuts down...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/climate-change-coal-environment-colorado-82d2d2af2c8e0f8c56cae205c5b5b9bd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAIG, Colorado (AP) — In a quiet valley tucked away from Colorado’s bustling ski resorts, far from his hometown in northern Mexico, Trinidad Loya found a way to support his family’s American dream: Coal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Those who recovered from prior infection MORE protected than jabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2022/01/19/those-who-recovered-from-covid-19-were-less-likely-than-vaccinated-to-get-infected-during-delta-wave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New data show those who recovered from Covid-19 were less likely than vaccinated people to get infected during the Delta wave. But the data contain caveats that stress the value of vaccination, even with prior infection, experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel turns down UN job offer...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/germanys-merkel-turns-down-top-un-job-offer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former German chancellor says no to António Guterres’ proposal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Supremes deny mask drama report...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/sotomayor-gorsuch-deny-npr-report-of-supreme-court-mask-drama/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justices Sonia Sotomayor and Neil Gorsuch issued a joint statement Wednesday denying a National Public Radio report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing laundry getting more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/19/business/tide-gain-downy-laundry-detergent-prices/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's going to cost you more to wash your clothes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer dies after catching Covid intentionally...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-60050996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hana Horka's son tells the BBC his mother was unvaccinated but wanted to acquire immunity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex says Clinton, Epstein were 'like brothers'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/19/prince-andrews-ex-clinton-epstein-were-like-brothers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Clinton was definitely very close to Jeffrey,” Lady Victoria Hervey said in the new ITV documentary, “Ghislaine, Prince Andrew and the Pedophile.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominates first Muslim woman to federal bench...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2022/01/19/biden-nominate-first-muslim-woman-federal-judge/6571815001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden's 13th round of federal judge nominations continues the efforts to put more women and judges of color on the bench.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic, who risks being frozen out of tennis, bets on cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/lifestyle/sports/djokovic-buys-80-danish-biotech-developing-covid-19-treatment-ceo-2022-01-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The pandemic has blocked Novak Djokovic's march to tennis history, so the 34-year-old may be pinning his hopes on a cure for COVID to get his hands on another glorious grand slam before time runs out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-jab parents send children to clandestine schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20220119-italian-anti-vax-parents-send-children-to-clandestine-schools-over-covid-19-protocol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy may have reported more than 80,000 Covid-19 cases on Monday, but the anti-vax movement there is still strong. Particularly in northern Italy where distrust of the vaccine has had a real impact…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NFL Prescott 'Deeply Regrets' Comments About Fans Throwing Trash at NFL Referees...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/dak-prescott-says-deeply-regrets-163051927.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dallas Cowboys quarterback apologized for not condemning fans after they threw trash at the referees following Sunday's game</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's core cooling faster than previously thought, researchers say...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/earths-core-cooling-faster-previously-thought-researchers-say-rcna12732</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earth's core is cooling at rates faster than previously thought, which could speed the planet's inevitable march toward inhabitability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eric Trump and Weisselberg invoked the Fifth more than 500 times...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/4-big-points-from-the-ny-attorney-general-e2-80-99s-trump-allegations/ar-AASW9Pr?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss researchers launch trial for covid 'patch' vax...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220119164630-7ji73</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Czechs scrap compulsory vaccination, want to avoid split in society...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20220119151524-ly020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skier charged with manslaughter after killing 5-year-old in crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/skier-charged-with-manslaughter-after-killing-5-year-old-in-crash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man faces manslaughter charges in connection with a high-speed crash on a ski slope that left a 5-year-old girl dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaspard Ulliel, French Actor and 'MOON KNIGHT' Star, Dies at 37 After Ski Accident...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/gaspard-ulliel-dead-dies-moon-knight-french-actor-1235157242/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French actor Gaspard Ulliel (“It’s Only the End of the World”), who stars in Marvel’s upcoming “Moon Knight” series, has died following a ski accident in the Alps on W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew quits social media as sex assault case looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220119-prince-andrew-quits-social-media-as-us-sex-assault-case-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth II's second son Prince Andrew has deactivated his social media accounts, users said Wednesday, as he faces a US civil case for sexual assault.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio police occupy favelas in new push to combat gangs...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220119131710-dp6cy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-RIO/FAVELAS (PIX):Rio police occupy favelas in new push to combat gangs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Eye Test Can Reveal How Long You Have Left To Live...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eye-test-how-long-youll-live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The discovery could lead to a routine screening tool for a host of life-threatening illnesses - including Alzheimer's disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than Third of  Country Gives Him 'F'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/biden/new-poll-more-than-a-third-of-the-country-gives-biden-an-f-for-his-first-year-in-office-just-11-percent-give-him-an-a/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One year into his term, more than a third of the country believes President Joe Biden is flunking out, a new survey finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE, Wintour Called Out for Not Paying Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-10416999/Andre-Leon-Talley-dead-73-Former-Vogue-editor-fashion-icon-passes-away-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fashion icon Andre Leon Talley has passed away of COVID complications at the age of 73. Talley is remembered as 'incredible' and recognized as one of the driving forces in Vogue's success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VOGUE, Wintour Called Out for Not Paying Tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vogue-called-out-for-not-paying-tribute-to-andre-leon-talley-after-his-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critic Roxane Gay said it’s a case study in “how your job will never love you no matter how much you give them.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham on Her First Film in Decade, Youthful Blind Spots and Rebooting 'GIRLS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-features/lena-dunham-interview-sharp-stick-girls-reboot-1235076390/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The polarizing auteur, back at Sundance with "sexual fable" 'Sharp Stick,’ reveals how surviving hate, sickness and addiction led to artistic rebirth: "I'd love the next decade to be less about apologizing and just about openly making art."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars including Jay-Z call for end to use of rap lyrics as criminal evidence...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2022/jan/19/stars-including-jay-z-call-for-end-to-use-of-rap-lyrics-as-criminal-evidence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meek Mill, Kelly Rowland and more sign letter supporting proposed change in New York state law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal may bring hundreds of Qatar Air Force members to Idaho base...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/branches/air_force/2022-01-18/deal-qatar-air-rorce-members-idaho-base-4330963.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Qatar's air force would live on Mountain Home Air Force Base to learn to fly the newest model of the F-15 fighter jet specially modified for the Persian Gulf state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power struggle among appointees gets personal over race...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/power-struggle-among-biden-appointees-gets-personal-over-race/ar-AASVzVf </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson, Facing Mutiny, Says England Will Ease Virus Rules...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/19/boris-johnson-facing-a-mutiny-says-england-will-ease-virus-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Prime Minister Boris Johnson, fighting for his political life, said on Wednesday that he would ease coronavirus restrictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traders Bet Oil at $100 a Question of When, Not If...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/only-china-virus-outbreak-shale-084115815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Surging demand, fading omicron fears, and OPEC+’s inability to ramp up output have underpinned an eye-watering rally in oil prices. Most Read from BloombergMicrosoft Buys Scandal-Tainted Activision in Bet on MetaverseFourth Pfizer Dose Is Insufficient to Ward Off Omicron, Israeli Trial SuggestsCovid-19 Infected Lions Prompt Variant Warning in South AfricaStock Selloff Deepens as Treasury Yields Climb: Markets WrapNew Satellite Images Show How Tonga Volcano Blew Island to PiecesGlo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Sixth Mass Extinction -- Already Underway...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mass-extinction-already-underway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study reveals that 7.5 to 13 percent of the two million different living organisms which inhabit the planet are now extinct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arthritis Cured -- By Zapping Bone With Electricity?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/arthritis-pain-regrowing-cartilage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The technique, which researchers have successfully tested on rabbits, uses small electric shocks to stimulate cartilage growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's All Just Wild': Tech Start-Ups Reach New Peak of Froth...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/19/its-all-just-wild-tech-start-ups-reach-a-new-peak-of-froth/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — How crazy is the money sloshing around in start-up land right now? It’s so crazy that more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative MP defects to Labour in protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/breaking-tory-mp-christian-wakeford-25989176</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bury South MP Christian Wakeford, who was only elected to the 'Red Wall' seat in 2019, has abandoned the Tories for Labour in a seismic move as the Prime Minister faces a possible vote of no confidence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions facing president at his second solo presser...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/590295-questions-facing-biden-at-his-second-solo-presser</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden on Wednesday will host just his second solo press conference from the White House since taking office, offering reporters a rare opportunity to press him on news of the day in such a format.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK mysterious robot eyeball tracks where person looking...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/facebook-working-mysterious-authentic-robot-165815802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The eye would ‘resemble a human eye’ that would appear ‘authentic to an observer’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In wealthy LA enclave, harsher penalties for wasting water...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-environment-and-nature-droughts-7eb1fdf1a19e15b1db41a000168b2cf6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a wealthy enclave along the Santa Monica Mountains that is a haven for celebrities, residents are now facing more aggressive consequences for wasting water. The Las Virgenes Municipal Water District northwest of Los Angeles hopes to spur water savings by making it easier to fine households that go over their allotted “water budgets" and threatening to vastly limit water flow to customers who repeatedly fail to conserve.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
