<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Central Florida still in path; Puerto Rico on hurricane watch...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-tropical-storm-dorian-update-20190827-doexcma7pbdu7iyyml6bklqsm4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Dorian held steady with 50 mph winds overnight and through the morning Tuesday but is expected to “gradually intensify,” and Central Florida and South Florida are still in the storm’s projected path, the National Hurricane Center said in its 11 a.m. update. Hispaniola is bracing for impact in 36 to 48 hours and Puerto Rico is under a hurricane watch, the NHC said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top MPAA Exec Fired Amid Sex Abuse, Blackmail Charges...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/film/news/mpaa-steven-fabrizio-fired-sexual-abuse-blackmail-charges-1203315135/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steven Fabrizio, a top executive at the Motion Picture Association of America, has been fired following charges of second degree sexual abuse and blackmail. Fabrizio served as general counsel to th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Memos Show Govt Lying About BACKPAGE All Along...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/08/26/secret-memos-show-the-government-has-been-lying-about-backpage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sealed memos fought over in federal court last week show authorities have known for years that claims about Backpage were bogus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's longest, tallest, fastest rollercoaster: 155mph!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/travel/9804461/fastest-tallest-longest-rollercoaster-six-flags/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE tallest, fastest and longest rollercoaster in the world is set to open in Saudi Arabia in 2023. The Falcon’s Flight could hit dizzying speeds of up to 155mph. The ride is just one of the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesbians don't want Pete...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/08/27/lesbians-pete-buttigieg-2020-president-1475900</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lesbian political activists are divided over which glass ceiling to aim for in the 2020 presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Falls Short in Big Screen Debut of 'IRSHMAN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/27/business/media/netflix-scorsese-the-irishman.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Martin Scorsese’s ‘The Irishman’ will debut in select theaters three weeks ahead of its Netflix release, a shorter run than Netflix had hoped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren isn't just former HARVARD prof. She doled out advice for Dr. Phil...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2019-08-26/like-trump-elizabeth-warren-made-her-bones-as-an-unlikely-tv-star</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Warren entered politics after honing her skills on "Dr. Phil," a staple of daytime confessional TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALMANAC: Winter to feature 'Polar Coaster' mix of frigid temps, snow...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/farmers-almanac-winter-snow-cold-frigid-temperatures</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enjoy the last moments of summer, because a wild ride apparently is in store this winter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Children develop 'werewolf syndrome' after taking tainted meds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/children-develop-werewolf-syndrome-after-19014094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hypertrichosis has developed in 16 children after indigestion medication was tainted with a remedy for alopecia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery as piglet found with 'elephant head'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-piglet-found-elephant-head-19013384</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mutant piglet had an elephant-like trunk and big flappy ears</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incredible moment base jumper leaps from bridge, parachutes 245 feet through thick fog...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7398489/Incredible-moment-base-jumper-leaps-bridge-parachutes-245-feet-fog.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photographer Jim Lampard was taking some photos of the Clifton Suspension Bridge in Bristol when he unexpectedly caught the atmospheric jump on camera on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CREEPY: Drone Follows Boys Walking Home From School...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/26/escalon-drone-follows-boys-home-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Escalon police say a drone reportedly followed two boys as they walked home from school Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside FACEBOOK underground meat market...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/27/inside-facebooks-underground-meat-market/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where’s the beef? Facebook, apparently. People have been using the social media site to “gamble” on high-end food items — including A5 Wagyu, stone crabs and in one case, a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Breaks Into BOTOX Clinic With Power Saw, Steals Anti-Aging Products...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/08/27/texas-woman-breaks-into-botox-clinic-with-power-saw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman was caught on camera using a power saw to break into a Houston-area Botox clinic and steal anti-aging products, police say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French president pushes for outreach to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4823dda1567d4a618e7f9519e29e81ab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — French President Emmanuel Macron says it's time for Europe to reach out to Russia — to keep it in the Western fold, check its global ambitions and avoid being caught in the middle of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men lied about being vets. Judge sentence: Wear signs saying 'I am a liar'... </title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/08/27/two-montana-men-who-lied-being-veterans-sentenced/2128167001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Men who lied about military service must wear signs that say "I am a liar" for eight hours on Memorial Day and Veterans Day to be eligible for parole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: Americans Believe Ideal Age For President Is 48...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/donald-trump-joe-biden-bernie-sanders-all-too-old-to-be-president-survey-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many polls point to a general election featuring President Trump facing off against Joe Biden in 2020, but would the country be better off with a younger president?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning storm-chasing video filmed across 30,000 miles in 3 months...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90395376/this-stunning-storm-chasing-video-was-filmed-across-30000-miles-in-3-months </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘From Darkness to Light’ is a love letter to the majestic, occasionally terrifying art-in-progress constantly churning above our heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020: TRUMP TROUBLE IN TOSSUPS?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-alabama-campaign-team-ignores-093000439.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump is struggling in states that matter most to his re-election chances, according to a new tracking poll by the Morning Consult.The president has sustained double-digit declines in net approval rate in nearly every state that could be considered a tossup, and more voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside most expensive home for sale in America...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/27/look-inside-the-most-expensive-home-for-sale-in-america.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This elegant French chateau-style estate in Bel Air, California, is the most expensive property currently for sale in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New golf ball automatically finds hole every time...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/tech/nissan-develops-golf-ball-that-automatically-finds-the-hole-every-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many people the game of golf is a great source of relaxation and entertainment. Here is a little gadget developed by Japanese automaker Nissan: The ProPilot Golf Ball. As the four-year-old in the video demonstrates, no matter where and how someone putts the ball on the green, it will automatically take control…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies facing employee burnout crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/08/14/5-ways-workers-can-avoid-employee-burnout.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent Gallup study found that about two-thirds of full-time workers experience burnout on the job. The biggest reasons? Unfair treatment at work, unreasonable deadlines, lack of support from managers and the stress that comes from never being unplugged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nervous Republicans focus energy on protecting Senate 'firewall'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/458898-nervous-republicans-focus-energy-on-protecting-senate-firewall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The GOP majority in the Senate is shaping up as a firewall for Republicans who are worried that President Trump might falter and lose the White House next year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 years after Berlin Wall fell, dashed hopes boost far-right...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/30-years-berlin-wall-fell-dashed-hopes-boost-021103391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A giant Karl Marx statue towers in the east German city of Chemnitz but, 30 years after the Berlin Wall fell, another political wind is blowing here as the ex-communist city battles the image of a far-right hotbed. Polls suggest that Sunday the region's voters will deliver strong gains for the anti-immigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missy Elliott rocks VMAs...</title>
      <link>https://news.avclub.com/missy-elliott-puts-on-a-masterclass-in-choreography-and-1837599300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.avclub.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At tonight’s MTV Video Music Awards, Missy Elliott was presented with the Video Vanguard award, signifying her many, many contributions to the music world and pop culture in general. Before that, though, she got a chance to show everyone why she deserved that award in the first place with a ridiculous, elaborate, and all-around awesome medley of her biggest hits—and biggest music videos. In her acceptance speech at the end, Missy Elliott made a point to highlight the work of dancers, saying they’re more than just background decoration, and her performance was pretty much entirely dedicated to proving that dancers are pretty damn cool. Oh sure, Missy Elliott was there, flying through the sky, dancing as a scarecrow, and pulling off seemingly effortless and instantaneous costume changes, but it was her team of dancers that stepped up and did cool shit while she made that stuff happen. In conclusion: Missy Elliott is cool and dancers are also cool. You can see the whole seven-minute performance below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VK8g-KR410</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Website: http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/ Support Tropical Tidbits on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/bePatron?c=651594 Please note that these posts do NOT r...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  Dorian Slicing through Windward Islands; Future Intensity a Big Question...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Dorian-Slicing-through-Windward-Islands-Future-Intensity-Big-Question</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Dorian was closing in on Barbados Monday evening, on a track destined to take its strongest winds and heaviest rains across the island and close to St. Lucia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage from camera outside Epstein's cell deemed unusable... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Footage-from-camera-outside-Epstein-s-cell-deemed-14380186.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one camera in the hallway outside the cell where authorities say registered sex offender Jeffrey Epstein hanged himself earlier this month had footage that is unusable, although other, clearer footage was captured in the area, according to three people briefed on the evidence gathered earlier this month.  It was not immediately clear why some video footage outside Epstein's cell is too flawed for investigators to use or what is visible in the other, usable footage. The incident is being investigated by the FBI and the Justice Department's inspector general's office, which are attempting to determine what happened and how to assess whether any policies were violated or crimes committed.  The footage is considered critical to those inquiries, and the revelation of an unusable recording is yet another of the apparent failures inside the Metropolitan Correctional Center, the short-staffed Bureau of Prisons facility in downtown Manhattan that held Epstein.  It's unclear whether the flaw in the taping affected a limited duration of the footage or whether it was a chronic problem in the beleaguered facility.  A Bureau of Prisons spokesman declined to comment, as did spokespeople for the FBI, the Justice Department and the U.S. attorney's office in Manhattan.  The people who spoke about the footage requested anonymity, citing the ongoing probe.  Epstein, a well-connected financier, had been charged in early July with sexually abusing dozens of young girls in the early 2000s and ordered held without bond. The arrest brought a sense of long-awaited justice to those who said Epstein abused them and who had earlier been dismayed by a 2008 plea deal he received to resolve similar allegations that was widely criticized as too lenient.  That deal allowed Epstein to plead guilty...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Optimists live longer...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencemag.org/news/2019/08/cheer-optimists-live-longer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large study finds association between positive attitude and extended life span</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOW MACRON TAMED THE DONALD...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/frances-emmanuel-macron-won-big-aggressive-approach-donald-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A president appeared to score a victory at a G7 summit in France. But it wasn't Donald Trump. Host Emmanuel Macron managed Trump - and scored big.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  109 counties have become majority nonwhite since 2000...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/08/21/u-s-counties-majority-nonwhite/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, 293 U.S. counties were majority nonwhite in 2018. Most of these are concentrated in California, the South and on the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promise and peril of front-runner campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-promise-and-peril-of-joe-bidens-front-runner-campaign/ar-AAGlUbk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISING POLLS...</title>
      <link>https://www.monmouth.edu/polling-institute/reports/monmouthpoll_us_082619/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.monmouth.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sanders and Warren rise; Biden drops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE CHAPPELLE: Worst time ever to be a celebrity...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/dave-chappelle-slams-michael-jackson-accusers-cancel-culture-netflix-special-1234633</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is the worst time ever to be a celebrity," he says in the special, which was released Monday. "You’re gonna be finished. Everyone’s doomed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AARON RODGERS: Reaction to Luck retirement 'disgusting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27471957/rodgers-backs-luck-calls-fans-boos-disgusting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aaron Rodgers said though he respects Andrew Luck's decision to retire, he doesn't see himself reaching that stage anytime soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERNIE:  HOW I WILL SAVE JOURNALISM!</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/opinion/bernie-sanders-media-silicon-valley.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourists alerted to mysterious rolling balls of poop in Smoky Mountains...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article234381417.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over-65s disco like medicine for seniors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/world-asia-49448760/seoul-s-over-65s-disco-like-medicine-for-seniors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A daytime party set up by the local government proves a hit in the rapidly-ageing country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows moratoriumon on media mergers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/sanders-vows-seek-moratorium-mergers-222024625.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders has taken on Wall Street, big oil producers, credit card issuers and private prison operators. Now the Democratic presidential candidate is taking aim at mergers among the nation’s biggest media companies.In a Monday op-ed in the Columbia Journalism Review, the Vermont senator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump seeks to avoid primary challenge and repeat of history...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5dc0d0509dd2459fa4452b67957f1b1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — "Never Trump" Republicans are eager to see the president confront a credible primary adversary. But the party will likely erect structural barriers that make that kind of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL SMILES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/568961a192964b849529746567b56a85</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — Never mind his differences with world leaders on China, trade, Russia, Iran and more. President Donald Trump's takeaway message from the Group of Seven summit in France was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules against JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON in landmark opioid case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29a69a81c0174c50bda7a190b03d65cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORMAN, Okla. (AP) — An Oklahoma judge on Monday found Johnson &amp; Johnson and its subsidiaries helped fuel the state's opioid crisis and ordered the consumer products giant to pay $572 million,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  Dorian Could Reach Puerto Rico as a Hurricane...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Now-Heading-Windward-Islands-Dorian-Could-Reach-Puerto-Rico-Hurricane</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watches and warnings are up for several Windward Islands ahead of Tropical Storm Dorian, which is gradually organizing over the Atlantic deep tropics and posing concerns for Puerto Rico, Hispaniola, and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH PLANS SOCIAL SCORES</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90394048/uh-oh-silicon-valley-is-building-a-chinese-style-social-credit-system </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In China, scoring citizens’ behavior is official government policy. U.S. companies are increasingly doing something similar, outside the law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EC74VteX4AAxEMA?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Ron Johnson denied Russian visa...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/26/ron-johnson-denied-russia-visa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Sen. Ron Johnson says the Russian government has denied him a visa to visit the country as part of a congressional delegation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eddie Murphy To Host 'SNL' For First Time In 35 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/eddie-murphy-to-host-saturday-night-live-for-first-time-in-35-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNL also announced several other celebrity hosts and musical guests for the upcoming season</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Appeals court judge's death suicide, coroner rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/aug/26/stephen-goss-appeals-court-judge-died-suicide-coro/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Georgia coroner says Stephen Goss, an appeals court judge who was found dead from a gunshot over the weekend, killed himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil facilitates deportation of its nationals after U.S. pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-immigration-brazil-exclusive-idUSKCN1VG1PL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazil is making it easier for the United States to deport undocumented Brazilia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As war fears skyrocket, Bibi orders rare security briefing for rival...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/as-war-fears-skyrocket-netanyahu-orders-rare-security-briefing-for-rival-gantz/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister’s advisers told to update Blue and White head on latest tensions, sparking speculation over significance of move</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Spies on the Offensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2019/08/inside-us-china-espionage-war/595747/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China’s spies are waging an intensifying espionage offensive against the United States. Does America have what it takes to stop them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. officials fear ransomware attack against 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-cyber-election-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-officials-fear-ransomware-attack-against-2020-election-idUSKCN1VG222</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government plans to launch a program in roughly one month that narrowly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40-person brawl at water park started over towel...</title>
      <link>https://www.kcra.com/article/raging-waters-closed-brawl-cal-expo-police/28810491</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kcra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raging Waters was shut down early Sunday afternoon after a large fight that started over a beach towel nearly killed a man, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Open to Meeting With Iran, Rouhani...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Middle-East/Trump-says-has-good-feeling-on-Iran-open-to-meeting-Rouhani-599764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I think he is going to want to meet and get their situation straightened out. They are hurting badly."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules against JOHNSON &amp; JOHNSON in landmark opioid case...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/08/26/judge-rules-against-johnson-johnson-in-landmark-opioid-case-in-oklahoma.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp; Johnson, which was the only defendant in the seven-week trial, has denied any wrongdoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insiders selling stock as recession worries mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/26/investing/stock-market-insider-selling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The leaders of Corporate America are cashing in their chips as doubts grow about the sustainability of the longest bull market in American history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs Look-Alike Sparks New APPLE Conspiracy Theories...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/steve-jobs-look-alike-photo-boots-up-new-apple-conspiracy-theories/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But wouldn't the Apple co-founder be wearing one of his company's smartwatches?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolving Door Between Govt, Cable News...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2019/08/26/the-revolving-door-between-government-and-cable-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Familiar faces move between government office and media slots, rarely questioning the institution that plays a core role in their lives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops Unveils High-Tech 911 System Featuring Live Streaming...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/08/26/new-jersey-police-department-unveils-high-tech-911-system-that-features-smartphones-live-streaming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal of the Gloucester Township Police Department's new system is to help first responders react better to emergencies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man paddleboards from San Fran to Hawaii in 76 days...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/travel/man-paddleboards-from-sf-to-hawaii-in-76-days/5493656/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RECORD BREAKER! An endurance athlete has become the first person to cross the Pacific Ocean on a paddleboard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE NIGHT ONLY: New poll doesn't add more Dems to debate stage, field holding at 10...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/new-poll-doesn-t-add-more-dems-debate-stage-field-n1046416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steyer, Gillibrand, Williamson, Gabbard and others risk being shut out of the faceoff next month as the qualification deadline looms Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flesh-eating bacteria took 25% of Florida man's skin...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article234386732.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ moves to add more marijuana growers for research...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f5aa406acfcd4eb3a10f1fce23df8b36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — The Justice Department said Monday it would move forward to expand the number of marijuana growers for federally-authorized cannabis research. The long-awaited move comes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOKS COLBERT...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/08/joe-biden-books-late-show-with-stephen-colbert-for-first-late-night-gig-since-launching-campaign-1202704258/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 47th vice president of the United States has a late-night date on CBS next week. The Late Show with Stephen Colbert will welcome Joe Biden on Wednesday, September 4. It will mark the Demcratic …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVEY IN HANDCUFFS; Trial postponed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f8279af289f34a10bd940616027bb5e5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Movie mogul Harvey Weinstein pleaded not guilty to a new indictment Monday that includes revised charges of predatory sexual assault, a development that caused the judge to delay...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Surveillance Secretly Infiltrating Police?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-08-25/amazons-surveillance-machine-secretly-infiltrating-police-departments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch doctor on trial in landmark euthanasia case...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/landmark-euthanasia-trial-opens-netherlands-093444669.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A landmark euthanasia trial opened in the Netherlands Monday seeking to pinpoint what to do with dementia patients who have previously stated their wish to die under certain circumstances but later might have second thoughts. "I want a humane farewell for my loved ones," the patient wrote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM WATCH:  Dorian Heading toward Lesser Antilles...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Dorian-Heading-toward-Lesser-Antilles</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tropical storm warning is in effect for Barbados in advance of Tropical Storm Dorian, a system that has the potential to strengthen quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEC COMMISSIONER WHO FOUGHT REGULATING DRUDGE RESIGNS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/fec-vice-chair-resigns-fought-internet-regs-leaves-agency-in-limbo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican vice chairman of the Federal Election Commission resigned Monday, leaving the election oversight agency without enough members to vote on enforcement actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows NYPD struggling to arrest man as onlookers taunt them...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/video-shows-nypd-struggling-to-arrest-man-as-onlookers-taunt-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republican New York state assemblyman retweeted a video that depicts four New York Police Department officers struggling to arrest a man resisting to get into a police car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Defends...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/08/26/tom-brady-andrew-luck-retirement-patriots-colts-nfl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom's clapping back at the Luck haters ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's deepest hole dubbed 'well to hell' revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9786114/worlds-deepest-hole-well-to-hell/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EARTH’S deepest artificial hole stretches 40,000 feet below the surface – but it’s only covered by a rusty metal lid. Russia’s Kola Superdeep Borehole was created by the Soviets i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIBAL:  ANGRY MOB BEATS MAGA SUPPORTER AT BAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/08/man-assaulted-by-angry-drunk-mob-for-wearing-maga-hat-into-portland-bar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Robot Ship Set to Cross Atlantic -- and Change World...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/maxlimer-the-robot-ship-set-to-cross-the-atlantic-and-change-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxlimer could be the first unmanned surface vessel to make the vaunted crossing—opening the way for a new generation of oceangoing drones, cutting prices and carbon footprints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Next Recession Will Destroy Millennials...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/08/millennials-are-screwed-recession/596728/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millennials are already in debt and without savings. After the next downturn, they’ll be in even bigger trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollution Linked To Psychiatric Disorders?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/smog-sadness-study-suggests-link-between-air-pollution-psychiatric-disorders/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they have identified a possible link between exposure to environmental pollution, specifically polluted air, and an increase in the onset of psychiatric and mental health problems in a population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-37B Military Space Plane Breaks Record on Latest Mystery Mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/x-37b-military-space-plane-otv5-duration-record.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 719 days of orbital spaceflight and counting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CIA doesn't spy on UAE...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-emirates-spying-insight/why-the-cia-doesnt-spy-on-the-uae-idUSKCN1VG0V3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Arab Emirates finances the military leader trying to topple a United ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arpaio seeks to reclaim mantle as 'America's toughest sheriff'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-sheriff/ex-arizona-lawman-seeks-to-reclaim-mantle-as-americas-toughest-sheriff-idUSKCN1VG0AD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Arpaio, the former Arizona sheriff who built a national reputation as a stau...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, French officials reach deal on digital tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-g7-summit-digital-tax/french-u-s-officials-strike-draft-compromise-on-french-digital-tax-idUSKCN1VG0N5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French and U.S. negotiators have reached a compromise agreement on France's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change in politics with more black voters in Deep South...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/08/12/a-change-in-politics-with-more-black-voters-in-the-deep-south</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-tropical-storm-dorian-update-20190825-koiaunm2zfcajj527oupyj6dyu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storm Dorian is expected to continue to strengthen, National Hurricane Center forecasters said, and they still predict it will become the first hurricane of the season by late Tuesday or early Wednesday. Some computer models have the storm tracking to Florida by next weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Football's Consequences Weigh Heavily...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/08/25/sports/football/andrew-luck-retirement-injuries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luck belongs to a young generation more carefully weighing the dangers of the game against the financial rewards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT05/refresh/AL052019_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/205313_5day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit Puerto Rico as hurricane?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/weather/tropical-storm-dorian-could-be-hurricane-when-it-reaches-puerto-n1046221</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dorian's path could shift markedly, but forecast maps suggest it could be a Category 1 hurricane when it marches close to the island midweek.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN ERA ENDING?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/cyborgs-will-replace-humans-remake-world-james-lovelock-says-ncna1041616</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Our supremacy as the prime understanders of the cosmos is rapidly coming to end.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens who lived in same neighborhood diagnosed with brain tumors...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/dozens-who-lived-in-same-neighborhood-diagnosed-with-brain-tumors/ar-AAGhbtr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Allies Target Journalists Over Coverage Deemed Hostile to White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-allies-target-journalists-over-coverage-deemed-hostile-to-white-house/ar-AAGjq3C</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third dengue fever case confirmed in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/health-care/article234329597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Floats Own Hotel as Site for Next Summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-floats-his-own-doral-hotel-as-site-for-next-g7-summit-its-very-big-great-conference-rooms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has suggested that next year's G7 summit should happen in Miami, specifically at his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARKETWATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forced removal of trans from L.A. bar investigated as hate crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-08-25/la-me-transgender-bar-fight-las-perlas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The LAPD is investigating possible hate crime after transgender women were forcefully removed from Las Perlas bar in downtown L.A.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Box Office Bummer: Revenue Dips, Theater Owners Panic...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/summer-2019-box-office-heads-unremarkable-finish-1234369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a starry lineup of sequels and remakes, revenue for the season is running 2 percent behind last year, contributing to a 6 percent downturn at the domestic box office so far in 2019.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Courting Dem Establishment...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/08/26/how-elizabeth-warren-is-courting-the-democratic-establishment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - SAN FRANCISCO — When Senator Elizabeth Warren of Massachusetts addressed a few hundred donors last week at a fund-raiser for the Democratic National</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex bots with coding errors prone to violence and could strangle...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robots-coding-errors-prone-18992240</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doll collector Brick Dollbanger fears what could happen if robots are not regulated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius monkey sharpens rock before smashing it against zoo window in escape bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/genius-monkey-sharpens-rock-before-19007139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The monkey's enclosure window shattered as the rock was smashed against it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein faces new charges; Trial postponed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7395397/Harvey-Weinstein-pleads-not-guilty-new-indictment.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein has pleaded not guilty to an indictment that adds two new charges of predatory sexual assault to his upcoming New York trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA woman dies from brain-swelling virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7395343/Massachusetts-woman-dies-rare-Eastern-Equine-Encephalitis-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laurie Sylvia, 59, fell ill last Monday and by Saturday she had died of the Eastern  Equine Encephalitis virus. A man over 60 years old in fell into a coma from the virus this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRETS OF PRINCE ANDREW'S SIX DAYS WITH EPSTEIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391369/Prince-Andrew-spent-six-days-Jeffrey-Epsteins-home-two-years-convicted.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of York stayed over a period of six days with shamed financier Jeffrey Epstein in 2010. This was two years after the businessman was convicted of having sex with a child.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Stephanopolous went to lavish party...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7391265/Woody-Allen-pictured-leaving-Jeffrey-Epsteins-mansion-lavish-party-royals-honor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial film director, 83, and his wife Soon-Yi, 48, attended the New York party. They left Epstein's house midway through Prince Andrew's visit, at 11.30am on December 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia test fires 2 missiles from nuke subs in Arctic Ocean...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/08/24/europe/russia-test-fires-ballistic-missiles/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missiles launch took place from two nuclear-powered submarines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantasy of being disconnected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/the-fantasy-of-being-disconnected/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An overactive world is hard to break away from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual deal keeps newspaper going in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/2019/08/26/vindicator-unusual-deal-keeps-shrinking-youngstowns-newspaper-going/2118333001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agreement appears to save the essence of a hometown newspaper</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Fallout: COLTS Plummet To 60/1 Super Bowl Longshots...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/andrew-lucks-retirement-leads-to-colts-afc-title-and-super-bowl-odds-plummeting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vegas is now questioning if the Colts have the firepower to make the postseason without Luck</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump denies he suggested nuking hurricanes. But govt once studied idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-nuclear-bombs-hurricanes-97231f38-2394-4120-a3fa-8c9cf0e3f51c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"People were astonished. After the meeting ended, we thought, 'What the f---? What do we do with this?'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: $125 Million Malibu Compound Sells to Tech Billionaire...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/dirt/moguls/ron-meyers-125-million-malibu-compound-sells-to-tech-billionaire-1203313863/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even as recession fears continue to plague an increasingly volatile U.S. stock market and high-end real estate transactions grow sluggish, several Los Angeles residential mega-deals have nonetheles…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN: 'I want to be clear, I'm not going nuts'...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/861039/joe-biden-want-clear-im-not-going-nuts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden is hopping on the defensive. After months of gaffes on the 2020 campaign trail prompting even his brain surgeon to chime in and defend his mind, Biden made a pointed comment about the state of his brain over the weekend. "I want to be clear, Iâ€™m not going nuts," Biden said during a campaign rally in New Hampshire â€” a comment that surely extended beyond the confusion he was trying to clear up at the time, the Los Angeles Times reports. Biden made the declaration while speaking to supporters at New Hampshire's Loon Lake, defending his inability to remember just where he'd spoken at Dartmouth College a few hours earlier. "I'm not sure whether it was the medical school or where the hell I spoke. But it was on the campus," he said, looking at the gathered reporters as he did it, per the Times. The obviously defensive comment comes after months of Biden stumbling over some pretty important details at campaign rallies, namely the locations of two mass shootings earlier this month. There's also the time Biden said "poor kids are just as bright and just as talented as white kids" in front of the the Asian &amp; Latino Coalition in Iowa. Yet the man who performed surgery on Biden three decades ago following two brain aneurysms agrees with the 76-year-old's weekend comment, saying that he's clearly "as sharp as he was 31 years ago." Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN:  YOU GOTTA LAY OFF TWITTER!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/458740-mark-penn-trump-should-push-china-but-drop-twitter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump has to learn that governing by Twitter is self-defeating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin built hypersonic arsenal -- while Pentagon slept...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/national-security/458769-putin-built-a-hypersonic-arsenal-while-the-pentagon-slept</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is almost certain to introduce almost all of its new hypersonic weapons well before they will appear in the American arsenal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters, Protestors Clash At Straight Pride Event In CA...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/08/24/approximately-200-people-gather-at-straight-pride-event-in-modesto/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately 200 people gathered, including protestors, at a Straight Pride event this afternoon in Modesto.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://pbs.twimg.com/media/EC6E2ldW4AEVTpm?format=png&amp;name=small</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pbs.twimg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam taxing robots as companies invest in advanced tech...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/08/25/brave-new-world-uncle-sam-is-taxing-robots-as-companies-invest-in-advanced-tech/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a brave new world for the IRS: taxing robots. Uncle Sam is padding the Treasury with millions of dollars to assess bots at the same time that corporations invest more in advanced technology an…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right surge rattles guardians of Nazi era remembrance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/far-surge-rattles-guardians-nazi-era-remembrance-042905806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tour group handpicked by the far-right party Alternative for Germany touched off a scandal last summer while visiting the former Nazi concentration camp Sachsenhausen north of Berlin. "As our horrified colleague told me, the comments by obviously rhetorically trained people culminated in them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Draws Crowd of 15,000 in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elizabeth-warren-draws-record-crowd-005435054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Elizabeth Warren drew the largest crowd of her presidential campaign Sunday in Seattle, as an estimated 15,000 people turned out to support what she calls a movement for change.When touting her wealth tax of 2 cents on every dollar of assets above $50 million, Warren drew chants of “2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Seeks to Avoid 2016 Repeat But Some Fear Gone Too Far...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dnc-seeks-avoid-2016-repeat-080000545.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bernie Sanders railed against a “rigged” Democratic primary during the 2016 election, but as he campaigns this year, his team has no complaints.That’s because the Democratic National Committee has taken pains to fix the problems that some said plagued the last nominating process. There</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>182 pigs killed en route to slaughterhouse...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/182-pigs-killed-en-route-french-slaughterhouse-090709312.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN! RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>https://granite3.com/advertise/drudge-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;granite3.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER  Republican resigns from Congress...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/08/26/republican-rep-sean-duffy-to-resign-from-congress/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin Republican Rep. Sean Duffy on Monday announced he will be resigning from Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NFL Star Pleads For Help On TWITTER Over Brain Troubles...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/08/26/nfl-fullback-leron-mcclain-says-he-needs-to-get-his-head-checked/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Ravens' fullback Le'Ron McClain took to Twitter Saturday to plead for help dealing with head and brain troubles he said have resulted from playing football.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020:  Bracing for nastiest contest in modern era...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ff2f787aceb34498bde8f6f948d5c471</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAMPTON, S.C. (AP) — President Donald Trump told American congresswomen of color to "go back" to where they came from. He vowed to revive a racial slur to tear down Elizabeth Warren, promoted a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domingo gets standing ovation in Salzburg...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ca308feb0f95471e8bc5f024eaeb3061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALZBURG, Austria (AP) — Plácido Domingo received a standing ovation as he took to the stage at the Salzburg Festival on Sunday, a concerted show of support at his first performance since nine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Pete making faith-based appeal to voters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bf10ec40db0b407f85a45edd1f261819</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KEOKUK, Iowa (AP) — In a story Aug. 24 about presidential candidate Pete Buttigieg and religion, The Associated Press reported erroneously that Buttigieg's father was a former Roman Catholic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice Film Fest More Relevant, Divisive Than Ever?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a19a2ce3aa0c4d96a0a74a477f26ec45</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be the oldest film festival in the world but at 76, the Venice International Film Festival is more relevant and divisive than ever. Kicking off Wednesday in the normally sleepy beach...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luck makes the decision of his life, for his life!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/68d7f96ba1e3412c8c66084935118301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The timing was bad, but even worse was the reaction of the fans who took it upon themselves to boo Andrew Luck the last time he walked off a football field in an Indianapolis Colts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims G-7 'unity' on Iran after unannounced invite...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/576ce36ba97b41ec89777c936e5b33bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BIARRITZ, France (AP) — U.S. President Donald Trump said he gave his approval for Iran's top diplomat to make an unannounced appearance on the margins of the G-7 summit, denying Monday that he was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News from The Associated Press, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walsh announces primary challenge from the right...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/exclusive-joe-walsh-announces-republican-primary-challenge-president/story?id=65122073</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative firebrand former Illinois Congressman Joe Walsh announced Sunday in an exclusive interview with ABC News Chief Anchor George Stephanopoulos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news, politics, culture, technology, health, and more, through its articles, podcasts, videos, and flagship magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://www.pravdareport.com/world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pravdareport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the House Judiciary Committee will subpoena Rob Porter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times opinion columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mediaite is the top U.S. website covering the intersection of media and politics with original reporting and bi-partisan commentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CRAP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN SHAPIRO</title>
      <link>http://www.jewishworldreview.com/0219/shapiro_archives.php3#.XG2A5KJKhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jewishworldreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELLO! brings you the latest celebrity &amp; royal news from the UK &amp; around the world, magazine exclusives, fashion, beauty, lifestyle news, celeb babies, weddings, pregnancies and more!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.com/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNBC is the world leader in business news and real-time financial market coverage. Find fast, actionable information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch CBSN the live news stream from CBS News and get the latest, breaking news headlines of the day for national news and world news today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Bill Press Podtable with @JonAllenDC of NBC News, @LeahAskarinam of InsideElections.com. We tackle Trump on Greenland and Jewish American loyalties plus the Warren surge and the Biden “return to normalcy” strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I screwed up," said the co-anchor, following the backlash to her segment last Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking the biggest stories in celebrity and entertainment news. Get exclusive access to the latest stories, photos, and video as only TMZ can.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, women’s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and analysis from the U.S. and around the world at WSJ.com. Politics, Economics, Markets, Life &amp; Arts, and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Magazine energizes people around shared interests, igniting important conversations on the news, politics, style, and culture that drive the world forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil president mocks Macron wife...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190826123312-r46z4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;G7-SUMMIT/BRAZIL-FRANCE (TV, PIX):Brazilian women should be ashamed of Bolsonaro for mocking my wife, says Macron</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston news, sports, politics, opinion, entertainment, weather and obituaries</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
