<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Emails Tell the Inside Story of How the NATIONAL ENQUIRER Got  Bezos Nudes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/emails-tell-the-inside-story-of-how-the-enquirer-got-jeff-bezos-nudes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* At least, they tell the Enquirer’s side of the story. But there are all kinds of inconsistencies in the tabloid’s account, drawn from emails, text messages, and sworn statements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In West Texas, Lingering Distrust in Public Health Measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/04/us/coronavirus-texas-lubbock.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early in the pandemic, much of rural Texas had low case counts and few worries. Now, conservative areas are seeing a surge in cases, but distrust in government mandates endure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:   I pledge to rebuild America's foundation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/think/opinion/trump-erodes-america-s-foundation-fourth-july-i-pledge-rebuild-ncna1232887</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There has always been a push and a pull between our founding ideals and the forces of inequality. But today is a celebration of our persistent march toward greater justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Reopening Is Warning Sign for Economy...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/the-nba-e2-80-99s-reopening-is-a-warning-sign-for-the-us-economy/ar-BB16ktX1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Population Growth Has Been Driven Exclusively by Minorities...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-population-growth-has-been-driven-exclusively-by-minorities/ar-BB16kTl6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$10 Trillion Rally Hinges on Earnings Nobody Has Clue About...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/a-2410-trillion-rally-hinges-on-earnings-nobody-has-a-clue-about/ar-BB16kqB8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHE KNOWS TOO MUCH!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8488471/New-Hampshire-county-jail-Ghislaine-Maxwell-is.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spencer Kuvin told DailyMail.com in an exclusive interview that Maxwell 'knows too much' and that powerful people may want to silence her even as she is locked up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearful and Frugal: Covid Wreaks Havoc on Psyche...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/business/article/Fearful-and-frugal-Coronavirus-wreaks-havoc-on-15386037.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. reopens, Americans aren't much interested in going out and spending.  A survey of 2,200 U.S. adults shows how Covid-19 has dramatically changed behavior in the world's biggest economy, potentially for the long haul. The data flashes warning signs for the recovery, showing waning interest in public events and material things, like appliances and clothes, and a new austerity, expressed through pantry stockpiling and delayed big-ticket purchases.  This foreshadows an era of fear and frugality that could push a full economic rebound-one that Washington and Wall Street are banking on-out of reach. The data also raises doubts about how much rising consumer confidence will translate into spending, on which the economy heavily relies. And this survey, polled last weekend, doesn't account for the past week when a spike in cases stalled reopenings in several states, potentially deepening the pandemic's behavioral impact.  "People are generally expressing that they'll do certain things less, or at home, on their own," said Victoria Sakal, managing director of brand intelligence at Morning Consult, Bloomberg News's partner on the survey taken the last weekend of June. "There's also a health component to how safe, comfortable and protected people feel."  Americans-often stereotyped around the world as confident to the point of arrogance-have developed a fear of enclosed retail spaces. While about three-quarters of U.S. adults feel OK shopping inside grocery stores or small businesses, more than half don't feel safe inside a shopping center, the data show. This is only adding to the woes of malls.  And that new preference for smaller retailers appears to have staying power: Even once the pandemic ends, nearly 30% of Americans say they plan to buy more from small businesses than they did before the virus.  "Small businesses...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen caught at NYC restaurant -- and it could land him back in prison...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/03/michael-cohen-eating-at-nyc-restaurant-could-land-him-back-in-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen could soon be back to chowing down in a prison cafeteria. The recently sprung jailbird was caught by The Post dining out on Manhattan’s Upper East Side — and the meal may …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Turning Point In Nation's History?</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/03/july-4th-independence-day-celebration-protest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A discussion of July 4th with Louise Stevenson, professor of History and American Studies at Franklin &amp; Marshall College.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PEAK:  Florida cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704142842-m73rh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Florida sees coronavirus cases spike to new daily record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57,683  cases single day in USA...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-covid-cases-hours-tracker.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US notched 57,683 COVID-19 cases in 24 hours Friday, a tally by Johns Hopkins University showed, the third consecutive day with record numbers of new infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUICIDE' WATCH</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1084647/epstein-lawyer-maxwell-die-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A LAWYER for the victims of Jeffrey Epstein believes Ghislaine Maxwell will also die in prison because she “knows too much.” Epstein’s alleged pimp was arrested by the FBI on Thursday on six …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom vows crackdown on scofflaws. Will law enforcement cooperate?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/newsom-vows-crackdown-coronavirus-scofflaws-120059900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gavin Newsom again Wednesday threatened more enforcement for businesses that fail to follow coronavirus guidance, but how it would work remains unclear</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wears maks made of gold to ward off virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/indian-man-wears-gold-face-mask-ward-off-134617710.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Indian man said he paid about $4,000 for a bespoke gold face mask to protect him from the coronavirus raging in the country. The precious metal covering weighs 60 grams (two ounces) and took craftsmen eight days to make, said businessman Shankar Kurhade, from the western city of Pune. "I am</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACK IN:  Spain quarantines 200,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/britain-eases-virus-quarantine-us-under-siege-132441661.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain put 200,000 people back in confinement and England reopened its beloved pubs on Saturday as Europe stuttered its way out of lockdown while the United States braced for large crowds hitting the streets to celebrate Independence Day. The death toll in Russia surpassed 10,000 and Brazil's right-wing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro fans applaud his maverick response despite more than 63,000 deaths in Brazil... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-fans-applaud-maverick-virus-response-013322991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the number of dead from coronavirus shot up in Brazil, the popularity of far right President Jair Bolsonaro has remained unchanged. For his supporters, the president has done nothing wrong despite more than 63,000 deaths and 1.5 million infections. Bolsonaro originally dismissed the coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia locks down high-rise apartments...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australia-locks-down-high-rise-apartments-virus-cases-100139655.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of residents in several high-rise apartments in Melbourne went into lockdown for at least five days Saturday, as officials struggle to control a virus outbreak in Australia's second biggest city. Hundreds of police were deployed to enforce the lockdown of nine public housing towers, as</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE PEAK:  Florida cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704134911-59b8w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida coronavirus cases rise by record 11,458 on Saturday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire flares at Iranian power plant, latest in series of incidents...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704130210-qbsd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-FIRE/:Fire flares at Iranian power plant, latest in series of incidents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris prepares for virtual fashion week...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704101435-e7ikl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FASHION-PARIS/HAUTE COUTURE-PREVIEW (PIX, TV):With no paparazzis or parties, Paris prepares for virtual fashion week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pubs open, gyms shut: England's health dilemma... </title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2020-07-pubs-gyms-england-health-dilemma.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is raining hard but Bradley, a fitness instructor, and four of his gym rats are sweating profusely while alternating between squats and abdominal exercises in a London park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57,683  cases single day in USA...</title>
      <link>https://cms.trtworld.com/life/us-marks-record-57-683-new-cases-in-24-hours-latest-updates-37850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cms.trtworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global coronavirus pandemic has infected more than 11.1 million people and claimed over 528,000 lives. Here are updates for July 4:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day in a land of confusion...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d70ce42ae5da13ef66be501df5a8be01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the worst of times. It was the weirdest of times. It was a season of sickness and shouting, of defiance and tension, of industrial-strength falsehood and spin. It was a moment of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French government ministers investigated over virus crisis...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1b0cffb6249302a0adcde84eafb540c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — A special French court ordered an investigation Friday of three current or former government ministers over their handling of the coronavirus crisis. COVID-19 patients, doctors,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimberly Guilfoyle Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/kimberly-guilfoyle-top-fund-raising-official-for-trump-campaign-tests-positive/ar-BB16jzWp?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiery anti-'cancel culture' speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704025425-njdrt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/ (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-Trump blasts "left wing cultural revolution" at Mount Rushmore</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimberly Guilfoyle Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/kimberly-guilfoyle-donald-trump-jrs-girlfriend-tests-positive-for-coronavirus/ar-BB16js5F?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine rooted in a govt partnership fueling financial rewards for company executives...</title>
      <link>https://www.wvgazettemail.com/washington_post/finance/a-coronavirus-vaccine-rooted-in-a-government-partnership-is-fueling-financial-rewards-for-company-executives/article_3189a6c4-1b44-533e-9650-b10562ce25de.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wvgazettemail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shares of biotech firm Moderna soared in May to record highs on news that its novel coronavirus vaccine showed promise in a clinical trial, the nation’s senior securities regulator</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimberly Guilfoyle Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/03/us/politics/kimberly-guilfoyle-trump-campaign-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is the third person in proximity of President Trump known to have contracted the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks putting people at each other's throats...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/masks-are-putting-people-at-each-others-throats-especially-in-palm-beach-county/ar-BB16jsXh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third person in proximity of President known to have contracted virus... MORE... </title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-donald-trump-jr-s-girlfriend-former-fox-news-commentator-kimberly-guilfoyle-reportedly-tests-positive-for-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News Commentator Kimberly Guilfoyle, Donald Trump Jr.'s Girlfriend, Tests Positive for Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Republicans set new goal of defeating the GOP Senate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article243939577.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida 'heading a million miles an hour in the wrong direction'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/505831-infectious-disease-specialist-florida-heading-a-million-miles-an-hour-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An infectious disease specialist is warning that Florida is "heading a million miles an hours in the wrong direction" on its handling of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curfew ordered in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200704003153-4dben</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Seven U.S. states post record COVID cases, curfew ordered in Miami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin mocks U.S. embassy for flying rainbow flag...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200703172008-hnudk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-PUTIN/RAINBOW (PIX):Putin mocks U.S. embassy for flying rainbow flag</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel bracing for retaliation as Tehran points fingers...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-said-bracing-for-response-as-tehran-points-fingers-over-nuke-site-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysts say blast destroyed lab where Iran develops next generation centrifuges to speed up uranium enrichment; one source says Iran nuclear program set back two months</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nigerian Email Scammer Who Stole Millions From Premier League Club, NY Law Firm, Banks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/nigerian-email-scammer-ray-hushpuppi-defrauded-millions-from-epl-club-ny-law-firm-feds-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He went by the name Ray Hushpuppi and he made no secret of his extraordinary fortune.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We need to live with it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/we-need-live-it-white-house-readies-new-message-nation-n1232884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The effort to craft a clearer response comes after months of Trump downplaying the health crisis and mixed signals from the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiery anti-'cancel culture' speech planned...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200703195116-8mcxi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/ (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Trump to criticize 'cancel culture' during Mount Rushmore trip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5G opponents set fire to Cyprus' mobile antennas...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e7cdfbfeca9ed47d3d283e2cba4ba43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICOSIA, Cyprus (AP) — A small group of people who oppose 5G mobile telephone technology is likely responsible for arson attacks against four mobile telephone antenna installations in Cyprus'...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Grim Reaper' Protests Beachgoers Again Despite Joining Mass Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/florida-grim-reaper-protests-beachgoers-again-despite-joining-mass-gatherings-last-month/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyer Daniel Uhlfelder visited Florida beaches again this week dressed as the "Stay at Home" Grim Reaper in an effort to protest people out during the coronavirus pandemic -- despite the fa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY: I would win THIS time!</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/clinton-coronavirus-crisis-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former 2016 presidential candidate Hillary Clinton believes she would have handled the coronavirus pandemic better than President Trump, and that she would win if she was on the ballot this November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man booted from Florida-bound flight at LGA for not wearing mask...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/03/man-booted-from-florida-bound-flight-at-lga-for-not-wearing-mask/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was captured on video being removed from a Florida-bound flight at LaGuardia Airport Friday for not wearing a face mask. The tense standoff unfolded when a man, whose name was not known, &amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EVIL AS EPSTEIN'</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12027059/ghislaine-maxwell-jeffrey-epstein-rape-claim-teenager-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A WOMAN has claimed Ghislaine Maxwell raped her dozens of times when she was a teenager — and says she’s willing to testify against her. The Jane Doe made the allegations one day after Maxwell was …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Has Flesh-Eating-Bacteria Problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/health/archive/2020/07/flesh-eating-bacteria-are-spreading/613762/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the beach towns south of Melbourne, everyone, it seems, knows someone who’s been attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 'Dog Years' A Myth...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/dog-years-just-a-myth-science-shows-us-how-old-fido-really-is-in-human-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How old is your dog in human years? Dog lovers have been using the "multiply by 7" method for ages, but a new study says that's just a myth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Ad Boycott That Has FACEBOOK on Defensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2020/07/03/activists-advertising-boycott-facebook-348528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of companies are boycotting the social media giant. Here’s the backstory of how it happened.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dukakis has advice for Biden: Don't take those polls seriously...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2020/07/03/opinion/dukakis-has-some-advice-biden-dont-take-those-polls-seriously/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In July 1988, a Newsweek/Gallup poll showed Mike Dukakis leading his presidential opponent, George H.W. Bush, by a 55 to 38 percent margin nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Gyms Reject Gov's Shutdown Order...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/03/arizona-gyms-reject-governor-doug-duceys-shutdown-order/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fitness centers across the state are turning up the resistance to lockdown orders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson's plane scrambled to support UK fighter jets intercepting Russian warplane...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12026502/raf-typhoon-fighter-boris-johnson-plane-scrambled-russian-scotland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BORIS Johnson’s newly-painted plane and two RAF Typhoon fighters were scrambled to intercept a Russian warplane off the coast of Scotland today. The Prime Minister’s Voyager jet was sen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASEBALL'S BACK: Surreal scenes socially distanced training camp...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/03/mets-training-camp-coronavirus-guidelines-make-for-surreal-scene/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social distancing. Hand sanitizer. Masks on the field. The first day of Mets’ spring training 2.0 at Citi Field was a surreal scene that showed MLB’s coronavirus guidelines in action. A…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intruder at Canada PM residence faces multiple charges...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/intruder-canada-pm-residence-faces-multiple-charges-police-175142042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Canadian army reservist who forced his way onto the estate where Prime Minister Justin Trudeau lives was carrying multiple weapons and is facing several charges, police said Friday. The suspect, who has not been formally named, was due on court to hear the charges against him over Thursday's intrusion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Havana stirs to life without tourists, amid scarcity...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200703172709-rj0v7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/CUBA-OPENING (TV, PIX):Havana stirs to life without tourists and amid scarcity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second wave of closures wallops California restaurants...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/second-wave-virus-closures-wallops-175608421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homayoun Dariyani was training servers and cooks for his soon-to-open gourmet hamburger grill in March when California abruptly shut down dine-in restaurants to slow the spread of the coronavirus. After a three-month delay, Dariyani held the grand opening for Slater’s 50/50 on June 18 after the state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Israeli cyberattack; F35s hit missile base...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/report-israeli-cyberattack-caused-iran-nuclear-site-fire-f35s-hit-missile-base/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kuwaiti newspaper cites unnamed senior source as saying Jerusalem behind recent incidents in Iran, following an alleged attempt by Tehran to hack Israel's water infrastructure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican state closes its border to Americans
...</title>
      <link>https://www.azcentral.com/story/news/local/arizona/2020/07/02/sonora-seeks-tougher-controls-arizona-border-over-covid-19-spread/3283270001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.azcentral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mexican government said U.S. visitors would be vetted at border crossings during the Fourth of July weekend and that tourist will be turned away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans get texts ordering masks...</title>
      <link>https://news4sanantonio.com/news/local/gov-abbotts-executive-order-on-mandatory-face-coverings-begins</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news4sanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN -Governor Greg Abbott's two new executive orders about face coverings in public and gatherings of 10 people or more have begun. The new orders took affect at noon on Friday. The first order requires all Texans to wear a face covering over the nose and mouth in public spaces in counties with 20 or more positive COVID-19. The City of San Antonio notified residents of the governor's orders by using the Wireless Emergency Alert System (WEA), which sent an alert to their smart phone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khashoggi murder trial told oven was lit after killing...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200703164637-v0tyy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KHASHOGGI/TURKEY-TRIAL (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Khashoggi murder trial told oven was lit after killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman attacks 5 airline agents, claims she has covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2020/07/01/woman-attacks-5-airline-agents-corrections-officer-over-carry-on-bag-claims-she-has-covid-19-attempts-to-escape-jail-police-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas woman is behind bars after she battered five airline agents and a corrections officer after becoming irate over issues with her carry-on bag, according to the Orlando Police Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GAGS, THE ROASTS!</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/TrumpPod</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
