<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Brennan Threatens to Sue After Being Stripped of Clearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/brennan-considers-legal-action-stop-clearance-revocations-151506505--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Former CIA Director John Brennan said Sunday that he is considering taking legal action to try to prevent President Donald Trump from stripping other current and former officials' security clearances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Prices Are Down. Nobody Told the Gas Pumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/2018/08/19/oil-prices-are-down-nobody-told-the-gas-pumps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oil Prices Are Down. Nobody Told the Gas Pumps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lanny Davis channels Watergate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/08/19/davis-cohen-john-dean-788456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The news adds new hints that Cohen could be open to being a potential witness in any case against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo tries again:  Searing speech from pulpit of church...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ny-gov-cuomo-trump-fooled-country-not-york-184653263.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — In a searing speech from the pulpit of a black church, New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo told a Brooklyn congregation on Sunday that Donald Trump is a "slick salesman" who fooled many people in this country, but the Democrat said the Republican president hasn't fooled New Yorkers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  POLITICAL ANGER UNITES A DIVIDED USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/if-you-think-the-political-divide-is-worse-than-ever-you-may-be-right/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Partisan identification is now a bigger wedge between Americans than race, gender, religion or level of education. There is a sense that partisan affiliation reflects more than just a voting preference; rather, it says something about your character.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman warms up rally with Trump death joke...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/08/19/dem-rep-jokes-president-trump-drowning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Department of Veteran Affairs in 'chaos'...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/military/sd-me-va-chaos-20180817-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's efforts to reform Veterans Affairs has resulted in low morale, fear among employees and a federal lawsuit alleging the president's union-busting executive orders violate federal law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyer who defended immigrants could face her own deportation...</title>
      <link>http://www.philly.com/philly/news/immigration-lawyer-deport-university-of-pennsylvania-20180819.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Esperanza Franco loved Penn - and Philadelphia. When she wasn't studying, she strolled South Street or took a seat at Rittenhouse Square to watch the world go by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman warms up rally with Trump death joke...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/browardpolitics/status/1031247046446141442</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“.@AlceeHastingsFL warms up Democratic rally in Sunrise with a joke about the difference between a crisis and a catastrophe. Crisis: if @realDonaldTrump falls into the Potomac River &amp;amp; can’t swim. Catastrophe: If “anybody saves his ass.””</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Women will tilt midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cbs-news-battleground-tracker-poll-democrats-in-stronger-position-to-take-the-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CBS News Battleground Tracker House model shows Democrats poised to win 222 seats if the election were held today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby kissed by Pope overcomes brain tumor...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/baby-brain-tumor-underwent-miraculous-recovery-kiss-pope-francis-204550103.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family commemorated Gianna's recovery with a generous donation to the local hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer Americans Uproot Selves for New Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/fewer-americans-uproot-themselves-for-new-jobs-1534690800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fewer Americans are moving around the country to pursue new work opportunities, as a tighter labor market and changing family ties make people less willing to uproot their lives for a job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears for environment in Spain as pigs outnumber people...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/aug/19/fears-environment-spain-pigs-outnumber-humans-pork-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official figures show there are 50m pigs to 46.5m humans in country famed for its pork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXODUS: Doctors leaving practices to pursue other careers...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/doctor-out-why-physicians-are-leaving-their-practices-pursue-other-n900921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“After 20 years, I quit medicine and none of my colleagues were surprised. In fact, they all said they wish they could do the same,” said one doctor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil sends troops after clashes at border...</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/20180819-brazil-sends-troops-after-clashes-venezuela-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOOKS TURN ON EACH OTHER!</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/sunday-talk-shows/402521-clapper-brennans-rhetoric-is-becoming-an-issue-in-and-of-itself</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper said Sunday that he thinks former CIA Director John Brennan's rhetoric is becoming an issue "in and of itself."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see chance in governorships... </title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/402342-dems-see-chance-to-cut-into-gop-governorships</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are contesting a huge number of Republican-held governorships across the country, seeking to put a dent in the GOP’s grip on state mansions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China shows off automated doctors, teachers, combat stars...</title>
      <link>http://news.abs-cbn.com/life/08/19/18/robot-wars-china-shows-off-automated-doctors-teachers-and-combat-stars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.abs-cbn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popular stars of this year's World Robot Conference were undoubtedly the small, amateur-made 'battle bots' which smashed, hammered and sawed their way through their opponents to a cacophony of cheers and shouts from a rapt audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shocking' amount of fruit and veg wasted, researchers say...</title>
      <link> http://www.itv.com/news/2018-08-19/shocking-amount-of-fruit-and-veg-wasted-researchers-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis march through Berlin -- with police protection...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6074131/Hitler-lookalike-far-right-mob-marching-Berlin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The neo-Nazi supporters held a banner reading 'I regret nothing' through Berlin today in memory of Rudolf Hess today. Left-wing protesters marched against them and threw stones at them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump lashes out at Russia probe as 'McCarthyism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-lashes-russia-probe-mccarthyism-132054232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump on Sunday angrily denounced the federal probe of Russia's 2016 election meddling as "McCarthyism at its WORST!," insisting he had authorized his White House counsel to testify to bring the matter to a close. Trump's Twitter storm was set off by a front-page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli questioning of US Jews at border exposes deeper rift...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/israeli-questioning-us-jews-border-103115055.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — When Simone Zimmerman arrived at the check-in window at the Israeli border with Egypt, it didn't take long for the young activist to run into trouble.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP LAWYER SPENDS 30 HOURS WITH MUELLER...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/08/18/us/politics/don-mcgahn-mueller-investigation.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HE'S NOT A RAT'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c960ddb8064b20ad3d663eb04662c5/Trump-says-WH-lawyer-McGahn-isn't-'a-John-Dean-type-'RAT%22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEWATER, N.J. (AP) — President Donald Trump insisted Sunday that White House lawyer Don McGahn isn't "a John Dean type 'RAT,'" making reference to the Watergate-era White Hous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood protest over tiny home development gets ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.kansas.com/news/nation-world/national/article216981455.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The proposed MicroMansions tiny homes development in Wichita, Kansas is generating a lot of controversy — and a few threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brennan Threatens to Sue Trump After Being Stripped of Clearance...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-brennan-threatens-sue-president-trump-after-being-stripped-c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'I am going to do whatever I can personally to try to prevent these abuses in the future; and if it means going to court, I will do that'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharpton botches spelling of R-E-S-P-E-C-T...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/politics/al-sharpton-messes-name-legendary-aretha-franklin-song-r-e-s-p-c-t/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Sunday, MSNBC’s “Politics Nation” host Rev. Al Sharpton called on President Donald Trump to be respectful but inadvertently misquoted legendary singer Aretha Franklin's most famous lyric.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archaeologists Explore Rural Field In Kansas -- And Lost City Emerges...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-kansas-lost-city-20180819-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kansas archaeology professor believes he's found the lost city of Etzanoa, spurring a rethinking of traditional views on the Native Americans' early settlement of the Midwest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA says conserving oil no longer economic imperative...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyherald.com/news/20180819/us-says-conserving-oil-is-no-longer-an-economic-imperative</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration says conserving oil is no longer an economic imperative for the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Preps For Spotlight...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/402362-kamala-harris-prepares-for-moment-in-the-spotlight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Judge Brett Kavanaugh testifies before the Senate Judiciary Committee during his confirmation hearings next month, he will face a united front of Democratic opposition. He may face no mo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMAROSA WARNS OF 'RACE WAR'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/402512-omarosa-i-believe-trump-wants-to-start-a-race-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House aide Omarosa Manigault Newman on Sunday said President Trump is “disingenuous” in his efforts to help the African-American community, and accused the president of wanting to start a race war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-Nazis march through Berlin -- with police protection...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/19/neo-nazis-march-through-berlin-police-protection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of neo-Nazis waving flags with the colors of the German Reich are marching through central Berlin, protected from counter-protesters by police in riot gear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIULIANI:  LEAK SHOWS MUELLER 'PANICKING'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/aug/19/don-mcgahn-leak-shows-robert-mueller-team-panickin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump attorney Rudy Giuliani suggested Saturday that investigators with the special counsel’s office are “panicking” by leaking information about White House counsel Donald McGahn’s cooperation in an effort to prod the president into testifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi to make first official visit to Pyongyang...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/world/2018/08/19/chinas-xi-to-make-first-official-visit-to-pyongyang-for-north-koreas-70th-anniversary.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese President Xi Jinping is set to visit North Korea next month accepting Kim Jong Un's invitation to attend the country's 70th anniversary of its founding, a report said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of baby abandoned in phone booth solved -- 64 years later...</title>
      <link>https://www.lancastereaglegazette.com/story/news/local/2018/08/17/lancaster-mystery-baby-abandoned-phone-booth-1950-s-solved/977491002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lancastereaglegazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians sort through 8 years of mail held by Israel...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1be6cc435a064d979b894287a277c61d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERICHO, West Bank (AP) — Palestinian postal workers in the West Bank are sifting through eight years' worth of undelivered mail held by Israel.        In recent days the P</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1.1 billion internet gambling ring cracked...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-police-crack-1-1-billion-internet-gambling-101820976--sector.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (Reuters) - Police in eastern China have busted a 7.8 billion yuan ($1.1 billion) online gambling ring and arrested 56 suspects, the official Xinhua news agency reported on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 suspected tomb robbers nabbed...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/china-nabs-26-suspected-tomb-robbers-recovers-valuable-090108838.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China has arrested 26 suspects and retrieved almost 650 cultural relics stolen from an ancient burial site in northwestern Qinghai province, the Ministry of Public Security said on Sunday. China's official Xinhua news agency said experts believe many of the items recovered are of "tremendous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty hotels, idle boats: What happens when island upsets China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pacific-china-palau-insight/empty-hotels-idle-boats-what-happens-when-a-pacific-island-upsets-china-idUSKBN1L4036</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Empty hotel rooms, idle tour boats and shuttered travel agencies reveal widening fissures in the tiny Pacific nation of Palau, which is caught in an escalating diplomatic tug-of-war between China and Taiwan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to Unveil Fighter Jet; Boosts Missile Capability...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/08/19/iran-to-unveil-new-fighter-jet-boost-missile-capability</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran to Unveil Fighter Jet as It Boosts Missile Capability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>14 injured by storm at BACKSTREET BOYS concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/08/18/backstreet-boys-concert-storm-injuries-oklahoma/1035074002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Winds at up to 80 mph knocked over supports as 150 people waited in line at the concert venue near Oklahoma City</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE: Man detained driving pregnant wife to hospital wanted for murder charges...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-ice-detained-man-with-pregnant-wife20180818-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An expectant mother must deliver her baby alone after her husband was detained by ICE while the couple were on the way to the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Lenses Creating Huge Problem for Waterways...</title>
      <link>https://www.inverse.com/article/48164-microplastic-pollution-contact-lenses</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inverse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All those tiny discs add up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'So much blood' after angry golfer's club flies into crowd...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/18/so-much-blood-after-angry-golfers-club-flies-into-crowd/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans often have to be watchful after a bad golf shot. They just don’t usually have to watch out for a flying club. After hitting an errant tee shot on the 15th hole Friday at a Web.com Tour event, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA says air marshals don't follow 'ordinary' travelers. Some ordinary travelers beg to differ...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2018/08/18/tsa-says-armed-air-marshals-don-follow-ordinary-fliers-some-ordinary-fliers-beg-differ/Y0k3mV3HPUCgzS20PpAU3H/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’s a social media for an arts and crafts company, and somehow became a target of a secret TSA surveillance program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA TURNS 60 IN MOROCCO...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6071889/Madonna-turns-60-Pop-icon-hosts-FIVE-day-party-Moroccan-palace-celebrate-birthday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen of Pop is throwing an extravagant five-day bash at a Moroccan palace to celebrate her 60th birthday, and looked sensational as she partied away on the first night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warnings grow from forgotten Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-warnings-grow-forgotten-republicans-044631823--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The ranks of forgotten Republicans are growing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota Dems endorse Ellison amid abuse allegation...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/minnesota-democrats-endorse-ellison-amid-abuse-allegation-193737151--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Minnesota Democrats are standing behind U.S. Rep. Keith Ellison and his bid for state attorney general, with the state party giving him an endorsement Saturday amid an allegation of domestic abuse from an ex-girlfriend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another trial looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/another-trial-looms-ex-trump-campaign-chairman-manafort-120430511--politics.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALEXANDRIA, Va. (AP) — As jurors weigh Paul Manafort's fate in a sprawling financial fraud case, the former Trump campaign chairman still has another trial looming in the nation's capital — and prosecutors there have a whole new set of charges and a huge volume of evidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Hernandez's suicide notes revealed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/08/18/aaron-hernandezs-suicide-notes-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When attorney Jose Baez first met Aaron Hernandez in 2016, the former NFL star was already serving life in prison. The then-26-year-old had been arrested for the murder of Odin Lloyd, an acquaintan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADONNA TURNS 60 IN MOROCCO...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-6074867/Madonnas-60th-birthday-bash-Inside-lush-350-night-Moroccan-palace-singer-threw-party.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Take a glimpse inside the magnificent boutique Riad El Fenn hotel where Madonna threw her boozy five-day 60th birthday bash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan vows Turkey will not be cowed by USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/erdogan-vows-turkey-not-cowed-us-131200921.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan declared Saturday that his country would not be cowed by the United States, his latest broadside in the bitter feud between Ankara and Washington. The two NATO members are at odds over Turkey's detention of an American pastor, which has triggered a trade row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Spacey Movie Earns $126 on Opening Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/box-office-kevin-spaceys-billionaire-boys-club-earns-126-friday-1135816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ensemble crime-drama — also starring Ansel Elgort and Taron Egerton — marks a career box-office low for the disgraced Spacey after premiering first on VOD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Woman Uses N-Word on DC City Bus, Gets Beat Up...</title>
      <link>https://wpgc.radio.com/blogs/white-woman-calls-someone-n-word-x2-bus-ne-gets-beat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpgc.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black director blasts Spike Lee for selling out...</title>
      <link>https://urbanhollywood411.com/2018/08/17/boots-riley-slams-spike-lees-black-kkklansman-as-made-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;urbanhollywood411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Riley claims the film fails to paint an accurate picture of police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER ADMITS:  WE LEAN LEFT...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/402495-twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-i-fully-admit-our-bias-is-more-left-leaning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey said on Saturday that he "fully admit[s]" Twitter employees share a largely left-leaning bias after facing accusations that conservatives are discriminated against on the social media platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8.2 MAG QUAKE STRIKES PACIFIC</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180819010104-ilciz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PACIFIC-QUAKE/ (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Magnitude 8.2 quake strikes in the Pacific, no damage expected -USGS</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
