<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>ALPHABET tries to salvage its smart city plans in Toronto...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/24/tech/sidewalk-labs-toronto-plan/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's parent company continues its attempts to sell Toronto on its controversial vision for a utopian city neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump caving on deportations?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/opinion/trump-blinks-on-immigration-failing-his-supporters-one-more-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Never underestimate the ability of some of President Trump’s most devoted supporters to delude themselves into thinking each one of his losses on immigration is actually a win. Case in point, the right-leaning Washington Times reported in earnest that House Democrats “blinked” by agreeing to “grant…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex smears fly in White House press secretary race...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/sex-crimes-and-incompetence-smears-fly-in-white-house-press-secretary-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anonymous tales of sex, vengeance, laziness, and criminal behavior are swirling in Washington as President Trump considers who to name his next White House press secretary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA WARSHIP DOCKS IN HAVANA</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9365741/russia-warns-cuban-missile-crisis-warship-havana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA has warned the US its build-up of weapons in Europe risks a repeat of the Cuban missile crisis – as a Moscow warship docked near Havana yesterday. Russian Deputy Foreign Minister Serge…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado's snowpack 40 times normal after rare summer solstice dump...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Colorado-s-snowpack-is-40-times-normal-after-rare-14036967.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On summer's opening day, up to 20 inches of snow buried the high terrain of the Colorado Rockies, boosting the state's snowpack to extraordinary levels for the time of year.  The solstice flakes marked a continuation of a snowy stretch that began in January and February and lingered through spring. Even before the solstice snow, The Denver Post wrote, the state's snowpack was "in virtually every numerical sense . . . off the charts." At the time, the snowpack was 751 percent above normal.  Due to the new snow Friday into the weekend, the Natural Resources Conservation Service reported that the state's snowpack ballooned to 4,121 percent above normal as of Monday. This number is so high because ordinarily very little snow is left by late June, and cold temperatures late into the spring helped preserve what fell earlier.  After the weekend blanket of white, the scenes in the high country west of Denver resembled midwinter. Enough snow fell to close roads, while many ski areas reported accumulation, including Breckenridge, Vail, Beaver Creek, Arapahoe Basin and Steamboat Springs.  At Steamboat, snow stakes showed up to around 20 inches Saturday. CNN wrote that the last time this area witnessed snow this late in the season was June 17, 1928. It averages just 0.1 inches in June and normally sees its last day of snow around May 6.  At Arapahoe Basin, so much snow has fallen since the winter that it has stayed opened for skiing on weekends through the month. It declared Saturday a powder day after a fresh coating of two inches. The resort plans to open again next weekend and possibly over the July 4 weekend, its blog says.  The snow was triggered by an unusually cold pool of air at high altitudes over the western United States combined with a vigorous weather disturbance that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie faces new kind of threat in Elizabeth Warren... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Bernie-Sanders-faces-a-new-kind-of-threat-in-14039192.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Bernie Sanders campaign, facing a new challenge in the rise of Elizabeth Warren, has settled for now on a careful if sometimes awkward strategy: emphasizing Sanders's unique position in the liberal movement, while avoiding direct attacks on Warren and rolling out plans that overlap with her attention-grabbing ideas.  That approach was on display Monday as Sanders introduced a proposal to cancel all student debt across the country. His plan came less than two weeks after Warren announced her own idea for scrapping student debt, one that would cover fewer people than Sanders's would. "Under the proposal we introduced today, all student debt would be canceled in six months," Sanders said.  But doubling down on his ideological purity and socialist credentials carries risks for the senator from Vermont, other Democrats say. It's enabled Warren to position herself as impassioned but reasonable, while Sanders holds down the leftward flank of the Democratic Party and serves as the ideological outlier in the race.  "They both have a crusader mentality around correcting what is wrong," said Rep. Pramila Jayapal, D-Wash., who knows both and has not yet endorsed in the contest. "They understand they are speaking to a similar vision of the country, and obviously they are trying to distinguish themselves from each other."  For Sanders, the threat from Warren, D-Mass., is different from any he's faced during his long political career, including in his 2016 presidential run, since Warren in many ways embraces the same brand of fiery liberalism.  Among some Sanders allies, there is private frustration that Warren is getting credit for ideas that they believe originated with him. And that frustration is starting to show.  Last Friday, Warren released a plan to end private prisons. That same day, Sanders adviser Josh Orton...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna Hits No. 1 for a Ninth Time With 'Madame X'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/madonna-achieves-ninth-no-1-album-billboard-200-chart-madame-x-1220485</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plus: Bruce Springsteen and Bastille debut in top 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems form circular firing squad...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/450127-press-democrats-form-circular-firing-squad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats, get ahold of yourselves. It’s still early in this silly political season, but you’ve already gone off the deep end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEFT GOES FOR DRUDGE -- WITH EX-FOXNEWS REPORTER HOSTING...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/450079-former-fox-news-reporter-says-he-left-because-of-partisan-misinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News reporter Carl Cameron said Monday that he left the network favored by conservatives because "right-wing hosts drowned out straight journalism with partisan misinformation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Proposes to Wipe Out All Student Debt With Funds Raised From Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a5cb6665aa1d4e4c961f84b66a2ed730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> MSM Ignores...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/blacklist-msm-ignores-project-veritas-bombshell-google-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Story red-linked on Drudge, addressed by members of Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. Names First Female CEO...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2019/biz/news/warner-bros-ann-sarnoff-1203251469/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warner Bros. has tapped BBC Studios Americas president Ann Sarnoff as its new CEO, a surprise pick that is sure to shake up the venerable studio. Sarnoff becomes the first woman to head Warner Bros…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sexually tortured bound man incapacitated by date-rape drug...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/revolting/alabama-torture-arrest-976315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 21--An Alabama woman has been charged with the sexual torture of a 25-year-old man who was “under the influence of GHB” and bound with duct tape when he was assaulted, according to court filing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced warship enters Havana harbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/24/admiral-gorshkov-russian-warship-enters-havana-har/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the Russian navy’s most advanced warships entered Havana’s harbor Monday and docked at the port used until this month by U.S. cruise lines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House moves to bar Kellyanne from testifying to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/kellyanne-conway-says-democrats-seeking-testimony-on-hatch-act-violations-are-retaliating-against-her-politically/2019/06/24/9398d3ea-9689-11e9-830a-21b9b36b64ad_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a television interview, the White House counselor said Trump’s opponents are trying to silence her because she successfully managed his 2016 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still working, 99-year-old woman shares secrets to health...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news/still-working-for-the-state-after-76-years-99-year-old-woman-shares-her-secrets-to-health/ar-AADlC2w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police release video of Jussie Smollett with noose around his neck...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/cpd-releases-investigative-files-video-of-alleged-staged-attack-on-jussie-smollett/5361979/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police released their investigative files and video Monday of the alleged staged attack on "Empire" actor Jussie Smollett in late January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activists to burn flag at D.C. July Fourth rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/burn-that-rag-activists-to-desecrate-the-flag-at-trump-july-fourth-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sparks will fly in Washington as activists torch an American flag to protest President Trump's July Fourth "Salute to America," which Trump claims will be one of the largest events in city history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Terrified' doctors refuse patients in pain amid opioid epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2019/06/24/pain-patients-left-anguish-doctors-who-fear-opioid-addiction/1379636001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cancer, cystic fibrosis and other chronic pain patients struggle to find doctors who will prescribe them painkillers amid the opioid addiction crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BURNING MAN HIRES LOBBYIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/politico-influence/2019/06/24/williams-jensen-lobbyist-heads-to-alignment-450037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Burning Man hires a lobbyist — Chinese drone company warns against ‘unsubstantiated speculation’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Coffee could be secret to burning fat...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2019/06/24/coffee-could-help-burn-fat-new-study-says/1545452001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study from the University of Nottingham has found that coffee can stimulate fat fighters in the body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Baby Boomers ruined America...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/06/boomers-are-blame-aging-america/592336/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mistakes of the past are fast creating a crisis for younger Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top scientists: Powerless to stop gene-edited babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2019/06/24/outraged-by-new-crispr-babies-plan-top-science-figures-say-theyre-powerless-to-stop-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two influential leaders in science publicly condemned a Russian biologist behind the plans but conceded it was beyond their authority to stop him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX poised for dramatic night launch...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/spacex-falcon-heavy-poised-for-dramatic-night-launch-tonight-2019-06-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SpaceX Falcon Heavy rocket carrying 24 satellites prepped for launch; also on board: portions of the cremated remains of 152 space enthusiasts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Missouri's last abortion clinic can stay open until Friday...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/450054-judge-extends-permission-for-missouris-only-abortion-clinic-to-remain-open</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missouri's lone abortion clinic can stay open until at least Friday after a judge ruled to extend a preliminary injunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Mistook 'Blood Moon' for Red Planet in Tweet...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/06/elon-musk-blood-moon-mars-spacex-tweet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The space entrepreneur was confused about what the red planet looks like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kangaroo seen hopping across Wisconsin walking bridge...</title>
      <link>https://www.postcrescent.com/story/news/2019/06/24/grand-chute-kangaroo-reportedly-seen-hopping-across-interstate-41-walking-bridge/1545337001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postcrescent.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The kangaroo was supposedly seen crossing the walking bridge over Interstate 41 heading east from Fox Cities Stadium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilot killed as Eurofighter jets collide in midair...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/24/europe/eurofighter-jets-crash-germany-grm-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two Eurofighter jets crashed in midair in northern Germany on Monday, killing one of the pilots, according to the German air force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAR GAMES:  USA Kicks Off 19-Nation Drills in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/u-s-kicks-off-19-nation-war-games-drills-in-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and partners from 19 countries are getting set to kick off a series of war drills in Ukraine amid rising threats from Iran and Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA launching deep-space atomic clock; Could transform exploration...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/nasa-launch-deep-space-atomic-clock-could-transform-space-exploration-ncna1021016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The device is designed to make navigation to distant objects in space more autonomous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muslim women 'inspired by Rosa Parks' defy pool burkini ban...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/muslim-women-inspired-by-rosa-parks-defy-burkini-ban-at-french-pool-11748156</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The women do not want to accept "another summer deprived of access to public pools" ahead of an expected heatwave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Popular Knitting Site Bans Support For President On Platform...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/06/24/ravelry-knitting-community-website-trump-white-supremacy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Raverly is accusing his administration of propagating "open white supremacy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch telephone outage hits emergency services' alarm number...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e610861f8a94525b4e81af446ff2bbf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puppy needs reconstructive surgery after mouth was tied shut to stop barking...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/us-news/puppy-needs-reconstructive-surgery-after-17101010</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARNING - DISTRESSING IMAGES: Vets say the four-month-old black Labrador mix now needs surgery after owner Alexis Callen allegedly taped her mouth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNER BROS. Names First Female CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/ann-sarnoff-named-warner-bros-ceo-surprise-pick-1217672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the former BBC executive, WarnerMedia CEO John Stankey finds a leader with the operational chops to woo the telecom giant's Dallas-based top brass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian mafia boss flees Uruguayan prison... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/italian-mafia-boss-morabito-flees-uruguayan-prison-154827753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italian mafia boss Rocco Morabito has fled prison in the Uruguayan capital Montevideo, where he was awaiting extradition to Italy, the interior ministry announced Monday. Morabito and three other inmates "escaped through a hole in the roof of the building" late Sunday and robbed the occupants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS FALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/ratings-nik-and-lijana-wallendas-highwire-live-nets-5-2-million-viewers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Vitamin D Supplements Have NO Impact On Heart Health, Don't Lower Risk For Disease; Researchers Surprised...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/vitamin-d-supplements-dont-lower-risk-heart-disease/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're taking vitamin D supplements every day to improve your heart's health and reduce your chances of suffering from cardiovascular disease, you're likely wasting your money, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia military jets prepare for 'observational flights' over United States...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/787592/russia-united-states-observational-flights-military-open-skies-treaty</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Voters not tuned in...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/705afbd6b5c247f8ba2f81d212e5808e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer scorcher... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/searing-heat-across-europe-sparks-scramble-shade-111231664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fans flew off store shelves and water fountains offered relief from the heat as temperatures soared in Europe on Monday, with officials urging vigilance ahead of even hotter conditions forecast later in the week. Meteorologists blamed a blast of torrid air from the Sahara for the unusually early summer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DANGER</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/joe-biden-faces-most-dangerous-080000279.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Joe Biden kicks off the most high-stakes week of his campaign so far, as he heads into the first Democratic debate with the opportunity to solidify his front-runner status — or jeopardize it with a gaffe, an inappropriate joke or a tone-deaf comment.The former vice president doesn’t need</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN begins Slurpee delivery in public spaces...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-eleven-deliver-slurpees-other-040551391.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;7-Eleven launched a delivery service Monday that will send a Slurpee or almost anything else carried by the chain to public places ranging from parks to beaches. The company told The Associated Press that more than 2,000 7-Eleven "hot spots" including New York's Central Park and Venice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES:  Gorsuch Joins Liberals To Deal Victory For Criminal Defendants...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/06/24/gorsuch-liberals-gun-crimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Justice Neil Gorsuch joined with the Supreme Court's liberal bloc to deal victory for criminal defendants Monday, striking down a law that punishes gun crimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE Threats...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cf67b367c4164d4885ce14a3126eaa2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE sanctions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9390faa746294f628b93beea57ba1e07</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants emptying Western Unions near border...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/western-unions-being-cleaned-out-as-migrants-pass-through-one-texas-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN ANTONIO, Texas — People assisting the thousands of migrants who have arrived in San Antonio after being released from federal custody say Western Unions downtown are regularly running out of cash as a result of the high number of withdrawals being made by emigrants from Central American and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famed snowboarding daredevil randomly killed on L.A. street...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-dmitry-koltsov-murder-20190624-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dmitry Koltsov was a Russian snowboarding champ and beloved member of L.A.'s skate and surf scene before police say he crossed paths with a troubled Utah man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Malibu Has Embraced 'Optimism' After Devastating Fire; 'Chance to Start Over'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-malibu-has-embraced-optimism-post-fire-1219016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sale prices are up in the tony beachside community, but only three permits have been issued to reconstruct homes destroyed by November's destructive flames.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspired by Nipsey Hussle, Crips and Bloods begin most extensive peace talks since riots...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/inspired-by-nipsey-hussle-crips-and-bloods-begin-the-most/article_4e56f002-80d5-5976-83ee-90026e328876.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — The men arrived in twos and threes, Crips and Bloods, young and middle-aged, gathering around a picnic table in a Compton park to confront their sworn enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man shot to death at his own birthday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/crime/article231884428.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN DANGER</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-06-24/joe-biden-faces-the-most-dangerous-week-of-his-campaign-so-far</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside China's 'thought transformation' camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/av/world-asia-china-48667221/inside-china-s-thought-transformation-camps</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The BBC gets rare access to facilities in Xinjiang thought to be holding more than a million Muslims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocked by Stock Collapse, 'HUNGER GAMES' Studio Ready to Talk...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rocked-stock-collapse-hunger-games-120000695.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The studio that brought you “The Hunger Games,’’ “Mad Men’’ and “John Wick’’ is now facing its own existential question.Lions Gate Entertainment Corp. has lost more than half its market value over the last year as the once-idolized filmmaker struggles to find new megahits. On top of that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man posed as UBER driver to kidnap drunken women...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/fake-uber-alabama-624190</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JUNE 24--An Alabama man who posed as an Uber driver to pick up intoxicated women has been charged with kidnapping and could face additional crimes in connection with his predatory scheme. Tommy Wayne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatens more attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2019/06/24/pompeo-coalition-iran/1544824001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pompeo spoke as he left Washington for Saudi Arabia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communist party USA sees chance as progressives surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/jun/23/communist-party-usa-chicago-cpusa-convention</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Chicago, an American party derided and feared for 100 years looked eagerly to a brighter future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago, where rich live 30 years longer than poor...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/23/chicago-latest-news-life-expectancy-rich-poor-inequality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In rich white Streeterville, Chicagoans can expect to live to 90. In poor black Englewood, it’s just 60 – the most divergent of any US city</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea killing fields where people shot for stealing cow, watching TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/north-koreas-killing-fields-people-16536727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report has found that hundreds are executed in Kim Jong-un's secretive state and that the family and friends of those condemned are forced to watch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intense heat wave to strike Paris, shimmer across Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2416500c2e9f49218bad783f2e28c57d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider Reveals GOOGLE Plan to Prevent 'Trump Situation' in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/2019/06/24/insider-blows-whistle-exec-reveals-google-plan-to-prevent-trump-situation-in-2020-on-hidden-cam/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Woman fell asleep mid-flight and woke up trapped in dark plane alone...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-za/lifestyle/travel/this-is-a-nightmare-a-woman-fell-asleep-mid-flight-and-woke-up-trapped-in-a-dark-plane-alone/ar-AADlv9v?li=BBqg6Q6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Leads Chorus of Wealthy Calling For New Wealth Tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/daviddawkins/2019/06/24/george-soros-leads-chorus-of-billionaires-calling-for-a-new-wealth-tax/#7375a071ce72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire George Soros and members of the Gund and Pritzker families are among a number of the world's wealthiest business leaders to have signed a letter calling for a new U.S. wealth tax.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tourist says doctors told her she was 'poisoned'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/24/health/dominican-republic-sickness-deaths-invs/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their island getaways went bad in ways that sound similar: crippling stomach cramps, explosive diarrhea and malaise that lasted after they returned home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Freaked' when pole slipped...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/77f900c907ea4b1cb6b0b590757a443e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  More Americans than ever call immigration top problem...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/259103/new-high-say-immigration-important-problem.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 23% of Americans naming immigration as the most important problem is the highest Gallup has recorded, though slightly more still say the government is the top U.S. problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of repeat of Cuban missile crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-usa-missiles/russia-warns-of-repeat-of-cuban-missile-crisis-tass-idUSKCN1TP14Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington's deployment of land-based missile systems near Russia's bo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mercury climbs as Europe braces for summer scorcher... </title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190624-searing-heat-across-europe-sparks-scramble-shade</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Searing heat across Europe sparks scramble for shade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of Money Bristle at Zuckerberg's New Financial Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/guardians-of-money-bristle-at-zuckerberg-s-new-financial-order-1.1277277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACK THAT! Iran says U.S. cyber attacks failed...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190624113136-xfxcm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIDEAST-IRAN/USA (WRAPUP 2, PIX):WRAPUP 2-Iran says U.S. cyber attacks failed, hints talks are possible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANNY BOYLE: 'I'd feel like imposter if made film with female lead'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/features/danny-boyle-yesterday-beatles-james-bond-25-robert-pattinson-batman-interview-a8967666.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A.I. May Not Take Job -- but Could Become Boss...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/technology/tech-news-technology/artificial-intelligence-may-not-take-your-job-but-it-could-become-your-boss-5796382/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Critics have accused companies of using algorithms for managerial tasks, saying that automated systems can dehumanize and unfairly punish employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York man becomes 11th Dominican Republic vacation death...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5dc.com/news/li-man-becomes-11th-dominican-republic-vacation-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Dominican officials try to quell rising concerns among would-be travelers worldwide about safety there, the U.S. Department of State&amp;nbsp;on Friday confirmed to Fox News the June 17 death of a New York business owner, Vittorio Caruso, 56, who died after becoming critically ill at the Boca Chica Resort in Santo Domingo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'You want black people to vote for you?'</title>
      <link>https://www.southbendtribune.com/news/local/marchers-confront-pete-buttigieg-police-chief-with-frustrations-after-south/article_25ff0d24-c317-53ed-9999-4f51ac5bcf36.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.southbendtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrators call for training, federal review of case in wake of shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE LEAKS:  Trump vetting docs...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/leaked-donald-trump-vetting-docs-hbo-6ce3cd26-1eb9-4da8-b15e-47b56020aef7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the contenders were strikingly swampy — even by the RNC vetters' standards.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
