<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Millions struggle through life with few to trust...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-459178f46ca2c62d6b6ad51517bada81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Karen Glidden's loneliness became unbearable during the coronavirus pandemic . The 72-year-old widow, who suffers from vision loss and diabetes and lives far from any relatives, barely left her house in Champion, Michigan, this past year, for fear of contracting the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL BRANSON BEAT BEZOS?</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/15212243/richard-branson-jeff-bezos-space-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IT could be a battle of the billionaires to see who can launch themselves into space first as Richard Branson could beat Jeff Bezos. The Amazon CEO announced this week that he and his brother would…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery surrounds DOJ pledge on journalist records...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/557683-mystery-surrounds-justices-pledge-on-journalist-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department’s pledge that it will no longer secretly obtain the records of journalists has left a number of unanswered questions about the department’s handling of leak investigations initiated under the Trump-era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have Echo Device? AMAZON May Help Itself to Your Wi-Fi...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2021-06-09/have-an-echo-device-amazon-may-help-itself-to-your-wi-fi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Do you own an Amazon smart device.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is She Being Set Up to Fail?</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2021/06/harris-biden-immigration-voting-rights.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vice president has been assigned to lead on the issues the White House finds particularly challenging. What does this bode for her political future?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New era of robot war may be underway unnoticed...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610093118-1xf7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APPS-DRONES/ (COLUMN, PIX):COLUMN-New era of robot war may be underway unnoticed: Peter Apps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoover Dam reservoir record low...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210610085045-9uvq6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-DROUGHT/ (PIX, GRAPHIC):Hoover Dam reservoir hits record low, in sign of extreme western U.S. drought</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocket on pad, China ready to send 1st crew to space station...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-science-7fa5ef676c9c4725579cf91443bd4564</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The rocket that will send the first crew members to live on China's new orbiting space station has been moved onto the launch pad ahead of its planned blastoff next week. The three astronauts plan to spend three months on the space station doing spacewalks, construction and maintenance work and science experiments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new guy? Joe debuts at democracy's most exclusive club...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-joe-biden-canada-europe-g-7-summit-52469dff2d3e135a89c352589e2908de</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Angela, Boris, Emmanuel, Justin, Mario, Yoshihide and a relative newcomer: Joe. They’re the board of global democracy’s most exclusive club, and they’re meeting this week after four years of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyberattack Forces College to Cancel Classes for Days...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/3aqaa8/hackers-force-iowa-college-to-cancel-classes-for-four-days</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “cyberattack” is disrupting classes at the Des Moines Area Community College, where the school has cancelled in-person classes for four days and counting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong Un weight loss could have consequences...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/kim-jong-un-appears-to-have-lost-some-weight-e2-80-94-and-that-could-have-geopolitical-consequences/ar-AAKTQVc </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of mysterious fast radio bursts detected in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/world/fast-radio-bursts-chime-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists used the CHIME radio telescope in Canada to detect 535 mysterious fast radio bursts in space over the course of a year. These bursts could be used to map the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador to use energy from volcanoes for bitcoin mining...</title>
      <link>https://uk.finance.yahoo.com/news/el-salvador-energy-volcanoes-bitcoin-082346002.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Country’s President tweeted plans to build full bitcoin mining hub powered by geothermal energy from volcano</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery malware steals 26M passwords from 3M PCs...</title>
      <link>https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2021/06/nameless-malware-collects-1-2tb-of-sensitive-data-and-stashes-it-online/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;arstechnica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Massive trove can be used for ransomware, espionage, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden personal diplomacy to be tested by allies -- and adversary...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-personal-diplomacy-to-be-tested-by-allies-e2-80-94-and-one-adversary-e2-80-94-on-his-first-trip-abroad/ar-AAKSCHZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden, on his first foreign trip as president, plans to reassert U.S. global leadership and let Russian President Vladimir Putin “know what I want him to know.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pursued CNN reporter records in secret court battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/politics/trump-pursuit-cnn-reporter-records-secret-court-battle/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration battled with CNN for half a year to obtain the email records of a reporter and insisted it all take place under an extraordinary order of secrecy, CNN's lead attorney revealed on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Tenn. gov linked to closed cold case murder...</title>
      <link>https://www.kens5.com/article/news/nation-world/ousted-tennessee-governor-ray-blanton-linked-to-closed-cold-case-chattanooga-murder/507-5167664a-187c-4ba5-b6e7-9fd3db59a1aa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kens5.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New details revealed for the first time Wednesday about the 1979 murder of a key federal witness in Tennessee have elements that seem like a movie plot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bogus Social Media Outrage Making Authors Change Lines in Their Books...</title>
      <link>https://slate.com/culture/2021/06/elin-hilderbrand-casey-mcquiston-antisemitism-israel-social-media.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;slate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The silly idea that a fictional character’s statements reflect an author’s actual beliefs is spreading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No vaccine, no job: Hospital suspends 178 health care workers for refusing shots...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2021/06/09/houston-methodist-hospital-workers-refuse-covid-vaccine-get-suspended/7616446002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scores of workers at a Houston Methodist hospital system have been suspended and face being fired for refusing the COVID-19 vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celeb plastic surgeon breaks ranks, says 'breast implant illness' real...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/06/09/celeb-plastic-surgeon-says-breast-implant-illness-is-real/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Youn, a Detroit-based plastic surgeon with a following of 4.6 million on TikTok, has made his stance known in the contentious debate over “breast implant illness,” which som…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beaches Across Country Plagued By Swarms Of Rowdy Crowds Organized Through Socials...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/06/09/hampton-beach-tiktok-crowds-police-chief-david-hobbs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Large and rowdy crowds that have been causing issues at Hampton Beach in recent weeks are organizing through social media, according to the town’s police chief.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improbable true story of Judge Judy and the reporter who made her a star...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/improbable-true-story-judge-judy-120011400.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Times profile launched Judith Sheindlin to daytime TV dominance. To mark her final episode, reporter and subject look back on an unlikely journey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI DOWNLOADS</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/dr-fauci-absolutely-unleashes-on-his-critics-when-you-attack-dr-anthony-fauci-you-are-attacking-science/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci has evidently had enough of the increasing criticism being pointed his way — particularly from the political right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In some countries, people think they have too much freedom of speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2021/06/07/in-some-countries-people-think-they-have-too-much-freedom-of-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.economist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey shows that in Kenya, Nigeria and Tunisia, citizens reckon there is too much liberty to give offence | Graphic detail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How processed foods became so unhealthy...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20210608-what-were-the-first-processed-foods</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From putrid water to fizzy cola, food processing gave us preservation, consistency and innovation. So how did it become associated with unhealthy food?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald backers lose big in NJ...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/08/ciattarelli-gop-new-jersey-primary-492354</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack Ciattarelli is New Jersey Republicans’ choice to take on Democratic Gov. Phil Murphy in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel first country to ban sale of fur to fashion industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-bans-the-fur-trade-to-fashion-industry-first-country-to-do-so-670538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gamliel: "Animal fur coats cannot cover the brutal murder industry that makes them."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador first to adopt Bitcoin as legal tender...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/09/el-salvador-proposes-law-to-make-bitcoin-legal-tender.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers in the Central American country's Congress voted by a "supermajority" in favor of the Bitcoin Law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK plans first smartwatch -- 2 cameras, heart monitor...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2021/6/9/22526266/facebook-smartwatch-two-cameras-heart-rate-monitor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A way for Facebook to get around Apple and Google.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Cold Makes Big Comeback...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/06/08/reemergence-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Perry Halkitis with Rutgers says it's going around, and you may catch it no matter how healthy or strong your immunity is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Pandemic Changed Antarctica...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7ev5n/how-the-covid-pandemic-changed-antarctica-v28n2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers returning home from Antarctica ‘left one world and have come back to another.’ But while their lives were in stasis, the continent they live on continued to struggle under the weight of diplomatic pressures and environmental concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns Venezuela, Cuba to turn away Iran ships believed to be carrying arms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/09/venezuela-cuba-iran-ships-492602</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caracas is trying to leverage the situation to gain relief from U.S. sanctions, officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exorbitant NFT prices mirror modern art?</title>
      <link>https://www.newsweek.com/dont-dismiss-digital-art-opinion-1598683</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With money machines around the world humming, it is not surprising that pieces of digital art have been selling at record prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials worry adversaries may exploit energy-emitting devices to harm Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/mystery-over-havana-syndrome-lingers-new-concern-emerges-n1270082</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials are concerned that foreign adversaries may exploit energy-emitting devices to harm Americans now that they’re suspected of causing debilitating symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB cheating worries as sticky baseballs become concern...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/06/09/mlb-working-to-combat-cheating-after-sticky-baseballs-become-a-concern.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB officials plan to empower umpires to enforce rules about players using sticky substances on baseballs, and the league could explore increasing suspensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mormon church unlocked medical pot for deep red states...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/06/09/mormon-church-medical-marijuana-491924</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“They did everything that they could to fight this until the people had spoken," a former state lawmaker said of the church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Mead lowest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/08/weather/hoover-dam-lake-mead-water-level-drought/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crippling drought in the western US is dropping the water level at Lake Mead and the Hoover Dam to a historically low level, putting pressure on the region's drinking water supply and the dam's electric capacity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Makes Rapid Tests Key to Everyday Freedoms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/06/09/germany-makes-rapid-virus-tests-a-key-to-everyday-freedoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN — Want to go out for a meal indoors in Germany? Get a test. Want to stay at a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billboards supporting Morgan Wallen pop up in Nashville before CMT Awards...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/06/08/morgan-wallen-billboards-pop-up-nashville-days-before-cmt-awards/7600098002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billboards mark the third set of billboards funded by fans of Morgan Wallen, voted ineligible now for multiple CMA Music Awards on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire rages near Jerusalem, villages evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210609-fire-rages-near-jerusalem-villages-evacuated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fire rages near Jerusalem, villages evacuated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global internet outage caused by customer change of setting...</title>
      <link>https://timesofmalta.com/articles/view/global-internet-outage-caused-by-customer-change-of-setting.878054</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;timesofmalta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worldwide internet outage affecting major websites was caused by a "customer configuration change" which triggered a "bug" in a key delivery network, the technology firm at the centre of the mishap said Wednesday. Nick Rockwell of US-based tech firm Fastly said in a blog post that the outage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics WILL NOT Be Cancelled Declares NBC, With Big Bucks On Line...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/06/nbcuniversal-says-tokyo-olympic-games-are-on-with-7000-hours-of-programming-across-platforms-1234770686/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBCUniversal said Monday that it will present an unprecedented 7,000 hours of coverage of the Tokyo Olympics this summer on two broadcast networks, six cable networks and multiple digital platforms…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House drops orders trying to ban TIKTOK, WECHAT...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/tiktok-wechat-technology-biden-trump-d866cf95c7f1b802ffb88b2834117f0b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House has dropped Trump-era executive orders that attempted to ban the popular apps TikTok and WeChat and will conduct its own review aimed at identifying national security risks with software applications tied to China, officials said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'All-in' Buddhist practice combines meditation and martial arts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-meditation-sports-martial-arts-religion-cc3c4a0c8a3ab0b89aec4d5d711be07d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(RNS) — In all Zen traditions, meditation is the backbone of the practice. Students sit with a tall spine, hands loosely interlocked and eyes half-closed. At Chosei Zen in Madison, Wisconsin, though, new students are never quite prepared for the rigor of Rinzai Zen, which asks participants to remain motionless for up to 45 minutes — twice a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Rich Laughing From Escape Pods...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeff-bezos-hardly-pays-taxes-and-is-going-to-space-and-hell-no-we-are-not-in-this-together</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If America were a group dinner, the uber wealthy would be the ones ordering several of the most expensive items on the menu and then skipping out without paying the tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House 'Perplexed' By Performance...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/white-house-perplexed-over-kamala-harris-first-foreign-policy-trip-performance-according-to-cnn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unnamed White House “insiders” were left “perplexed” by the performance of Vice President Kamala Harris on her recent trip to Guatemala and Mexico to address the root causes of the immigration problems at the US Southern border. This report comes from CNN’s Jeremy Diamond, who joined the vice president on her trip and shared his […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron slapper ID'd as far right follower, Middle Ages enthusiast...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/french-president-emmanuel-macron-slapper-identified-far-right-royalist-middle-ages-enthusiast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two 28-year old men have been arrested following the incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The perfect storm making everything you need more expensive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/09/business/rising-prices-inventories-post-pandemic/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steel, lumber, plastic and fuel. Corn, soybeans, sugar and sunflower oil. Houses, cars, diapers and toilet paper. Prices are rising almost everywhere you look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' set to blaze sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/solar-eclipse-ring-of-fire-rare-watch-june-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look up! But don't forget your solar eclipse glasses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China conducts amphibious landing drill after US senators land on Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-taiwan-media-business-health-9d53b2ed7b38462888e5ec1fc659ad88</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese military has conducted an amphibious landing exercise in waters near Taiwan amid renewed tensions between Beijing and Washington .</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
