<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>The battles of Roseanne Barr and why spinoff could lead to epic fight...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/tv/la-et-st-roseanne-war-20180614-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A look back at the battles that Roseanne Barr has fought her whole career, what they have in common with her current break up with ABC over a racist tweet and why a proposed spin-off series without Roseanne could set off the biggest battle yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite record high confidence, businesses can't find workers they need...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/14/despite-record-high-confidence-main-street-businesses-need-workers.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite record-high confidence on Main Street, a labor shortage issue is increasingly weighing on small businesses around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's that selling steaks off truck? It's AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory/selling-steaks-off-truck-amazon-55883585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donna Brunswick drove to a Costco last month to pick up 2 pounds of raw flank steak — not at the wholesale club, but from a truck in the parking lot. "Typically you wouldn't buy meat off a random truck," says Brunswick, a technical manager in Atlanta. But she says $20 for the slab of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots can outsmart humans to make SLAVES, expert warns...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/709583/AI-robots-outsmart-humans-make-slaves-expert-warns-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Could Be Heading for Fifth Term -- Or to Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/2018/06/14/israel-s-netanyahu-could-be-heading-for-a-fifth-term-or-to-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benjamin Netanyahu Could Be Heading for a Fifth Term. Or to Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungarian PM: Population Replacement Underway in Europe; Speculators Profit from Ruination...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/london/2018/06/14/hungarian-pm-population-replacement-underway-europe-speculators-soros-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Viktor Orbán has warned another "high tide" of immigration is approaching, and that speculators like George Soros hope to profit from "Europe's ruination".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Psychic' cat predicts winner of opening game...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/14/russias-psychic-cat-achilles-predicts-winner-opening-world-cup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian cat reputed to have psychic powers has predicted the result of the first game of the World Cup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KICK OFF!</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/soccer/world-cup/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the latest FIFA World Cup 2018 football results, fixtures and video highlights from Yahoo Sports including live scores, match stats and team news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report Expected To Condemn FBI Violations In Clinton Email Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2018/06/14/612387464/report-expected-to-condemn-fbi-violations-in-2016-clinton-email-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Justice Department's inspector general is expected to conclude that James Comey ignored official guidelines in investigating Hillary Clinton's private email server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uproar over Australian army vehicle flying swastika flag...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/uproar-over-australian-army-vehicle-flying-swastika-flag-031149513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Australian army vehicle flew a Nazi swastika flag during an operation in Afghanistan, the prime minister confirmed Thursday in an act he called "completely and utterly unacceptable". Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull said displaying a Nazi flag was "absolutely wrong". "The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Forced' sterilization of Brazilian woman sparks uproar...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/forced-sterilization-brazilian-woman-sparks-uproar-051426364.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claims that a drug-addicted Brazilian woman was subjected to forced sterilization are sparking accusations of a nightmarish "dystopia" in a country where a leading presidential candidate has stirred controversy with his own birth control proposals. The facts of the case not under dispute are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IVANKA OPENED DOOR TO KOREAN DIPLOMACY --  LAST WINTER!</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5511525/South-Koreas-foreign-minister-met-IVANKA-Washington.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump sat down Thursday with South Korea's foreign minister for a meeting whose purpose remains a mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline says vortex sent plane into terrifying nosedive...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/13/airline-says-vortex-sent-plane-into-terrifying-nosedive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers have described the terrifying moment a vortex sent their Qantas flight into a 10-second “nosedive.” Hundreds of horrified travelers held hands ­believing they were about to die as the ai…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web giants 'are fuelling child mental health crisis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/13/nhs-picking-pieces-mental-illness-epidemic-caused-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NHS is &amp;ldquo;picking up the pieces&amp;rdquo; of an epidemic of mental illness among children, fuelled by social media, the head of the service has warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web giants 'are fuelling child mental health crisis'...</title>
      <link>http://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/aa45affc-6f5a-11e8-bea3-bf1a5a054f3a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NHS is being forced to pick up the pieces of a childhood mental health epidemic driven by social media, its chief executive warned yesterday. Companies such as Google and Facebook should face...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Mediterranean Diet Study Was Flawed. But Was It Wrong? </title>
      <link>http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2018/06/following-charges-flawed-statistics-major-medical-journal-sets-record-straight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencemag.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An anesthesiologist’s review prompts The New England Journal of Medicine to issue five corrections and one retraction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young people developing new accent as Latino population grows in rural Kansas...</title>
      <link>http://www.kansas.com/news/local/article213100119.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kansas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at K-State find that people in Liberal and other southwest Kansas communities are developing an accent with subtle Spanish characteristics. The accent is most prominent in youths and young people, as the Latino population grows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> No COKE, No PEPSI: Bottlers leave city hit by crime...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/no-coke-no-pepsi-bottlers-leave-mexican-city-210937975.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexicans are among the biggest soda drinkers in the world, so residents of the southern city of Ciudad Altamirano were hit hard when first Coca-Cola then Pepsi closed their distribution centers amid drug gang extortion demands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 100 nukes needed to cause catastrophe around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/100-warheads-enough-cause-starvation-180719460.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nations with huge nuclear arsenals are wasting their money because just 100 missiles would be enough to destabilise the globe and kill their own citizens, scientists have said. Britain currently possesses approximately 215 warheads of around 15,000 worldwide, the vast majority of which are American or</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imam Orders Hit... </title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/06/update-tommy-robinson-receiving-death-threats-in-new-uk-prison-imam-places-hit-on-tommy-robinson-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who gets Yosemite? Where top landmarks would fall in 3 Californias plan...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/06/13/three-victors-and-a-lot-of-spoils/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Californians prepare to vote on whether to divide their state into three, we look at who gets what in the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern life so stressful need more sleep?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/13/modern-life-is-so-stressful-that-humans-need-even-more-sleep/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’d be hard-pressed to find anyone who says they get enough sleep. But what is “enough?” Is it eight hours? Seven hours? Enough that you don’t need a straight IV of espresso just to get out…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People of faith live four years longer than atheists...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-5840523/Religious-people-live-four-years-longer-atheists-study-finds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ohio State University study was based on 1,000 obituaries published across the US in 2011. While the data set is small, the psychology research team insisted there is merit to the correlation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay, high heel wearing veteran elected mayor in Texas...</title>
      <link>http://www.connectingvets.com/articles/gay-high-heel-wearing-veteran-elected-mayor-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.connectingvets.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Big Gay Dance Party' to greet Pence in Ohio...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/politics/2018/06/13/mike-pence-met-dancing-drag-queens-ohio/698031002/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dance party is planned outside the Vice President's speaking engagement Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes on OPEC...</title>
      <link>https://www.afp.com/en/news/23/all-eyes-opec-trump-gripes-over-prices-doc-15w7pi1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.afp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young more religious than old  -- in only two countries in world...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/jun/13/young-more-religious-than-old-in-only-two-countries-in-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis of 106 nations finds Ghana and Georgia are only places where under-40s are more religious than older compatriots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million move from Venezuela to Colombia --  in just two years!</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article213081609.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 1 million people from Venezuela are thought to have poured into neighboring Colombia in the last two years, amid a grinding economic, social and political crisis that has rattled the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS MOVES TO BAN CHILD SEX ROBOTS</title>
      <link>http://www.fresnobee.com/news/politics-government/article213126084.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislators move to ban anatomically correct child sex dolls and robots. No U.S. laws currently ban their importation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS CORP CEO: Tech Platforms Must 'Protect Professional Journalism'...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/tech/2018/06/13/news-corp-tech-must-protect-professional-journalism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaking at an event on social media and its impact on the news industry, News Corp CEO Robert Thomson called for social media platforms to "protect professional journalism" and be subject to an "algorithm review board" made up of "experts."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary election lesson for Republicans: Don't cross the president...</title>
      <link>http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/us-politics/ct-republicans-trump-primary-elections-20180613-story.html#nt=oft13a-3gp1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don't cross President Donald Trump. That's the lesson many Republicans are drawing from Rep. Mark Sanford's surprise primary defeat in South Carolina.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDONISTAN:  Tommy Robinson Fears For Life After Moved to Heavily Muslim-Populated Prison...</title>
      <link> https://www.infowars.com/tommy-robinson-fears-for-his-life-after-being-moved-to-heavily-muslim-populated-prison/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CABLE GIANT BIDS $65 BILLION CASH...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/13/comcast-bids-65-billion-for-21st-century-fox-assets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a widely-anticipated move, Comcast makes a new bid for the businesses Fox is currently in an agreement to sell to Walt Disney Co.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles DA reviewing case against Stallone...</title>
      <link>http://abc7.com/entertainment/los-angeles-da-reviewing-sexual-assault-case-against-sylvester-stallone/3599331/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles County District Attorney's Office is reviewing a sexual assault case against actor Sylvester Stallone, a DA's office spokesperson said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic bishops rebuke US immigration policy, suggest 'penalties'...</title>
      <link>https://religionnews.com/2018/06/13/catholic-bishops-rebuke-trumps-asylum-changes-suggest-policy-is-a-life-issue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;religionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (RNS) — The president of the U.S. Conference of Catholic Bishops delivered a rebuke of the Trump administration's recent immigration polices at the group's spring conference as individual bishops urged protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sessions slams Comey on eve of damning IG report...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/administration/392189-sessions-defends-firing-comey-warns-doj-report-could-prompt-more-terminations?rnd=1528937163</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the eve of the release of a potentially explosive new report, Attorney General Jeff Sessions defended the termination of the FBI’s top two former executives and warned that the forthcoming report on the FBI's handling of the Hillary C</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First human case of plague in Idaho since 1992 confirmed...</title>
      <link>http://www.idahostatesman.com/latest-news/article213042289.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.idahostatesman.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The infection is normally found in wildlife in both Oregon and Idaho, but a child in Elmore County contracted it, the first human case in 26 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO HOST WORLD CUP 2026!</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/u-s-canada-mexico-win-right-host-2026-world-cup-105218462.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2026 World Cup is coming to North America. FIFA&amp;apos;s members gathered in Moscow and voted to award hosting rights to the U.S., Canada and Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Deer kills dog during backyard bathroom break...</title>
      <link>https://www.twincities.com/2018/06/12/dog-attacked-deer-killed-doe-shoreview-mn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.twincities.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A routine morning bathroom break for Pepper, a 9-pound miniature poodle, quickly turned tragic after an encounter with an aggressive doe in Shoreview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller 'Accidentally' Exposes Names in Manafort Case...</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/mueller-appears-to-have-screwed-up-by-accidentally-exposing-names-in-manafort-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After decades of CGI-glut, filmmakers rekindle interest in effects they can touch...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-jurassic-world-old-school-effects-make-a-comeback-1528896399</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to filmmakers with a rekindled interest in making creatures they can touch, “Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom” breaks with some of its CGI-heavy predecessors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Men Opt For Plastic Surgery: Breast reductions to botox...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2018/06/13/men-attracted-plastic-surgery-torso-tucks-hair-transplants/695422002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Still an area dominated by women, men are getting in on plastic surgery as well to look younger or make a bigger impression</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK: Man serves amputated leg tacos to guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/gykmn7/legal-ethical-cannibalism-human-meat-tacos-reddit-wtf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“One friend had to spit me into a napkin.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela eyes first-ever use of foreign oil for contracts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-pdvsa-refineries/exclusive-venezuela-eyes-first-ever-use-of-foreign-oil-for-contracts-documents-idUSKBN1J92SQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela is considering refining foreign crude for the first time to produce fuels like gasoline or diesel, according to internal planning documents seen by Reuters on Wednesday, in the latest sign of the country's strain to meet obligations to customers despite having the world's largest crude reserves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camel Milk -- the new rage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/voraciously/wp/2018/06/13/move-aside-pea-milk-camel-milk-is-the-new-rage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The soon-to-be-trendy milk is full of nutrients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US University Seeks More Chinese Students, Claims Won't Curb In-State Access...</title>
      <link>http://www.newhampshire.com/education/unh-wants-more-chinese-students-assures-public-it-wont-reduce-in-state-access-20180611</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newhampshire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DURHAM – The University of New Hampshire has a new program designed to attract Chinese high school graduates who are exploring college options in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Einstein travel diaries reveal 'shocking' xenophobia...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2018/jun/12/einsteins-travel-diaries-reveal-shocking-xenophobia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private journals kept by the scientist and humanitarian icon show prejudiced attitudes towards the people he met while travelling in Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE to undercut law-enforcement tool for cracking iPhones...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-cracking/apple-to-undercut-popular-law-enforcement-tool-for-cracking-iphones-idUSKBN1J92ZY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc said on Wednesday it will change its iPhone settings to undercut the most popular means for law enforcement to break into the devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Speak truth to power': WHOLE FOODS CEO talks clashes with AMAZON in leaked audio...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/features/whole-foods-ceo-describes-clashes-with-amazon-in-leaked-audio-recording</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Mackey is heard saying he is “not afraid to get fired” by the retail giant either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tops DISNEY Offer...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/06/comcast-launches-competing-bid-fox-tops-disneys-offer-1202409389/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comcast today submitted a competing bid for 21st Century Fox, initiating what could well result in a high-stakes bidding war with its biggest media rival, The Walt Disney Co. The U.S. cable giant m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man indicted for threatening to kill Bernie, Kamala...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/13/sanders-harris-nicholas-bukoski-indicted-643894</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The defendant also threatened to harm participants at a gun control rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKER RENEWS AT CNN THROUGH 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/06/jeff-zucker-renews-at-cnn-through-the-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump’s old boss, and favorite media adversary, is back for a rematch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepening woes for newspapers...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/more-grim-news-us-newspapers-survey-193835686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The troubled picture for US newspapers became even grimmer in 2017 with declines in revenue and both print and digital readership, a new research report showed Wednesday. The Pew Research Center found total US daily newspaper circulation, print and digital combined, was 31 million for weekday and 34</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>113 Politicians Killed Ahead Of Election. Still 2 Weeks To Go...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/karlazabludovsky/113-politicians-killed-this-election-season-in-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A politician killed on a public bus. A candidate murdered while taking a selfie. This campaign season may be the deadliest ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Gets Head Stuck In Truck Exhaust, Given Citation...</title>
      <link>http://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2018/06/12/head-stuck-in-exhaust-pipe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A young woman found herself in the wrong place at a central Minnesota music festival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY SELLING FAMED ABCNEWS HQ...</title>
      <link>http://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/2018/06/13/disney-selling-abc-news-longtime-headquarters-as-trouble-looms-for-embattled-tv-stars-journalists.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney is selling the New York City buildings, currently the headquarters of ABC News, to a real estate developer who’s expected to demolish them in order to build luxury condominiums. The sale is raising new questions about the future of Disney’s troubled news operation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis Ball-Sized Hail Damages Homes Across Colorado Springs...</title>
      <link>http://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/hail-storm-el-paso-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hail the size of tennis balls caused a lot of damage to communities south of Colorado Springs early Wednesday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  FED RAISES OUTLOOK FOR ECONOMY!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/13/fed-raises-2018-outlook-for-us-economy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Policymakers' median real GDP forecast rose to 2.8 percent, up from 2.7 percent, for this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Trio Haim Fired Agent After Being Paid 10X Less Than Male Artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/music-trio-haim-fires-agent-after-receiving-10-times-less-pay-than-male-artists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sisterly music trio Haim said they fired their booking agent last year after discovering they were paid 10 times less than a male artist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES AMERICA'S BIGGEST ENEMY IS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5840261/Trump-calls-media-countrys-biggest-enemy-right-North-Korea-nuke-summit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Our Country’s biggest enemy is the Fake News so easily promulgated by fools!'' the president tweeted after saying the despot Kim Jong-un 'has great potential for the future.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WOLF BLITZER: 'We Love The American People'...</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/politics/wolf-blitzer-we-are-not-the-enemy-of-the-american-people-we-love-the-american-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTEREST RATES ZOOM...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/13/fed-hikes-rate-by-a-quarter-point.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The market widely expected the Fed's policymaking body to increase its benchmark interest rate by a quarter point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New supersonic missile developed for Israel Air Force...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Israel-News/The-Rampage-Supersonic-missile-developed-to-destroy-high-quality-targets-559785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The missile can be fitted to the Israel Air Force’s F-15, F-16 and F-35 fighter jets and is meant to be dropped outside areas protected by air-defense systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO: FACEBOOK Algorithm To 'Damage' Democracy...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/13/nyt-ceo-doubts-fake-news-algorithms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Will not make democracy healthier but damage it further'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama aide: Meds, hookups common on press plane...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5832517/Obamas-former-stenographer-lifts-lid-party-culture-staffers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former White House stenographer Beck Dorey-Stein tells how traveling with President Obama and his press pool was like 'summer camp on steroids' in her new memoir, From Corner of the Oval.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norwegian Lawmakers Nominate Trump For Nobel...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/13/nominate-trump-nobel-peace-prize/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Taken a huge and important step'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adults in Japan getting younger...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-44465196</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is the first time in 142 years that the age of adulthood has been changed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kudlow Home From Hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/13/larry-kudlow-discharged-from-walter-reed-national-military-medical-center-earlier-on-wednesday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top White House economic advisor Larry Kudlow was discharged from the hospital Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable seafood dealer sold fishy tale...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73646ad2aaac4666a7124806b2e6a5bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTAUK, New York (AP) — Even after winter storms left East Coast harbors thick with ice, some of the country's top chefs and trendy restaurants were offering sushi-grade tuna sup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER Aims to Predict What You Want to Know...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-13/twitter-aims-to-predict-what-you-want-to-know-when-it-happens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter Inc. will personalize news for users and send them notifications of events, trying to attract a bigger, broader audience with one of its most comprehensive product updates in years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversy After Trans High Schoolers Place 1st, 2nd In Girls Track Championships...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/transgender-track-athletes-win-connecticut-state-championship-debate-ensues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of transgender girls dominated the competition at Connecticut's girls track and field championships, causing some to say it's unfair.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Invests $3 Million In NYTIMES... </title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/issues/george-soros-invested-3-million-new-york-times-stock-holdings-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal billionaire George Soros purchased $3 million worth of stock holdings in the publisher of the New York Times, filings show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graft allegations dominate final presidential debate in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/graft-allegations-dominate-final-presidential-debate-mexico-080915839.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico's presidential candidates traded accusations of corruption Tuesday in a hard-fought final debate ahead of the July 1 election. The three trailing candidates took turns attacking the leftist front-runner, Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador, and also lashed out at each other. "Andres Manuel,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DECLARES AMERICA'S BIGGEST ENEMY IS 'FAKE NEWS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/michael-w-chapman/trump-our-countrys-biggest-enemy-fake-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD: Serial Phone Bandit On Bike Snatches Devices Right From Pedestrians' Hands...</title>
      <link>http://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/06/13/nypd-search-on-for-bandit-on-bicycle-snatching-cell-phones/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police believe the suspect first started the string of robberies on May 28.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is COMCASTFOX a done deal?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c0d533d459b94e29aed34b66ca4e7796/After-AT&amp;T-Time-Warner-win,-is-Comcast-Fox-a-done-deal?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Comcast will likely bid for Fox's entertainment business as early as Wednesday now that a federal judge has cleared AT&amp;T's $85 billion takeover of Time Warner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares NKorea nuke threat over...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/31b82018ce384e1b99b300e3fbc40cad/Trump-declares-via-Twitter-the-NKorea-nuclear-threat-is-over</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump declared on Wednesday that there was "no longer a Nuclear Threat from North Korea," a dubious claim following his summit with leader Kim J</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raccoon reaches roof after scaling Minnesota skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://www.kare11.com/article/news/climbing-mpr-raccoon-has-been-trapped/89-563763824</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kare11.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Public Radio news reporter Tim Nelson tweeted the news shortly after 7 a.m. saying building management had successfully captured the little raccoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Steps Up Hollywood Talent War With NETFLIX...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/new-amazon-chief-steps-up-talent-war-netflix-courts-a-list-creators-1119671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jennifer Salke's plan for the streamer includes "hands-on" development, 'Lord of the Rings' by 2021 and a strategy to use her deep relationships to build an "alternative to Netflix's volume."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Burton reveals live-action 'DUMBO' remake trailer...</title>
      <link>http://ew.com/movies/2018/06/13/dumbo-trailer-tim-burton/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The beloved big-eared baby elephant takes center stage in a film for a new generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  OBAMA FAILED TO BRING BACK GAMES...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/football/2009/apr/14/barack-obama-world-cup</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Barack Obama has written to Fifa president Sepp Blatter to signal his support for the USA's bid to host either the 2018 or 2022 World Cup</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN FLIPS?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-cooperate-attorneys-leave-case/story?id=55861988</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As attorneys for Michael Cohen rush to meet Judge Kimba Wood’s Friday deadline to complete a privilege review of over 3.7 million documents seized in the April 9 raids of Cohen’s New York properties and law office, a source representing this matter has disclosed to ABC News that the law firm...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anticipation surrounds Fed's rate forecasts after next hike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f953b4d3cae04ccfb189e06a6da612b9/Anticipation-surrounds-Fed's-rate-forecasts-after-next-hike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Federal Reserve is set Wednesday to modestly raise its key short-term interest rate for the second time this year. But attention will be focused mainly on an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: 50 worst cities to reside in...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/economy/2018/06/13/50-worst-cities-to-live-in/35909271/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;24/7 Wall St. created an index with measures in eight categories -- crime, economy, education, environment, health, housing, infrastructure, and leisure -- to identify the 50 worst cities to live in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who shot cockfight ref? Secret arena outside Miami was packed but nobody's talking...</title>
      <link>http://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article212673589.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami-Dade police detectives are searching for the killers of Jose Garcia, a referee for cockfighting, an illegal sport that continues to draw crowds of gamblers to secret events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE Stars Get Rich Making Bomb Threats and Streaming It...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/youtube-stars-get-rich-making-bomb-threats-and-streaming-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For just a few bucks, anyone can pay people like ‘Arab Andy’ to broadcast anything in public—and he makes hundred of dollars a day doing it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'UFO' sighting on American west coast rogue missile?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/weird/973702/UFO-sighting-alien-news-missile-launch-whidbey-island</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A STRANGE missile-shaped object blasted over the skies of western US, but military officials say that it was not a weapon, prompting confusion over what the UFO actually was.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising rates, deficit spell big trouble for USA, warns bond king...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-us-is-on-a-suicide-mission-warns-bond-king-gundlach-2018-06-13</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s Fed day and the central bank will need to fill the excitement gaps lacking after the North Korea summit. Our call of the day from Jeffrey Gundlach has a dreary forecast for the the U.S. fiscal situation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria to Stage Border Defense War Games After Migrant Surge Warning...</title>
      <link>http://www.breitbart.com/london/2018/06/13/austria-wargames-mass-migration-surge-border-closure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian troops will carry out war games preparing the nation’s border defence against a migration influx later this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department weighs appeal in AT&amp;T case...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/att-time-warner-what-happens-next-152884826-4be36e74-1b09-4301-b704-bc13c127bb61.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government has six days to decide whether to appeal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguay marijuana legalization leads to pot shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/uruguay-marijuana-legalization-pot-shortage-demand-outpaces-farmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contrary to U.S., experts say Uruguay's licensed growers only have capacity to produce about a third of the marijuana consumed in the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thefts rise after California reduces criminal penalties...</title>
      <link>http://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/article213078369.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California researchers are linking a voter-backed reduction in criminal penalties for drug and property crimes to a jump in car burglaries, shoplifting and other theft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocks Under I-95 Present Odd, and Scary, Threat to Power Grid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/2018/06/13/rocks-under-i-95-present-odd-and-scary-threat-to-power-grid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rocks Under I-95 Present Odd, and Scary, Threat to Power Grid</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
