<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAKE UP TO POLITICS</title>
      <link>https://www.wakeuptopolitics.com/archives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wakeuptopolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Michael 'squatter' ex-boyfriend arrested for smashing up star's mansion!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/9572544/fadi-fawaz-arrest-george-michael-london-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GEORGE Michael’s ex Fadi Fawaz was dramatically arrested after going berserk and allegedly smashing up the late singer’s £5million house. Cops swooped on the London property last night after …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing takes aim at USA, Taiwan in new military blueprint...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/China-takes-aim-at-U-S-Taiwan-in-new-military-14118706.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - China sharpened its hostility toward the United States and Taiwan in a new high-level report on its future military strategy that accused Washington and its allies of undermining global stability.  Releasing the document on Wednesday, officials of the People's Liberation Army repeatedly warned that Beijing would be willing to deploy military force to assert its claims over Taiwan. The self-ruled island has pulled closer to the Trump administration and agreed this month to buy $2.2 billion in weapons, including M1A2T Abrams tanks and Stinger missiles.  Taiwan's incumbent Democratic Progressive Party favors declaring formal independence from China, a move that could spark confrontation in the Taiwan Strait, one of the world's most heavily militarized flash points. China's navy this month sailed its sole aircraft carrier into the strait in a show of force reminiscent of similar U.S. operations two decades ago that showcased American military dominance in Asia.  "If anyone dares to separate Taiwan from China, the Chinese military would not hesitate to go to war," Chinese military spokesman Wu Qian said as he laid out what officials called a revised national defense policy for "the New Era" - a catchphrase that denotes the imprimatur of China's assertive leader, Xi Jinping.  The military blueprint comes as tensions simmer in the western Pacific and China moves to enforce its strategic aims across the region, including in the disputed South China Sea. Beijing views democratically ruled Taiwan, which separated from the Communist-ruled mainland in 1949, as a renegade province.  Global military competition was rising, with the United States "strengthening its Asia-Pacific military alliances" and engaging in "technological and institutional innovation in pursuit of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: NFL star Adrian Peterson deep in debt despite earning $99 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jul/24/adrian-peterson-nfl-debt-washington</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Financial problems continue to mount for Washington running back Adrian Peterson, who is being sued for failure to repay a $5.2m loan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confused, Stuttering...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/07/robert-mueller-stuttering-confused-doddering-lost-nervous-he-did-not-run-this-thing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GATEWAY PUNDIT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions Between Sanders, MSNBC Boil Over...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-war-between-bernie-sanders-and-msnbc-reaches-a-new-peak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vermont senator’s campaign sees the cable news network as part of a brewing problem that allows vague and unverified claims to go unchecked on air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETER BAKER</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/peter-baker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Baker is the chief White House correspondent for The New York Times, responsible for covering President Trump, the fourth president he has covered. He covered President Obama for The Times and Bill Clinton and George W. Bush for The Washington Post. Mr. Baker joined The Times in 2008 after 20 years at The Post and has written about Mr. Trump since the inception of his administration, through the turmoil inside his White House and the many battles with adversaries outside it. He has written about controversies over a travel ban, the investigation into Russia’s election interference, the firing of the F.B.I. director, legislative struggles over health care and tax cuts and decisions of war and peace in Afghanistan, Syria and North Korea. During his first tour at the White House, Mr. Baker co-authored the Post’s original story breaking the Monica Lewinsky scandal and served as the paper’s lead writer on the impeachment and trial of Mr. Clinton. During his next White House assignment, he covered the travails of Mr. Bush’s second term, from the Iraq war and Hurricane Katrina to Supreme Court nomination fights and the economic crisis. During Mr. Obama’s presidency, he covered the raid that killed Osama bin Laden, the reelection campaign and debates over health care, economics, terrorism and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. In between stints at the White House, Mr. Baker and his wife, Susan Glasser, spent four years as Moscow bureau chiefs for The Post, chronicling the rise of Vladimir Putin, the rollback of Russian democracy, the second Chechen war and the terrorist attacks on a theater in Moscow and a school in Beslan. Mr. Baker also covered the early months of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He was the first American newspaper journalist to report from rebel-held northern Afghanistan after Sept. 11, 2001, and he spent the next eight months covering the overthrow of the Taliban and the emergence of a new government. He later spent six months in the Middle East, reporting from inside Saddam Hussein's Iraq and around the region before embedding with the United States Marines as they drove toward Baghdad. At The Times, he served briefly as Jerusalem bureau chief. Mr. Baker is the author of five books, most recently</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGGIE HABERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/by/maggie-haberman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maggie Haberman is a White House correspondent who joined The Times in 2015 and was part of a team that won a Pulitzer Prize in 2018 for reporting on Donald Trump’s advisers and their connections to Russia. Before joining The Times as a campaign correspondent, Ms. Haberman worked as a political reporter at Politico, from 2010 to 2015. She previously worked at other publications, including The New York Post and The New York Daily News. She was a finalist for the Mirror Awards, with Glenn Thrush, for the 2014 profile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Prepping Troops for Laser, Electromagnetic Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2019/07/air-force-wants-simulated-wargames-plan-lasers-electro-magnetic-weapons/158589/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wargames are meant to teach airmen about these new weapons and help the Air Force develop new tactics and procedures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live-tracking deflections...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/robert-mueller-house-testimony-tracker-july-2019-n1033166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Follow along as the former special counsel delivers his testimony in front of House committees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlogger dies live-streaming himself eating poisonous centipedes and lizards...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/man-35-dies-live-streaming-18763663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese vlogger, named only by his surname Sun, was reportedly found lifeless in his flat after the bizarre stunt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He's Chinese billionaire and member of Mar-a-Lago. Also communist spy?</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article232973237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. willing to offer Maduro deal if he leaves...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article232964207.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX long, cruel summer; Hate-watching...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/tv/story/2019-07-23/netflix-earnings-report-emmy-nominations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As industry delight over recent losses proves, Netflix has gone from the new kid on the block to the company everyone loves to hate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarantino 'HOLLYWOOD' big summer gamble. Will it pay off?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/business/story/2019-07-23/quentin-tarantinos-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-is-sonys-big-summer-gamble-will-it-pay-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sony Pictures fought hard to land Quentin Tarantino's first film after Weinstein. Will the $90-million bet on originality and star power pay off?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JP MORGAN Warns: Dollar Could Lose Status As World's Dominant Currency...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/jp-morgan-warns-dollar-could-lose-status-as-worlds-dominant-currency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America's largest bank sounds alarm in face of skyrocketing debt, rise of China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror site told readers to 'hunt' gays. Then activist stabbed to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-horror-movie-themed-website-told-readers-to-14118182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The frightening Russian website promoted it as a "game" - identify gay people, upload their photos and information to a database and then proceed to hunt them down and torture them, like the gruesome "Saw" movies that inspired the site's name.  The page was blocked in Russia last week, but not before the names of prominent journalists and activists began appearing there. Yelena Grigorieva was among them. The 41-year-old was a fierce advocate for LGBTQ rights, and on Saturday she was found dead near her home in St. Petersburg with eight stab wounds and signs she'd been strangled.  One suspect has been arrested, local media reported.  The grisly attack is the latest in a spate of violence and threats against the gay community in Russia, where in 2013 the government outlawed so-called "gay propaganda" - a ban that a European court later said "reinforced stigma and prejudice and encouraged homophobia."  "This tragedy is yet another painful episode in the ongoing plague of anti-LGBTQ violence and atrocities that have been taking place in Russia and the region," Jay Gilliam, global director of the Human Rights Campaign, told The Washington Post.  Grigorieva's killing prompted protests in Russia's second largest city on Tuesday and demonstrators there connected her death to her activism.  "Yelena was killed because she was not afraid to tell the truth about the subjects that are traditionally silent in Russia and on the country's state TV channels," attendee Marina Ken told the Associated Press.  Grigorieva, who was also active in a number of other causes, regularly received death threats and reported them to the police, who her friends say didn't take them seriously, the Moscow Times reported. Officials at the Human Rights Campaign, which is the largest LGBTQ rights organization...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth rotation slowing?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1157223/Nasa-earthquake-what-is-earthquakes-how-fast-does-the-earth-spin-earthquake-map-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EARTH’S rotation is slowing down as the Moon moves farther away from the planet – and scientists believe it could cause major earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY WIRE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailywire.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailywire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Led by the incomparable Ben Shapiro, The Daily Wire is a hard-hitting, irreverent news and commentary site for a new generation of conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eat last meal at 2pm to lose weight?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-7280855/Eating-meal-2pm-help-lose-weight-suppresses-appetite.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study at the University of Alabama Birmingham tested Early Time-Restricted Feeding (eTRF), which is a type of fasting where dinner is eaten in the afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read opening statement...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/07/24/robert-mueller-testimony-opening-statement-on-trump-russia-probe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller is expected to testify on Capitol Hill for hours about his investigation into Russian interference, possible coordination by members of President Donald Trump's campaign, and possible obstruction of justice by Trump himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vowed millions of immigration arrests in dramatic raids. ICE caught 18 family members....</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/President-Trump-vowed-millions-of-immigration-14117006.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When President Donald Trump vowed to deport "millions" of immigrants from the United States, he was telegraphing an Immigration and Customs Enforcement operation that targeted migrants with final deportation orders. The real list had about 2,100 families on it, with the goal of deterring Central American migrants from trying to cross the southern border.  The final tally from the operation, according to federal officials: 18 family members were arrested, not enough to fit into a school bus. Immigration officials arrested another 17 undocumented immigrants they encountered in their searches, what are known as collateral arrests.  ICE announced the data Tuesday morning, tucking it into a news conference that included information about worksite enforcement and routine criminal arrests. Aside from the 35 immigrants apprehended in the much-anticipated family operation, immigration agents separately picked up nearly 900 adults - most of them convicted criminals - and delivered more than 3,000 notices to companies nationwide that authorities will audit their records to ensure that workers are in the United States legally.  Acting ICE Director Matthew Albence called the criminal operation successful and said the family operation, Operation Border Resolve, will continue, though the number of arrests were lower than in the past. The first such operation over New Year's weekend in 2016 under the Obama administration led to the arrests of 121 adults and children in Georgia, Texas and North Carolina.  Officials would not say where the arrests were made during the recent operation, nor when the operation took place, and immigration arrests are not public record. Families were not separated during the arrests, Albence said.  Albence said public blowback and publicity surrounding the raids likely dampened their numbers, but he said the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES: MSNBC, CNN Ratings Collapse Double Digits...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/07/24/nolte-fox-news-audience-grows-msnbc-cnn-collapse-double-digits/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Fox News grew its audience last week, CNN and MSNBC saw their audience flee by double digits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNISM: Cuba Running Out of Medicine...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/health/2019/07/24/cuba-the-healthcare-darling-of-the-international-left-is-running-out-of-medicine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Healthcare authorities in Cuba blamed a "complex situation" Tuesday for growing shortages of basic medicines that many need to stay alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/author/howie-carr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Howie Carr has written two New York Times bestsellers, is a member of the National Radio Hall of Fame and has won a National Magazine Award. He hosts a syndicated daily four-hour radio show, two hours of which are simulcast on Newsmax TV. His website is howiecarrshow.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING Burns $1 Billion in Cash as Max Grounding Costs Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/boeing-burns-1-billion-in-cash-as-737-max-grounding-costs-mount-1.1291631</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Robot Photographer...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-07-22/robot-photographer-snaps-products-at-a-warehouse-in-brooklyn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JONATHAN SWAN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/authors/jonathanswan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASIA TIMES</title>
      <link>https://www.asiatimes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.asiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian news hub covering geo-political news and current affairs across Asia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico sets murder record...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c197a3ee34834ea69f745975fa632ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC Slap on Wrist for Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/47f5f7fd9e0941a880b929af081a37a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATEST...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1b98bfdbea19426faf1be2006ac9334f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paleo tied to heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/health-med-fit-science/paleo-caveman-diet-linked-heart-disease-biomarker-study-finds/nhpqZohLPYSntwe4CdB55H/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Paleolithic diet, also known as the caveman regimen, is touted for improving gut health. But those who follow the Paleo diet may have twice the amount of a key blood biomarker closely associated with heart disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can be indicted after office...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/854609/mueller-confirms-that-president-indicted-after-leaving-office</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Special Counsel Robert Mueller is maintaining that his investigation team did not have the authority to indict a sitting president, citing an opinion from the Office of Legal Counsel. But he did leave the door open for the future. During Mueller's testimony before the House Judiciary Committee on Wednesday, committee chair Rep. Jerrold Nadler (D-N.Y.) asked Mueller if it was true that even if he had concluded President Trump had obstructed his office's investigation into 2016 Russian election interference, the special counsel could not have publicly stated so because of the OLC opinion. Mueller confirmed. But he also confirmed that a president could be prosecuted for an alleged crime after leaving office. Chairman Nadler: "Under Department of Justice policy, the president could be prosecuted for obstruction of justice crimes after he leaves office, correct?"Mueller: "True." pic.twitter.com/kdBHUYEZJ3 â€” NBC News (@NBCNews) July 24, 2019 Of course, Mueller was likely not hinting at anything other than establishing his interpretation of the legal opinion. It does mean, however, that no matter how this situation resolves in the present moment, it could crop up again in the future. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/454471-media-frenzy-for-mueller-testimony-as-broadcast-cable-networks-go-wall-to-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media coverage has reached a fever pitch for former special counsel Robert Mueller's testimony before Congress on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP STRATEGIST:  2020 WILL BE THISCLOSE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/454323-top-strategist-projects-narrow-electoral-college-victory-for-democrats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top Democratic strategist on Tuesday projected his party would win a narrow Electoral College victory over President Trump if the election were held today, but cautioned that the contest could go either way depending on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAACP calls for president impeachment...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/454333-naacp-calls-for-trump-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of the NAACP are calling for President Trump's impeachment, the latest effort to push members of Congress to pursue impeachment against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NADER: Trump will 'defeat himself' if goaded...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/454421-ralph-nader-trump-will-defeat-himself-in-2020-if-hes-goaded</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s been dubbed an election “spoiler” by countless critics, but Ralph Nader says there’s one person likely to spoil President Trump’s 2020 reelection hopes: Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straight Pride Parade In California?</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/07/22/city-of-modesto-straight-pride-parade/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Modesto is considering awarding a permit for a straight pride march in a local park and residents have mixed reviews on the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NICK GILLESPIE</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/search?f[author][]=nick-gillespie&amp;q=*&amp;s=-pubdate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside reports of deaths, sickness that have consumed Dominican Republic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/07/24/inside-the-reports-of-deaths-sickness-that-have-consumed-dominican-republic/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s fear surrounding the Dominican Republic these days. In just the past few months, the beach oasis has been battered by a steady stream of disturbing reports about tourist deaths, sudde…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela blames 'electromagnetic attack' for blackout...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venezuelas-lights-coming-back-life-121544879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela's opposition on Tuesday sought to harness anger over a massive blackout that deepened hardship nationwide, but turnout at a Caracas demonstration was relatively modest as many Venezuelans despair of an imminent solution to their plight. Lights came back on in parts of the capital and other</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: NIKE sneakers sell for record $437,500...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/over-moon-nike-sneakers-sell-record-437-500-225653835.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new world record for a pair of sneakers was set at auction on Tuesday when an avid collector splashed out $437,500 on Nike's 1972 "Moon Shoe," Sotheby's said. The sale smashed the previous record of $190,373 spent in 2017 on a pair of signed Converse worn by Michael Jordan in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAZED AND CONFUSED</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-confused-looking-mueller-repeatedly-asks-questions-be-repeat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Can you repeat the question, sir?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Explanation From NASA Over Large, Low-Flying Jetliner Buzzing Over LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/07/23/altadena-nasa-plane-flying-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The large DC-8, painted white with a blue stripe and the NASA logo on the tail, was spotted flying over Altadena at the height of afternoon rush hour in the San Gabriel Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA LOOMER</title>
      <link>https://lauraloomer.us/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lauraloomer.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Laura Loomer Official</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'COULD YOU REPEAT QUESTION?'</title>
      <link>https://grabien.com/story.php?id=244735</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Can you repeat the question, sir?’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE seeks tariff exemption after moving Mac production to China...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-seeks-mac-pro-parts-170038851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sign up for Next China, a weekly email on where the nation stands now and where it's going next.Apple Inc. has asked the Trump administration to exclude components that make up the forthcoming Mac Pro high-end desktop computer from import tariffs, weeks after planning to re-locate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>