<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Barron Hilton dead at 91...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/09/20/barron-hilton-who-expanded-hilton-hotels-empire-dies-91/2388047001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotelier and philanthropist Barron Hilton died on Thursday of natural causes at his home in Los Angeles. He was 91.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, dozens injured in Utah tour bus crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/09/20/tour-bus-crashes-near</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Driedonks’ voice broke as he described what he saw Friday along State Road 12, after a tour bus carrying Chinese-speaking tourists crashed next to his business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car plows into mall near Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/09/20/police-on-the-scene-after-reports-of-car-driving-through-woodfield-mall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCHAUMBURG, Ill. — A driver was taken into custody after a car drove through Woodfield Mall Friday afternoon. Police were on the scene at the Schaumburg mall around 2:30 p.m. after witnesses said a black SUV drove through Sears, striking kiosks. The incident took place on the lower level of the mall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver 'Dazed And Confused'; No Injuries...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/09/20/stores-at-woodfield-mall-placed-on-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An SUV smashed into Woodfield Mall and drove down the main hallway, slamming into a kiosk and stores, sending panicked shoppers scrambling for safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic first? Israel's Arabs could lead parliamentary opposition...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920142751-zacrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ARABS (PIX, GRAPHIC):A historic first? Israel's Arabs could lead parliamentary opposition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Rose Faces New Allegations From Makeup Artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecut.com/2019/09/charlie-rose-hit-with-new-harassment-allegation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His longtime makeup artist says Rose was verbally abusive, and that he used his Bloomberg TV studio as “a sexual hunting ground.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwarf porn star jailed in Vegas, accused of stabbing boyfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/stabbings/dwarf-porn-star-jailed-in-las-vegas-accused-of-stabbing-boyfriend-1852654/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress known as “Bridget the Midget,” was booked Wednesday under her legal name, Cheryl Marie Murphy, in connection with a domestic disturbance early that morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Calls For New Laws So Sitting Presidents Can Be Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/09/20/762594886/pelosi-says-congress-should-pass-new-laws-so-sitting-presidents-can-be-indicted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I do think that we will have to pass some laws that will have clarity for future presidents. [A] president should be indicted, if he's committed a wrongdoing," House Speaker Nancy Pelosi told NPR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felons could regain voting rights in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/nonviolent-felons-could-regain-voting-rights-georgia/xZOpRkDHfml2GhtHjigvUK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia senators on Friday began considering whether to restore the voting rights of many of th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Trump must give deposition in protesters' lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cf76347381d4470bcb9eed36947654b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge has ordered President Donald Trump to give a videotaped deposition in a lawsuit filed by protesters who claim they were roughed up outside Trump Tower. State...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, dozens injured in Uath tour bus crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/09/20/tour-bus-crashes-near/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tour bus carrying Chinese-speaking tourists crashed Friday morning near Bryce Canyon National Park, killing at least four people and critically injuring at least a dozen others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL goaltenders getting concussions at alarming rate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dca05dd0915f43dcb8ef40f24fd99e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stanley Cup-winning experience isn't worth what it used to be. Neither is experience of any kind. As NHL teams move toward paying their stars more money and relying on young players to fill...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley moves back to SC, fuels political speculation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/nation-world/national/article235301277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM lays off thousands as plants lie idle in labor strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/autos/gm-lays-thousands-workers-plants-lie-idle-labor-union-strike-n1056946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite feeling the effects of the U.S. strike, GM workers in Canada are “”very supportive” of the action, said the head of Canada’s autoworkers trade union. “People are furious with General Motors. People feel betrayed.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declines to say whether he discussed Biden in call with Ukrainian president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-declines-to-say-whether-he-discussed-joe-biden-in-call-with-ukrainian-president/ar-AAHAwF0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough device generates electricity from night sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/breakthrough-device-can-generate-electricity-from-the-night-sky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An innovative new device is able to generate electricity from the night sky, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says going into Iran would be 'very easy decision'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-holds-press-conference-with-australian-prime-minister-scott-morrison-today-2019-09-20-live-stream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's remarks came at a news conference after the U.S. announced intensified sanctions on Iran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Corporate America Profits Off Being Green...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-business-turns-profit-environmentalism-100018045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s time to stop crediting corporate sustainability efforts as acts of altruism. For big business, protecting the environment often means padding the bottom line.Nike Inc. has come up with a way to weave more efficiently, reducing the raw material and labor time needed to make each shoe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau pivots from blackface scandal, pledges assault rifle ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-election/canadas-trudeau-pledges-assault-rifle-ban-pivots-campaign-amid-blackface-scandal-idUSKBN1W51KJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, embroiled in a blackface picture scandal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious magnetic pulses discovered on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/09/mars-insight-feels-mysterious-magnetic-pulsations-at-midnight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nighttime events are among initial results from the InSight lander, which also found hints that the red planet may host a global reservoir of liquid water deep below the surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattress salesman rescues 120 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/news/trending/i-can-t-let-my-people-drown-houston-mattress-salesman/article_060bfa3b-188a-5069-b249-38de35fa1af1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mattress Mack" knew what he had to do now: He opened his showroom as a shelter and sent out the furniture trucks to rescue Imelda's stranded victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DECLARES IT'S A 'PUBLISHER,' CAN CENSOR WHOMEVER IT WANTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/facebook-declares-its-a-publisher-can-censor-whomever-it-wants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giant walking into legal trap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's 'sonic weapon' may have been mosquito gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-49770369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mystery illness that has blighted diplomats in Havana may have been due to fumigation, a study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu clings to power as coalition talks loom...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920112523-rab0m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ (PIX, GRAPHICS):Israel's Netanyahu clings to power as coalition talks loom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE CALL 'PROMISE'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistleblower-complaint-about-president-trump-involves-ukraine-according-to-two-people-familiar-with-the-matter/ar-AAHyi0V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unethical to upgrade iPhone?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/865944/unethical-upgrade-iphone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How our addiction to new and shiny devices is doing more harm than good</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLARD: Manufacturing in recession...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/20/feds-james-bullard-says-us-manufacturing-appears-in-recession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US manufacturing sector “already appears in recession” and overall economic growth is expected to slow “in the near horizon,” St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank president James Bullard said on Frid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth making big comeback in America...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meth-us-big-comeback-145207167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meth producers in Mexico are cranking up the speed of production, and the drug is making a big comeback in the U.S., drug experts warn. And “it’s really out of control.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCKED:  Officials detail shocking case against political donor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4f2f1f7bb4f24663ad2fbd3e5f14f29f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Gemmel Moore had moved back home with his mother in Texas two years ago and was missing Los Angeles when he texted a photo of syringe in an arm to a wealthy gay man he knew in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends himself against whistleblower complaint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/034de586020942c8a6c1367cb8dfd39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Girl left alone in car while mother danced at strip club...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/child-neglect/stripper-busted-for-child-neglect-384692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While her mother worked the pole inside, a three-year-old girl was roaming around the parking lot of a Florida strip club early yesterday morning, police report. Responding to a 911 call about the un</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saga Threatens to Blow Up 2020 Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-whistleblower-saga-threatens-to-blow-up-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two reports on Thursday night say the conversation in the complaint involved Ukraine, the country that the president’s close lawyer has turned to in looking for dirt on Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Military to present Trump with several options on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4d4ce92397ba44a68bedd60edb2aee36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattress salesman rescues 120 people...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/462301-houston-mattress-salesman-rescues-about-120-people-from-imelda-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Houston furniture salesman reportedly rescued more than 100 people from flooding caused by Tropical Storm Imelda.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican cartel girl assassins bathe in blood of victims, have sex with corpses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9954708/el-chapo-kim-k-female-assassins-mexico-drugs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITH her red hair flowing over her shoulders, pretty Juana looks like any other young woman in her 20s – apart from the fact she’s holding a machine gun. Though she may have an innocent face,…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Journalists to be tested on loyalty to Xi...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/20/chinese-journalists-to-be-tested-on-loyalty-to-xi-jinping</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exam will test journalists on president’s teachings on socialism and propaganda</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery 'craft' explodes over Area 51...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mystery-craft-explodes-over-area-20082582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: A renowned conspiracy theorist said the photos could show a black project spy plane that uses alien technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA emails reveal how agency didn't see large, 'sneaky' near-miss asteroid...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7485763/Internal-NASA-emails-reveal-missed-asteroid-skimmed-Earth.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internal emails have revealed the US space agency was caught by surprise by the asteroid named '2019 OK' which passed Earth on July 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien enthusiasts descend on Nevada desert near secretive base...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7480385/Nevada-desert-towns-prep-possible-Storm-Area-51-influx.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a thousand tourists have already descended upon the tiny towns of Rachel and Hiko - which have a combined population of just 175 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of Unaccompanied Alien Children Entering USA Highest in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/news/article/melanie-arter/hhs-number-unaccompanied-minors-entering-us-reached-highest-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of unaccompanied children (UACs) entering the United States during fiscal year 2019 has grown to levels never seen before, Jonathan Hayes, director of the HHS’s Office of Refugee Resettlement (ORR), told Congress on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLARD: Rate cut too small!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/feds-james-bullard-says-cutting-rates-by-a-bigger-half-percentage-point-would-have-been-more-appropriate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Bullard said he dissented on this week's Fed decision to lower rates by a quarter percentage point because he didn't think the cut was big enough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2,200 'burned out' nurses walk off job in Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/university-of-chicago-nurse-strike-2200-nurses-walk-off-job-today-2019-09-20-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nurses strike after contract talks with the hospital broke down this week amid a dispute over staffing levels and pay raises</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellison: UBER 'worthless'; 'App cat could have written'...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/larry-ellison-says-uber-wework-are-almost-worthless-barrons-2019-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire cofounder or Oracle who is on Tesla's board isn't a fan of WeWork either, he told a group of entrepreneurs at his San Francisco home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of Emergency in 13 Counties...</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/news/news/2019-09-19-tropical-depression-imelda-impacts-southeast-texas-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's how Imelda is impacting parts of Texas and Louisiana along the Gulf coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray shows how vaping left teen lungs caked with hardened oil...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/09/19/shocking-x-ray-shows-how-vaping-left-teens-lungs-caked-with-hardened-oil-10775166/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;19 year-old Anthony Mayo has the lungs of a 60 year-old who has been smoking two packets of cigarettes a day all their adult life, doctors told his father Keith</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN Flight Cancelled Over Concerns About Muslim Passengers...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/09/19/american-airlines-flight-dallas-cancelled-concerns-about-muslim-passengers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A North Texas Muslim said American Airlines cancelled his flight Saturday because the flight crew didn't feel comfortable with him and his Muslim friend on the plane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No crowds as iPhone 11 hits stores in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-iphone-china-idUSKBN1W515K</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's latest iPhone 11 range hit stores in China on Friday, with short qu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deeper danger of deepfakes: Powerless people...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ny-oped-the-real-deepfake-danger-20190920-mnu6w7xbdzgklgfr7ibmq6bcne-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the last year, news coverage of deepfakes — counterfeit videos that make it seem as though people are doing or saying something they actually aren’t doing or saying — has positioned them as dangerous to democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE FED PUMPING IN CASH CRUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2019/09/19/repo-madness-heads-into-day-4-another-75-billion-liquidity-drop-from-ny-fed-coming-friday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fed's life support for the short-term funding market will continue on Friday. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER closes thousands of fake news accounts worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/twitter-closes-thousands-fake-news-accounts-worldwide-000942848.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter said Friday it has closed down thousands of accounts across the world for spreading fake news as well as pro-government propaganda, including in places like the United Arab Emirates, China and Spain. Accounts coming from China seeking to sow discord among protesters in Hong Kong were closed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: NFL teams battle QB crisis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/no-country-old-men-nfl-teams-battle-qb-010322274--nfl.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Roethlisberger is out for the season, Drew Brees faces an extended injury layoff, and Eli Manning has been benched. The opening weeks of the 2018/2019 NFL campaign are making a persuasive argument that the league is no country for old men. After just two rounds, no fewer than five of the league</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Blasts Refs For 'Ridiculous Penalties'...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/19/tom-brady-tweets-ridiculous-penalties-thursday-night-football/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The QB took to his Twitter account -- which is generally reserved for dad jokes and pump-up videos -- to vent about penalties in the Titans-Jaguars game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The wearable chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/shortcuts/2019/sep/19/the-wearable-lex-chair-lets-you-sit-where-you-want-but-will-it-catch-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of aluminium legs that you strap to your bum could be the solution for people who find there are not enough chairs in the world. As long as they don’t mind looking ridiculous</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
American struggles with medical bills foreign concept in other countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/americans-struggles-with-medical-bills-are-a-foreign-concept-in/article_c412fecf-22e5-5edc-9e52-2925b9702a88.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GORINCHEM, Netherlands — In France, a visit to the doctor typically costs the equivalent of $1.12.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sacha Baron Cohen 'womanizer' portrayal of Mossad agent slammed by family...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7483209/Sacha-Baron-Cohens-portrayal-Israels-Mossad-agent-Netflix-drama-blasted-family.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eli Cohen's family have hit out at the new Netflix mini series about the Mossad agent's life undercover behind enemy lines in Syria saying the flamboyant womaniser isn't the man they knew.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio pulls plug on sputtering presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/20/bill-de-blasio-pulls-the-plug-on-his-sputtering-presidential-bid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio finally pulled the plug on his ill-fated presidential bid that failed to draw more than 1 percent support in national polls — but brought plenty of ire from New Yorkers w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schoolchildren hit streets in vast global climate strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/students-demand-change-vast-global-climate-strike-082628597.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vast crowds of children skipped school Friday to join a global strike against climate change, heeding the rallying cry of teen activist Greta Thunberg and demanding adults act to stop environmental disaster. It was expected to be the biggest protest ever against the threat posed to the planet by climate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With lines and blackouts, Cubans suffer fuel crisis...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/queues-blackouts-cubans-suffer-fuel-crisis-060245703.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ernesto Mirabal gave up a night's sleep for a few gallons of gas at a Havana service station, where lining up for five hours has become the norm during a severe fuel shortage on the Communist-run island. Since President Miguel Diaz-Canel's shock announcement on September 11 that the country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogue Oil Trader Causes $320 Million Loss...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/mitsubishi-unit-expects-320-million-071334064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mitsubishi Corp. said a rogue oil trader at its Singapore unit lost $320 million in unauthorized transactions disguised as legitimate hedges for customers.The employee, a Chinese national working at Petro-Diamond Singapore Pte, has been fired and reported to police, Mitsubishi said in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most common antidepressant barely relieves symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/09/19/common-antidepressant-barely-helps-improve-depression-symptoms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most commonly prescribed antidepressant barely relieves symptoms of modern depression, a major study reveals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hand Sanitizer Not Effective Against Flu; Takes 4 Mins Rubbing To Kill...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/flu-season-alert-hand-sanitizer-not-very-effective-against-virus-strain/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to a new study, it took nearly four minutes of exposure to hand sanitizer to completely deactivate the flu virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown Accuser Says Sent Her 'Intimidating' Text Messages...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/2019/09/19/antonio-brown-accuser-text-messages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Antonio Brown accuser says she received “intimidating” text messages from the Patriots receiver, and has asked the NFL to act.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOME DEPOT, LOWE'S ACCUSED OF SCANNING MILLIONS OF FACES...</title>
      <link>https://www.shtfplan.com/headline-news/home-depot-and-lowes-accused-of-scanning-millions-of-customers-faces_09192019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.shtfplan.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper performs with Boris Johnson 'decapitated head'...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/article/mercury-prize-slowthai-boris-johnson-dummy-head-brexit-prime-minister-9112981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret FBI Subpoenas Scoop Up Personal Data From Scores of Companies...</title>
      <link>https://www.enmnews.com/2019/09/20/secret-f-b-i-subpoenas-scoop-up-personal-data-from-scores-of-companies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.enmnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ENM NEWS - The F.B.I. has used secret subpoenas to obtain personal data from far more companies than previously disclosed, newly released documents show.The</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT: State dinner in White House Rose Garden...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7484459/Melania-Trump-uses-Australias-national-colors-set-stage-glamorous-state-dinner.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia's national colors of green and gold set the theme for Friday night's state dinner in the Rose Garden of the White House, picked by first lady Melania Trump to honor the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Admits He Asked Ukraine to Investigate Biden...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/462277-giuliani-says-of-course-he-asked-ukraine-to-look-into-biden-seconds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's personal attorney Rudy Giuliani gave conflicting answers in an interview on CNN on Thursday night as to whether he asked Ukraine to look into former Vice President Joe Biden, saying at one point "of course I did."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unshackled Trump finally gets the presidency he always wanted...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/19/trump-presidency-aides-white-house-1502041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No longer hemmed in by aides, Trump has bent the presidency into the mold of the Trump Organization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEORGE CONWAY</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/gtconway3d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alien enthusiasts descend on Nevada desert near secretive base...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/local-nevada/officials-say-theyre-ready-for-whatever-comes-from-area-51-events-1852066/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials looking over a pair of Storm Area 51 festivals still don’t know what to expect as the first day of events is set to kick off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man electrocuted, drowns trying to rescue horse...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/national-international/Its-Bad-Water-Rescues-Begin-as-Imelda-Soaks-East-Texas-560786191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The slow-churning remnants of Tropical Storm Imelda dangerously flooded parts of Texas and Louisiana on Thursday, scrambling rescue crews and volunteers with boats to reach scores of stranded drivers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani Admits He Asked Ukraine to Investigate Biden...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/must-watch-giuliani-says-he-asked-ukraine-to-probe-biden-seconds-after-denying-it-in-trainwreck-cnn-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump's personal lawyer Rudy Giuliani says he asked Ukraine to investigate Joe Biden seconds after denying it in trainwreck CNN interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLT suspends production of AR-15 for civilian market...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fbdf5e5f6d654332bbedfaffe3663154</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST HARTFORD, Conn. (AP) — Gun-maker Colt is suspending its production of rifles for the civilian market including the popular AR-15, the company said Thursday in a shift it attributed to changes...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXECUTIVE PRIVILEGE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/48f63d46490a409ca20aecc1c4fdf573</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News from The Associated Press, the definitive source for independent journalism from every corner of the globe.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
