<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>10 DAYS LATER: Candles, flashlights, no AC in Florida's hurricane zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/candles-flashlights-no-ac-floridas-hurricane-zone-123055049.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PANAMA CITY, Fla. (AP) — More than 100,000 Florida customers are still without power due to Hurricane Michael, which tore into the Florida Panhandle more than a week ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors blast CDC...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/as-afm-illness-strikes-dozens-of-children-doctors-say-cdc/article_4debc074-5f93-5d4b-9d61-1750bf88729d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — LaMay Axton watched in horror as her granddaughter Cambria stumbled and toppled over as she ran into the kitchen of their house. The 2-year-old tried to stand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey won't allow 'cover-up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/086a03cd1b4d44b0a1d06263e353c092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL (AP) — Turkey will "never allow a cover-up" of the killing of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi in Saudi Arabia's consulate in Istanbul, a senior official in Turkey's ruling party said Saturday after Saudi Arabia announced hours earlier that the writer died during a "fistfight" in its consulate. The critical reaction by Numan Kurtulmus, deputy head of the Justice and Development Party, suggested that Turkey, which started its own investigation amid pro-government media reports that a Saudi hit squad killed Khashoggi, was not prepared to go along with the Saudi version of what happened to the writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nudist beach surfer punches shark to escape attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nudist-beach-surfer-punches-shark-escape-attack-070339086.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A surfer who got bitten by a shark at an Australian nudist beach managed to make his break for freedom after punching the creature until it let him go, he said Saturday. Paul Kenny was riding the waves off Samurai Beach, a naturist spot 200 kilometres (125 miles) north of Sydney, when he accidentally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: 63 Remains of Fetuses Found at Second Detroit Funeral Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/detroit/2018/10/19/fetuses-perry-funeral-home-detroit/1702594002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Of the grisly total, there were 36 fetuses stored in boxes and another 27 found in freezers, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vancouver Drowning in Chinese Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/pursuits/vancouver-is-drowning-in-chinese-money#gs.72Padkw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vancouver was the first place to experience the tidal wave of Chinese cash. Now the city is leading efforts to stop it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands turn out for anti-Brexit protest in London...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8ce2135b264e49e59614ff87d1ea0014</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Thousands of protesters were gathering in central London on Saturday to call for a second referendum on Britain's exit from the European Union. London Mayor Sadiq Khan was among those set to address the People's Vote March, which culminates at a rally in Parliament Square. Organizers expect the protest to be the biggest of its kind, with about 150 buses ferrying thousands of activists from across the country to the capital. Britons voted to leave the trade bloc by a narrow margin in the 2016 EU membership referendum. Prime Minister Theresa May has ruled out another public vote on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/b913157e71ec4730b414b357758a450c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MESA, Ariz. (AP) — President Donald Trump, seeking to frame the choices for voters in the midterm elections, said Friday that Democrats are "too extreme and too dangerous" to take control of Congress. On a three-day swing out West to make his closing arguments for Republican candidates, Trump sought to hone in on immigration as one of the defining election issues this fall by falsely accusing Democrats of wanting "open borders" and encouraging illegal immigration. "Anybody who votes for a Democrat now is crazy," Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL THEY TURN BACK?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181020015542-5zzjs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/CARAVAN (UPDATE 6, PIX, TV):UPDATE 6-Migrant caravan halted on Mexico-Guatemala border, pressure to turn back mounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil election battle rages over FACEBOOK's WhatsApp...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181019225559-3eodi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 1, PIX, TV):UPDATE 1-Brazil election battle rages over Facebook's WhatsApp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORMS MEXICO BORDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/honduran-migrants-gather-mexico-border-despite-trump-threats-164133863.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of migrants forced their way through Guatemala's northwestern border Friday and flooded onto a bridge leading to Mexico, where riot police battled them back, halting their trek toward the United States -- at least temporarily. The caravan of mainly Honduran migrants, whose journey has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crown prince had 'no knowledge'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-khashoggi-investigation/saudi-crown-prince-had-no-knowledge-of-specific-khashoggi-operation-source-idUSKCN1MU00F</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's crown prince had no knowledge of the specific operation that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zirinsky close to clinching top '60 MINUTES' job...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/19/susan-zirinsky-close-to-clinching-top-60-minutes-job/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“48 Hours” producer Susan Zirinsky has emerged as the front-runner to become the new executive producer of “60 Minutes” at CBS News, sources told The Post. Zirinsky is now the favorite to fill the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUDI ADMITS: KHASHOGGI KILLED IN CONSULATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/saudi-arabia-acknowledges-jamal-khashoggi-died-consulate-says-18-detained-n922336</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jamal Khashoggi disappeared on Oct. 2 after visiting the Saudi consulate in Istanbul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER CEO complains about 'unfairness' in San Fran homeless tax on corporations...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/412335-jack-dorsey-complains-about-unfairness-if-san-francisco-homeless-tax-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dorsey and Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff, who strongly supports the proposition, have butted heads on the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 DETAINED...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/saudi-arabia-detains-18-people-in-connection-with-journalists-death-1539987519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Saudi Arabia prosecutor says a dispute inside the consulate in Turkey led to the death of journalist Jamal Khashoggi as the kingdom issues the preliminary findings of its investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King asserts authority...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-saudi-politics-king-insight/as-khashoggi-crisis-grows-saudi-king-asserts-authority-checks-sons-power-sources-idUSKCN1MT1LF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So grave is the fallout from the disappearance of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashog...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Songwriter wins $44,000,000 in suit over Usher song...</title>
      <link>http://www2.philly.com/philly/entertainment/celebrities/usher-lawsuit-44-million-bad-girl-stairway-to-heaven-20181019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www2.philly.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Usher is off the hook, though</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEOs Avoid Riyadh Conference, But Not Kingdom Cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/19/business/ceos-saudi-money.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even though American and European executives are staying away, companies are unlikely to sever ties or avert future deals after the killing of Jamal Khashoggi.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insects invading VA, PA could be 'most destructive' in 150 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/spotted-lanternfly-invading-virginia-and-pennsylvania-could-be-most-destructive-species-in-150-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An invasive insect species native to China, India, and Vietnam is posing a problem in at least two states in the northeastern and southeastern part of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedentary worse than smoking, diabetes, heart disease...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/health/study-not-exercising-worse-than-smoking/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Being unfit should be treated as a disease that has a prescription, called exercise, the study's author said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albatrosses to spy out illegal fishing...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/albatrosses-spy-illegal-fishing-192539540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chizé (France) (AFP) - Fishermen illegally trawling the Indian Ocean might soon find they have more to worry about than the proverbial albatross around their neck -- real bad luck might now lurk in the form of one of the birds spying on them from the sky. A scientific programme, designed to study the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryptojacking: Your computer quietly mining bitcoin -- for someone else?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/your-computer-could-be-quietly-mining-bitcoin-someone-else-n922101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The act, known as cryptojacking, has grown in popularity because it is hard to detect, reasonably passive and lucrative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Lawyer Previews Defense: Police Misconduct, 'Non-Victim' Actresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/thr-esq/harvey-weinstein-criminal-lawyer-previews-defense-strategy-police-misconduct-victim-actresses-1153774</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a NY Bar Association panel behind closed doors, Ben Brafman addresses Gwyneth Paltrow and Rose McGowan ("quintessential non-victims"), the Brett Kavanaugh hearings ("an embarrassment to watch") and a #MeToo movement he says could undo progress for women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi hints at short-term lease on speakership...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-nancy-pelosi-speaker-20181019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Without term-limiting herself, the Democratic leader says she "has things to do, books to write, places to go." Without picking a favorite, says she would be delighted to hand speaker's gavel to another woman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military members catfished, blackmailed on dating apps by male prisoners posing as women...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2018/10/19/soldiers-are-getting-catfished-blackmailed-on-dating-apps-by-male-prisoners-posing-as-women-report-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The alleged sextortion scheme began in 2015, with prisoners posing as women in the same age bracket as the targeted soldier.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSE OF FILTH: 250 Snakes, Skunks, Ferrets, Gators Inside PA Home...</title>
      <link>http://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/10/18/officials-find-more-than-250-snakes-alligators-and-skunks-found-in-montgomery-county-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators believe the home is connected to a similar incident in Macungie.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ charges Russian with interference in Midterms...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/19/first-criminal-case-filed-over-russian-interference-in-2018-midterms-916787</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russia-based accountant was accused of buying social media ads and web postings intended &amp;quot;to sow division and discord in the U.S. political system.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TESTED</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d52af53fc55b49cdbd320df9a19ff626</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TECUN UMAN, Guatemala (AP) — Central Americans traveling in a mass caravan broke through a Guatemalan border fence and streamed by the thousands toward Mexican territory Friday, defying Mexican authorities' entreaties for an orderly migration and U.S. President Donald Trump's threats of retaliation. Arriving on the Mexican side of a border bridge, they were met by a phalanx of police with riot shields. About 50 managed to push their way through before officers unleashed pepper spray and the rest retreated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff bans alcohol sales after Hurricane Michael...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/weather/hurricane/article220302375.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials in Bay and Gulf Counties in Florida have banned alcohol sales while survivors of the hurricane-ravaged area deal with Michael’s aftermath. But Panama City officials have bucked the ban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Reporter Hit With Tear Gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/cnns-bill-weir-hit-with-tear-gas-during-harrowing-live-report-at-mexico-guatemala-border/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Controversy-Marred Playoffs, MLB Sees Ratings Decline...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/10/19/mlb-postseason-alcs-nlcs-tv-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ratings have been mostly down year over year, but how much of a concern is that for Major League Baseball?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special Counsel Probes WIKILEAKS Contacts...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/mueller-probes-wikileaks-contacts-with-conservative-activists-1539978208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Mueller’s probe is scrutinizing how a collection of activists and pundits intersected with WikiLeaks, the website that U.S. officials say was the primary conduit for publishing materials stolen by Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  F-bombs, storm-out among Trump's top staff as tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/f-bombs-storm-out-among-trump-s-top-staff-tensions-n922151</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry exchange between Trump officials over how to curtail rising border crossings points to White House divide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Hip-Hop Music Videos 'Public Health Threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/public-health-threat-hip-hop-videos-tobacco-marijuana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are hip-hop music videos a danger to the millions of young fans who enjoy watching them? According to researchers from The Dartmouth Institute and Johns Hopkins University, many very well may be</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for threatening Kavanaugh-supporting senators...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/19/man-arrested-for-threatening-kavanaugh-supporting-senators/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Long Island man was busted for making death threats against two US senators for their support of newly minted US Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh. Ronald DeRisi, 74, was taken into custody e…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEO berats analyst on earnings call: 'Embarrassment to your parents'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d55394848697bca59990ab60c20f7f98</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLEVELAND (AP) — The CEO of a mining company exploded at Wall Street analysts on Friday, saying they can't read financial reports and should resign. Lourenco Goncalves told analysts on a conference call that they didn't understand his company, Cleveland-Cliffs Inc., or even their own businesses. "You guys should resign for your lack of knowledge of things," the CEO said. "You are a disaster. You are an embarrassment to your parents." The rant earned Goncalves an invitation to appear later on CNBC, but Cleveland-Cliffs shares sank nearly 8 percent in afternoon trading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort pushed into court in wheelchair, missing shoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/donald-trump/paul-manafort-shows-court-wheelchair-learns-sentencing-date-n921826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort’s lawyer told the judge, "There are significant issues with Mr. Manafort’s health concerning confinement."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses 10 charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/paul-manafort-sentencing/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort appeared in a wheelchair in a Virginia courtroom Friday afternoon, where he learned he will be sentenced next February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant galaxy supercluster found lurking in early Universe...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/giant-galaxy-supercluster-found-lurking-early-universe-105630607.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have discovered a primitive "supercluster" of galaxies forming in the early Universe, just 2.3 billion years after the Big Bang. The structure, nicknamed Hyperion, is the largest and most massive to be found so early in the formation of the Universe, which sprang into existence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen: Vote out 'craziness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/19/politics/michael-cohen-vote-craziness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, Donald Trump's former lawyer, pleaded with the American public on Friday to head to the polls and vote against the President and the Republican Party, predicting that if they did not, there would be two or six more years of "craziness."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jones Really Wants Bezos to Buy SEAHAWKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/nfl/2018/10/19/-jerry-jones-jeff-bezos-seattle-seahawks-ownership-paul-allen-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jones told the MMQB's Jenny Vrentas that he'd "carry [Bezos] piggyback to get him to the NFL."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Plans to Launch 'Artificial Moon'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/china-plans-to-launch-an-artificial-moon-to-light-up-the-night-skies/ar-BBOAHOu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Economy SLOWS...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/finance/city/1033779/China-news-China-economy-US-trade-war-Shanghai-Composite-Index-Beijing-growth</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA’S economy has felt the brunt from an escalating trade war with the US as latest figures show growth is at its slowest for almost a decade. The Asian stock market has been rattled on consumer fears of a slowdown in economic growth, with stocks plunging to an almost four-year low this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chances of Senate flipping 'slim'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/19/democrats-look-to-win-house-in-midterms-but-senate-chances-are-dim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prognosticators believe Republicans have a strong grasp on the Senate even as massive fundraising numbers help Democrats in their bid to take the House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group crosses into Mexico, testing Trump's red line...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/first-group-honduran-caravan-cross-mexico-testing-president-trump-s-n922086/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"If migration and the federal police do not allow us access, we will do the impossible to cross into Mexico," one migrant said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  FORD boosts production of $400,000 GT supercar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/18/ford-boosts-production-of-400000-gt-supercar-to-keep-up-with-demand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Applications for the GT outstripped the previously planned limited run of 1,000 cars by more than six-to-one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US, SKorea again call off a major military exercise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7c4c40989a98451493664fb11f27f861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — The United States and South Korea are scrapping another major military exercise this year, a Pentagon official said Friday, citing a push for diplomatic progress with North Korea. The top Pentagon spokeswoman, Dana W. White, said Washington and Seoul are suspending an air exercise known as Vigilant Ace "to give the diplomatic process every opportunity to continue." It was the latest move aimed at trying to nudge North Korea, which despises such U.S.-South Korean exercises, into negotiating about giving up its nuclear weapons in a way that can be verified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEX TO ALLOW ENTRY...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/migrant-caravan-masses-near-mexican-border-1539952930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican authorities have agreed to grant humanitarian and asylum visas to a caravan of 3,000 Honduran migrants massing at the country’s southern border—but the authorities also appear to be breaking up the group into smaller pieces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator accused of 'unwanted' advance against woman...</title>
      <link>https://www.cincinnati.com/story/news/politics/2018/10/19/ohio-senate-race-sherrod-brown-accused-unwanted-advance-against-woman-80-s-brown-threate/1693877002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cincinnati.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the statement, Canton, Ohio area attorney, Laura Mills, described a sexual encounter her client had with Brown in the late 1980s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French lawmaker wants to outlaw mockery of accents...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-accents/french-lawmaker-proposes-bill-to-outlaw-mockery-of-accents-idUSKCN1MT2BU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A French member of parliament has proposed that mockery of accents be outlawed, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  'Poliolike' disease stumps scientists...</title>
      <link>https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/poliolike-childhood-muscle-weakening-disease-reappears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scientificamerican.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have traced some cases of acute flaccid myelitis to a known virus, but treatments remain elusive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO IS FUNDING?</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/18/donald-trump-suggests-someone-is-paying-migrants-in-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump suggested Thursday that someone was paying migrants in the caravan traveling to the United States from Honduras.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poverty blossoms in 'forgotten California'...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/e94318e243084d62b2271f8f70a4a191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HURON, Calif. (AP) — A rooster signals the start of the day as workers wearing sombreros emerge from the shadows and shuffle past boarded-up businesses in this tiny farm town. They converge on a dimly lit dirt lot outside Panaderia de Dios, a bakery sweetening the air with the aroma of Mexican cookies and bread as workers catch rides to the fields. Little else is sweet in Huron, where jobs not displaced by automation in farming are mostly done by hand, and residents struggle to scrape by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom to blame top intel officer?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/412096-saudi-arabia-mulls-blaming-top-intel-officer-for-khashoggi-disappearance</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia's leaders are considering blaming a top Saudi intelligence officer for the apparent murder of U.S.-based journalist Jamal Khashoggi,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's at stake if investors begin to shun...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1669f46f63a945659d6d1f9f82fbd86a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRANKFURT, Germany (AP) — The disappearance of a Saudi journalist last seen entering the kingdom's consulate in Istanbul has shaken businesses' confidence in the country as a place to do business, with potential consequences for billions of dollars in investments into and out of the country. It's a blow, analysts say, to efforts by Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman to convince the world that the country is a reputable place to strike the deals needed the to power a wide-ranging transformation of the economy. As allegations emerge that Jamal Khashoggi was gruesomely murdered, political pressure to isolate Saudi Arabia is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Do or die for Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/10/border-caravan-puts-trump-legacy-on-the-line/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our mainstream media remain consumed with the grisly killing of Washington Post columnist Jamal Khashoggi in the Saudi consulate in Istanbul, and how President Donald Trump will deal with Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman. Understandably so, for this is the most riveting murder story since O.J. Simpson and has strategic implications across the Middle East. […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside notorious 'serpent church' where devotees die from grabbing rattlesnakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/ 7512634/inside-snake-church- kentucky/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New DNA tools can decode your natural lifespan...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612256/want-to-know-when-youre-going-to-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your life span is written in your DNA, and we’re learning to read the code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge sign painted on lawn sparks HOA fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/state/texas/article220267920.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Katy, Texas, family is fighting their HOA after they were told they violated landscaping codes by painting a giant white BETO sign on the front lawn. The family says neighbors are hostile to Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Artist Depicts Maxine Waters as 'HALLOWEEN' Villain...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/maxine-waters-halloween-billboard-made-by-la-street-artist-sabo-1153715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sabo, a conservative street artist, swapped a photo of killer Michael Myers and replaced it with the congresswoman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'Very Severe' consequences if Saudis killed Khashoggi...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0ee14c584a034c82b47ba10017139153</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump has acknowledged it "certainly looks" as though missing Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi is dead, and he threatened "very severe" consequences if the Saudis are found to have murdered him. His warning came as the administration toughened its response to a disappearance that has sparked global outrage. Before Trump spoke Thursday, the administration announced that Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin had pulled out of a major upcoming Saudi investment conference and a U.S. official said Secretary of State Mike Pompeo had warned the Saudi crown prince that his credibility as a future leader is at stake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley headlines Al Smith dinner...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/video/haley-pokes-fun-at-trump-elizabeth-warren-at-al-smith-dinner-1347885635691</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambassador Nikki Haley delivered the keynote speech at the annual Al Smith dinner. Her remarks included political jokes before taking a more serious tone about “evil” in politics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems push to repeal tax cuts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/19/kamala-harris-democrats-push-to-repeal-and-replace-trump-tax-cuts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The measures are significantly more dramatic than some previous Democratic proposals – a reflection of the proximity to the midterm elections and the early interest surrounding the presidential race in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Oldest Working Man In Texas' Turns 101...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/10/18/oldest-working-man-in-texas-turns-101-still-drinks-2-dr-peppers-a-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Considered the oldest man still working in Texas, Chester Hollingsworth celebrated his 101st birthday today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark washes up dead on Florida shore with old hat wrapped around head...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/opinion/audience/richard-tribou/os-ae-shark-with-hat-florida-shore-20181017-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shark was found dead washed ashore in St. Johns County with the plastic brim of an old hat wrapped around its body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes in sky: More suburban police using drones...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailyherald.com/news/20181019/eyes-in-the-sky-why-more-suburban-police-are-using-drones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aurora is the latest suburban police force to add drones to their crime-fighting arsenal. Here's how they plan to use them - and how state law says they can't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN: Assange sues Ecuador for 'violating rights'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/wikileaks-founder-julian-assange-sues-ecuador-for-violating-his-rights-11529587</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julian Assange is launching legal action against Ecuador, accusing its government of violating his "fundamental rights and freedoms".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fentanyl smuggled from China is killing thousands of Americans...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-china-fentanyl-20181019-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fentanyl produced in China is being smuggled into the United States at such alarming levels that it is now the leading cause of opioid overdoses, killing nearly 29,000 Americans last year. A recent U.S. indictment of a Shanghai gang has exposed how the deadly network works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Acosta message to former Melania aide: 'F**k you'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/412196-cnns-acosta-sends-private-message-to-former-melania-trump-aide-fk-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN chief White House correspondent Jim Acosta sent a direct message to a Twitter follower that read "F**k you" after being mocked on the social media platform on Thursday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEAK:  Kelly, Bolton Profane Shouting Match Outside Oval Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/kelly-bolton-in-shouting-match-as-white-house-tensions-reemerge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kelly and Bolton fought over immigration and border crossings, including the performance of the Homeland Security Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE MORE TIME?</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/802785/former-hillary-clinton-adviser-says-theres-chance-run-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready to go through the 2016 election all over again? Philippe Reines, who worked for Hillary Clinton going back to 2002 and was her senior adviser at the State Department, made the argument to Politico Friday that the former Democratic nominee might actually be the party's best hope for defeating Trump in 2020. He said no other Democrat has "anywhere near a base of 32 million people," especially not Sens. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) or Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.). The party, he feels, shouldn't dismiss her as a failed candidate because she's "smarter" and "tougher" than most, and she "could raise money easier than most." But it doesn't sound like this is just wishful thinking on his part. He really thinks it could happen, saying the chances of Clinton running in 2020 are "not zero.â€� Publicly, Clinton has said she will not run again, but Reines doesn't sound so sure she'll keep her word on that. Politico explored Clinton's careful re-entry into the political arena, noting that she's going on tour with former President Bill Clinton this fall and has reportedly even called up journalists who cover the White House to put out "the occasional feeler." Despite her non-zero interest in public office, her favorability is even lower than it was in 2016. A recent Gallup poll found that Clinton is now polling at 36 percent â€” five points lower than President Trump. Read more about her political future at Politico. Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White privilege symposium will feature 'racial justice' board game...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/white-privilege-symposium-will-feature-road-to-racial-justice-board-game/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The board game 'supports and encourages cross-cultural understanding.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto supporters can't name any of his accomplishments...</title>
      <link>https://www.campusreform.org/?ID=11425</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.campusreform.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I honestly couldn't point to anything."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Caught Faking as 'Unaccompanied Minor'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/border/2018/10/17/adult-migrant-at-border-faked-being-unaccompanied-minor-say-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A CBP officer in El Paso, Texas, reportedly discovered an adult who fraudulently claimed to be an unaccompanied minor during a crossing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Presidential Helo Mechanic In Meth Bust...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/meth-mechanic-720349</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OCTOBER 18--A mechanic who helps maintain the White House helicopter fleet is facing criminal charges after allegedly calling cops while under the influence of methamphetamine to report that his fami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Releases Radical Islamist Preacher From Prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7531943/anjem-choudary-released-from-prison-early-morning-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANJEM Choudary smirked at crowds after being released from Belmarsh prison at 4am this morning – with his new neighbours in North London saying they are “disgusted”. The Islamic c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope accuser strikes back, blames gay priesthood for abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6294837/Pope-accuser-strikes-blames-gay-priesthood-abuse.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) - The Vatican ambassador who accused Pope Francis of rehabilitating a disgraced ex-American cardinal is doubling down on his claims,...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
