<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Exquisite rudeness of Nancy Pelosi...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/The-exquisite-rudeness-of-Nancy-Pelosi-s-clap-at-13593718.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lasting visual image from Tuesday night's State of the Union address was captured by photographer Doug Mills. It featured House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., applauding President Donald Trump in a way that can only be described as . . . withering? Pitying? Lucille Bluth-like in its contemptuousness? At his lectern, the president mentioned bipartisanship and turned to acknowledge Speaker Pelosi; she rewarded him by cocking her head, arching an eyebrow, and inventing, as comedian Patton Oswalt would put it online, a clap that somehow managed to be a profanity. Its power was in its restraint. Pelosi was not booing the president. She was acknowledging his words.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES subscribers skyrocket in age of Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-york-times-subscriber-numbers-are-skyrocketing-in-the-trump-age-2019-02-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Over 265,000 digital subscriptions were added in the last three months of 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested after barking at police K9...</title>
      <link>https://www.jconline.com/story/news/crime/2019/02/05/lafayette-woman-arrested-after-barking-police-k-9/2778711002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jconline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kiana Fletcher, 20, stood outside her homeÂ late Monday barking at a police dogÂ that was sniffing a car during a traffic stop, according to police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative radio host killed by AMTRAK train...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/haltom-city/2019/02/05/amtrak-train-kills-pedestrian-trinity-railway-express-tracks-haltom-city</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One person was killed Tuesday afternoon after being struck by an Amtrak train in Haltom City.The incident was reported about 3:45 p.m. on the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff announces sweeping investigation into Trump's finances, Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/06/politics/house-intelligence-transcripts-mueller/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Intelligence Committee Chairman Adam Schiff announced Wednesday a broad investigation his committee would undertake "beyond Russia" into whether President Donald Trump's financial interests are driving his actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela military barricades bridge in attempt to block aid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/011ef02872f5452e8114116573c9cd4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CUCUTA, Colombia (AP) — The Venezuelan military has barricaded a bridge at a key border crossing, issuing a challenge on Wednesday to a U.S.-backed effort by the opposition to bring humanitarian aid into the troubled nation. The Tienditas International Bridge was blocked a day prior by the Venezuelan National Guard with a giant orange tanker, two large blue containers and makeshift fencing near the border town of Cucuta, Colombian officials said. The bridge is at the same site where officials plan to store humanitarian aid that opposition leader Juan Guaido is vowing to deliver to Venezuela. The Trump administration has pledged $20 million in aid and Canada has promised another $53 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greek health minister slammed for defying smoking ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/health/eu-health-official-slams-greek-minister-for-defying-smoking-ban-11204604</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS: The European Union's top health official hit out at Greece's deputy health minister for publicly defying the country's smoking ban, saying ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Big Democratic Fight Over How to Tax the Rich...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-02-06/the-big-democratic-fight-over-how-to-tax-the-richest-americans?srnd=businessweek-v2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage After Cupertino Mayor 'Proposes' Wall To Keep TESLAs, Outsiders Away...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/02/06/cupertino-mayor-jokes-build-wall-san-jose-pay-for-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mayor of Cupertino faces scrutiny after apparently joking that his community should build a wall and have neighboring cities pay for it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD to GOOGLE:  Stop revealing location of police checkpoints...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/06/nypd-to-google-stop-revealing-the-location-of-police-checkpoints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYPD is calling on Google to yank a feature from its Waze traffic app that tips off drivers to police checkpoints — warning it could be considered “criminal conduct,” according to a repor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army developing grueling fitness exam to make soldiers more fit...</title>
      <link>http://www.hartfordcitynewstimes.com/video/us-army-uses-new-test-to-prep-troops-for-combat/youtube_db28cb1e-0613-5f4b-85cf-e9c83a89e541.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hartfordcitynewstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Army is developing a new, more grueling and complex fitness exam that adds dead lifts, power throws and other exercises designed to make soldiers more fit and ready</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French farmer taking on MONSANTO...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190206-france-paul-francois-french-farmer-taking-monsanto-lasso-herbicide-weed-killer</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul François, a farmer from France’s rural Charente region, is seeking more than €1 million in damages from Monsanto, arguing that use of the company’s Lasso weed killer has left him disabled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE taking on health care...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/06/alphabet-most-ambitious-health-care-projects.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet has a wide range of health-care research projects, from rehab efforts and medical tests to new devices for people in need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 'very large explosions' send manhole covers in air Atlanta...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/traffic/breaking-manhole-covers-blowing-off-major-midtown-street/9NB2vgBDb8tVpwzZgyWAiP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten “very large explosions” sent thick smoke into the air in front of Emory University H...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Plays Starring Role in Netanyahu's Re-Election Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-plays-starring-role-in-netanyahus-re-election-bid-11549449000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is putting President Trump at the center of his re-election campaign, aiming to leverage close ties with Washington as he faces pressure from political rivals and a possible indictment on corruption charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,809 illegal crossing attempts a day...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/new-border-crisis-1-809-illegal-crossing-attempts-a-day-ticking-time-bomb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pro-Trump group has taken the president’s demand for border wall funding to the streets around Capitol Hill, warning that a barrier is needed to thwart 1,809 illegal crossing attempts every single day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB mulls dramatic rule changes...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/2019/02/06/mlb-union-discuss-major-rule-changes/2787961002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the league has made some tweaks in recent years, the new proposals would drastically change the game on and off the field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  Aborted babies' body parts fused with mice for 'Frankenstein' experiments...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8367760/aborted-baby-body-parts-sewn-mice-experiments-us-labs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABORTED babies are being used in macabre experiments in the US that involve grafting dead fetus parts onto mice which are then used to test drugs. Documents seen by Sun Online outline procedures th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT Partner 'NewsGuard' Removes DAILY MAIL from Blacklist...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/02/05/microsoft-partner-newsguard-removes-daily-mail-from-news-blacklist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NewsGuard, the browser extension that rates the “trustworthiness” of news outlets which is included by default in Microsoft's mobile Edge browser, has removed the Daily Mail from its blacklist — which includes Breitbart News, WikiLeaks, and the Drudge Report. NewsGuard claims that with the "benefit" of the Daily Mail's "input," it realized "we were wrong."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED to pursue high-fare travelers with more premium seats...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7d34c6a2366c477ea563e70e26dd99c0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;United Airlines will woo high-fare passengers by retrofitting more than 100 planes to add more premium seats on key routes. The airline also plans to start using a new 50-seat jet with mostly premium seats on some key business-travel routes. United announced the moves Wednesday. They are part of an industry trend to give more space and better service to high-paying passengers who account for a disproportionate share of airline revenue. Andrew Nocella, the airline's chief commercial officer, said executives decided that United has "a shortage of business-class seats into the premium markets, and this fixed that problem."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to California, land of 1,000 laws  -- and that's just this year!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/judiciary/428328-welcome-to-california-land-of-1000-laws-and-thats-just-this-year</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many of the state's laws taking effect this year range from the unnecessary to the silly to the sad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Trump is divisive. He splits his opposition perfectly'...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/one-nation-trumpism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theater First To Offer 'Virtual Reality Movies' In Effort to Boost Slumping Sales... </title>
      <link>http://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2019/02/05/cineplex-virtual-reality-movies-lure-gamers-to-big-screen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KPIX 5 got an exclusive sneak peek at the Bay Area‘s first virtual reality movie theater. Think: gaming meets movies meets Disneyland.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Plays Starring Role in Netanyahu's Re-Election Bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-plays-starring-role-in-netanyahus-re-election-bid-11549449000?mod=searchresults&amp;page=1&amp;pos=14</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Embattled Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is putting President Trump at the center of his re-election campaign, aiming to leverage close ties with Washington as he faces pressure from political rivals and a possible indictment on corruption charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covington Catholic teen sues 54 news outlets, lawmakers and celebrities...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/feb/5/covington-catholic-teen-begins-legal-battle-agains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident involving the Covington Catholic High School boys last month at the Lincoln Memorial may be long over, but the legal battle has just begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siri-Like Phone Assistant Out for Blood in Slasher Movie 'AMI' Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/siri-ami-trailer-slasher-movie-exclusive-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horror film starring Debs Howard and Sam Robert Muik launches for international sales in Berlin this week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen testimony before Housel panel delayed...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/02/06/michael-cohen-testimony-delay-1151101</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen was slated to testify Friday behind closed doors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT SORRY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/06/ocasio-cortez-is-not-apologizing-for-her-state-of-the-union-reaction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez shot back at critics who complained that she didn’t show much enthusiasm while attending the State of the Union address, saying President Trump’s speech wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'NETFLIX of porn'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-netflix-of-porn-how-bree-mills-is-shaking-up-the-adult-industry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The porn auteur is launching a subscription service for high-quality XXX productions that she’s calling ‘The Netflix of Porn.’ And it could be huge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Media's Crash: Will Hollywood Buy In or Cash Out?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/digital-medias-crash-will-hollywood-buy-cash-1183114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As BuzzFeed and Vice cut hundreds of jobs, Comcast or Disney could look at takeover bids, but "why would they want to double down on failing businesses that aren't even strategic to them?"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporters Stunned by Appeal to Both Sides...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/the-media/2019/02/06/reporters-stunned-by-state-of-the-unions-appeal-to-both-sides/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran White House reporters noted -- to their surprise -- that President Donald Trump's State of the Union won applause from Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path to enlightenment now worth $1 BILLION?</title>
      <link>https://venturebeat.com/2019/02/06/the-meditation-unicorn-calm-raises-88-million-at-1-billion-valuation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;venturebeat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mindfulness startup Calm has raised $88 million in a series B round of funding, elevating the startup to much-coveted "unicorn" status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to hold first rally of 2019 in El Paso...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/428702-trump-to-hold-first-rally-of-2019-in-el-paso</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's campaign on Wednesday announced that he will hold his first rally of 2019 in El Paso, Texas, next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ratings Rise Over 2018, Obama... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/02/state-of-the-union-ratings-cable-broadcast-donald-trump-address-1202550542/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump never mentioned the unprecedented government shutdown nor the Democrats’ newly installed majority in the House of Representatives in his second official State of the Union address last…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA probes mysteriously vanish after Mars flyby...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/8363761/nasa-marco-spacecraft-mysteriously-disappear-after-mars-fly-by/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pair of Nasa probes have mysteriously disappeared after a close flyby with Mars. It’s been over a month since Nasa last heard from the £14million spacecraft, which were named WALL-E and EVE…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety, AWOL Execs, 'Bloodshed': How DISNEY Making FOX Disappear...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-disney-will-make-21st-century-fox-disappear-1182704</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the $71.3 billion merger of two studios about to close, fears are mounting on the storied Fox lot as colleagues prepare to become rivals, Bob Iger's every move is scrutinized and 4,000 jobs are about to vanish: "There will be bloodshed."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sfrican land grab farmers fleeing in 'record numbers'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/757905/south-africa-farmers-land-grabs-australia-emigration-migration</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREAT: Trade deficit narrows much more than expected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/06/us-trade-deficit-narrows-much-more-than-expected-in-a-win-for-trump.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gap had closed in November to $49.3 billion from $55.7 billion in October, representing an 11.5 percent decline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia jails Jehovah's Witness for six years in landmark case; 'Extremism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-russia-politics-religion/russia-jails-jehovahs-witness-for-six-years-in-extremism-case-idUSKCN1PV0W2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian court on Wednesday found a Danish adherent of the Jehovah's Witne...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoking Marijuana Linked to HIGHER Sperm Counts?</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/64693-marijuana-sperm-counts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings contradict previous research, but they are far from conclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Miami estate sells for record $50 million...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/02/06/miami-estate-sells-for-a-record-50-million.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An estate on Indian Creek Island sells for $50 million, making it the most expensive single-family home ever sold in the Miami area, according to people familiar with the deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torture still scars Iranians 40 years after revolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/072580b5f24b4f8ea2402221d530257e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — The halls of the former prison in the heart of Iran's capital now are hushed, befitting the sounds of the museum that it has become. Wax mannequins silently portray the horrific acts of torture that once were carried out within its walls. But the surviving inmates still remember the screams. Exhibits in the former Anti-Sabotage Joint Committee Prison that was run under Shah Mohammad Reza Pahlavi include a frightened man trapped in a small metal cage as a cigarette-smoking interrogator shouts above him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Starts to Worry Maduro Grip Slipping...</title>
      <link>https://themoscowtimes.com/news/russia-starts-to-worry-maduros-grip-is-slipping-in-venezuela-64416</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;themoscowtimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow is acutely aware of how few levers it has to rescue Maduro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Special place in Hell' for Brexiteers: EU leader...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/special-place-hell-brexiteers-eu-leader-005252544.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Union leader Donald Tusk on Wednesday condemned those calling for Brexit with no idea how to carry it out, saying he hopes Theresa May now has a "realistic" plan. The British prime minister is due in Brussels on Thursday to discuss ways to ensure Britain's orderly withdrawal from</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns 'sex slaves' scandal fresh blow to Catholic church...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/nuns-sex-slaves-scandal-fresh-blow-catholic-church-002950866.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis's public admission that priests have used nuns as "sexual slaves" -- and may still be doing so -- marks a new chapter in the abuse crisis rocking the Catholic church. "It is the first time that the pope, but also the church as an institution, has publicly admitted this</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Tested in Philly...</title>
      <link>https://6abc.com/health/patient-being-tested-for-ebola-at-hospital-of-the-university-of-pennsylvania/5123171/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;6abc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A patient is being tested for Ebola at the Hospital of the University of Pennsylvania in Philadelphia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacteria-killing travel robot cleans hotel bed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6658027/The-bacteria-killing-travel-robot-cleans-hotel-bed-enjoy-holiday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 'marvel of engineering and design', the U.S-made CleanseBot weighs just 220 grams – less than half a pound – and kills 99.99 per cent of bacteria, germs, and dust mites, it's claimed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watching TV could give bowel cancer?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6669889/Watching-TV-BOWEL-CANCER-hour-day-increase-young-peoples-risk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Study looked at sedentary behaviours of 90,000 women. Researcher Dr Yin Cao from Washington University School of Medicine said younger people may benefit from screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola Fears Take Monkey Meat Off Menu...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ebola-fears-stalking-congo-s-neighbor-put-monkey-meat-off-menu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ebola Fears Take Monkey Meat Off the Menu</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Racing to Make Pot Like Booze So Can Drink It...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/scientists-are-racing-to-make-pot-like-booze-so-you-can-drink-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists Are Racing to Make Pot Like Booze So You Can Drink It</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filings raise prospect of more indictments...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/428616-mueller-probe-filings-raise-prospect-of-more-indictments</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller’s references to “uncharged individuals” in recent court filings that aim to restrict certain evidence are being read by some as an indication more people could be indicted in his sprawling investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it sign? Huge wooden cross washes ashore on Fort Lauderdale beach...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/broward/fort-lauderdale/fl-lauderdale-cross-comes-ashore-20190205-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A very large barnacle-encrusted wooden cross washed ashore in Fort Lauderdale, Florida, behind the Ocean Manor Beach Resort along Galt Ocean Mile during the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN: 59%  Had 'Very Positive' View of Speech...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-cnn-our-poll-respondents-had-very-positive-view-trump-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘59%, very positive’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightmare of Human Organ Harvesting in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-nightmare-of-human-organ-harvesting-in-china-11549411056</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transplants far outnumber official donors. Prisoners of conscience evidently account for the difference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS POLL: 76% APPROVE OF SPEECH</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/02/poll-stunner-76-percent-of-viewers-approve-president-trumps-state-of-the-union-speech-72-percent-approve-his-immigration-ideas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Dem Jaime Harrison may challenge Sen. Lindsey Graham in SC...</title>
      <link>https://www.postandcourier.com/politics/ahead-of-re-election-lindsey-graham-s-challenge-shifts-from/article_ea44940a-2635-11e9-bdc9-8b57192462f7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postandcourier.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the "First in the South" 2020 presidential primary has garnered much of the attention in recent weeks, South Carolina Democrats have also been using the early days of 2019</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris fire: Ten dead as woman arrested for 'revenge arson attack on fireman neighbor'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/seven-reported-dead-many-injured-044920085.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least 10 people died and 37 were injured in an overnight blaze at an apartment block in Paris that police are treating as possible arson. At least one of the victims is a "young child", according to the local mayor. The fire on the upper floors of the building in the rue Erlanger in the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Actor Liam Neeson denies racism after admitting hunt for black men...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/liam-neeson-denies-racism-hunting-black-men-attack-190441412.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood star Liam Neeson insisted on Tuesday he was "not racist" after confessing that he once set out to attack a random black man after a friend of his told him she had been raped. "I'm not a racist," Neeson said on ABC News, while admitting he had felt a "primal urge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kidneys grown in rats could pave way for human transplants...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/kidneys-grown-rats-could-pave-way-human-transplant-160119583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tokyo (AFP) - Scientists said Wednesday they have successfully used mice stem cells to grow kidneys in rat embryos, using a technique that could one day help grow human kidneys for transplant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest speech since Clinton 2000...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trumps-2019-state-of-the-union-address-was-the-longest-since-clintons-in-2000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s State of the Union address Tuesday night, at 82 minutes in length, was the longest such speech since President Bill Clinton's 89-minute one in 2000 and the third-longest ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WE WILL NEVER BE SOCIALIST COUNTRY'</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2019/02/05/trump_america_will_never_be_a_socialist_country_we_were_born_free_and_we_shall_stay_free.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We stand with the venezuelan people in their noble quest for freedom -- and we condemn the brutality of the maduro regime, whose socialist policies have turned that nation from being the wealthiest in south America into a state of abject poverty and despair. [applause] pres. Here, in the United States, we are alarmed by new calls to adopt socialism in our country. America was founded on liberty and independence - not government coercion, domination, and control. We are born free, and we will stay free. Tonight, we renew our resolve that America will never be a socialist country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts elite as they push for open borders 'while living behind walls'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8363077/state-of-the-union-address-donald-trump-border-wall-elite-hypocrisy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump tonight blasted wealthy elites for backing “open borders while living behind walls”. In a State of the Union speech marked by calls for unity, the president did not hold ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBCNEWS Chuck Todd Blasts 'Theater of the Absurd'...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/nb/nicholas-fondacaro/2019/02/05/chuck-todd-blasts-trumps-sotu-theater-absurd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In advance of Tuesday’s State of the Union address, the White House told the press that President Trump wanted to use the occasion to hit the reset button on strained relationships in Washington, D.C. and to bring Americans to together. But liberal media folks like MSNBC’s Chuck Todd couldn’t believe it. During that evening’s MTP Daily, Todd denounced Trump’s second SOTU as “shaping up to be a night of absurdist theater”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takes swipe at Mueller investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/card/trump-takes-swipe-mueller-investigation-n967916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ROCKS   HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6672199/We-work-says-Trump-uses-State-Union-call-bipartisan-unity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a State of the Union address Tuesday night designed to call for an end to partisan bickering, President Donald Trump stressed that he could bring bipartisan unity to Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern District Eyes Trump Org Execs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/02/05/politics/new-york-federal-prosecutors-trump-organization-executives/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors in New York have requested interviews in recent weeks with executives at the Trump Organization, according to people familiar with the matter, signaling a growing potential threat to President Donald Trump and those in his orbit from criminal investigations by the Manhattan US Attorney's office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Wins over Dems After Touting Job Gains for Women...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-trump-gets-applause-democrats-no-one-has-benefitted-more-our</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘We also have more women serving in the Congress than ever before’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto will decide if 2020 run by month's end...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a7de74cd5074caabad81eabb97b0b9b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Breaking months of near-silence about his political future, Democrat Beto O'Rourke said Tuesday that he would announce his decision about a 2020 presidential run "before the end of the month" and suggested he's leaning toward it. The former Texas congressman, who found political stardom in his unsuccessful Senate bid last fall, opened up about a potential 2020 run in a conversation with a bigger star, Oprah Winfrey, during a taping of her program "Oprah's SuperSoul Conversations from Times Square."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calls on divided Congress to end political stalemate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/449885686d4b4db7b0724314bdba6577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In his first State of the Union address to a divided Congress, President Donald Trump warned Democrats on Tuesday that "ridiculous partisan investigations" could derail the nation's economic progress. Trump peppered his speech with calls for bipartisanship, urging Washington to govern "not as two parties, but as one nation." But his message clashed with the rancorous atmosphere he has helped cultivate in the nation's capital, as well as the desire of most Democrats to block his path during his next two years in office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez refuses applause for 'cooperation, compromise, common good'...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-sour-ocasio-cortez-refuses-to-applaud-cooperation-compromise-common-good/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez has no interest in working with President Trump, or applauding his call for “cooperation, compromise, and the common good.” “But we must reject the politics of revenge, resistance and retribution, and embrace the boundless potential of cooperation, compromise, and the common good,” Trump said during his State of the Union address. As …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST: Was Bezos Affair Expose Political Hit Job?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/was-tabloid-expose-of-bezos-affair-just-juicy-gossip-or-a-political-hit-job/2019/02/05/03d2f716-2633-11e9-90cd-dedb0c92dc17_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dueling investigations seek to learn how the National Enquirer obtained texts sent by the owner of The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian media threatens US with nuclear doomsday device...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/russia-threatens-us-with-nuclear-doomsday-device-after-inf-failure-2019-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It cannot be excluded that one of the Poseidon with a 100 megaton nuclear warhead will lay low off the US coast, becoming 'the doomsday weapon.'"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man jumps aboard moving AMTRAK train, tries to take over controls...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/california/la-me-ln-dylan-thomas-baldini-moving-train-20190205-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities said the 26-year-old man tried to change the locomotive’s controls and blasted the train's horn several times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidential Memo: Company of Inaugural Chair Sought to Profit From Connections...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/trump-inc-podcast-tom-barrack-colony-company-of-trump-inaugural-chair-sought-to-profit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The memo outlines how Colony, the company founded by Tom Barrack, an investor who chaired the inaugural, aimed to exploit its connections to Donald Trump. Federal prosecutors are conducting a wide-ranging probe into the nonprofit that ran the inaugural.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren identified as 'American Indian' for State Bar registration; Additional docs to surface?</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/politics/2019/02/05/elizabeth-warren-identified-native-american-her-state-bar-texas-registration/fevojNFJErrYPmNK5jR25J/story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The senator apologized for identifying herself as a Native American for almost two decades, reflecting her ongoing struggle to quiet a controversy that continues to haunt her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK ministers hold secret talks of delaying Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu/uk-ministers-hold-secret-talks-of-delaying-brexit-by-eight-weeks-the-telegraph-idUSKCN1PU2ML</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK cabinet ministers have secretly held talks on plans to delay Brexit by eight ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former TESLA workers paint grim picture: 'Building plane as we're flying it'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wivb.com/news/investigates/former-tesla-workers-paint-grim-picture-of-buffalo-plant/1754568826</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wivb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of former Tesla workers in Buffalo are breaking their silence about problems they witnessed at the plant, including what they termed as “a lack of urgency” shown by management to improve operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia scandal puts 'believe all accusers' standard to test...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/justin-fairfax-is-testing-the-lefts-believe-all-accusers-standard</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sexual assault allegation against Democratic Lt. Gov. Justin Fairfax has added to the chaos in a state already reeling from the publication of Democratic Gov. Ralph Northam's yearbook page that included a photo featuring one person in blackface and another one in a Ku Klux Klan costume. But more…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial shoe thief says crimes motivated by sexual pleasure of sniffing used footwear...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/asia/east-asia/article/2185097/japanese-shoe-sniffer-admits-stealing-used-footwear-sexual</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Makoto Endo, 40, is suspected of stealing 70 pairs of shoes worth nearly US$3,000 over a 13-month period</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF THE ART</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-touts-drudge-report-labelling-him-teflon-donald-ahead-of-state-of-the-union/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of decapitated fish with bladders torn out wash ashore in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/757887/thousands-of-headless-fish-wash-up-bladders-torn-out-BIZARRE-video-Germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLF NOW 'CONTACT SPORT'; BAD BACK EPIDEMIC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6667923/Golf-bad-participants-CONTACT-sport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A focus on strength over style is making spinal injuries common among both amateurs and professionals. More than half of those who golf for a living suffer from back injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Husband opens fire after wife tryst in hot tub with friend...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/hot-tub-tryst-603941</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEBRUARY 5--An “enraged” Florida Man fired two shots after discovering his wife performing a sex act on a male friend of the couple’s while the pair were in a backyard hot tub, police report. Accordi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg rips AMAZON tax breaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/albany/story/2019/02/05/bloomberg-billionaire-and-possible-presidential-candidate-disputes-tax-breaks-for-amazon-837970</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bloomberg inveighing against corporate welfare gives the potential Democratic candidate a connection to an economic populist message.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER BRAWL: Fists fly at PATRIOS parade...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/02/05/patriots-fans-celebrate-super-bowl-53-win-with-all-out-brawl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots fans sure have an odd way of celebrating the team’s Super Bowl win. Tuesday’s parade for the six-time NFL champions began by irking local commuters by bringing thousands of fan…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORCED ABORTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/397f2c76afc04532908035a66ccaacc8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD THE PAPAL PLANE (AP) — Pope Francis has for the first time publicly acknowledged the scandal of priests and bishops sexually abusing nuns and says he is committed to doing more to fight the problem. Speaking to reporters Tuesday, Francis noted that Pope Benedict XVI had taken action against a France-based order after some of its religious sisters had been reduced to "sexual slavery" at the hands of the priest who founded the order and other priests. "Should we do something more? Yes. Is there the will? Yes. But it's a path that we have already begun," Francis said while returning home from the United Arab Emirates.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
