<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust survivor watched starving prisoners 'roast and eat child'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/holocaust-survivor-watched-starving-prisoners-21045977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nazi Holocaust survivor Josef Lewcowicz witnessed "so much cruelty" from the Nazis that "nothing surprised" him during his time in five brutal concentration camps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal rights YOUTUBer viciously beaten in Miami pizza shop...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7767097/Videos-Brother-Nature-savagely-assaulted-Miami-pizza-shop-just-days-beach-clean-up.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brother Nature - whose real name is Kelvin Peña - was in Miami doing a beach clean up and had stopped at the La Sandwhicherie on early Saturday morning when he was brutally attacked.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judiciary panel releases report defining offenses...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473515-house-judiciary-committee-releases-staff-report-on-constitutional-grounds-for</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House Judiciary Committee on Saturday released a report explaining the constitutional grounds for the impeachment of President Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems battle for Hollywood cash...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/473419-democrats-battle-for-hollywood-cash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle for celebrity support — and dollars — is growing in the Democratic presidential primary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudis distance selves...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudis-distance-themselves-us-naval-shooter-113700686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia sought to distance itself Saturday from a student who carried out a fatal shooting at an American naval base, as it seeks to repair its image of being an exporter of Islamic extremism. The Saudi military trainee reportedly condemned the US as a "nation of evil" before going on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says denuclearization talks 'out of negotiation table'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/north-korea-says-us-denuclearization-talks-negotiation-table-173115232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea on Saturday said denuclearization talks with the United States were "out of the negotiation table," while slamming European UN Security Council members who had recently denounced its "provocative" ballistic missile launches. The statement from North Korea's ambassador</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk defamation win may reset legal landscape for social media...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191207011842-sg7qs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSK-LAWSUIT/LANDSCAPE (ANALYSIS):Musk's defamation win may reset legal landscape for social media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Deen Accuser Disgusted by His Porn Awards Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/james-deen-sexual-assault-accuser-disgusted-by-his-porn-awards-nominations-nobody-seemed-to-care</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashley Fires was the third of nearly a dozen women to accuse porn actor James Deen of sexual assault. Now, she’s found herself nominated for an award with her alleged attacker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hobnails, drill and boot camp: Secrets of Sam Mendes war epic 1917...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2019/dec/07/sam-mendes-1917-hobnails-drill-boot-camp-war-epic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director tells how getting every detail right was crucial to helping his cast understand emotions of war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quoted Bin Laden...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-shooting/saudi-suspect-in-u-s-navy-base-attack-linked-to-anti-u-s-twitter-screed-idUSKBN1YB0FK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Saudi airman accused of killing three people at a U.S. Navy base in Florida ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Monet instead of Treasury? Art returns rival bonds...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/07/art-has-shown-long-term-returns-that-rival-bonds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Art's rate of return and lack of correlation with other asset classes is making it an increasingly popular investment, a new report from Citi said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson, Josh Allen rush into historic meeting...</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001084685/article/lamar-jackson-josh-allen-rush-into-historic-meeting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their fleet feet having carried them to much success, Lamar Jackson's 977 rushing yards and Josh Allen's 430 combine for a tally of 1,407 -- the most all-time between two opposing quarterbacks entering a game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scorpion stings passenger on UNITED flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/12/07/united-airlines-passenger-stung-scorpion-flight-san-francisco-atlanta/4364415002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on a United Airlines flight from San Francisco (SFO) to Atlanta (ATL) had a nasty surprise: A scorpion sting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consequential choice -- limited or broad articles...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Democrats-face-a-consequential-choice-limited-14889490.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats are heading into the final days of drafting articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump by reopening an internal debate that has roiled their caucus for more than six months.  Some Democrats, particularly the more liberal members of the House Judiciary Committee now writing potential articles, want to wrap in charges against the president linked to Russian interference in the 2016 election to help Trump defeat Hillary Clinton.  Ever since his report was released in the spring, these Democrats believe that Robert Mueller, who served as special counsel, painted a portrait of criminal behavior by Trump that at the least demonstrated an attempt to obstruct justice.  "The real question is whether we want to focus on a singular, discrete episode or focus on patterns of misconduct. And I do think we need to focus on patterns of misconduct, I think that the Constitution directs us to examine that," said Rep. Jamie Raskin, D-Md., a member of the Judiciary Committee.  To ignore the Mueller findings, Raskin and other liberals believe, is to let Trump escape condemnation for a pattern of behavior. "The misconduct that we saw with respect to the Ukraine shakedown was not some kind of aberration," he said.  Democrats will have an easier time writing charges against Trump for trying to pressure Ukraine's leaders into investigations that would have helped the president politically, an inquiry that all but two Democrats supported last month.  The evidence, produced in hearings before the House Intelligence Committee, has only gotten stronger since that vote, so Democrats are optimistic they have more than enough votes already to impeach Trump based on the Ukraine matter.  But any articles reaching beyond Ukraine would renew an old clash between...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They grew up in K-pop limelight. Is it to blame for their deaths?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-12-06/sulli-goo-hara-kpop-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did K-Pop cause the death of Sulli and Goo Hara?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Pearl Harbor veteran interred at USS Arizona Memorial...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2019-12-07/pearl-harbor-survivor-last-interment-hawaii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lauren Bruner, who died in September at 98, will be the 44th and final crew member of the U.S. battleship Arizona to be interred at the site of the Dec. 7, 1941, attack that sunk the ship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi airman opens fire at naval base in Pensacola, killing 3...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/75a8adc71422596a54052540fabb7230</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PENSACOLA, Fla. (AP) — U.S. officials investigating the deadly attack by a Saudi aviation student at a naval air station in Florida were working Saturday to determine whether it was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The season of Adam Driver has been decade in making...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/entertainment/article/The-season-of-Adam-Driver-has-been-a-decade-in-14887321.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching a scene primarily concerned with the dynamic between a film's protagonist and his romantic rival, a viewer might not expect the random guy in the corner to attract too much attention. And yet as Oscar Isaac and Justin Timberlake's characters in 2013's "Inside Llewyn Davis" record a novelty song begging President John Kennedy not to shoot them into outer space, it isn't just their harmonizing or the lyrics that make the bizarre tune work, but the manner in which their screenmate Adam Driver punctuates it with comical noises and refrains - "Outer ... space!" - delivered in his trademark baritone.  That's Driver in a nutshell, someone who, in part thanks to his large presence and general way of being, can't help but command the screen. HBO's "Girls," on which he broke out as the volatile Adam Sackler, even features a scene in which another character notes that he "does sort of look like the original man." The episode aired in 2012, early in a decade that proved to be star-making for the Oscar-nominated actor, and which he has capped with a robust fall slate: He stars as a lead in two films, "Marriage Story" and "The Report," and plays a villain in the upcoming holiday blockbuster "Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker."  So how did the season of Adam Driver come to be? There's the aesthetic intrigue mentioned above that once led the Guardian to ask the lanky actor about "not being the standard Hollywood McHunk," to which he candidly responded, "I have been told before that I have an unusual face. But my face is my face." His success is likely due more to how that sense of grounded honesty comes through in his performances.  Driver, who trained at Juilliard after serving in the Marines, broadcasts a quiet intensity that can capture a range of feelings, sometimes all at once. In the earlier seasons of "Girls," for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Senate Republicans who could convict...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/473478-here-are-the-senate-republicans-who-could-vote-to-convict-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assailed USA as 'nation of evil'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/three-killed-shooter-dead-us-navy-attack-170619246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Saudi military student reportedly condemned America as a "nation of evil" in an online manifesto prior to opening fire Friday at a US naval base, killing three people before being shot dead by police. The shooting, which took place in a classroom building at Naval Air Station Pensacola in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No let-up in French strikes as fresh turmoil hits weekend...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-let-french-strikes-fresh-turmoil-awaited-031814736.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most serious nationwide strike to hit France in years caused new weekend travel turmoil on Saturday, with unions warning the walkouts would last well into next week. The challenge thrown to President Emmanuel Macron over his plans for radical pension reform has seen hundreds of thousands take to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teflon Musk Wins Again With Escape From 'Pedo Guy' Firestorm...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/teflon-musk-wins-again-escape-023017645.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Even before the verdict came in Friday, Elon Musk had earned the sobriquet Teflon Man on Twitter.Once a jury decided that he hadn’t defamed a British man by calling him a “pedo guy” in a post on the social media platform -- Musk’s favorite -- his reputation as a controversy-stirring billionaire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Loans Rise to Record Highs as Auto Debt Piles Up...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/high-tech-features-push-u-120000047.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The average loan amount for new and used vehicles in the U.S. set records in the third quarter, as more sophisticated features like self-driving technology pushed up car prices.The average amount of a new-vehicle loan rose by 5% to $32,480 from a year earlier, according to information</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Candidates Jostle for Position, a Long Race May Become Marathon...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/12/07/as-candidates-jostle-for-position-a-long-race-may-become-a-marathon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MASON CITY, Iowa — With just under two months until the Iowa caucuses, the already-volatile Democratic presidential race has grown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems to spend weekend drafting impeachment charges...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191207102929-qmqpw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/IMPEACHMENT:Democrats to spend weekend drafting impeachment charges against Trump</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second Epstein victim claims she had sex with Prince Andrew...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10501918/second-jeffrey-epstein-victim-claims-she-had-sex-with-prince-andrew/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SECOND woman allegedly abused by paedophile billionaire Jeffrey Epstein has claimed she had sex with Prince Andrew. The fresh allegations come after Epstein’s “sex slave” Virgin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pig monkey hybrids created in bizarre world first...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/pig-monkey-hybrids-created-china-21043717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese team is just one of several racing to create perfect hosts for human organs – extending human lifespans massively</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six others arrested; Three filmed attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7766473/Saudi-Air-Force-trainee-condemned-nation-evil-hate-fueled-Twitter-manifesto.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, identified as Mohammed Saeed Alshamrani, opened fire inside a classroom at Naval Air Station in Pensacola early Friday morning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA BLOODBATH: 7,600 JOBS LOST IN '19...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/2019-media-layoffs-job-cuts-at-buzzfeed-huffpost-vice-details-2019-2#gannett-189-jobs-december-400-jobs-january-23-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Layoffs and buyouts in the media industry have claimed more than 7,600 jobs in 2019. The latest were at Gannett, Highsnobiety, and the CBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran releases American graduate student in prisoner swap...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/473495-iran-releases-american-held-since-2016-in-prisoner-exchange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration on Saturday announced the release of Xiyue Wang, a Chinese-American graduate student detained in Iran since 2016, as part of a prisoner exchange with Tehran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump White House, that elusive China trade deal is always 'close'...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/at-trump-white-house-that-elusive-china-trade-deal-is-always-close</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the Trump White House, a trade agreement with China is always "close." Despite repeated promises, however, there's no deal in sight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hit by fires and droughts, California voters call 'climate change' their top priority...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/hit-by-fires-and-droughts-california-voters-call-climate-change-their-top-priority/ar-BBXR6I5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How progressives are plotting to stop Mayor Pete Buttigieg's rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/article238088149.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court halts subpoena to DEUTSCHE BANK for Trump records...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/473461-supreme-court-halts-subpoena-to-deutsche-bank-for-trump-financial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court on Friday granted President Trump's emergency request to temporarily block a congressional subpoena for his financial records from Deutsche Bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amash says he will vote in favor...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/473442-amash-says-hell-vote-in-favor-of-articles-of-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Justin Amash (I-Mich.) said Friday that he would vote for the articles of impeachment when House Democrats bring them to the House for a vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAYS AFTER PEARL HARBOR SHOOTING...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2dec5ee8ce885061fe25c699a43eb71b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — The U.S. Navy sailor who fatally shot two people at Pearl Harbor before killing himself was unhappy with his commanders and had been undergoing counseling, a military official said...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey blasts Mattis for silence on Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/i-would-be-a-coward-if-i-didnt-speak-out-comey-blasts-mattis-for-silence-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI Director James Comey expressed his disappointment with former Secretary of Defense Jim Mattis for not speaking out against President Trump since he left the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mohammed Saeed Alshamrani...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/active-shooter-reported-naval-air-station-pensacola-n1096966</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia is "going to owe a debt here given that it was one of their individuals," Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis said. "The government of Saudi Arabia needs to make things better for these victims."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In USA for flight school...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox9.com/news/official-pensacola-shooter-saudi-arabian-aviation-student</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. official says the Florida Naval station shooting suspect was an aviation student from Saudi Arabia and authorities are investigating if the shooting was terrorism-related.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-male, half-female bird found...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cardinal-with-rare-abnormality-discovered-in-central-texas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Inland Bird Banding Association, the bird shows apparent bilateral gynandromorphism, a rare abnormality that causes it to have female plumage on one side of its body, and male on the other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk wins; Not liable in 'pedo guy' defamation trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/06/unsworth-vs-musk-pedo-guy-defamation-trial-verdict.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Elon Musk called British caver Vernon Unsworth a "pedo guy" on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg on other 2020 hopefuls: 'Trump would eat them up'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/michael-bloomberg-interview-with-gayle-king-trump-joe-biden-race-policing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview, Bloomberg spoke to Gayle King about the 2020 presidential race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading Geneticist: Reversing Aging Process In Humans 20 Years Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/leading-geneticist-george-church-reversing-the-aging-process-in-humans-could-be-20-years-away-60-minutes-2019-12-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Aging reversal is something that's been proven about eight different ways in animals," geneticist George Church says. So when will humans get to turn back the clock? Church tells 60 Minutes it's not that far away. See the full report, Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel voices 'deep shame' on first visit to Auschwitz...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-visit-auschwitz-first-time-040430156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Merkel visited the former Auschwitz Nazi death camp on Friday for the first time as chancellor and said admitting Nazi crimes was a key part of Germany's identity that could combat growing anti-Semitism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pensacola Shooter Saudi Air Force Officer; Terrorism Being Investigated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1102076110d04018176b4f7f12017347</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. law enforcement officials were digging into the background of the suspected Florida Naval station shooter Friday, to determine the Saudi Air Force officer's motive and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused of Killing Gambino Mob Boss, He's Presenting Novel Defense...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/accused-of-killing-a-gambino-mob-boss-hes-presenting-a-novel-defense/ar-BBXQdmJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Organizing Effort Powering Mayor Pete's Iowa Surge...</title>
      <link>https://www.motherjones.com/politics/2019/12/inside-the-organizing-effort-thats-powering-pete-buttigiegs-iowa-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;â€œThe messenger matters as much as the message."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More cities banning natural gas in homes, citing climate change...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cities-are-banning-natural-gas-in-new-homes-because-of-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As states and cities set ambitious clean-energy goals, they're moving to eliminate the "cleaner" fossil fuel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finance Bros Taking Over Local Sports Teams...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-12-06/masters-of-the-universe-are-taking-over-your-local-sports-teams</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE WON'T PARTICIPATE IN NADLER HEARINGS...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7765609/White-House-tells-Jerry-Nadler-wont-participate-Mondays-hearing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deciding to steer clear of Judiciary hearings means Trump won't call witnesses, introduce evidence, or make a presentation. Nadler had given the White House a 5:00 p.m. Friday deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy changing how it fights in face of China threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/naval/2019/12/06/with-china-gunning-for-aircraft-carriers-the-us-navy-says-it-must-change-the-way-it-fights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Navy can't afford to throw up its hands when it come to the vulnerability of aircraft carriers, its new top officer says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female Kentucky judge accused of threesomes in courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7763841/Female-judge-Kentucky-accused-using-court-frat-house-threesomes-drinking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family Court Judge Dawn Gentry allegedly used her chambers as a swingers club to facilitate threesomes with former pastor turned guitar player, Stephen Penrose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady's Dad Weighs In QB's Future: 'Up To' Belichick If Son Returns To PATRIOTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-bradys-dad-weighs-in-on-qbs-future-says-its-up-to-bill-if-brady-returns-to-patriots-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady's dad believes that Belichick holds all the cards when it comes to how his son's career will end in Foxboro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:  No Regrets -- Even If This Leads To Reelection...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/archives/allahpundit/2019/12/06/pelosi-ill-no-regrets-impeachment-leads-trump-reelected/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I truly believe that the times have found us to save our democracy."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Seahorse whisperer' builds underwater sanctuary for rare species...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/society/seahorse-whisperer-builds-underwater-sanctuary-for-rare-species-in-long-beach/5736126/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roger Hanson, a 69-year-old retired teacher, drives almost every day from Moreno Valley to Long Beach to study and care for a rare colony of Pacific seahorses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 50 ankle-bracelet violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/weinstein-off-the-grid-dozens-of-times-prosecutors-tell-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A month before the start of Harvey Weinstein’s felony sex crime trial, prosecutors urged a judge Friday to quintuple his cash bond to $5 million, citing more than 50 ankle-bracelet violations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA Spending $1 Billion To House Homeless. It's Failing...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/los-angeles-is-spending-over-1-billion-to-house-the-homeless-its-failing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 2,500 homeless individuals sleep on the streets of the 53-square-block Skid Row area in downtown Los Angeles. "Skid</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
