<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>RED CROSS DECLARES BLOOD CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/589152-red-cross-declares-first-national-blood-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Red Cross announced on Thursday that it was declaring its first-ever national blood crisis in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undersea Cable Connecting Norway With Arctic Satellite Station Severed...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/43828/undersea-cable-connecting-norway-with-arctic-satellite-station-has-been-mysteriously-severed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cables run through a highly strategic stretch of water near where the Barents and Norwegian Sea meet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITED cuts flights as 3,000 workers call out sick...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/11/united-cuts-flights-as-about-3000-workers-call-out-sick-from-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schools close!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/environment-and-nature-new-york-boston-new-york-city-maine-150620f0d2f43f6d487d19b3d3e82a7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The Northeast girded Tuesday for extreme cold that was expected to reach a wind chill value of minus 40 degrees Fahrenheit (minus 40 Celsius) in some northern areas and closed some schools elsewhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Trusting Societies Fare Better During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/trusting-societies-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More trusting societies were able to get the virus under control in a more efficient manner, achieving a faster decline in infections and deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD HOSPITALIZATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/01/11/1071568846/u-s-covid-hospitalizations-hit-new-record-high-raising-risks-for-patients</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are more patients and, in some places, not enough health care workers to go around. Research shows the crowding will impact care and increase mortality for all patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families fall deeper in debt amid rising prices...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/11/amid-rising-prices-us-households-fall-deeper-in-debt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between inflation and ongoing supply chain issues, prices are rising and it's eating away at the average family budget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: Glamping on Wheels Going to Be Even Bigger in '22...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-11/overlanding-aka-glamping-on-wheels-is-going-to-be-even-bigger-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY cases peak?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/11/new-york-may-have-passed-peak-omicron-surge-data-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health data shows clear dips in recent cases, deaths, and hospitalizations across all five boroughs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic could face jail for 'lying on Australia travel form'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/4437831/novak-djokovic-face-jail-lying-australian-travel-form/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NOVAK Djokovic could face jail over claims he lied on his travel forms as bombshell pictures appear to show he travelled before jetting off to Australia. Aussie Border Force officials are investiga…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron May Infect Half Europeans in Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/01/11/world/who-omicron-spread-europe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fast-spreading variant represents a "west-to-east tidal wave sweeping across the region,” said Hans Kluge, the regional director of the WHO for Europe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 million in China now under lockdowns ahead of Olympics...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/china/589133-20-million-in-china-now-under-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China placed a third city on lockdown this week, bringing the number of people in the country confined to their homes to nearly 20 million just weeks before the start of the Olympics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Positioning Helicopters, in Possible Sign of Ukraine Plans...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/10/russia-positioning-helicopters-in-possible-sign-of-ukraine-plans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The number of Russian troops at Ukraine’s border has remained steady in recent weeks, despite U.S. intelligence predictions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil Suits Against Trump Seek Damages for Jan. 6 Attack...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/10/civil-suits-against-trump-seek-damages-for-jan-6-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Members of Congress, police officers and government watchdog groups argued in federal court on Monday that Donald J.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to back filibuster changes to push voting rights bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-joe-biden-georgia-voting-martin-luther-king-jr-dc4544c23622f35fc95d63afe512554d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden will use a speech in Georgia to endorse changing Senate filibuster rules that have stalled voting rights legislation , saying it’s time to choose “democracy over autocracy.” But some civil rights groups won’t be there, in protest of what they say is administration inaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America More Liberal -- But Voting More Republican...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/american-society-more-liberal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average American may be more liberal today when it comes to topics such as gender, sexuality, race, and personal liberty than in the 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Cuba, queueing for hours 'just to be able to eat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-ca/news/world/in-cuba-queueing-for-hours-just-to-be-able-to-eat/ar-AASDUsE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cubans are no strangers to queuing for everything from bread to toothpaste, often standing for hours under a blazing sun with no access to a toilet or drinking water, and always with the fear of leaving empty-handed. It is a daily ordeal Cubans have endured for about 60 years of communist rule, now worsened by the coronavirus pandemic, a steep economic downturn and tightened US sanctions. "I spent almost all night here just to buy something. It...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems eager to fill power vacuum after Pelosi exit...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/589108-democrats-eager-to-fill-power-vacuum-after-pelosi-exit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) isn’t showing her cards, but the longtime Democratic leader has vowed that this year will be her last at the top of the party, auguring a fast-approaching power vacuum that younger lawmakers have been salivating to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CONFUSION IN WHITE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/we-have-gone-backwards-covid-confusion-snarls-biden-white-house-n1287282</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A half dozen former health policy makers, including members of Biden’s transition team, said the Biden administration needs an urgent strategy reset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 34-year-old father tried to walk home in last week's record snowstorm. His body was found three days later...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-34-year-old-father-tried-to-walk-home-in-last-week-s-record-snowstorm-his-body-was-found-three-days-later/ar-AASDTvg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury warns of delayed tax refunds due to 'enormous challenges'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/589037-treasury-warns-of-delayed-tax-refunds-due-to-enormous-challenges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Treasury Department is warning that tax refunds and other services may be delayed this year because of “enormous challenges" including the coronavirus pandemic and previous budget cuts made at the Inte</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC weighs recommending better masks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/cdc-weighs-recommending-better-masks-032518946.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The agency will likely advise people opt for the highly protective N95 or KN95 masks worn by healthcare personnel, if they can do so consistently, the newspaper reported, citing an official close to the deliberations. The CDC guidance is expected to say that if people can "tolerate wearing a KN95 or N95 mask all day, you should," the report said. Last week, CDC Director Rochelle Walenksy told NBC News' "Today" program the Omicron-driven surge in U.S. COVID-19 cases has likely not topped out yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety doors failed in NYC high-rise fire that killed 17...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-new-york-bronx-new-york-city-c8bd4a00e992b6da7380a23e6e7b38e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Investigators sought answers Monday for why safety doors failed to close when fire broke out in a New York high-rise, allowing thick smoke to rise through the tower and kill 17 people, including eight children, in the city's deadliest blaze in more than three decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris faces lockdown-breach claims over garden party...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-london-boris-johnson-3a521263aea5e679029647bd81192ab8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson faced a wave of public and political outrage on Tuesday over allegations that he and his staff flouted coronavirus lockdown rules by holding a garden party in 2020 while Britons were barred by law from mingling outside the home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dosed Rep Positive 2nd Time...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/politics-government/article257197652.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’m feeling OK. This is more mild than the first time. I’m completing quarantine and working from home as I recover,” Rep. Nancy Mace said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope hits out at 'cancel culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/pope-francis-cancel-culture-vatican-holy-see/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trend is ‘invading many circles and public institutions,’ says Catholic Church leader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA orders 'full ground stop' at West Coast airports as NKorea fires missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10389401/FAA-orders-ground-stop-west-coast-airports-North-Korea-fired-suspected-missile.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The stop only lasted for seven minutes, according to officials at San Diego International Airport. A spokesperson for the airport said they got the instruction around 2:30 p.m. pacific time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: SAGET DEATH CAUSE INVESTIGATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/entertainment/bob-saget-cause-death-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An autopsy was completed on Bob Saget Monday, according to the Orange County Medical Examiner in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG HEART IN MAN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pig-heart-transplant-6651614cb9d73bada8eea2ecb6449aef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a medical first, doctors transplanted a pig heart into a patient in a last-ditch effort to save his life and a Maryland hospital said Monday that he's doing well three days after the highly experimental surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA breaks hospitalization record...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-breaks-covid-19-hospitalization-record-omicron-surges-2022-01-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 hospitalizations in the United States reached a record high on Monday, according to a Reuters tally, as a surge in infections caused by the highly contagious Omicron variant strains health systems in several states.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaines' MAGNOLIA pulls show after homeowners allege makeovers ruined homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/tv/celebrity/chip-and-joanna-gaines-magnolia-network-pulls-show-after-homeowners-allege-that-makeovers-ruined-their-houses/ar-AASy3kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ highest since start of pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/covid-19-hospitalizations-in-nj-highest-since-start-of-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Jersey hospitals now have the most coronavirus patients at any point since April 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPD Cops Ignored Robbery in Progress to Play 'POKEMAN GO'...</title>
      <link>https://uproxx.com/edge/pokemon-go-lapd-robbery-officers-fired/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uproxx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pokémon Go is still an incredibly fun game to play, but you should not play that if you are a police officer being called to a robbery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER predicts 'annual shots'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2022/01/10/covid-omicron-variant-live-updates/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 5,400 K-12 schools stopped in-person instruction at some point during the first week of January, according to one tracker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge charged with failing to pay taxes on cash she earned officiating weddings...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/bad-judgment-new-orleans-judge-charged-with-allegedly-failing-to-pay-taxes-on-cash-she-earned-officiating-weddings-11641842702</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prosecutors say Ernestine Anderson-Trahan officiated hundreds of weddings for cash fees of $80 and up, but never disclosed the income to the IRS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate hospitals ask sick staff to return...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/10/doctors-covid-staff-shortage-526842</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While most health workers are vaccinated, many are still falling sick, exacerbating a staff shortage as more Americans seek hospital care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Vice Chair out following scrutiny over pandemic trades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/fed-vice-chair-clarida-to-step-down-early-following-scrutiny-over-his-trades-during-pandemic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Vice Chairman Richard Clarida said Monday he will be leaving his post with just a few weeks left on his term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Off to Worst Start Since Dawn of Crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/bitcoin-is-off-to-its-worst-annual-start-since-the-dawn-of-crypto-1.1705389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin dipped below US$40,000 for the first time since September, putting it on pace for its worst start to a year since the earliest days of the digital alternative to money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems NOT shutting things down this time...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2022/01/09/omicron-is-surging-and-democrats-arent-shutting-things-down-this-time-1404752</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From New York to California, Democratic mayors and governors are fighting to keep schools and businesses open with an urgency they haven’t flexed before in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26th House Democrat NOT Running for Reelection...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/589046-rep-perlmutter-says-he-wont-seek-reelection-in-november</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden imposing curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/omicron-variant-coronavirus-news-01-10-22/h_2e186532ee244a0ad2ee07854a540d0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A US federal vaccine mandate goes into effect today for all businesses with 100 employees or more as coronavirus cases continue to increase across the country. Follow here for the latest news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimon sees best economic growth in decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/jamie-dimon-sees-the-best-economic-growth-in-decades-more-than-4-fed-rate-hikes-this-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JPMorgan is the biggest U.S. bank by assets and has relationships with half of U.S. households.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Schools Closing; Power Grid Threatened...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-boston-massachusetts-weather-6fe725adbda1ef6adaf9f4e941e23975</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The New England states are bracing for extreme cold that is already closing some schools and threatening the power grid this week. Boston, the state's largest public school district, announced Monday that schools will not open Tuesday because of expected extremely cold temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci's NIH Paid $205K To Study Trans Monkeys...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/biden-administration/faucis-nih-division-paid-205k-for-researchers-to-study-transgender-monkeys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci's division of the National Institutes of Health paid over $200,000 during the coronavirus pandemic for researchers to study why transgender women have high rates of HIV by injecting male monkeys with female hormones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In baseball first, YANKEES name woman to manage minor league team...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/baseball-first-new-york-yankees-name-woman-manage-minor-league-team-rcna11603</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Yankees are promoting Rachel Balkovec to manager of the Low A Tampa Tarpons, making her the first woman to skipper a team affiliated with Major League Baseball, according to two people familiar with the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike in autoimmune diseases blamed on fast food...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/spike-in-autoimmune-diseases-blamed-on-fast-food-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asia and the Middle East have seen the biggest upswing in inflammatory bowel disease — these regions have experienced a boom of the fast food industry during that time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Durst, real estate heir and convicted killer, dead at 78...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/nyc-real-estate-heir-robert-durst-dead-at-78/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Durst, the bizarre New York real estate scion and long suspected serial killer, has died. He was 78.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Western troops sick in Wuhan months before Covid outbreak officially began...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4427364/western-troops-ill-wuhan-months-before-covid-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WESTERN troops allegedly fell ill with a mystery illness after attending the World Military Games in Wuhan shortly before the Covid outbreak officially began. A long-serving Canadian officer was am…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagine another Civil War, but this time in every state...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/10/1071082955/imagine-another-american-civil-war-but-this-time-in-every-state</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If America has another civil war, it is more likely to be a war within the states than between them. Citizens of any state of any size, red or blue, may not have to go far to find a fight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge prehistoric 'sea dragon' fossil discovered in reservoir...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/prehistoric-sea-dragon-ichthyosaur-fossil-discovered-uk-reservoir-rcna11565</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The skeleton of an extinct prehistoric reptile predator, known as a sea dragon, is the largest and most complete ever discovered in the U.K., researchers said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cable Cabinet: Texts reveal influence of hosts on previous White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-s-cable-cabinet-new-texts-reveal-the-influence-of-fox-hosts-on-previous-white-house/ar-AASADdl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petition for $2,000 monthly stimulus checks has 3 million signatures...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/petition-for-2000-stimulus-checks-reaches-3-million-signatures.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurant owner Stephanie Bonin started a petition for monthly payments in March 2020. Nearly two years later, the cause still resonates with many Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Deadliest NYC blaze in 30 years tears through Bronx building, 17 killed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/10/bronx-fires-death-toll-revised-down-to-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Eric Adams said during a press briefing Monday that the toll is actually currently 17, with eight children and nine adults dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUND BY HOUSEKEEPING AFTER MISSING CHECKOUT</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/4433230/bob-saget-found-dead-ritz-carlton-orlando/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOB Saget was reportedly found dead by hotel housekeeping on Sunday afternoon after he failed to checkout on time. The iconic actor and comic was found dead at the Ritz Carlton in Orlando, Flo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE CHILL MAP...</title>
      <link>http://hp2.wright-weather.com/icons/us_chill.gif</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hp2.wright-weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coldest air in years coming to USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/weather/coldest-air-three-years-coming-parts-country-rcna11618</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monday started the work week with 15 million people under wind chill alerts stretching from the Northern Plains and Upper Midwest into the interior Northeast</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More commentary, less news?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/media/jesse-watters-fox-7pm-host/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesse Watters, the right-wing talk show host who throughout his career has courted controversy with incendiary commentary, will be Fox's new 7 p.m. host, the network announced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duluth -18&amp;#8457;...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/coldest-air-of-the-season-to-send-midwest-northeast-into-deep-freeze/1122650</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bitter cold is expected to keep temperatures in the teens and single digits in spots, with one location not expected to climb above zero on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson to launch 'Living with Covid' plan in UK...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/politics/what-living-covid-boris-johnson-25900277</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Boris Johnson is reportedly drawing up plans for a "living with Covid" strategy which aim to avoid any long-term restrictions in England from March this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 'Deltacron' likely result of lab error...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/10/deltacron-variant-prompts-doubts-among-experts-as-possible-lab-error.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global experts are casting doubts over reports of a new possible Covid strain appearing to combine both the delta and omicron variants and dubbed "deltacron."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'IDOL' star Aiken will run for NC seat in Congress...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/politics-government/election/article257130772.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former “American Idol” star and Raleigh native declared a run for North Carolina’s 6th Congressional District.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jesse Watters named permanent host of 7pm hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/jesse-watters-named-permanent-host-of-7-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jesse Watters has been named the permanent host of the 7 p.m. ET timeslot on Fox News Channel with a new hour-long program "Jesse Watters Primetime," FOX News Media CEO Suzanne Scott announced on Monday.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
