<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Mag 3.9 quake rattles SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/local-news/magnitude-3-9-earthquake-rattles-socal-strikes-near-maywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 3.9 magnitude earthquake shook parts of Southern California early Sunday. The quake was centered near the Los Angeles County community of Maywood. Check back for updates on this developing story.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELTICS support for Enes Kanter after Beijing criticisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nba/celtics-support-enes-kanter-amid-his-stance-for-tibet-and-against-chinese-government/ar-AAPQEUW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran center on Wednesday posted a video on his social media platforms in which he blasted the Chinese government for its policies regarding Tibet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan hurtling toward collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/24/asia/afghanistan-collapse-sweden-pakistan-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Afghanistan will shortly collapse into chaos unless the international community acts rapidly, Swedish and Pakistani ministers warned on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tahoe braces for 100 mph winds, 3 feet of snow...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weather/article/atmospheric-river-Tahoe-Sierra-California-2021-16558088.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snow levels in the Tahoe Basin could drop as low as 6,000 feet on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgruntled employee sentenced to 6 months for releasing rats in workplace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-disgruntled-employee-has-been-sentenced-to-6-months-in-prison-for-releasing-rats-at-his-workplace/ar-AAPTDB9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John O'Neill, a 61-year-old man from Cork, in Ireland, released two live rats in a council building after an alleged dispute with his manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci under fire after 'dogs were locked in cages to be eaten ALIVE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3920949/fauci-puppy-experiments-beagles-locked-in-cage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DR Anthony Fauci is under fire for allegedly funding experiments where beagle puppies were locked in cages with hungry sandflies that would eat them alive. The non-profit organization White Coat Wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB stripped Atlanta All-Star Game. Can't stop BRAVES playing in World Series...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/mlb/columnist/bob-nightengale/2021/10/23/braves-defeat-dodgers-return-world-series/6161051001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Braves defeated the defending World Series champion Dodgers to win their first pennant in 22 years. They will face the Astros in the Fall Classic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor's Training Video Raises More Eyebrows...</title>
      <link>https://popculture.com/movies/news/alec-baldwin-rust-co-star-jensen-ackles-gun-training-video-raises-eyebrows-deadly-accident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;popculture.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details on the tragic accidental shooting on the set of Rust continue to spill out and expand the [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan shaken by 6.5 mag quake...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/taiwan-earthquakes-taipei-c43ff75eec967f3065b1476c9c0798b2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — An earthquake shook Taiwan's capital, Taipei, on Sunday and caused falling rocks that injured a woman and damaged a car. No deaths were reported. The 6.5-magnitude quake struck at 1:11 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sexually transmitted infections at 'highest numbers' in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/oct/24/us-sti-rates-covid-sexually-transmitted-infections-funding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebound of sexually-transmitted infections the result of sluggish testing, changing behaviors and persistent issues with education</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German police stop far-right vigilantes patrolling Polish border...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/german-police-stop-far-right-vigilantes-patrolling-polish-border-2021-10-24/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police said on Sunday they had stopped more than 50 far-right vigilantes armed with pepper spray, a bayonet, a machete and batons who were trying to patrol the Polish border to stop migrants from entering the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the jaw-clenching world of cricket fighting...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/10/23/1045988512/china-cricket-fighting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's cricket fighting season in China, so NPR went ringside to learn about the centuries-old sport. Turns out, the bugs are really high maintenance, big money's involved and big mandibles matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negligent manslaughter?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/10/23/alec-baldwin-could-face-liability-in-shooting-of-halyna-hutchins-legal-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alec Baldwin, who fired a prop gun Thursday that accidentally killed the film’s director of photography Halyna Hutchins, could face legal repercussions for the shooting, legal experts told Th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding comfort, and home, in 64 square feet...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/finding-comfort-and-a-home-in-64-square-feet/ar-AAPTqwR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A photographer documents the lives of those who live in L.A.'s tiny home villages, which aim to offer a first step out of homelessness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tragic End of Scientology's Biggest Pop Star...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bloody-tragic-end-scientology-biggest-083833792.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by The Daily Beast / Photos GettyOn April 22, the day before he died, Jakub Stepniak recorded a phone message for one of his doctors.He is barely audible in it. He thanks his doctor for calling him and, barely above a whisper, says that he is there with his uncle, and that “the inflammation is so bad.” He then says something about trying to reach another doctor. And he finishes the message with an ominous final utterance: “I don’t know if I’ll survive to the morning.”The next</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia's most wanted drug lord captured in jungle raid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/colombia-s-most-wanted-drug-lord-captured-jungle-raid-n1282224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities said U.S. and U.K. intelligence led more than 500 soldiers and members of Colombia’s special forces to Dairo Antonio Úsuga hideout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  People with covid jab less likely to die of other causes...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/people-vaccinated-against-covid-19-less-likely-to-die-of-other-causes-study-682908</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Those who received the Pfizer-BioNTech, Moderna or J&amp;J vaccines are less likely to die from non-COVID-related causes, a CDC study found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington, District of Cats: First city to count felines...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211024-washington-district-of-cats-us-capital-first-city-to-count-its-felines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, District of Cats: US capital first city to count its felines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of millions of filthy, used medical gloves imported into USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/10/24/health/medical-gloves-us-thailand-investigation-cmd-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trash bags stuffed full of used medical gloves, some visibly soiled, some even blood-stained, litter the floor of a warehouse on the outskirts of Bangkok.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag 6.2 quake hits Taiwan... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/magnitude-6-2-quake-hits-061214387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 6.2 earthquake was reported Saturday evening at 10:11 p.m. Pacific time 13 miles from Yilan, Taiwan, according to the U.S. Geological Survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Wild Homophobic Rant Against Lil Nas X...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2021/10/23/boosie-calls-lil-nas-x-homophobic-rant-slur-new-song-joke/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lil Nas X was told to kill himself by Boosie Badazz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors in Detroit uncover massive money-laundering operation between USA, Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/us/2021-10-23/money-laundering-operation-us-dubai-3347270.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In this California county, one town has no water. Another has enough to share...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/In-this-California-county-one-town-has-no-water-16557412.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT BRAGG, Calif. - This town took a big step toward making fresh water along the rocky,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Baldwin pulled trigger, two workers handled gun...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/before-alec-baldwin-pulled-the-trigger-two-film-set-workers-handled-gun-on-set/ar-AAPQUKK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An assistant director grabbed one of three prop guns from a rolling cart, and gave it to the actor, shouting it was a “cold gun," or not loaded, according to a warrant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks 'Phony Culture Wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/obama-attacks-gop-candidate-e2-80-99s-e2-80-98phony-culture-wars-e2-80-99-in-virginia/ar-AAPSmKk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama waded into Virgina’s gubernatorial race, criticizing Republican candidate Glenn Youngkin for supporting “phony, trumped-up culture wars” in his bid to flip the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New migrant caravan breaks through police blockade in Mexico, heads north...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/americas/20211023-new-migrant-caravan-breaks-through-police-blockade-in-mexico-heads-north</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several thousand migrants from Haiti, South America and Central America set off from southern Mexico headed north on Saturday, clashing with law enforcement trying to hold the caravan back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas CBD, vape shops take legal action after delta-8 THC deemed illegal by state...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/politics/2021/10/22/texas-cbd-vape-shops-take-legal-action-after-delta-8-thc-deemed-illegal-by-state/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas CBD and vape shops are searching for answers, and some have filed temporary restraining orders against the state after they say health officials...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama gives fiery speech for McAuliffe: 'Don't sit this one out'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/578163-obama-gives-fiery-speech-for-mcauliffe-dont-sit-this-one-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sheikh, the Businessman and Hacking Mystery on 3 Continents...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/23/the-sheikh-the-businessman-and-a-hacking-mystery-on-3-continents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For decades, Farhad Azima navigated the shadowlands where business blends with intrigue and the limits of the law. He popped</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inadvertent Discharges...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/10/23/inadvertent-gun-discharges-occurred-on-alec-baldwin-film-before-fatal-shooting-crew-members-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE — There were at least two accidental gun discharges on the set of an Alec Baldwin movie being filmed</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
