<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Submarine sent to find source of MYSTERY sonar noise off US coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/713315/noaa-submarine-shipwrecks-mysterious-sonar-noise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot brothel opens 24 hours-a-day as demand during World Cup SKYROCKETS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/712680/sex-doll-brothel-russia-world-cup-moscow-lumidolls-fans-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Abolish ICE' becomes rallying call... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/abolish-ice-call-democrats-left-flank-195227858--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — Several prominent Democrats who are mulling a bid for the White House in 2020 sought to bolster their progressive credentials this week by calling for major changes to immigration enforcement, with some pressing for the outright abolition of the federal government's chief immigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic elections marred by vote-buying and violence...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-mexico-election-20180701-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Mexico's presidential election approaches, the ruling party is accused of using government institutions to try sway the results. Opposition parties warn of possible fraud on election day. And vote-buying has been rampant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President defends 'brave' ICE agents...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/30/trump-defends-brave-ice-agents-as-dems-call-to-abolish-agency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As more Democrats join the parade of liberal pols calling for the end of the federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) agency, President Trump is pushing back. “To the great and brave men a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Does Deep Dive on High Court Finalists Before July 9 Pick...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-29/trump-has-narrowed-supreme-court-list-will-reveal-pick-july-9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump spent Saturday engaged in a deep dive into the backgrounds of the top prospects to fill an opening on the U.S. Supreme Court but hasn’t begun interviews with the finalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters responds to death threats: 'You better shoot straight'...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/395016-maxine-waters-responds-to-serious-death-threats-you-better-shoot-straight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN: Left needs to face reality: Trump is winning...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/30/the-left-needs-to-face-reality-trump-is-winning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To understand the madness gripping American leftists, try to see the world through their eyes. Presto, you’re now part of the raging resistance. Like the Palestinians who mark Israel’s birth as the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicaragua's crisis deals crushing blow to businesses large and small...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nicaraguas-crisis-deals-crushing-blow-businesses-large-small-012929256.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With hotels, restaurants, bars, stores, workshops and even tortilla sellers driven out of business or struggling to survive, and with thousands of people left jobless, the turbulent political crisis sundering Nicaragua has taken a broader toll, plunging its economy into a tailspin. Business closings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO ON THE BRINK: Leftist favorite as Mexico heads to polls...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/leftist-amlo-favorite-mexico-heads-polls-013217052.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed up with corruption and violence, Mexicans will elect their next president Sunday, deciding whether to believe in the change promised by the anti-establishment leftist Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador, the heavy favorite. Leading by more than 20 points in the polls, the sharp-tongued, silver-haired politician</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbs for Bezos but Bill Gates largely admired in Seattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/barbs-bezos-bill-gates-largely-164452048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — The Seattle region is home to America's two richest men, but their local legacies to date represent two very different eras for the city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winner to face tough rival: World Cup...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/sports/soccer/la-sp-world-cup-mexico-20180630-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Mexico had taken care of business in its final group-stage game with Sweden, it would be facing Switzerland in the round of 16 this week, safely tucked in the softer side of the World Cup bracket alongside Russia, Denmark and Colombia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian state cuts internet after three new lynchings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/indian-state-cuts-internet-three-lynchings-085617385.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in northeastern India have cut internet access after crazed mobs beat three people to death in lynchings sparked by rumours spread on smartphones, officials said Friday. "The administration has decided to cut off the internet and mobile messaging services for next 48 hours... to stop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Flying brain' blasts off on cargo ship toward space station...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/flying-brain-blasts-off-cargo-ship-toward-space-143500507.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ball-shaped artificial intelligence robot nicknamed the "flying brain" because it is trained to follow and interact with a German astronaut blasted off Friday toward the International Space Station aboard SpaceX's Dragon cargo ship. A spare hand for the station's robotic arm, an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Nile Virus found in mosquitoes in Ohio, Washington...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/06/29/west-nile-virus-found-mosquitoes-ohio-washington/745103002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mosquitoes trapped in Ohio and Washington tested positive for West Nile Virus, health officials said. This is the first batch of mosquitoes to test positive for West Nile Virus this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman posted revenge tweets marking enemies...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6655952/maryland-shooting-annapolis-capital-gazette-gunman-jarrod-ramos-sacrifice-warning-twitter/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE newsroom massacre gunman posted revenge tweets marking enemies with chilling sacrifice symbols before killing five journalists yesterday afternoon. Jarrod W. Ramos was today charged with five c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA: 'You are right to be concerned'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/29/barack-obama-advice-to-democrats-685940</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first public comments in months, the former president talks about anger, regrets – and what the Republicans are doing right.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada slaps retaliatory tariffs on USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/06/29/canada-makes-retaliatory-tariffs-official-we-will-not-back-down.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada’s foreign minister announced Friday that Ottawa plans to impose about $12.6 billion worth of retaliatory tariffs on U.S. goods on July 1, joining other major U.S. allies striking back in the escalating trade dispute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freaked Out Americans Desperately Seek to Escape the News...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/2018/06/29/freaked-out-americans-desperately-seek-to-escape-the-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“State of the nation” trumps money and work to be America’s primary source of stress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD HEAT CHICAGO, DC, NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-06-29/u-s-girds-for-heat-wave-as-new-york-cooling-demand-set-to-spike</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temperatures will soar across much of the U.S. the next few days, approaching 100 degrees Fahrenheit (38 Celsius) from Chicago to New York as the summer’s first heat wave takes hold and spurs electricity demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Trump Counter Soaring Gasoline Prices?</title>
      <link>https://oilprice.com/Energy/Energy-General/Can-Trump-Counter-Soaring-Gasoline-Prices.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;oilprice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. SPR has traditionally been considered a key part of the country’s national security policy, but as oil production booms in the U.S. it may soon be used as a political tool – with the first example of this being in November</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS WERE WARNED...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/06/29/accused-newsroom-shooters-stalking-victim-i-warned-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman who claimed that the Capital Gazette shooting suspect had stalked, harassed and sued her warned a former police official that “he will be your next mass shooter,” according to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILE FRY CITY: DENVER'S HOTTEST DAY!</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/heat-record-denver-hot-xcel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Xcel Energy says that they anticipate Thursday to be the highest-usage day of 2018. Denver broke the heat record which was previously at 99 degrees by reaching 100 degrees at 11:31 a.m. Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE BANK investors unshaken by stress test failure...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/shares-deutsche-bank-edge-higher-u-stress-test-070829388--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deutsche Bank investors took a largely long view on its failure in this year's U.S. stress tests, with its shares recovering on Friday from a record low hit earlier this week. The Fed last year classified Deutsche Bank's U.S. unit as troubled and Deutsche Bank's shares had been falling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's rulers face discontent as U.S. pressure mounts...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/irans-rulers-face-discontent-u-pressure-mounts-140111749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Parisa Hafezi ANKARA (Reuters) - Mounting pressure from the Trump administration combined with discontent among many Iranians at the state of the economy are rattling the Islamic Republic, with little sign that its leaders have the answers, officials and analysts say. Three days of protests broke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barricaded exit doors; Pre-planned attack...</title>
      <link>http://www.capitalgazette.com/news/for_the_record/bs-md-ramos-charges-20180629-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 38-year-old Laurel man accused of gunning down five employees of The Capital on Thursday swore a “legal oath” in court documents to kill a writer for the Annapolis newspaper. Yet he legally purchased the pump-action shotgun he allegedly used in the rampage, authorities said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-establishment fervor grips Dems...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/homenews/house/394690-anti-establishment-fervor-grips-dems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The public debate for Democrats has centered around whether the party is drifting to the left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has ET Gone Home? UFO Sightings Slump...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-06-29/has-et-gone-home-ufo-sightings-slump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Merkel draws up new measures to tackle migration...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/embattled-merkel-draws-measures-tackle-migration-145629247.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel has drawn up a raft of measures to tighten controls on the influx of migrants, according to a document submitted to her coalition partners Saturday as she battles for political survival. Merkel has also secured deals with 14 EU member states to take back from Germany</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comedian gets visit from Secret Service after hoax calling Trump on Air Force One...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/comedian-gets-visit-from-secret-service-after-hoax-calling-trump-on-air-force-one</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A comedian who posed as Sen. Bob Menendez, D-N.J., and spoke with President Trump over the phone about a number of hot topics, claims he got a visit from Secret Service following the exchange.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Saudi king agrees to raise oil production...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-saudi-trump-oil/trump-says-saudi-king-agreed-to-raise-oil-production-up-to-2-million-barrels-idUSKBN1JQ0ES</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump said in a tweet on Saturday that Saudi Arabia's King Salman had agreed to his request to increase oil production "maybe up to 2,000,000 barrels" to offset a decline in supplies from Iran and Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani says end is near for Iran's rulers...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-nuclear-opposition-giuliani/trump-ally-giuliani-says-end-is-near-for-irans-rulers-idUSKBN1JQ0PA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. President Donald Trump will suffocate Iran's "dictatorial ayatollahs", his close ally Rudy Giuliani said on Saturday, suggesting his move to re-impose sanctions was aimed squarely at regime change.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND SCORCHER...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/most-intense-heat-to-peak-ahead-of-july-4th-in-northeastern-us/70005343</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Defends NETFLIX Film From Accusations of Child Pornography...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/netflix-desire-film-child-pornography-director-statement-1202862741/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Director Diego Kaplan has released a statement defending his erotic thriller film “Desire” after a conservative commentator and others online accused it of containing child pornography.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration protests nationwide...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5903915/Trump-praises-brave-men-women-ICE-ahead-mass-protests-immigration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a pair of tweets at around 7am, the president said he had 'watched' ICE 'liberate' entire towns from gangs and said they were responsible for 'eradicating the worst criminal elements'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: 1 in 5 adults use pot, many report driving high...</title>
      <link>http://www.bostonherald.com/news/local_coverage/2018/06/study_about_1_in_5_adults_use_pot_many_report_driving_high</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON — About one in three Massachusetts residents who use marijuana say they have driven while under the influence of the drug.That&amp;#39;s among the findings of a statewide study of marijuana use released Friday by the Department of Public Health.In all, about 21 percent of those surveyed by the agency said they had used marijuana within the last 30 days, with the highest proportion of users between ages 18 and 25.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant YELP page flooded with one star reviews after boots Trump supporter...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/394989-yelp-reviewers-give-canadian-restaurant-one-star-reviews-after-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reviewers flooded the Yelp page of a Canadian restaurant with one-star reviews after a manager was fired for kicking out a man wearing a “Make America Great Again” hat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAL-like robot to help astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hal-robot-help-astronaut-space-odyssey-080402803--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Joey Roulette CAPE CANAVERAL, Fla. (Reuters) - A science fiction-inspired robot hardwired to assist astronauts launched from Florida early Friday to become the first personal, artificial intelligence-powered companion in space.  The Crew Interactive Mobile Companion, or CIMON, is an English-speaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the virus hunters: Scientists track diseases X, Y and Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/06/29/scientists-hunt-diseases-x-y-z/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the pandemic threat currently keeping scientists awake at night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's biggest sex festival: 700 swingers meet in field...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/713065/swingfields-sex-festival-2018-swingers-orgy-malvern-gloucestershire-uk-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDS:  Risks to Lake Mead, Colorado River intensifying greatly...</title>
      <link>https://tucson.com/news/local/risks-to-lake-mead-colorado-river-intensifying-greatly-federal-officials/article_ed5a3146-29fb-59ba-ab6b-a65d34ba258b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tucson.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depending on what assumptions are made in its computer models, the risks of catastrophically low levels at Mead by 2026 have jumped three to six times since 2007, Bureau of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Man Charged With WMDs In Connection To Mysterious PA Explosions...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/06/28/sources-authorities-investigating-multiple-locations-in-bucks-county-in-connection-to-mysterious-explosions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say more than 20 explosions during the early-morning hours are the reason for the booms happening in Bucks and Lehigh Counties since April 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Pelosi brain freezes; Trips over 'soy beans,' asks reporter to 'repoot' question...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/whats-wrong-with-nancy-pelosi-trips-over-soy-beans-asks-reporter-to-repoot-question/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What is wrong with Nancy Pelosi? As the noose seems to be tightening on her prospects to return to party power after the November elections, the House Minority Leader stumbled over words, suffered brain freezes and stared at reporters during a Thursday press conference. ﻿ “Last week, soy bean futures hit a nine-year low,” Pelosi …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'He'll be next mass shooter'...</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-5899859/Woman-stalked-Annapolis-shooter-say-warned-police-5-years-ago-mass-shooter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annapolis shooter Jarrod W. Ramos, 38, had been flagged up to police as 'the next mass shooter' by a woman he obsessively stalked to the point where she had to change her name and flee the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  5 SHOT DEAD AT NEWSPAPER...</title>
      <link>http://www.capitalgazette.com/bs-md-gazette-shooting-20180628-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.capitalgazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Journalists dove under their desks and pleaded for help on social media. One described the scene a “war zone.” Another said he jumped over a dead colleague and fled for his life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration protests expected nationwide...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/latino/394782-protests-against-trump-immigration-policy-expected-nationwide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protesters are expected to demonstrate nationwide on Saturday against President Trump’s immigration policies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation indicator hits 6-year high...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/key-us-inflation-indicator-hits-6-high-144543815.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key measure of US inflation hit a six-year high in May, matching the central bank's target in another sign price pressures are finally rising, the government reported Friday. The long-awaited rise in the Personal Consumption Expenditures price index, the Federal Reserve's preferred inflation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD HEAT CHICAGO, DC, NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/heat-wave-scorches-u-midwest-east-072547664.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Brendan O'Brien MILWAUKEE (Reuters) - A blistering heat wave will sweep the U.S. Midwest and East on Saturday and Sunday, when temperatures and humidity levels are expected to reach well above normal. Tens of millions of Americans will be under heat warnings, watches and advisories as temperatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The socialist machine behind Cortez upset win...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democratic-socialists-america-show-muscle-new-york-congressional-upset-211526095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez will be the first DSA member in Congress this century, but she isn’t the first candidate to score a dramatic upset with the help of the left-wing organization. And if they have their way, she won’t be the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Pollution plays significant role in diabetes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/air-pollution-plays-significant-role-diabetes-study-055031393.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Air pollution caused one in seven new cases of diabetes in 2016, according to a US study, which found even low levels raised the chances of developing the chronic disease. Diabetes has primarily been associated with lifestyle factors like diet and a sedentary lifestyle, but research by the Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Elites Recreate Burning Man Inside Living Rooms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/tech-elites-recreate-burning-man-inside-their-living-rooms/17665087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To Chad Mureta, a Silicon Valley app guru, the intimate salons of Jess Magic, a New Age troubadour, are “like drugs, without taking anything.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDONISTAN: Khan called 'jihadist' by Tommy Robinson supporters...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6658524/shocking-moment-london-mayor-sadiq-khan-is-heckled-with-vile-abuse-by-tommy-robinson-supporters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SADIQ Khan has been heckled with vile abuse and called a “jihadist” by far-right activists at a speech. During a debate last night supporters of Tommy Robinson caused chaos, shouting &amp;#…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It started with shoes, then water. Now TSA wants snacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/it-started-with-your-shoes-then-your-water-now-the-tsa-wants-your-snacks-1.535518</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers at airports across the country are reporting that increasingly TSA agents are instructing them to remove their snacks and other food items from their carry-ons and place them in those ubiquitous plastic bins for separate screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP may have led FBI to Manafort storage locker...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/06/29/paul-manafort-storage-locker-associated-press-687776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The April 2017 meeting between AP reporters and officials from the Justice Department and the FBI has been the subject of inquiries from congressional Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's oldest veteran, 112, robbed of savings, identity...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/texas/2018/06/29/112-year-old-austin-resident-oldest-living-veteran-robbed-savings-identity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone is impersonating the oldest man in America.Family members of Richard Overton, the 112-year-old World War II veteran who lives in Austin,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sends carrier to Atlantic because of increased Russian sub activity...</title>
      <link>https://news.usni.org/2018/06/29/carrier-uss-harry-s-truman-operating-in-the-atlantic-as-russian-submarine-activity-is-on-the-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.usni.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The aircraft carrier USS Harry S. Truman (CVN-75) has left the Mediterranean Sea and is now operating in the Atlantic Ocean, a defense official confirmed to USNI News. This week the carrier, the embarked Carrier Air Wing 1 and some of its escorts passed through the Strait of Gibraltar into the Atlantic after spending several days in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Man Takes Truck On Destructive Joyride Through WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/06/29/truck-crashes-into-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Witnesses allege that it appeared the driver was purposely confronting a woman as she exited the store with another patron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration protests expected nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/69ceb617e2c241d29dd123cde6c40ae7/Protests-planned-nationwide-over-Trump-immigration-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Liberal activists, parents and first-time protesters motivated by accounts of children separated from their parents at the U.S.-Mexico border plan to rally i</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOMACH SPIES: Swallowable 'FitBit' transmits data from gut...</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/speedreads/782276/fitbit-stomach-charges-itself-using-organs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIT wants to help you listen to your stomach. No, it won't project the grumbles you get before your lunch break. Instead, this team of scientists has created a "FitBit for your stomach" to monitor your gastrointestinal system, lead researcher Canan Dagdeviren tells Stat. These so-called "conformable decoders" are packaged inside a pill and swallowed by a patient, Stat reports. The pill dissolves, and an embedded device latches to the stomach lining. It can then start transmitting messages, revealing how your stomach behaves when you're stressed, eating, or sleeping. The device powers itself on heartbeats and other organ movements using a form of electrical energy Pierre Curie first discovered in the 1800s. And since it conforms to the stomach wall, the decoder can likely stay in the body indefinitely, Dagdeviren told Stat. Eventually, it could be used to diagnose gastrointestinal issues. Watch a video explaining the device below, and read more about it at Stat. Kathryn Krawczyk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indigenous spurn vote with blockades, bulldozers...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180630120000-8illo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-ELECTION/DEMOCRACY (PIX,TV):Indigenous Mexicans spurn presidential vote with blockades, bulldozers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Chair: Obama Still 'Real President'...</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/2018/06/29/tom-perez-obama-president/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nope nope nope</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French nudists get cheeky with theme park and museum outings...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-nudists-cheeky-theme-park-museum-outings-045358236.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a nude yoga class in a Paris park and a "no clothes day" at the city's trendiest art museum, hundreds of naturists are due to descend on a theme park near the French capital Sunday for a spot of trampolining. France may be the world's top destination for naturist tourism -- with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL MOORE: We Have to 'Put Our Bodies on the Line'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/michael-moore-we-have-to-put-our-bodies-on-the-line-to-stop-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Trump is not going to leave,’ Moore predicted to Stephen Colbert, urging Democrats to do everything they can to get him out.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
