<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO: GOOD COVID NEWS THREATENS AGENDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/newsletters/playbook-pm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the U.S. and Iran agree to indirect talks next week in a possible breakthrough.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman gives birth to 'super twins' conceived 3 weeks apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/super-twins-superfetation-three-weeks-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Roberts said when she found out she was pregnant with a second baby, she was shocked. "It was a good job I was laying on the couch or I would have fainted on the floor," she said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Friend has been singing to the feds'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9430921/Matt-Gaetzs-arrest-imminent-sources-say-Joel-Greenberg-singing-feds.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep Matt Gaetz is expected to be indicted within the next few weeks as sources say former Florida official and friend Joel Greenberg has been 'singing to the feds' in the investigation against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB All-Star Game moved from Atlanta after voting law...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/sports/atlanta-braves/mlb-will-move-all-star-game-out-of-atlanta/TCUEJPUPZZD2RCO3DY5OZH62OU/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major League Baseball’s All-Star Game, a marquee event that had been scheduled for Truist Park in July, will be moved out of Georgia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerable Dems fret after getting shock: AOC campaign cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/02/alexandria-ocasio-cortez-campaign-contributions-478943</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ocasio-Cortez's largesse — and an oversight at the campaign headquarters — has raised awkward questions among her colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insider-trading indictment shows ties to BLOOMBERG scoops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cjr.org/business_of_news/an-insider-trading-indictment-shows-ties-to-bloomberg-news-scoops.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cjr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more than six months, federal prosecutors say, a New York man used inside information to make illegal profits in the stock market—and a core element of his alleged scheme was his interaction with Bloomberg News, which published several stories shortly after the trader arranged to make significant purchases of the companies’ shares. Last month, […]&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elite Public School Changes Admissions To Help Whites, Hurt Asians...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/04/02/thomas-jefferson-asian-admissions-plf-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the name of helping racial minorities, officials are adopting a plan that would boost whites at the expense of Asian Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After year of 'hibernation,' cities wake up...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/after-year-of-coronavirus-hibernation-israels-cities-wake-up-663884</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATIONAL AFFAIRS: “When the shuk is full, the heart is full,” a vendor in Mahaneh Yehuda told a television reporter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40% of adults dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/about-40-percent-of-adults-in-the-united-states-have-received-one-dose-of-a-covid-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;America is hitting a milestone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christians mark Good Friday amid lingering virus woes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/christians-good-friday-coronavirus-93d314d71d1b64ee936c5727c4c2c76b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Christians in the Holy Land are marking Good Friday this year amid signs the coronavirus crisis is winding down, with religious sites open to limited numbers of faithful but none...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deer crashes through school bus, lands on sleeping student!</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/wild-video-shows-deer-crashing-through-school-bus-landing-sleeping-n1262896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“He’s laying there asleep and the deer comes in, lays on top of him and rolls off onto the floor,” a Virginia school official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonic origins aside, checks please evangelical critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/demonic-origins-aside-checks-please-biden-s-evangelical-critics/article_527e4235-367d-51cd-b160-9a940b0087e9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evangelical Christians and small-government activists, among the fiercest critics of President Joe Biden and the Democratic Congress, are finding solace in $1,400 stimulus checks that some are sharing with churches</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting a prescription to die remains tricky even as aid-in-dying bills gain momentum...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/montana-medical-aid-in-dying-legal-gray-zone-reviving-legislation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Access to physician-assisted death is expanding across the U.S., but the procedure remains in Montana’s legal gray zone more than a decade after the state Supreme Court ruled physicians could use a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPER STRAIN FEARS ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2627827/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torches 'Looneyville' FOXNEWS and 'nut' hosts...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/john-boehner-spills-on-shocking-meeting-with-roger-ailes-to-try-to-put-a-leash-on-fox-news-hosts-like-nut-sean-hannity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former House Speaker John Boehner did not hold former Fox News founder Roger Ailes, or current prime time host Sean Hannity, in the highest esteem. Politico has just published an excerpt adapted from his book On the House, to be published by St. Martin’s Press on April 13, 2021, in which Boehner calls out the […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of new witnesses to testify at Netanyahu trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/politics-and-diplomacy/hundreds-of-new-witnesses-to-testify-at-netanyahus-trial-663890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu’s trial hears witnesses, and the public will hear what the cases are about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government Grew by 136,000 Workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/national/terence-p-jeffrey/government-grew-136000-workers-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal, state and local governments in the United States increased their employment by a combined 136,000 in March, according to the numbers released today by the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACKER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-variant-tracker-where-different-strains-are-spreading-ffd71934-1596-43e6-923d-32c4698e2f8b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our live tracker keeps you updated with the need-to-know info on the new coronavirus variants now spreading through the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUPER MUTATION' FEARS...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14509332/covid-super-mutation-beat-vaccines-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID could mutate into a new super variant which could beat vaccines, make people sicker and reinfect victims in a devastating new outbreak, leading experts have warned. Scientists told The S…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baby boy 'first in world born with three penises', doctors say...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/baby-boy-first-world-born-23841946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unidentified child, from Duhok city, Iraq, has a rare condition called triphallia and it was only diagnosed after three months when his parents discovered swelling in his scrotum</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang hospitalized with likely kidney stone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210402132703-55zwe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/YANG-NEW YORK (PIX):Andrew Yang, New York City mayoral candidate, hospitalized with likely kidney stone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Gov Was Tested by Pandemic. Now Recall Looms...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/californias-governor-was-tested-by-the-pandemic-now-a-recall-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO — Things have been looking up in California. Vaccines will soon be available to everyone over 16. Los Angeles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just living his life'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210331224231-zj3vm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/GEORGEFLOYD (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-'Just living his life': Jurors see videos taken before and after Floyd's deadly arrest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Atmosphere of terror': Bloody rise of Mexico's top cartel...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/an-atmosphere-of-terror-the-bloody-rise-of-mexicos-top-cartel/ar-BB1feRlt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was mid-spring when residents of the wasteland behind Guadalajara’s international airport noticed a dog roaming their community with a strange object in its mouth: a human forearm. Search teams in the ramshackle neighbourhood of La Piedrera entered a roofless red brick shack flanked by trees decked with bright orange mistletoe. Under several layers of dusky earth they made an even more grotesque discovery. “There were 26 of them here. We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas GOP candidate bashes Chinese immigrants: 'I don't want them here at all'...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Texas-GOP-candidate-bashes-Chinese-immigrants-16071973.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At a political forum on Wednesday, GOP congressional candidate Sery Kim falsely suggested...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TEXT MESSAGES</title>
      <link>https://uk.sports.yahoo.com/news/text-messages-led-feds-matt-132534243.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GettyIn late January 2020, U.S. Secret Service agents received information that Rep. Matt Gaetz had accompanied a Florida county tax official they were already investigating on an unusual nighttime visit to a government office—where the local official was allegedly making fake IDs, a source close to the investigation told The Daily Beast.That tip to the feds came in a text message conversation that Seminole County Tax Collector Joel Greenberg had with an employee explaining why they were both in the office one weekend two years earlier, according to this person.A timestamp visible in the text message thread indicated the conversation took place on Monday, April 16, 2018.The Creepy, Disturbing Case That Ensnared Matt GaetzAccording to three people with direct knowledge of the incident: Greenberg visited the Lake Mary, Florida branch of his tax collection agency that weekend. Grainy surveillance footage captured Greenberg standing near a manager’s desk with another man. Greenberg forgot to set the alarm on the way out, which concerned the assistant branch manager when she walked into the office Monday morning. That employee was surprised to find that driver licenses—which are normally turned in when expired at the tax office for shredding—were scattered all over the desk instead of in the appropriate disposal basket. She reviewed the camera footage and alerted her boss, who in turn contacted Greenberg via text.“Did you happen to visit the Lake Mary Office on the weekend?” the text message read.The image obtained by The Daily Beast shows that Greenberg allegedly responded: “Yes I was showing congressman Gaetz what our operation looked like. Did I leave something on?”When Greenberg later came under investigation by the Secret Service for identity theft and stalking, agents approached former employees at the tax office to obtain proof of the public official’s activities. That’s when they were suddenly directed to Gaetz.According to the source who provided the text message conversation, who spoke on condition of anonymity to guarantee their safety, Secret Service agents directed them in the final days of January 2020 to print out the full text message conversation with Greenberg from online AT&amp;T records. That source said those text messages were delivered to the Secret Service, Florida Department of Law Enforcement, and most recently, another federal agency.Gaetz, a Florida Republican, is now the target of a Justice Department investigation that is focusing on allegations that the Republican congressman and Greenberg recruited young women and paid them for sex, according to The New York Times.CNN first reported the existence of text messages on Thursday. The Orlando Sentinel confirmed their existence as well.On Wednesday, The Daily Beast attempted to file a public records request to obtain a copy of the video surveillance that is believed to show Gaetz with Greenberg on that weekend in April 2018. However, a Seminole County representative indicated that the video is unavailable because the government agency has a policy of deleting all surveillance footage after 60 days. County officials would not comment on what exactly employees have told federal investigators about their recollection of the incident.The Daily Beast also attempted to reach the former employee who interacted with Greenberg via text message, but was unsuccessful. That employee eventually signed a $50,000 settlement with the Office of the Seminole County Tax Collector over claims of unfair retaliation at work after Greenberg allegedly used a circle of personal friends he hired at the agency to harass and intimidate her and her family. That settlement bars her from “false or defamatory statements” about her former employer, but importantly does not prevent her from speaking to government investigators, according to a copy obtained by The Daily Beast.Republicans Have Been Waiting for a Matt Gaetz Scandal to BreakHer attorney, Daniel A. Pérez, declined to comment on any current efforts to assist federal law enforcement.The U.S. Attorney’s Office for the Middle District of Florida would not confirm the existence of an ongoing investigation into Gaetz.Prosecutors there do have an ongoing case against Greenberg, who came under federal scrutiny after he repeatedly angered fellow county officials with his bizarre, erratic behavior.According to people familiar with the investigation, Secret Service agents were initially interested in Greenberg’s failed attempt to allow Seminole County residents to pay their taxes in Bitcoin. Attorneys have revealed in court that the federal probe quietly began by April 2019. That began to heat up when Greenberg ran for re-election and faced political opposition from a fine arts teacher at Trinity Preparatory School.Federal agents arrested him at his Lake Mary home on June 17, 2020, and the case initially hinged on accusations that Greenberg had set up fake online profiles to defame the teacher and had sent several letters to the school with lurid accusations that his opponent had engaged in sexual misconduct with a student.As of Tuesday, that case has now vastly expanded to a 33-count indictment that includes a diverse list of crimes that range from wirefraud to sex trafficking. Investigators say Greenberg recruited at least one teenager between 14 and 17 years old to engage in a “commercial sex act” between May and November 2017 in Central Florida and elsewhere.Matt Gaetz Keeps Digging Deeper Holes for HimselfInvestigators also say that Greenberg used his privileged access to Florida’s driver license database to look up private information on “individuals” with whom he “was engaged in ‘sugar-daddy’ relationships.”Additionally, Greenberg is also accused of making fake IDs—potentially explaining why the 2018 surveillance footage raised concerns that led to that text message conversation handed to investigators.The Daily Beast obtained text messages handed to federal investigators that allegedly show Greenberg acknowledging that he visited the office on the weekend of August 4, 2018, where there were driver licenses “scattered across the desks and not put away in an organized manner.”Greenberg has maintained a close relationship with Gaetz for several years. Both were rising stars in Florida’s Republican Party in 2016. They have taken selfies together with political operative Roger Stone in 2017, at AIPAC in 2018, and at the White House in 2019. Gaetz publicly lent his support to Greenberg, cheering him as “a disrupter” who should run for Congress.They were also together in the Florida panhandle region on July 4, 2019 when they called a state legislator, Rep. Anna V. Eskamani, and left her a peculiar voicemail that has been obtained by The Daily Beast.“My dear Anna, this is your favorite tax collector. I’m up in the panhandle with your favorite U.S. congressman, Mr. Gaetz,” Greenberg starts to say.“Hi Anna!” Gaetz jumps in.“And, uh, we were just chatting about you, and talking about your lovely qualities,” Greenberg continued.“We think you’re the future of the Democratic Party in Florida!” Gaetz said.On Thursday, Eskamani told The Daily Beast that she maintained Greenberg at arm’s length for years. Their interactions started when she called him out over Islamaphobic comments then helped him connect with the Muslim community to recover from that. Eskamani said she cautiously entertained “weird” contacts from Greenberg and Gaetz that made her uncomfortable.“We were not friends. We never hung out. We didn't talk ever, really. I just played nice. For so many women you're either very blunt and be called a bitch, or you try to play nice and pivot and deflate,” she said.Read more at The Daily Beast.Got a tip? Send it to The Daily Beast hereGet our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW FLOOD: Border officials say more sneaking past them as crossings soar, agents overwhelmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Border-officials-say-more-people-are-sneaking-16071962.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly 1,000 people per day are sneaking into the United States without being identified...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden opens up about family intervention, addresses laptop reports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hunter-biden-joe-family-intervention-laptop-reports-memoir/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hunter Biden described an emotional intervention his family staged at his father's home in Wilmington during the 2020 presidential campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin says any NATO troop deployment to Ukraine would raise tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-ukraine-crisis-russia-kremlin/kremlin-says-that-any-nato-troop-deployment-to-ukraine-would-raise-tensions-idUSKBN2BP0O6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kremlin said on Friday that any deployment of NATO troops to Ukraine would lead to further tensions near Russia's borders and force Moscow to take extra measures to ensure its own security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Pen smells blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1418169/macron-emmanuel-french-president-lockdown-fight-political-survival-le-pen-ont</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Macron was left isolated and politically adrift, after ordering a third national lockdown on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Cab ride' train-travel videos hypnotic escapes...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/lifestyle/travel/article/Cab-ride-train-travel-videos-are-hypnotic-16070384.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A warning chime sounds, the doors whoosh shut, and the train begins to glide into the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House tries to craft gun executive orders that can't be undone...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210402095518-5iyhi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-GUNS/ (ANALYSIS, PIX):ANALYSIS-Biden White House tries to craft gun executive orders that can't be undone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California bellwether warns contagious variants at worrisome levels...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401225445-jktnh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA (PIX):Pandemic poised to surge again in California's Silicon Valley tech hub</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boomers Vaccinated and Down to Party...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/boomers-are-vaccinated-and-down-to-party/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a glimpse of our post-pandemic world, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recently set forth guidelines for vaccinated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan Sales Market Revival...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/02/manhattan-sales-market-is-poised-for-a-revival-just-a-year-after-it-collapsed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A year after Covid-19 cratered the Manhattan sales market, the borough is poised for a recovery, thanks to price cuts,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy may be in lockdown, but party's on at sea...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/travel-pandemics-italy-music-coronavirus-pandemic-64294f5587f6ee286884d5182696bd7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ABOARD THE MSC GRANDIOSA (AP) — Italy may be in a strict coronavirus lockdown this Easter with travel restricted between regions and new quarantines imposed. But a few miles offshore, guests...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAY 5 GEORGE FLOYD CASE: Trial resumes after jury hears officers could have ended restraint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/trials-coronavirus-pandemic-minneapolis-racial-injustice-death-of-george-floyd-a9a6c37d5cbc8595e73d9e40d4c2fa56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — A Minneapolis police supervisory sergeant who was on duty the night George Floyd died testified that he believes the officers who restrained Floyd could have ended it after he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel dilemma: Can unvaccinated return to workplaces?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-israel-immunizations-coronavirus-pandemic-tel-aviv-7e18cdee3a66018c36a6c61d5bc8a4c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — After spending much of the past year in lockdown, Tel Aviv makeup artist Artyom Kavnatsky was ready to get back to work. But when he showed up for a recent photo shoot, his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE TRIPPED ON ECSTASY?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/women-say-rep-matt-gaetz-paid-them-for-sex-report-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gaetz, who is under investigation for potential sex trafficking of a minor, denied the allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showed Off Photos of Naked Women on House Floor?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/01/politics/matt-gaetz-photos-women/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz, the Florida Republican being investigated by the Justice Department over sex trafficking allegations, made a name for himself when he arrived on Capitol Hill as a conservative firebrand on TV and staunch defender of then-President Donald Trump. Behind the scenes, Gaetz gained a reputation in Congress over his relationships with women and bragging about his sexual escapades to his colleagues, multiple sources told CNN.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA HERO IN MEGA MESS!</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/01/justice-dept-inquiry-into-matt-gaetz-said-to-be-focused-on-cash-paid-to-women/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A Justice Department investigation into Representative Matt Gaetz and an indicted Florida politician is focusing on their involvement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUGAR DADDY:  GAETZ PROBED FOR PAY SEX</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/01/us/politics/matt-gaetz-justice-department.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The congressman and a former official in Florida sent money to the women using cash apps, receipts showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK sentences antisemite to jail for Holocaust denial for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/diaspora/antisemitism/uk-sentences-antisemite-to-jail-for-holocaust-denial-for-first-time-663850</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is not Chabloz’s first conviction for disseminating grossly offensive antisemitic material.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo exhumes old graves to make space for new...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210401183056-qow2d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRAZIL (PIX, TV):Sao Paulo exhumes old graves to make space for surging COVID-19 burials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraged Blowout: How Hwang Blindsided Global Banks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/leveraged-blowout-hwang-archegos-blindsided-194632717.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Shares of the “old media” company shot up almost 300% in weeks, and small investors were abuzz with theories: It’s undervalued, like GameStop! It’s a takeover target!Inside Wall Street’s top trading firms, however, some executives had an idea of what caused the move. A trading whale -- Bill Hwang’s Archegos Capital Management -- was building a massive position in ViacomCBS Inc.Banks around the world kept giving Hwang the leverage he needed to acquire more and more of the stock. What they couldn’t see, according to people with knowledge of the situation, was the full extent of his wagers. He stealthily amassed $10 billion of Viacom and colossal positions in a few other companies.The holes in oversight and risk management are one reason banks were so vulnerable when the Viacom bet unraveled and Archegos imploded last week.Underscoring the chaos of an escalating situation, representatives from Credit Suisse Group AG floated a suggestion as they met last week to confront the reality of such an exceptional margin call and consider ways to mitigate the damage: Maybe wait to see if his stocks recover? Viacom, some noted, seemed artificially low after its run-up past $100 just two days earlier.Yet it was Hwang’s own orders that had helped make Viacom the year’s best performer in the S&amp;P 500, forcing benchmark-tracking investors and exchange-traded funds to buy as well. Without him creating that momentum, Viacom and his other positions had little hope of rebounding.At several points during those exchanges, bankers implored Hwang to buy himself breathing room by selling some stocks and raising cash to post collateral. He wouldn’t budge, people who participated in the meetings said.Read more: One of World’s Greatest Hidden Fortunes Is Wiped Out in DaysNow, as regulators assess the fallout, Wall Street’s habit of lending to lucrative clients with few questions asked is getting unwanted attention.Hwang’s family office built positions in at least nine stocks that were big enough to rank him among the largest holders, fueled by a level of bank leverage that would have been unusual even for a hedge fund.Archegos was able to place outsize wagers using derivatives and, as a private firm, avoid the disclosures required of most investors. Almost invisibly, he accumulated a portfolio that some people familiar with his accounts estimate at as much as $100 billion.As more details emerge of how banks played such an instrumental role in helping Archegos ramp up those bets, increasingly evident are the blind spots that prevent the industry from effectively managing the risks it creates.Read more: SEC Opens Probe Into Archegos Trades That Triggered RoutAlready, regulators are privately dropping hints of new rules to come. Securities and Exchange Commission officials have signaled to banks that they intend to make trading disclosures from hedge funds a higher priority, while also finding ways to address risk and leverage.Senior finance executives acknowledge that a crackdown of some form, whether on borrowing or transparency or both, is inevitable.While some of those firms have disclosed the financial impact of their roles in the Archegos collapse, none is willing to comment on how or why they enabled Hwang to become such a force in the market. Hwang declined to comment through a representative.Limited VisibilityWhat’s clear, according to people involved in the margin call and what followed, is that Hwang’s financiers, the prime-brokerage units of Nomura Holdings Inc., Goldman Sachs Group Inc., Morgan Stanley, Credit Suisse and others, had clues about what Archegos was doing. These firms knew about the trades they had financed, of course, and also had some visibility into his total borrowings, the people said.But the lenders couldn’t see that Hwang was taking parallel positions at multiple firms, piling more leverage onto the same few stocks, according to the people. While most clients insist on such opacity, it has obvious implications for a lender’s ability to manage risk: Unwinding a series of large, leveraged bets placed by a single account is one thing; doing so when rival banks are liquidating the same positions held by the same client is quite another.On March 25, Hwang’s prime brokers met again and discussed the possibility of standing down temporarily to let tensions ease, according to people who participated in the talks. But any attempt at solidarity proved short-lived. That day, some sent Archegos notices of default, clearing the way to sell his positions.Analysts at JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. estimate some of the banks may end up absorbing as much as $10 billion in combined losses.Read more: Credit Suisse Bid for Archegos Fix Ends With Banks Brawling“Hopefully this will cause the prime brokerages of regulated banking organizations (and their supervisors) to re-assess their relationships with highly leveraged hedge funds,” Sheila Bair, a former chairman of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp., tweeted.Hwang had already lived through one crisis. In 2012, he submitted a guilty plea on behalf of his hedge fund to a charge of wire fraud, and he resolved related civil claims of insider trading without admitting or denying wrongdoing. Archegos is the family office he formed after winding down that firm, Tiger Asia Management.Prime brokerages began lining up to help the new business. Morgan Stanley was among his early backers. Deutsche Bank AG signed him as a client at the urging of at least one senior executive who was unperturbed by the insider-trading taint and didn’t believe Hwang had done anything wrong, according to a person familiar with that decision.One firm resisted the lure. Archegos approached JPMorgan sometime between 2016 and 2018 and was rebuffed, according to a person briefed on the situation. At the time, JPMorgan was still revamping the equity prime-brokerage unit it had acquired with Bear Stearns during the 2008 financial crisis. Dumb luck or not, the bank dodged a bullet.Another holdout was Goldman Sachs. For years, executives in its equities division tried to open an account for Hwang, and the compliance department consistently said no. Goldman finally jumped on board in the final months of 2020, enough time to ramp up business with Archegos and land in the middle of last week’s mayhem.Settling SwapsThat business, at Goldman and everywhere else, was swaps. Swaps are agreements between a bank and its client that are settled on the basis of changing prices in the underlying assets -- such as shares of Viacom.One benefit of swaps is they allow big investors like Hwang to build positions in a stock anonymously. A prime broker would buy the shares and report itself as the beneficial owner when in reality Archegos was bearing the economic risk.To execute such a swap, Archegos would put up a percentage of the position’s value in cash as margin. The rest of the trade would be financed by the prime broker.Because swaps are settled daily, with gains and losses netted out, Archegos also had to post a second type of collateral known as variation margin if the value of its portfolio dropped. If it increased in value, the bank would pay the firm cash.One feature that protected Hwang’s lenders was the right, in the event he couldn’t meet a margin call, to seize all the collateral in his swap accounts and sell the positions. That’s what happened last week after Viacom plunged.Hwang’s buying had helped to drive the stock above $100 for the first time ever, giving his position a market value of around $10 billion. The next biggest holder was indexing giant Vanguard Group, with a stake 40% smaller, according to data compiled by Bloomberg.Late on March 22, Viacom announced a $3 billion sale of stock and convertible debt. Over the next two days, shares of Viacom plunged 30%, pushing Archegos over its margin limits and tripping alarms at his prime brokers. In urgent meetings, they finally realized the full extent of his bets.Hwang’s RefusalInitially, some of Hwang’s lenders were reluctant to abandon him. The group pleaded with Hwang to reduce his positions, a decision that would force him to take some losses. He refused.By the close of trading on March 25, a Thursday, Viacom was down an additional 5.3% to $66.35. At one of the emergency sessions, Credit Suisse representatives suggested some sort of standstill agreement -- holding off on selling Hwang’s collateral to see if the stock would trade up.On Friday, well before the 9:30 a.m. open of trading in New York, Goldman was already offering $3.3 billion of Archegos’s holdings in massive blocks. Morgan Stanley and Wells Fargo &amp; Co. soon followed. On Monday in Zurich, Credit Suisse revealed that it faced a “highly significant” loss, one that has since been linked to Archegos and is projected to reach into the billions of dollars. Nomura could lose $2 billion.Read more: Deutsche Bank Dodged Archegos Hit With Quick $4 Billion Sale“Risk controls still are not where they should be,” David Herro, one of Credit Suisse’s biggest shareholders, said Wednesday in a Bloomberg TV interview. “Hopefully, this is a wake-up call to expedite the cultural change that is needed in this company.”The SEC has already opened a preliminary investigation into Hwang’s trades and is calling other big investors to inquire about their use of swaps and access to leverage from prime brokers. A regulatory shadow is creeping over the industry.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA NEARS 100 MILLION VACCINATIONS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-us-news-mlb-baseball-coronavirus-pandemic-46d35c154adacda41a2d3afbe60fb5dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. moved closer Thursday toward vaccinating 100 million Americans in a race against an uptick in COVID-19 cases that is fueling fears of another nationwide surge just as the major league...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a rare admission, MTV says its programming offers dim view of mental health...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/In-a-rare-admission-MTV-says-its-programming-16070434.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI ON THE BRINK:  Pivotal Islamic leader demands change in Israel after vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/pivotal-islamic-leader-demands-change-in-israel-after-vote/ar-BB1fdwlh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of a conservative Islamic party who has emerged as a kingmaker following Israel's latest inconclusive election called for change Thursday, without endorsing Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu or his rivals. Mansour Abbas's primetime address was carried live by multiple Israeli broadcasters, underscoring his pivotal role in determining whether a stable governing coalition is possible after last week's election. The vote, Israel's fourth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Food delivery apps add to pandemic pounds, exempt from posting nutrition information...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/food-delivery-apps-are-exempt-from-posting-nutrition-information-this-loophole-has-added-to-our-pandemic-pounds-advocates-say/ar-BB1fdBUd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDA has given third-party food delivery apps a free pass not to post calorie counts. Americans’ health has suffered, advocates say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showed Off Photos of Naked Women on House Floor?</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/matt-gaetz-reportedly-showed-fellow-lawmakers-naked-pictures-of-women-he-slept-with/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-FL) allegedly showed fellow lawmakers photos of naked women on the House floor, claiming to have had sex with them, according to a new report from CNN. The flamboyantly pro-Trump congressman found himself at the center of controversy this week after it was reported that he was under a Justice Department investigation […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prisoner admits to murdering serial killer, calls it 'mission for avenging' his victims...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9425671/California-prisoner-confesses-strangling-5-Strangler-five-page-letter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jason Budrow, 40 (left), claimed he murdered the notorious killer Roger Kibbe, 81, (top right) in a five-page letter he titled 'Ascension … May Their Souls Go To Heaven.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Smallpox 'virus squads' and mandatory vaccinations upheld by Supreme Court...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Smallpox-virus-squads-and-mandatory-16070603.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E. Edwin Spencer had no way of knowing he would be making history that day when he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID CASES +17% FOR WEEK IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/coronavirus-cases-infections-hospital-variants-d0f5850c-6098-431c-b38c-55b82cce2b8c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cases are up 17% over last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF:  Pandemic sharpens inequalities, could fuel unrest...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-sharpens-inequalities-could-fuel-191859446.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus pandemic has worsened long-standing inequalities around the world, which left unaddressed could undermine economic stability and lead to unrest, the IMF warned on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost one in seven suffers long Covid...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-covid-uk.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one in seven Britons who tested positive for COVID-19 continued to have symptoms for at least 12 weeks, according to a UK study released Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Judge blocks sales of Lil Nas X 'Satan shoes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/1/lil-nas-x-satan-shoes-sales-blocked-federal-judge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Satan shoe can go to hell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Abby: Husband turned on by amputation!</title>
      <link>https://www.pennlive.com/life/2021/03/dear-abby-wife-is-unsettled-by-mans-obsession-with-amputation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pennlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He recently told me that not only does he find amputees attractive, but he wants to be one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell claims treatment in prison 'fit for Hannibal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9428619/Ghislaine-Maxwell-claims-treatment-prison-fit-Hannibal-Lecter.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ghislane Maxwell claims that the prison conditions as she awaits trial would be appropriate for the fictional serial killer in The Silence of the Lambs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'She-Wees', Plastic Bags: AMAZON Pee Scandal Much Worse for Women...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akd54e/she-wees-and-plastic-bags-amazons-pee-scandal-is-much-worse-for-women</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon delivery drivers describe the great lengths they’ve gone to to pee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Messy Breakup of OnlyFans Model and Her Uber-Wealthy Boyfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/04/inside-the-messy-litigious-breakup-of-an-onlyfans-model-and-her-uber-wealthy-boyfriend</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Cloobeck says he was fleeced by the woman he loved. Stefanie Gurzanski says her ex is trying to ruin her life. Both have lawyered up, and are taking the explosion of their romance public.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: Foreign Billionaire Funneled Cash to American Political Campaigns...</title>
      <link>https://www.opensecrets.org/news/2021/04/straw-donor-scheme-foreign-billionaire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.opensecrets.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Lebanese-Nigerian billionaire conspired to route illegal foreign contributions into U.S. elections in a straw donor scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  18 massage therapists defend star NFL QB as 'professional,' 'polite'...</title>
      <link>https://www.khou.com/article/news/local/massage-therapists-defend-deshaun-watson-rusty-hardin-says/285-b5c7d715-b93d-47f1-9d7c-677434348d79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.khou.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"He was respectful in every session," one woman said. "I never had any issues with him being inappropriate." The statements were released by attorney Rusty Hardin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock pics of home where hoarder found MUMMIFIED...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2623745/pictures-evelyn-sakash-designer-hoarder-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHOCKING pictures of the home where a hoarder was found mummified under garbage after neighbors noticed a small have been released. Evelyn Sakash, 66, was found by cops in her New York City home on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba erects giant concrete flag in front of US embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210401-cuba-erects-giant-concrete-flag-in-front-of-us-embassy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuba erects giant concrete flag in front of US embassy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New test and trace rules for pubs mean EVERYONE as to sign in...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14525657/new-test-trace-rules-pubs-everyone-over-16-sign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW test and trace rules for pubs mean that EVERYONE over 16 has to sign in. UK pub industry reps have today accused the Government of “stealthy backsliding on pub reopening rules”. 🦠 R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's 'Transformative' Plan Redefines Infrastructure to Include Caregiving...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/economy/biden-infrastructure-plan-caregiver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden wants to put $400 billion toward expanding quality home or community care. Ai-jen Poo tells The Nation that’s “historic” progress.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
