<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  St. Louis couple hit with felony charges for pulling guns at protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/20/mark-and-patricia-mccloskey-st-louis-couple-face-f/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;St. Louis’ top prosecutor told The Associated Press on Monday that she is charging a white husband and wife with felony unlawful use of a weapon for displaying guns during a racial injustice protest outside their mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall of CBS Showrunner: 'This Was Abuse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2020/07/the-fall-of-a-cbs-showrunner</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier this month, CBS fired Peter Lenkov, who’d overseen a powerful fiefdom. V.F. spoke to 30 sources about what happens when a network gives somebody a difficult job, then seems to let problems pile up for years because he’s making it money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious 450-foot 'blue hole' off Florida has researchers looking for signs of life...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/national/article244345437.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas county warns positive residents must stay home or face prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/local/article/Texas-county-warns-COVID-19-positive-residents-to-15420079.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The COVID-19 surge in rural Texas has escalated into a deepening public health crisis for Hidalgo County, where officials issued an order Sunday requiring those who test positive for the virus to not leave home for 14 days under threat of criminal prosecution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The people with hidden immunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20200716-the-people-with-hidden-protection-from-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the latest research suggests that antibodies against Covid-19 could be lost in just three months, a new hope has appeared on the horizon: the enigmatic T cell.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Musk Now 5th Richest Man in the World!</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/elon-musk-keeps-climbing-list-of-worlds-wealthiest-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That’s some pay raise. Tesla CEO Elon Musk added a whopping $5 billion to his net worth on Monday thanks to Tesla’s never-ending stock rally, allowing him to finish the day as the fifth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to send federal forces to more 'Democrat' cities...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200720182331-pw695</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-RACE/PROTESTS-PORTLAND (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Trump to send federal forces to more 'Democrat' cities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hecklers Interrupt DeSantis News Conference Claiming Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/hecklers-interrupt-gov-ron-desantis-news-conference-claiming-covid-19-data-cover-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis put out a call Monday for people who have had COVID-19 to donate blood, but shortly after his news conference started, he was heckled by protesters who accused him of mishandling the pandemic and covering up COVID-19 data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Time with Mrs. Stephanopoulos: Watching PORN with the Kids!</title>
      <link>https://www.newsbusters.org/blogs/culture/gabriel-hays/2020/07/19/family-time-mrs-stephanopoulos-watching-porn-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You know which side ABC anchor George Stephanopoulos comes down on whether our kids should go to school this fall during the Chinese virus outbreak. He wouldn’t want us to endanger our kids’ lives, of course. But his wife’s latest admission should have you wondering whether the Stephanopoulos family knows what’s in your kids' best interests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA Passengers Must Undergo Medical Screening To Fly Without Mask...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/delta-face-mask-customers-maskless-medical-screening/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Major airlines have for months required masks on board their flights, but struggled to enforce this rule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to send federal agents to major cities...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/508138-trump-signals-he-will-send-federal-agents-to-major-cities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday signaled he may order federal agents to be deployed to Chicago, New York City, Philadelphia and other major cities as he threatens to crack down further on unrest across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect in shooting identified as lawyer, men's rights activist...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/roy-den-hollander-idd-as-suspect-in-shooting-at-judge-esther-salas-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gunman suspected of killing the son and wounding the husband of a federal judge in New Jersey before taking his own life has been identified as lawyer and men's rights activist Roy Den Hol…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci: 'Worst Nightmare Comes True'...</title>
      <link>https://health.usnews.com/hospital-heroes/articles/dr-anthony-fauci-fighting-the-coronavirus-pandemic-is-my-entire-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;health.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate giants shut down Trump texting program...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/20/trump-massive-texting-program-suspended-372302</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took days to resolve anti-spam concerns that halted a July 4 test run, costing Trump donations and raising GOP fears about November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida sheriff says he can't muster security for GOP convention...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/20/florida-sheriff-gop-convention-security-373089</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a lack of clear plans, adequate funding and enough law enforcement officers, he says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAIM:  Poor diets threaten US national security...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/20/health/us-poor-nutrition-illness-death-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poor nutrition is the leading cause of US illnesses, creating a growing burden on the nation's economy, exacerbating health disparities and impacting national security, according to a white paper in the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Company Develops Electrostatic Drone to Disinfect Stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/electrostatic-disinfecting-drone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Pittsburgh area company says they have developed a drone that could sanitize entire stadiums in three hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to remain closed to foreign visitors until at least September...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israel-to-remain-closed-to-foreign-visitors-until-at-least-september/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Airports Authority says current restrictions, under which entry granted only to nationals or those obtaining special permit from Immigration Authority, to stay in force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz sounds alarm on Republicans losing Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8541229/Ted-Cruz-warns-Democrats-win-Texas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Ted Cruz warned the Texas GOP State Convention if the Democrats win the Lone Star State both the White House and the Senate are gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man found dead of self-inflicted gunshot wound possibly linked...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/20/man-found-dead-possibly-linked-to-shooting-of-nj-judge-esther-salas-family</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man found dead in New York’s Catskills may have been behind the shooting of federal Judge Esther Salas’ son and husband in New Jersey, police sources said Monday. The man was found on Monday in R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BBC apologizes for playing song with racial slur...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bbc-apologises-playing-song-containing-174300336.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We will work to ensure this does not happen again."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  FEAR OF COVID TURNING INTO ANGER...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/global-frustration-covid-19-fear-turning-to-anger-twitter-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study in JMIR Public Health &amp; Surveillance adds angry coronavirus posts made up nearly 30 percent of Twitter reaction on March 12. That is the same day the World Health Organization officially declared COVID-19 a global pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE VAX HYPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/20/oxford-universitys-coronavirus-vaccine-shows-positive-immune-response-in-an-early-trial.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The researchers said in the medical journal The Lancet that the vaccine produced antibodies and killer T-cells to combat the infection that lasted at least two months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATAKI:  For the first time ever I fear for the future of New York City...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/18/george-pataki-warns-big-apple-on-brink-nyc-is-going-to-die/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in his life, George Pataki is worried about New York City’s future. In an exclusive interview with The Post at his Peekskill, New York, office, the former three-term Republ…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Sees Push to Tax Trades With Revenue in Free Fall...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/york-sees-push-tax-stock-133340361.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Democrats in New York, the world’s financial capital, may finally have the right moment to resurrect the state tax on stock trades.One-fifth of the state’s revenue is disappearing, leaving a projected four-year deficit of $61 billion. Progressive Democrats are on the ascent in the state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP says it will capitalize Black but not white...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e36c00c5af0436abc09e051261fff1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — After changing its usage rules last month to capitalize the word “Black” when used in the context of race and culture, The Associated Press on Monday said it would not do the same...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:   JOE WOULD KNOCKOUT DONALD IN BOXING MATCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/pow-most-see-biden-beating-trump-in-boxing-match</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The political polls haven’t been very good for President Trump, even those that have shown him treading water against Democratic challenger Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI:   Trump may have to be 'fumigated' out of White House!</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/second-in-line-nancy-pelosi-trump-may-have-to-be-fumigated-out-of-the-white-house  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANYE CRACKING</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2020/07/20/kanyes-campaign-appearance-seriously-upset-kardashian-family/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West's off-the-rails campaign stop Sunday in North Charleston, South Carolina may not only hurt Ye politically, he has concerned, upset and alarmed many of his friends and the Kardashians ... sources connected to Kanye tell TMZ.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple forced to wear ankle monitors for refusing to sign quarantine documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1166277/coronavirus-couple-house-arrest-ankle-monitors/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY bans eating while walking after guests break mask rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/travel/1168535/disney-world-food-drink-ban-face-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DISNEY World has banned guests from eating and drinking while walking around the park after people were using the loophole to avoid wearing face masks. Less than 10 days after reopening, the theme …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rapped for health secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/19/ruth-bader-ginsburg-scotus-transparency-370570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the court sharply divided on many pivotal issues, a health crisis on the part of one justice has the potential to upend Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity sexologist found naked and dead in luxury hotel...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/celebrity-sexologist-26-found-dead-22383280</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Married TV doctor and psychologist Anna Ambartsumyan, who often gave her opinions on celebrities in Russia, was found dead aged just 26 - police are now investigating her death</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists provide conclusive data that mosquitoes can't spread it...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/scientists-provide-conclusive-data-that-mosquitoes-cant-spread-covid-19-635648</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To date there has been no information nor evidence to suggest that the new coronavirus could be transmitted by mosquitoes," WHO said on their COVID-19 "mythbusters" page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kasich set to speak at DEM convention!</title>
      <link>https://www.cleveland.com/open/2020/07/ex-gov-john-kasich-slated-to-speak-at-the-democratic-national-convention-for-joe-biden.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cleveland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s a move that would be unthinkable just a few years ago, when Kasich clashed with Democrats on a range of issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Will Be Most Litigated in History...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/2020-election-will-be-the-most-litigated-in-u-s-history</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2020 Election Will Be the Most Litigated in U.S. History</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombian President calls for multilateral covid solutions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/508015-the-hill-interview-colombian-president-duque-calls-for-multilateral-covid-19-solutions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombian President Iván Duque believes the missing ingredient in the Western Hemisphere's response to the pandemic was multilateralism, and an accelerant in the virus's spread was populism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It's a breaking point. We're at a critical stage'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/07/20/hialeah-mayor-carlos-hernandez-one-plan-in-place-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hialeah Mayor Carlos Hernandez wants one plan in place for South Florida to fight the rising surge of coronavirus cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Struggles To Explain Handcuffed, Blindfolded Uighurs Loaded Onto Train...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/geopolitical/chinese-ambassador-struggles-explain-shocking-footage-handcuffed-blindfolded-uighurs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep South supermarket takes stand: No masks required...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2020/07/19/winn-dixie-doesnt-require-masks-while-other-supermarkets-do/5467748002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Walmart, Target, CVS, Walgreens and Kroger are the biggest retailers to announce they will soon mandate masks at stores nationwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESCAPE: Rural real estate prices rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/rural-real-estate-prices-rise-people-consider-leaving-cities-n1234309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The virus is impacting how we spend money, how we shop and, perhaps, even where we want to live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's elite given experimental 'vaccine' for months...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/russias-elite-experimental-vaccine-months-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of Russia’s business and ruling elite have been given access to an experimental vaccine against the novel coronavirus since April, according to a report on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Cuban warns of stock similarities to dot-com bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/20/mark-cuban-coronavirus-stock-comeback-similar-to-1990s-dot-com-bubble.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire businessman Monday on CNBC compared the stock market's big run-up from its late March coronavirus low to the 1990s tech frenzy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Camps Bring Ominous Warning in Test Run for Schools...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/coronavirus-outbreak/summer-camps-bring-ominous-virus-warning-in-test-run-for-schools</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Summer camps in parts of the U.S. are closing as children and counselors test positive for Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida reports over 10,000 new cases for sixth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200720140811-wyc7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-FLORIDA (URGENT):Florida reports over 10,000 new cases of COVID-19 for sixth day in a row</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As pandemic surges, so do waistlines...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cde7e5cca347c7303e7b35211fd21d99</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When Allison Weiss Brady and Michael Ladin emerged from weeks of locking down during the pandemic, they needed new clothes in new sizes — for different reasons. Brady, 49, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First COVID-19, now mosquitoes: Bracing for bug-borne ills...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d588bb4f42d92dca86c43443204fe1ba</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sophia Garabedian had been dealing with a persistent fever and painful headache when her parents found her unresponsive in her bed one morning last fall. Doctors ultimately diagnosed the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona turns blue?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jul/20/arizona-trump-republicans-white-house-democrats-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Changing demographics and a backlash to Trump has reshaped the state’s politics – so could Arizona really turn Democratic?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aging 'Master Circuit' Discovered: Extended Human Lifespan To Follow?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/cellular-aging-master-circuit-discovered-extended-human-lifespan-to-follow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study by UCSD molecular biologists and bioengineers reveal a groundbreaking discovery regarding the intricacies of cellular aging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuralink chip will stream music directly to brain?</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/gadgets-and-tech/news/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-computer-chip-music-stream-a9627686.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Portland tear gas, an apparition emerges, capturing imagination of protesters...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/portland-tear-gas-apparition-emerges-020522608.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iconic image has emerged on Twitter since early Saturday morning in Portland, when a woman wearing nothing but a mask and cap strode toward federal agents as they fired tear gas at protesters — a surreal image of human vulnerability in the face of an overpowering force.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Friendliest,' not fittest, is key to evolutionary survival, scientists argue...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Friendliest-not-fittest-is-key-to-15419832.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British naturalist Charles Darwin got it right, but maybe we got Darwin wrong.  Most people assume that Darwin was talking about physical strength when referring to "survival of the fittest," meaning that a tougher, more resilient species always will win out over its weaker counterparts. But what if he didn't mean that at all?  Scientists Brian Hare and Vanessa Woods, both researchers at Duke University's Center for Cognitive Neuroscience, believe something else has been at work among species that have thrived throughout history, successfully reproducing to sustain themselves, and it has nothing to do with beating up the competition.  Their new book, "Survival of the Friendliest: Understanding Our Origins and Rediscovering Our Common Humanity," posits that friendly partnerships among species and shared humanity have worked throughout centuries to ensure successful evolution. Species endure - humans, other animals and plants - they write, based on friendliness, partnership and communication. And they point to many life examples of cooperation and sociability to prove it.  "Survival of fittest, which is what everyone has in mind as evolution and natural selection, has done the most harm of any folk theory that has penetrated society," Hare says. "People think of it as strong alpha males who deserve to win. That's not what Darwin suggested, or what has been demonstrated. The most successful strategy in life is friendliness and cooperation, and we see it again and again."  "Dogs are exhibit A," he says. "They are the extremely friendly descendants of wolves. They were attracted to humans and became friendly to humans, and changed their behavior, appearance and developmental makeup. Sadly, their close relative, the wolf, is threatened and endangered in the few places where they live, whereas there are hundreds of millions of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood nervously awaits fallout from explosive Johnny Depp trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/jul/19/hollywood-nervously-awaits-fallout-from-explosive-johnny-depp-trial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amber Heard’s team will have their say this week. Whatever the result, reputations could be tarnished</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet asked officers to remember oaths. They broke his hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/A-Navy-vet-asked-federal-officers-in-Portland-to-15419760.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. - He came to the protest with a question. He left with two broken bones in a confrontation with federal officers that went viral.  Christopher David had watched in horror as videos surfaced of federal officers in camouflage throwing Portland Ore., protesters into unmarked vans. The 53-year-old Portland resident had heard the stories: protesters injured, gassed, sprayed with chemicals that tugged at their nostrils and burned their eyes.  David, a graduate of the U.S. Naval Academy and former member of the Navy's Civil Engineer Corps, said he wanted to know what the officers involved thought of the oath they had sworn to protect and defend the Constitution.  So, he said, on Saturday evening, he headed to downtown Portland to ask them.  That night's protests outside the federal courthouse - the 51st day of ongoing demonstrations - began with a line of local moms linking arms and demanding the federal agents stop targeting Portland kids. David, who had never attended a protest before, hung back and watched.  He was trying to keep his distance, he said, as a host of health problems have made him especially vulnerable amid a still-raging coronavirus pandemic. He asked one woman when the feds would show up, but she said it was also her first protest since the Department of Homeland Security deployed tactical units from U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement and U.S. Customs and Border Protection to bolster protections for federal buildings and officers in the Pacific Northwest city.  Just as he was about to leave, David said, the federal officers emerged. They rushed a line of protesters nearby, knocking protesters to the ground. David walked toward a gap in the line, calling out to the officers.  "Why are you not honoring your oath?" he bellowed. "Why are you not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge's son killed, husband shot at home by gunman disguised as delivery driver...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Federal-judge-s-son-killed-husband-shot-at-home-15419761.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gunman disguised as a delivery driver shot and killed the son of a federal judge and wounded her husband at their New Jersey home on Sunday, law enforcement confirmed to The Washington Post.  U.S. District Judge Esther Salas was not injured in the shooting, which the FBI, U.S. Marshals and local authorities are investigating.  The gunman showed up to Salas's home in North Brunswick, N.J., wearing an outfit described to police as a FedEx uniform, law enforcement said. Both Mark Anderl, 63, a defense attorney and former Essex County assistant prosecutor, and Daniel Anderl, 20, a student at Catholic University in Washington D.C., were shot after one of them opened the door for the gunman around 5 p.m., ABC News reported.  "He was shot through the heart," North Brunswick Democratic Mayor Francis "Mac" Womack told ABC News of Daniel Anderl.  Salas's son died and her husband was rushed to the hospital for surgery, the Associated Press reported. Mark Anderl is now in stable condition, Womack told NJ Advance Media.  The FBI said it is looking for one suspect. The Marshals Service said it is also investigating, adding in a statement to HuffPost that the agency "is responsible for the protection of federal judicial officials and we take that responsibility very seriously."  Authorities have not given any indication of a motive in the shooting. Womack, who is friends with Salas and her husband, told ABC he wasn't aware of any specific threat against the judge.  "As a judge, she had threats from time to time, but everyone is saying that recently there had not been any," Womack said.  Salas, 51, was New Jersey's first Hispanic woman to serve as a U.S. district judge. President Barack Obama nominated her for the position in 2010, and she was confirmed by the Senate in 2011. Salas...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe eyes GOP supporters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/99d19335011e2fb19035dc83ac2fb481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the four months since Joe Biden effectively won the Democratic presidential nomination, he has focused on consolidating the party's divergent and often warring factions. As the closing stretch...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tens of thousands to walk off job to protest racial inequality...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0fbc6aa5a60520900a434b51bd3c7ef6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Organizers of a national workers strike say tens of thousands are set to walk off the job Monday in more than two dozen U.S. cities to protest systemic racism and economic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy vet asked officers to remember oaths. They broke his hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2020/07/20/christopher-david-portland-protest-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Portland protester and Navy veteran Christopher David was beaten and pepper sprayed by federal troops in a viral video. He says the officers broke his hand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREGG: When the dollar is worth 60 cents...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/508046-judd-gregg-when-the-dollar-is-worth-60-cents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OPINION: The deficits being incurred in response to the pandemic pose a serious danger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rulers of Oil-Rich Saudi Arabia, Kuwait Hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rulers-top-oil-producers-saudi-050303224.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- King Salman bin Abdulaziz of Saudi Arabia has been admitted to a hospital in Riyadh early Monday for medical tests, the second elderly ruler of an oil-rich Gulf Arab nation to be hospitalized in less than a week.The 84-year-old monarch was undergoing medical tests at King Faisal Specialist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. mayor warns city 'on the brink' of new stay-home order...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trump-challenged-over-claims-as-coronavirus-deaths-mount/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - As coronavirus cases and hospitalizations climb, state and local officials nationwide are sounding the alarm, warning that they're missing key resources to confront the surge. They are weighing new restrictions and complaining of persistent backlogs in the mass-testing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Calls Biden 'Incompetent,' Says He'd Cry 'Mommy, Mommy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-calls-biden-e2-80-98incompetent-e2-80-99-says-he-e2-80-99d-cry-e2-80-98mommy-e2-80-99/ar-BB16VWUC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE MONDAY:  Virus is crushing United States...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/health-news/the-crisis-that-shocked-the-world-americas-response-to-the-coronavirus/ar-BB16WaBS?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple forced to wear ankle monitors for refusing to sign quarantine documents...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/kentucky-couple-fit-with-ankle-monitors-placed-on-house-arrest-for-refusing-to-sign-quarantine-documents</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Kentucky couple was fitted with ankle monitors and placed on house arrest after the wife tested positive for coronavirus but refused to sign self-quarantine documents, according to reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican president mourns virus dead... </title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/mexican-president-mourns-39-000-virus-dead-01595205605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican president Manuel Lopez Obrador on Sunday vowed to improve health standards in the nation, which has the fourth-highest coronavirus death toll in the world, as the number of fatalities rose to nearly 39,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Harriet Tubman never actually freed the slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2020/music/news/kanye-west-breaks-down-harriet-tubman-south-carolina-rally-1234710640/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West broke down in tears, made an outrageous claim about abolitionist Harriet Tubman, had a heckler ejected and claimed his brain was too big for his skull on Sunday at the first campaign eve…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/KEEMSTAR/status/1284987982748033029</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astrophysicists unveil biggest-ever 3D map of Universe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/astrophysicists-unveil-biggest-ever-3d-map-universe-004852227.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astrophysicists on Monday published the largest-ever 3D map of the Universe, the result of an analysis of more than four million galaxies and ultra-bright, energy-packed quasars. The efforts of hundreds of scientists from around 30 institutions worldwide have yielded a "complete story of the expansion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE:  Virus Will Make Everything You Hate About Flying Worse...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/virus-everything-hate-flying-worse-220046295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- As the coronavirus pandemic continues, Bloomberg Opinion will be running a series of features by our columnists that consider the long-term consequences of the crisis. This column is part of a package on the future of transportation. Last month, my wife and I planned our first</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Dems Seek Probe of Secretive Federal Police Actions...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/democrats-seek-probe-secret-police-000000897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior Democratic lawmakers have called for inquiries into the Trump administration’s use of federal law enforcement officers to quell protests in Oregon, saying the administration did not have “unfettered authority” to crack down on peaceful demonstrations. The request from Jerry Nadler, the chairman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holds 'rally' in Charleston...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c4645f9e0c206471414b8c1dd7d5ab49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Rapper Kanye West, in his first event since declaring himself a presidential candidate, delivered a lengthy monologue Sunday touching on topics from abortion and religion to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Players Warn Season Might Not Happen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9cb112c6323436f6e86eaceaf2c37bd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players are publicly pleading with the league to address several health and safety concerns on the eve of training camp. The league informed teams on Saturday that training camps will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85 Babies Test Positive In One County!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2fe63502311b576573c791740c3166ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUSTIN, Texas (AP) — A health official on the Texas Gulf Coast said 85 infants have tested positive for the coronavirus. Corpus Christi Nueces County Public Health Director Annette...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE RACE: First Arab space mission to Mars launches from Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ac2805903b50493f42081568755b2c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — A United Arab Emirates spacecraft rocketed away Monday on a seven-month journey to Mars, kicking off the Arab world’s first interplanetary mission. The liftoff of the Mars...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bahamas closes borders to U.S. tourists after spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.traveloffpath.com/bahamas-bans-flights-from-usa-and-closes-beaches-due-to-surge-in-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.traveloffpath.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;19 days after reopening for tourism, Bahamas is baning flights from the USA and many other countries, plus closing beaches to stop the surge of new cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo whistleblower complaint reveals ongoing inquiry over 'questionable activities'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article244328882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACESPOOK!  Zuckerberg surfboards in Hawaii with way too much sunscreen...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/19/mark-zuckerberg-surfboards-in-hawaii-with-way-too-much-sunscreen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New photos show Facebook honcho Mark Zuckerberg zipping around on an electric surfboard in Hawaii</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
