<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>White House Turns to Antitrust Enforcers to Combat Inflation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-turns-to-antitrust-enforcers-to-combat-inflation/ar-AAS8D3w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron Divides Fans By Equating Covid to Flu, Cold...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/sports/lebron-james-divides-nba-fans-with-meme-comparing-covid-to-the-flu-and-the-common-cold/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LeBron James ignited a Twitter firestorm when he compared Covid-19 to both the flu and the common cold in a post on his Instagram account page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Dems who could run in '24 if Biden doesn't...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/586948-ten-democrats-who-could-run-in-2024-if-biden-doesnt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2022 midterm elections are less than a year away, but questions are already being raised about what the Democratic ticket will look like in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More shows go dark on Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/24/thoughts-of-a-colored-man-and-waitress-go-dark-on-broadway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Great White Way was darker on Christmas Eve as two Broadway productions permanently closed due to surging COVID-19 cases in the Big Apple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER booster's ability to prevent wanes within WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/uk-agency-pfizer-boosters-ability-to-prevent-symptomatic-covid-wanes-within-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data shows 3rd shot 70% effective in preventing illness after 2 weeks but only 45% after 10 weeks; Moderna seems to offer more durable protection, staying at 70% after 10 weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's well-oiled military machine launches 3 warships in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3161052/chinas-well-oiled-military-machine-launches-three-warships-one</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two vessels destined for Thailand and Pakistan while a third built to bolster PLA fleet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After years of doubts, hopes grow nuclear fusion finally real...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/12/22/science/after-years-doubts-hopes-grow-that-nuclear-fusion-is-finally-real-could-help-address-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After breakthroughs this year at MIT and elsewhere, scientists — and a growing number of deep-pocketed investors — insist that fusion is for real and could start sending power to electricity grids in about a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Webb telescope launches, starting nail-biting mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2021/12/25/nasa-james-webb-telescope-launches-south-america/9016763002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's flagship science instrument took flight from South America early Saturday, a high-stakes mission that will peer deep into the universe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy warship sidelined with outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/12/24/navy-warship-milwaukee-covid-526138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USS Milwaukee is staying in port.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Suspect charged with shooting man over loud music...</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/story/news/crime/2021/12/25/boca-raton-christmas-eve-shooting-over-loud-music/9016891002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The victim's family was able to wrestle Zachary Moncada to the ground after he fired at them, according to a report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood banks experiencing biggest shortage in decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/live/2021/12/25/world/omicron-covid-vaccine-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blood banks across the country are struggling to maintain their usual three-day supply as virus cases make donors and medical staff scarce. Britain is administering booster shots throughout the Christmas holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowds, arguments across NYC as demand for tests rises...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/angry-crowds-arguments-across-nyc-as-demand-for-covid-tests-rises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In some parts of the city, larger-than-expected turnouts for free at-home COVID testing kits led to angry scenes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBNB cracks down on disruptive FL parties...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-florida-orlando-holidays-new-years-eve-dcb7746159cbfd916b99b5a7d558efd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORLANDO, Fla. (AP) — If you're planning to rent a home in central Florida over New Year's Eve, you may be out of luck. Airbnb says potential guests without a history of positive reviews will be unable to make one-night reservations in Orlando and Kissimmee over New Year's Eve, in an effort to crack down on disruptive parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Nuns Who Grow Weed...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-features/california-weed-cannabis-nun-sisters-valley-1272595/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How a New Age order of feminist nuns is reimagining spiritual devotion and trying to heal the world — one joint at a time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 10 Londoners infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/one-in-10-londoners-are-likely-infected-with-covid-new-figures-show/ar-AAS7uGV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over masks mandates, other rules, spurs states to curb power of public health officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/anger-over-masks-mandates-other-covid-rules-spurs-states-to-curb-power-of-public-health-officials/ar-AAS8BLX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New record for daily infections in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dpa-international.com/topic/new-record-daily-infections-australia-marks-second-covid-urn%3Anewsml%3Adpa.com%3A20090101%3A211225-99-500849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Stories from around the globe brought to you by dpa International.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/12/23/united-delta-cancel-dozens-of-christmas-eve-flights-as-covid-hits-crews.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. airlines have recently ramped up pressure on the CDC to loosen quarantine rules for breakthrough Covid cases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador frees women convicted of abortions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-caribbean-nayib-bukele-el-salvador-san-salvador-894e8808713a4174d127d1ba513a8847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — President Nayib Bukele's government has freed three Salvadoran women who were sentenced to 30 years in prison under the nation's strict anti-abortion laws after suffering obstetric emergencies, according to abortion rights groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA HIT WITH RECORD CASES...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-miami-florida-b10650dbe748751d2c2c830813d64df8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — With Florida hitting a record number of cases, getting a COVID test Saturday on Christmas Day was almost as popular as eating a ham or drinking egg-nog-like coquito, for some. Hours before a testing site opening at Tropical Park in Miami, dozens of cars lined up along a road leading to its entrance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GONSALVES:  Biden failing on pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2021/12/22/president-biden-is-failing-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is playing catch-up and doing damage control as omicron rages across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARE CONTINUES:  MORE DELAY DELAYS ON XMAS DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10344125/Christmas-Day-airport-misery-thousands-flight-cancelations-climb-quarter-24-hours.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Domestic travelers are facing a nightmare this holiday season as airlines on Christmas day cancelled over 850 flights and delayed 520.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police arrest armed man breaking into Windsor grounds...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/armed-intruder-arrested-in-grounds-of-windsor-castle-as-queen-celebrates-christmas-12503764</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Queen is celebrating this Christmas at Windsor Castle with Prince Charles and Camilla, the Duchess of Cornwall, after cancelling her traditional plans of going to Sandringham.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen's Christmas speech particularly personal...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-queen-elizabeth-ii-lifestyle-health-europe-b2e2e0abe96f5a8bf94e9f9d166903e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Queen Elizabeth II in her Christmas Day message shared the pain she felt after the death of her husband as she encouraged people everywhere to celebrate with friends and family, despite the grief caused by a pandemic now stretching into its second year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER COVID CHRISTMAS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-lifestyle-health-religion-new-zealand-9ec85a6390d13e3144bdaa236b988666</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Christians around the world celebrated their second COVID-19 Christmas on Saturday with surging infections in many countries overwhelming hospitals, canceling flights and curbing religious observances, even as coronavirus vaccines were more available than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic decimates tourism at Jesus' birthplace...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211225133739-sqk9w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 10,000 troops returning to bases after drills...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211225082435-ynljw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders NYT to return PROJECT VERITAS internal memos...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20211224220928-h7dpr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK TIMES-PROJECT VERITAS (PIX):Judge orders New York Times to return Project Veritas internal memos</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Black Moderates Awoke The Woke...</title>
      <link>https://michaelshellenberger.substack.com/p/why-black-moderates-awoke-the-woke</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelshellenberger.substack.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The backlash to progressive Wokeism, or victimology, has been brewing for years. Why did black moderates tip it over the edge?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoo closes after pack of wolves escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/dec/24/french-zoo-closes-after-pack-of-nine-wolves-escapes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four wolves were shot dead by park workers and five anaesthetised by officials at scene</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23 retirements rocks Dems' hopes of holding House...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/wave-retirements-rocks-democrats-hopes-holding-house-n1286398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, 23 Democrats and a dozen Republicans in the House have announced they're not seeking re-election or are running for another office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Upholds Block on NYT Coverage of 'VERITAS'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/24/business/media/new-york-times-project-veritas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State judge also ordered The Times to turn over physical copies and destroy any electronic versions of documents a lawyer prepared for the conservative group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 stuck on cruise ship; Mexico refuses to allow disembark...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10343163/American-passengers-banned-disembarking-Mexican-cruise-21-crew-members-COVID-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A total of 1,035 passengers were banned from leaving their cruise ship in Puerto Vallarta, Mexico, on Thursday after 21 crew members produced positive COVID-19 tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer killed in CA shark attack...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/morro-bay-shark-attack-surfer-killed-bite/11382320/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a surfer has died after an apparent shark attack in Morro Bay on California's Central Coast on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver charged with raping passenger during Vegas ride...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/uber-driver-charged-raping-passenger-190321575.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Uber driver is charged with raping a female passenger who police said fell asleep before waking up as she was attacked during a ride in metro Las Vegas. Dawed Oumer Mekonene, 30, was arrested Tuesday and remained in jail Friday pending a court hearing on charges of sexual assault and battery by strangulation to commit sexual assault, according to Clark County Detention Center records. An arrest report said Mekonene, after stopping to rape the out-of-state passenger, took her to her destination at an apartment complex, pulled her out of the car and threw her clothes and belongings at her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The leader who's standing up to China...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/the-leader-whos-standing-up-to-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave of suicides hits Texas National Guard's border mission...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-army/2021/12/23/wave-of-suicides-hits-texas-national-guards-border-mission/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operation Lone Star's sudden and rapid expansion has left many Texas guardsmen struggling to balance their military and civilian lives, sometimes with tragic results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Franco to be deposed over alleged Amber Heard affair...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/12/24/james-franco-to-be-deposed-over-alleged-amber-heard-affair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Franco has been served in the long-running legal battle between Johnny Depp and Heard and will be quizzed over whether he had an affair with the actress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's health agency admits tracking 33 million devices during lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/canadas-public-health-agency-admits-it-tracked-33-million-mobile-devices-during-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Omicron symptom: Loss of appetite...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/12/24/the-surprising-new-omicron-symptom-that-you-might-notice-at-christmas-dinner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Omicron COVID symptom could first alert you to infection as you sit down for Christmas dinner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 'warning', Tehran claims to fire 16 ballistic missiles...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/iran-says-it-fired-16-ballistic-missiles-capable-of-hitting-israel-during-drill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armed forces chief says exercise is a response to Israeli threats; Guards leader adds: We'll cut off Zionist regime's hands if they make a mistake</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kid's Father Says 'Let's Go Brandon!' on President's Christmas Call...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-kids-father-says-lets-go-brandon-live-on-air-during-president-bidens-christmas-calls/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden took it in stride when a parent blurted out "Let's go Brandon!" during a live broadcast of calls to kids tracking Santa Claus.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
