<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses lawsuit over SOUTHERN POVERTY LAW CENTER's  'hate' group labels...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/sep/16/judge-amy-berman-jackson-tosses-lawsuit-over-south/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge has thrown out a lawsuit that accused leaders of the Southern Poverty Law Center of trying to financially destroy one of the organizations that it has labeled as a hate group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein sex slave tried to swim shark-infested waters to escape...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/09/13/prosecutors-must-probe-jeffrey-epsteins-trafficking-network/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After months of torture, suddenly there was a sliver of hope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu fights for new term after decade in power...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-election/israels-netanyahu-fights-for-new-term-after-decade-in-power-idUSKBN1W12UY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu faces a battle for political survival ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABBARD: USA Acting Like Saudi Arabia's Bitch...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/09/16/saudi-trump-oil-iran-1498147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;Having our country act as Saudi Arabia's bitch is not ‘America First,’” Rep. Tulsi Gabbard of Hawaii tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Rivals Slug It Out in Second Election This Year... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israel-rivals-set-to-slug-it-out-in-the-second-election-this-year/ar-AAHouFP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT&amp;T accused of faking DIRECTV accounts to boost numbers...</title>
      <link>https://www.law.com/newyorklawjournal/2019/09/16/investors-claim-att-created-fake-streaming-service-accounts-to-hide-failure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.law.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to an amended complaint filed last week in Manhattan federal court, AT&amp;T management overreported the number of customers who had signed up for the company's $35-per-month product, leading investors to believe it was well-positioned to compete with cheaper online streaming services such as Netflix and Hulu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRADE:  In Defense of 'JOKER' and Its Violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/defense-joker-1239858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Phillips' bravura work dares to confront the things we're most afraid to see.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500,000 Apply for Yang's Free Cash Giveaway...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/09/16/andrew-yang-gets-huge-expansion-to-email-list-nearly-500000-apply-for-12k-giveaway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Yang’s offer to pay ten America families $1,000 a month for a year has drawn almost a half a million email entries. | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall St May Get $40 Billion Reprieve From Trump Regulators...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wall-street-may-40-billion-220557005.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Wall Street could soon get one of its most consequential wins of the Trump era as regulators are considering ripping up a rule that’s forced banks to set aside billions of dollars for swaps trades, according to people familiar with the matter.At issue is a requirement approved during the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRONES GROWING THREAT</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/saudi-attacks-underscore-evolving-drone-threat-experts-153814789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An attack on Saudi oil facilities at the weekend has exposed the vulnerability of the kingdom to drone strikes and underscores how traditional air defences can be breached by new low-cost technology, experts say. Saudi Arabia is one of the world's biggest buyers of weapons and spent an estimated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Has 'No Excuse for Its Military Failures'...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/saudi-arabia-no-excuse-military-160258656.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- President Donald Trump has declared that, once it has been verified that Iran was indeed responsible for last weekend’s attack on major Saudi Arabian oil facilities, the U.S. is “locked and loaded.” To do what, exactly, is unclear.Trump has previously threatened the Islamic Republic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT faces questions all around for Kavanaugh story...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b166b4bf4698411eaf2a13fdf2d4bd9c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Between an offensive tweet and a significant revision, the New York Times' handling of a new sexual misconduct allegation against Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh attracted...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 YEARS OF TRUMP TAX RETURNS SUBPOENAED</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/8-years-of-trump-tax-returns-are-subpoenaed-by-manhattan-da/ar-AAHo5K0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM walkout brings factories and warehouses to standstill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c54f47d7569c44d382995a3c3992eb53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — More than 49,000 members of the United Auto Workers went on strike Monday against General Motors, bringing more than 50 factories and parts warehouses to a standstill in the union's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY INVESTIGATIONS INTENSIFY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7b2fa6c0100a4d5cb58128676e4adbbe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City prosecutors have subpoenaed President Donald Trump's tax returns, a person familiar with the matter told The Associated Press on Monday. Manhattan District...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover most massive neutron star ever seen...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/mach/science/scientists-discover-neutron-star-so-massive-it-almost-shouldn-t-ncna1054996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sugar-cube's worth of the dead star's material has a mass of about 100 million tons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton Talking with Book Agents: 'Has Lot to Dish'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/former-trump-adviser-john-bolton-already-talking-with-book-agents-he-has-a-lot-to-dish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He penned one after leaving the Bush administration. Now, the president’s former top national-security aide is exploring another book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER breaks into scripted original content...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-tinder-television-exclusive-idUSKBN1W12CT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Popular dating app Tinder has wrapped filming on its first television series, as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Handcuffed suspects caught having sex in rear of police car...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/the-amazing-lewdinis-139285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEPTEMBER 16--While under arrest in the rear of a police car, a handcuffed Florida couple removed their clothes and began having sex, an encounter that eventually was interrupted when a sheriff’s de</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rod Stewart Reveals Secret Battle With Cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/rod-stewart-reveals-secret-battle-with-prostate-cancer-132446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch the legendary singer's courageous announcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Fires Shane Gillis Over Racist, Homophobic Comments...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/09/16/shane-gillis-fired-snl-cast-member-racist-homophobic-comments/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Live from New York, it… won’t be Shane Gillis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: 3 In 5 Americans Can't Name Single Local Congress Member...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/stumped-just-2-in-5-americans-could-name-local-congress-members/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With so much attention on the presidential campaign, how many Americans could actually name at least one of their local Congress members?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vapers seek relief -- by turning to cigarettes...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2019-09-16/vapers-seek-relief-from-nicotine-addiction-with-cigarettes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some are turning away from vaping and back to cigarettes — or taking them up for the first time — in a dangerous bid to lower their nicotine intake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado first state to ban barcodes for counting votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/16/politics/colorado-qr-codes-votes/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Citing security concerns, Colorado has become the first state to stop counting ballots with printed barcodes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Economic approval takes hit in battleground states...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/461570-trumps-economic-approval-takes-hit-in-battleground-states-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump’s economic approval numbers are declining in key battleground states and he trails a generic Democrat in the race for the White House, according to a poll conducted by Priorities USA, the nation’s lar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17th service member killed in Afghanistan this year...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/us-service-member-killed-afghanistan-1st-combat-death/story?id=65643062</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. service member was killed in action in Afghanistan on Monday, the first combat death since President Donald Trump called off peace talks with the Taliban.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami data breach exposes personal information on every Ecuadorean...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/article235137087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA sent bomb-sniffing dogs to Jordan. Now they're dying...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/16/us/jordan-dog-death-intl-hnk-scli/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bomb-sniffing dogs sent from the United States to its Middle Eastern ally Jordan are falling ill and dying due to poor treatment and negligence, a federal investigation has found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another Antonio Brown accuser comes forward...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/16/another-antonio-brown-accuser-comes-forward/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A second woman is accusing Antonio Brown of sexual misconduct, saying he inappropriately propositioned her at his Pennsylvania home in 2017 — standing behind her fully naked, holding a small …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Air Force's radical plan for future fighter...</title>
      <link>https://www.defensenews.com/digital-show-dailies/2019/09/16/the-us-air-forces-radical-plan-for-a-future-fighter-could-field-a-jet-in-5-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defensenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Air Force is seeking rapid-fire plane production as it tries to surpass the capabilities of near-peer competitors like Russia and China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injured Drew Brees out next 6 games...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/drew-brees-reportedly-needs-surgery-to-repair-torn-ligament-in-hand-could-miss-six-weeks-or-more/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saints' Drew Brees reportedly requires surgery to repair torn ligament in hand, could miss six weeks or more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Six Years in Exile, He Explains Himself...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/after-six-years-in-exile-edward-snowden-explains-himself/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a new memoir and interview, the world’s most famous whistle-blower elucidates as never before why he stood up to mass surveillance—and his love for an internet that no longer exists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS leader calls for more terror attacks on West... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9939894/isis-leader-abu-bakr-al-baghdadi-audio-message/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“BADLY injured” ISIS leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi has released a new message calling for more deadly attacks on the West – four months after he emerged from the shadows. The latest speec…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inbreeding blamed as 86 tigers die after rescue from notorious Thai temple...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/sep/16/half-of-tigers-rescued-from-thai-temple-have-died-officials-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inbreeding blamed as only 61 of 147 big cats survive after removal from tourist attraction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women UBERLYFT drivers share horror stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/women-uber-lyft-drivers-safety-rideshare-cars-14438666.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently, Lyft and Uber have taken measures to improve safety for women passengers. But what about the women drivers?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREFOX Owner Wants To Create A New Internet Without Ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90403645/mozilla-and-creative-commons-want-to-reimagine-the-internet-without-ads-and-they-have-100m-to-do-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The funds would support projects using a new “web monetization” protocol, including open source tools and individual creators</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEK TWO: Empty Seats Outnumber Fans in Several NFL Stadiums...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/09/15/weak-two-empty-seats-outnumber-fans-several-nfl-stadiums/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Week Two of the NFL's 100th season kicks off, a quick look through social media finds many fans still wondering about all the empty seats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREGG:   Trump's socialist policies...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/461505-judd-gregg-trump-is-the-almost-occasionally-pretty-close-to-socialist-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president seems to have a definite tinge of socialism in his chaotic policy closet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEELERS Lose QB Roethlisberger For Season... </title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/09/16/pittsburgh-steelers-quarterback-ben-roethlisberger-out-for-the-season-with-elbow-injury/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Steelers have announced that Ben Roethlisberger is out for the rest of the season with an elbow injury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRIKE!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/general-motors-auto-workers-call-strike-us-173343962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Auto Workers union began a nationwide strike against General Motors on Monday, with some 46,000 members walking off the job after contract talks hit an impasse. The move to strike, which the Wall Street Journal described as the first major stoppage at GM in more than a decade, came after the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SUNDAY NIGHT FOOTBALL' FALLS 30% IN DEMO...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/articles/the-sked-sunday-network-scorecard-9-15-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  Ari Emanuel's ENDEAVOR IPO to Raise Up to $700 Million...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/endeavor-ipo-to-raise-as-much-as-712-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Endeavor believes its IPO will value the company at as much as $712 million, according to a Monday filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIBI READY FOR ELECTION BATTLE!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190916-netanyahu-gantz-spur-supporters-on-eve-of-tense-israeli-polls</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netanyahu, Gantz spur supporters on eve of tense Israeli polls</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartels still causing chaos...</title>
      <link>https://www.conservativereview.com/news/even-numbers-falling-rest-border-crisis-not-solved/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.conservativereview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The smuggling and crime are as bad as ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOWDEN: I'D LIKE TO COME HOME...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/edward-snowden-nsa-cbs-this-morning-interview-today-2019-09-16/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former NSA contractor is shedding new light on his decision to reveal classified documents about the U.S. government's mass surveillance program</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REX REED: JLo Brings Trashy 'HUSTLERS' to Life...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2019/09/hustlers-review-jennifer-lopez-constance-wu-rex-reed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;J-Lo has relentless perseverance, and the qualities her fan base adore most—awesome beauty, tireless energy and more curves than a scenic railway—are very much in evident in ‘Hustlers.’…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech to spot weapons hidden under clothing on trial at train station...</title>
      <link>https://jerseyeveningpost.com/news/uk-news/2019/09/16/technology-to-spot-weapons-hidden-under-clothing-on-trial-at-train-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;jerseyeveningpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A five-day trial of the equipment began in Stratford train station in east London.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNF' RATINGS FALL...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/09/falcons-win-julio-jones-sunday-night-football-ratings-down-week-2-nfl-nbc-eagles-1202735662/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Battle of the Birds between the Atlanta Falcons and Philadelphia Eagles have seen dramatic finishes in their last two faceoffs, and last night on Sunday Night Football proved no different  &amp;#82…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pigeon Poops on Lawmaker -- Discussing Pigeon Poop Problem...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/09/16/jaime-andrade-pigeon-poop-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk about dumb luck during a Morning Insiders interview – near a very busy Chicago Transit Authority stop nicknamed the “pigeon poop station.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE bans Trump rally broadcaster from streaming...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/09/google-is-evil-youtube-censors-top-trump-media-outlet-right-side-broadcasting-network-removes-live-stream-capabilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Great Leap Backward on Free Expression...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/09/hollywoods-great-leap-backward-free-expression/598045/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing moves to co-opt the American film industry as it seeks to penetrate the world’s largest market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Issues major correction...</title>
      <link>https://www.mrctv.org/blog/nyt-corrects-their-kavanaugh-bombshell-after-internet-explodes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mrctv.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi executes 134 as crucifixions spike...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/saudi-arabia-executes-134-people-20072152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least six teens were reportedly executed this year for supposed "crimes" when they were kids</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Iranian weapons used'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-iranian-weapons-were-used-20074776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabian military officials said 'initial investigations' showed Iranian weapons were used in the attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Russia carried out 'stunning' breach of FBI comms system...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/exclusive-russia-carried-out-a-stunning-breach-of-fbi-communications-system-escalating-the-spy-game-on-us-soil-090024212.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian compounds and diplomats in the U.S. played key roles in a counterintelligence operation that stretched from the Bay Area to the nation’s capital, according to former U.S. officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RASMUSSEN: TRUMP APPROVAL 50%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/trump_administration/prez_track_sep16?fullbrowser</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Recession?</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/economics/michigan-could-be-recession-next-couple-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factory Index Slumps...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/empire-state-factory-index-remains-barely-above-zero-in-september-2019-09-16</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York Fed’s Empire State business conditions index fell 2.8 points to 2 in September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty stomachs lead to poor decisions, research says...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/world/empty-stomachs-lead-to-poor-decisions-research-says-951019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;University of Dundee scientists believe that hunger could be exploited by marketers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religions Around World Introduce Robotic 'Priests'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201909161076811116-ex-machina-religions-around-the-world-introduce-robotic-priests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mechanical ‘priest’ has recently begun conducting Buddhist prayers in Japan. It is not the first attempt to deliver religious teachings and advice through the use of a programmed machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE bans Trump rally broadcaster from streaming...</title>
      <link>https://reclaimthenet.org/youtube-livestream-right-side-broadcasting-ban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reclaimthenet.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After amassing over 300 million views since the network started, and having been funded through "super chats" by the live viewers of the broadcasts, the network is now left with a message saying, “Your ability to livestream has been revoked.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First image of mystery object approaching from interstellar space...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9936922/interstellar-object-mystery-extrasolar-space-comet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MYSTERY object from deep space heading towards our solar system has been pictured for the first time. Astronomers first spotted the extrasolar comet around two weeks ago, but the scientific world…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drug dealers peddling steroids on FACEBOOK, YOUTUBE...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Drug-dealers-are-peddling-steroids-on-Facebook-14442534.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drug dealers are turning to Facebook and other popular social media sites to peddle steroids, raising more questions about whether the companies are properly policing their platforms.  Those substances, which are illegal without a prescription, are being aggressively sold or marketed through posts and videos on sites including Facebook, Instagram, YouTube and Twitter, according to new research by Internet safety nonprofit Digital Citizens Alliance and cyberintelligence firm GiPEC. During the first half of the year, the researchers say they found more than 100 examples of such pages or posts.  Even as recently as this week, more than a dozen Facebook pages, YouTube videos and an Instagram account were selling or promoting prescription steroid and appearance enhancing drugs were still live on the platforms. After a Washington Post inquiry, the social media companies removed the pages and posts violating their terms of service, which prohibit illegal drug sales.  The posts turn devices into drug dealers, said Tom Galvin, Digital Citizens Alliance executive director. "Parents should know that," he said. Their kids are "gaining access to this online on sites that are mainstream."  The sale of these types of drugs is just the latest example of harmful and illicit content proliferating on social networks, turning the platforms into potentially dangerous places for users. Disinformation, hate speech and illegal sales continue to plague the sites, despite efforts to better moderate content both with thousands of humans and improved algorithms.  Amazon and Google recently were selling firearm and gun accessories on their sites in apparent violation of their own policies. YouTube, Facebook and Twitter played Whac-A-Mole after the Christchurch shooting in New Zealand, when the shooter's video surfaced and proliferated across the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crude spikes most in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/15/us-crude-oil-jumps-15percent-after-drone-strikes-disrupt-saudi-crude-production.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An oil processing facility at Abqaiq and the nearby Khurais oil field was attacked on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vapes spiked with illegal drugs show dark side of CBD craze...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7b452f4af90b4620ab0ff0eb2cca62cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jay Jenkins says he hesitated when a buddy suggested they vape CBD. "It'll relax you," the friend assured. The vapor that Jenkins inhaled didn't relax him. After two puffs, he ended up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Warren releases plan to tackle DC corruption...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/6539d6cff0c047f9862e72bd01a4f0af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Elizabeth Warren has released a sweeping anti-government corruption proposal, providing a detailed policy roadmap for a fight she says is at the core of her presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kremlin warns against 'hasty conclusions'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190916104544-b9qfg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-ARAMCO/RUSSIA-KREMLIN (URGENT):Kremlin warns against 'hasty conclusions' over attacks in Saudi Arabia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another tanker seized in Hormuz...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1178571/iran-news-iran-oil-tanker-Strait-of-Hormuz-gulf-saudi-arabia-uk-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN is believed to have seized another oil tanker passing through the Strait of Hormuz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain computers only rich can afford to create 'superior species'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/brain-computers-only-rich-can-20050639</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When skills and abilities can be bought rather than learned, it will be survival of the richest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive tax-the-rich push gains momentum...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/461368-progressive-tax-the-rich-push-gains-momentum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The progressive push to raise taxes on the rich is gaining new momentum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mens Suits Market Booming...</title>
      <link>http://researchnewscast.us/354/mens-suits-market-is-booming-worldwide-hugo-boss-ermenegildo-zegna-tom-ford/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;researchnewscast.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMA Research added a comprehensive research document of 200+ pages on 'Mens Suits' market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whites need not apply: Campus sci-tech symposium to only feature scholars of color...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/whites-need-not-apply-campus-sci-tech-symposium-to-only-feature-scholars-of-color/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Event at Williams College to explore sci-tech’s ‘relationship to society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK BOMBSHELL ACCUSER HAS 'NO MEMORY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/09/the-new-york-times-anti-kavanaugh-bombshell-is-actually-a-dud</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The authors omit the fact that the alleged victim has no memory of the alleged incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Takes on EU in Record $14 Billion Tax Claim...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/apple-takes-on-eu-s-vestager-in-record-14-billion-tax-battle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Takes on EUâ€™s Vestager in Record $14 Billion Tax Battle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT deletes bizarre tweet referencing Brett Kavanaugh's 'harmless' penis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/15/nyt-deletes-bizarre-brett-kavanaugh-tweet-about-having-a-penis-thrust-in-your-face/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a bizarre series of tweets and retractions on @nytopinion on Saturday, The New York Times cringingly opined on its latest Brett Kavanaugh story, then retracted the tweet, then retracted the retr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong: 100 days of huge rallies, violent clashes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/100-days-hong-kongers-sustain-protests-creativity-025120458.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Hong Kong shaken by 100 days of huge pro-democracy protests, activists have adopted a host of creative ways to fuel their movement away from the barricades. From laser pen light shows, to flashmob singalongs and human chains, we look at some of the inventive methods embraced by a movement that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoworkers cross janitors' picket lines...</title>
      <link>https://eu.freep.com/story/money/cars/2019/09/15/uaw-autoworkers-striking-janitors-flint-gm-contract-talks/2333546001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eu.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're the front line," striking janitors say at Flint GM plant as autoworkers await instructions on their next step.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers in Chicago inch closer to possible strike...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/02448262fac045dbb0b3fc5134846018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Teachers in the nation's third-largest school district are inching closer to a strike that could happen as early as next month. After rejecting the district's latest offer,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World must transform food production or face unrest, scientists warn...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190916033639-jucse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GLOBAL-ENVIRONMENT/FOOD:World must transform food production or face unrest, scientists warn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden struggles to recall the word 'escalator'...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/biden-struggles-to-recall-the-word-escalator-when-denouncing-trumps-2015-rapists-comment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic front-runner Joe Biden struggled to recall the word "escalator" while bashing President Trump during a campaign stop in Miami, Florida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-GOOGLE worker fears 'killer robots' could cause mass atrocities... </title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/sep/15/ex-google-worker-fears-killer-robots-cause-mass-atrocities</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Engineer who quit over military drone project warns AI might also accidentally start a war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RON PAUL:  BUBBLE TO BURST...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/15/ron-paul-us-interest-rates-are-going-negative.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former presidential candidate Ron Paul is warning negative interest rates will crush the global economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW:  19% of Americans considered upper class...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/14/how-many-americans-are-considered-upper-class.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About one-fifth of American adults live in "upper-income households," according to a 2018 report from Pew Research Center. Here's the median income of that group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reveals supply fragility...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/saudi-attacks-reveal-oil-supply-142715098.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The latest and most destructive attacks on Saudi oil facilities provide stark evidence of the vulnerability of global crude supply in an age of disruptive technologies that can bring a century-old industry to its knees -- at least temporarily.From remote-controlled drones to anti-ship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone attack on Saudi oil field seen as 'Pearl Harbor' moment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/drone-attack-saudi-oil-field-192155398.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- For many of the national security teams that monitor threats on the U.S., the apparent drone strike Saturday on the heart of Saudi Arabia’s oil production facilities was the realization of their worst fears.Based on early reports, multiple relatively inexpensive drone devices were able</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAW calls national strike against GM; 46,000 to stay out...</title>
      <link>https://eu.freep.com/story/money/cars/2019/09/15/uaw-strike-gm-autoworker-contract-talks/2333883001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eu.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UAW contract with GM expired at midnight Saturday and the union on Sunday called for a strike of all 46,000 GM workers in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OxyContin maker files for bankruptcy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c2780653e7934908856bfbf00eafddf1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Purdue Pharma, the company that made billions selling the prescription painkiller OxyContin, filed for bankruptcy in White Plains, New York, days after reaching a tentative settlement with many of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong: 100 days of huge rallies, violent clashes...</title>
      <link>http://www.sinodaily.com/afp/190916025133.918w1tkj.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sinodaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
