<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>China offers digital yuan as alternative...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/china-digital-yuan-bring-surveillance-state-at-expense-of-us-dollar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's emerging digital currency could enhance the yuan’s importance in the international financial system at the expense of the U.S. dollar and extend the Chinese surveillance state into wallets around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Biden billboard angers locals who are demanding removal...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/anti-biden-sign-maryland-angers-locals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pro-Trump sign in Maryland is causing a stir in the community due to its graphic language and has some calling for its removal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military AI can detect sarcasm on socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2020/05/how-ai-will-soon-change-special-operations/165487/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new SOCOM office is pursuing tools to understand and influence populations, clear rooms with robots, and spot new forms of jamming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major rioting and chaos erupt...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog-may-11-2021/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emergency declared in city, Border Police forces rushed in as synagogues, stores burned by Arab mobs; PM: terror groups will pay after unprecedented rocket fire on central Israel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dosed YANKEES Coach Tests Positive, Others Pending...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/yankees-dealing-with-covid-issues-on-coaching-staff-but-expect-to-play-series-opener-vs-rays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The team announced third-base coach Phil Nevin tested positive on Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF EMERGENCY IN VA</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/virginia-gov-ralph-northam-issues-state-of-emergency-to-address-gasoline-supply-disruptions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virginia Governor Ralph Northam has signed an executive order declaring a state of emergency in the state to address gasoline supply disruptions throughout the Commonwealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000+ GAS STATIONS RUN OUT OF FUEL</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-stations-run-out-of-fuel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 1,000 gas stations in the Southeast reported running out of fuel, primarily because of what analysts say is unwarranted panic-buying among drivers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University president caught plagiarizing speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.fitsnews.com/2021/05/11/usc-president-resigned-after-plagiarized-speech-scandal-but-board-didnt-accept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fitsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debacle at USC deepens...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD GET WORSE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/colonial-spot-gas-shortages-may-worsen-if-pipeline-doesnt-reopen-soon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If the Colonial Pipeline is not back in business by the weekend, prices could continue to rise at the pump and there will be broader localized fuel shortages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Man killed 6, self at Colorado party after not being invited...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/colorado-shootings-e66fa3c58eaff7671e6ba4d691f32a80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (AP) — A gunman who killed six people at a Colorado birthday party held by his girlfriend's family over the weekend opened fire because he had not been invited and then killed himself, police said Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIPELINE HIT</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/middle-east/israeli-energy-pipeline-hit-gaza-rocket-attack-israels-channel-12-tv-2021-05-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A pipeline belonging to an Israeli state-owned energy company was hit in a rocket attack from Gaza late on Tuesday, an Israeli government official and an energy sector official told Reuters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book portrays Secret Service riven by scandal...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-book-portrays-a-secret-service-riven-by-scandal-and-growing-pains/ar-BB1gCogj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Zero Fail’ depicts missteps, successes and evolution of the agency tasked with protecting the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COULD GET WORSE...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comould worse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comould worse&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses NRA bankruptcy in victory for New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/us-bankruptcy-judge-rejects-nra-bid-reorganize-texas-2021-05-11/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Rifle Association cannot use bankruptcy to reorganize in gun-friendly Texas, a federal judge in Dallas ruled on Tuesday, handing a defeat to the influential firearms rights group that is facing an effort to dissolve it in New York state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL RACE PREAKNESS...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/05/11/medina-spirit-permitted-to-enter-preakness-maryland-jockey-club-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite a failed drug test after the Kentucky Derby, Medina Spirit will be able to run the Preakness in Baltimore Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Van Morrison's fall from eccentric genius to conspiracy theorist...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/happened-van-morrison-fall-eccentric-215325922.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On his new album, 'Latest Record Project, Vol. 1,' Van Morrison shocked fans by espousing an array of conspiracy theories. The seeds were always there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 3 More Cars Report Windows Blown Out On SoCal Freeways...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/10/car-windows-shot-out-in-riverside-county-as-flurry-of-southland-freeway-shootings-continue/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're the latest in a series of such shootings which have taken place on multiple Southland freeways over the past several weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inheritance tax poised for comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.crainsnewyork.com/politics/inheritance-tax-poised-comeback-post-covid-era</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.crainsnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis company growing weed in Colombia goes public in US...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/11/investing/flora-growth-cannabis-ipo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most cannabis companies that list their stocks in the United States grow their products in indoor greenhouses, often in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEN GURION AIRPORT CLOSED</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/israel-hamas-launches-rocket-attack-on-tel-aviv-12303773</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The terrorist group said it had fired 130 rockets towards Tel Aviv and its suburbs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland A's to start looking at relocating elsewhere...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/mlb/story/_/id/31427293/oakland-athletics-start-looking-relocating-elsewhere-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The A's, who have played in Oakland since 1968, will look into relocating elsewhere, sources told ESPN, after years of failed plans for a new stadium. The team has asked the city council to vote on a new site prior to its late-July recess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say CDC exaggerating outdoor transmission rate...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/11/cdc-exaggerates-outdoor-transmission-rate-covid-19-experts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At issue is the research cited by the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention in touting its outdoor transmission statistic, which put the figure at a murky and allegedly too high “less …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoarding fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.starnewsonline.com/story/news/2021/05/11/colonial-pipeline-shutdown-lead-gas-lines-shortages-wilmington/5036048001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.starnewsonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Leland, the Citgo station had a long line early Tuesday, and the Scotchman on River Road in Belville was already out of gas by 10 a.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang begins leaking DC police data...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailydot.com/debug/babuk-ransomware-dc-police-leak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailydot.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of cybercriminals leaked internal files after Washington, D.C.'s police department was targeted with ransomware last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Baffert admits betamethasone ointment on Medina Spirit...</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/sports/horses/horse-racing/2021/05/11/bob-baffert-says-ointment-used-medina-spirit-includes-betamethasone/5019077001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trainer Bob Baffert says Otomax could be the source of the drug that has put Medina Spirit's victory in Kentucky Derby in jeopardy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario to give mixed doses due to ASTRAZENECA shortage...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/ontario-likely-to-mix-1st-and-2nd-vaccine-doses-amid-lack-of-astrazeneca-supply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES forced to add stops on long flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2866153/american-airlines-long-haul-flights-colonial-pipeline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMERICAN Airlines is adding extra stops to two long-haul flights so planes can refuel as a result of the cyberattack on the Colonial Pipeline.  The airline was forced to alter the schedule …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's president rallying base -- so he can expand his power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-president-is-rallying-his-base-e2-80-94-so-that-he-can-expand-his-power/ar-BB1gBnJl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our research finds that voters may encourage democratically elected leaders to undermine democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Denies Involvement in Pipeline Hacking...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world-report/articles/2021-05-11/russia-denies-involvement-in-darkside-attack-on-colonial-pipeline</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials believe Russian cybercriminals were behind a ransomware attack that shut down a major artery of America’s fuel supply, portending similar attacks on U.S. infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's blog isn't lighting up internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/trumps-blog-isnt-lighting-internet-rcna890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ex-president’s blog has drawn a considerably smaller audience than his once-powerful social media accounts, according to engagement data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci Battles With Rand Paul...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/you-are-entirely-and-completely-incorrect-watch-faucis-epic-throwdown-with-rand-paul-on-wuhan-lab-covid-theory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci and Senator Rand Paul engaged in an epic battle over the origins of the deadly Covid-19 contagion that has thus far led to the deaths of almost 600,000 Americans. There are two competing theories of its origins: one is that it emanated from wet markets in Wuhan, China that sold civets, which […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware gang threatens release of DC police records...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ransomware-gang-threatens-release-of-washington-dc-police-records</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian-speaking ransomware syndicate that stole data from the Washington, D.C., police department says negotiations over payment have broken down and it will release sensitive information that could put lives at risk if more money is not offered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUCKENMILLER:  Fed endangering dollar's reserve status with endless pumping...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/stanley-druckenmiller-says-the-fed-is-endangering-the-dollars-global-reserve-status.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fed policies could end up threatening the long-term health of the U.S. dollar, investing magnate Stanley Druckenmiller told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlyn Didn't Even Vote In 2020...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/05/11/caitlyn-jenner-cnn-interview-trump-vote/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner is attempting to defy ideological definition as she runs to unseat Gov. Gavin Newsom in California's all-but-certain recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWS QUEEN:  WASH POST names Buzbee executive editor!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ks-state-wire-sally-buzbee-donald-trump-middle-east-health-1ee82d121623381c1afad6306d892744</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Sally Buzbee, senior vice president and executive editor of The Associated Press, was named Tuesday as executive editor of The Washington Post, succeeding the recently retired Marty Baron...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customers demand 'angel' model with wings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robot-customers-demand-angel-24085045</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RealDoll teased its followers with a picture of a female mannequin with wings and a halo. The company produces a range of sex robots, some of which have incredible capabilites</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average daily U.S. Covid cases fall below 40,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/11/covid-19-cases-deaths-vaccinations-daily-update.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rate of average new Covid cases in the U.S. fell to 38,800 per day Monday, the first time daily case counts have been below 40,000 since September.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Feeling Younger Slows Aging, Protects Against Stress...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/feel-younger-protects-stress-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adults with a youthful outlook displayed stronger cognitive abilities, less inflammation, and even lived longer compared to adults who "feel old."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST names Sally Buzbee executive editor; First woman to lead newsroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/washington-post-executive-editor-c3e7a229-b2ec-44ad-9cc7-5ed09e00bf21.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She will be the first woman to lead the newsroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Home Prices Surge Most on Record in Buying Frenzy...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-home-prices-surge-most-141744748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The median price for a single-family home in the U.S. rose the most on record in the first quarter, as buyers fought over a dearth of inventory, according to the National Association of Realtors.Prices jumped 16.2% from a year earlier to a record high of $319,200. The growth eclipsed the 14.8% rate in the fourth quarter, which was the highest in data going back to 1989, the group said in a report Tuesday.Americans are taking advantage of low mortgage rates to buy homes in the suburbs and in less-costly cities across the country, where supplies are tight and bidding wars are common.“The record-high home prices are happening across nearly all markets, big and small, even in those metros that have long been considered off-the-radar in prior years for many home-seekers,” said Lawrence Yun, the group’s chief economist.The metropolitan area with the largest increase from a year earlier was Kingston, New York, a picturesque Hudson Valley town about 90 miles (145 kilometers) north of Manhattan. Prices there soared 35.5%. Fairfield County, Connecticut -- home to Greenwich -- followed, with 34.3%.Of the 183 metro areas measured by the group, 163 had double-digit price gains, up from 161 in the fourth quarter. Springfield, Illinois, was the only area where prices fell.(Updates with Fairfield County price gain in fifth paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST names Sally Buzbee executive editor; First woman to lead newsroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/media/sally-buzbee-washington-post-editor/2021/05/11/63491212-b25d-11eb-ab43-bebddc5a0f65_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The longtime journalist has led the news service since 2017, serving as Washington bureau chief before that. She succeeds Martin Baron, who retired in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAIN IMPLANT MADE MICE IMMEDIATELY BECOME FRIENDS...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/brain-implant-mice-friends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We didn't actually think this would work."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large companies 'rigged' CEO pay during pandemic, study claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/chief-executive-officer-pay-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review of filings shows companies boosted CEO comp by average of 29% in 2020, yet cut pay of regular employees by 2%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatal TESLA crash mystery intensifies: Was there driver behind wheel?</title>
      <link>https://thenextweb.com/news/fatal-tesla-crash-mystery-intensifies-was-there-a-driver-behind-the-wheel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thenextweb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NTSB released a preliminary report on the recent fatal Tesla crash in Texas. Footage shows that the owner entered the Model S' driver's door, but remains incoclusive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This dog 'flunked out' of service school. Now he's star sniffing out arson fires...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/fort-worth/article251150314.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Saginaw firefighter and his dog are trained by State Farm Insurance to investigate suspicious fires in Dallas-Fort Worth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hour waits!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/colonial-pipeline-shutdown-gas-lines-shortages-price-rises/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motorists, especially in Southern states, are finding long lines at many stations. Some are out of gas. And prices could rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far Right Ready to Claim Slice of Real Power in Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/the-far-right-is-ready-to-claim-a-slice-of-real-power-in-sweden</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Far Right Is Ready to Claim a Slice of Real Power in Sweden</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Outbreaks Threaten Status of Places That Had Virus Contained...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/outbreaks-threaten-status-places-had-081842702.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Taiwan and Singapore are reimposing pandemic restrictions as the return of a small number of virus cases challenges what have been some of the most successful places at containing and snuffing out Covid-19. In Taiwan, indoor gatherings will be limited to fewer than 100 people and outdoor events capped at 500 for the next four weeks, Taiwan’s Centers for Disease Control said in a statement Tuesday. It’s the first time the island has tightened anti-Covid measures since it began easing curbs mid-last year, and comes after the government reported seven new cases in the community and four in travelers from overseas.Singapore -- the city-state that is ranked the best place to be in the coronavirus era by Bloomberg’s Covid Resilience Ranking -- has also been tightening up restrictions amid a sudden recurrence of local infections, limiting social gatherings and upping border curbs. The co-chair of Singapore’s virus task force, Lawrence Wong, said Tuesday that companies looking to bring in foreign workers from higher-risk nations could face delays of more than six months because of the greater vigilance. The country has also begun mass testing all hospital staff in an attempt to fence off infections, after a cluster of cases emerged at a medical center.The two places are among the handful in the world that have virtually eliminated Covid domestically, among them Australia, New Zealand and China -- where cases of the new coronavirus first emerged more than a year ago. The return to tighter curbs risks disrupting what has been months of largely normal social activity in Taiwan and Singapore should the outbreaks persist.Zero ToleranceWhile having a zero tolerance approach to infections has meant very few deaths in these places, they’re now lagging countries like the U.S. and Israel on vaccination, which could put them at a disadvantage as parts of the world start to open up to international travel.Read more: Singapore Goes on Defensive as Virus Success Status at RiskAfter an initial outbreak of cases very early in the pandemic, Taiwan has managed to basically keep the virus out, even going more than eight months without a single domestic infection between April and December. The island has had just over 1,200 cases and 12 deaths in total since Covid-19 first emerged.Taiwan’s success has meant it never imposed stringent restrictions internally, like lockdowns. Businesses, government offices and schools have remained open throughout much of the pandemic, although municipal authorities canceled their usual large-scale Lunar New Year holiday celebrations in February as a precaution.Malaysia ResurgenceIn recent weeks, health authorities in Taiwan have been battling a steady rise in infections centered around a hotel used to quarantine pilots for local carrier China Airlines returning from overseas. Investors showed their concern by selling Taiwanese shares, with the benchmark Taiex index falling almost 3.8% Tuesday, the biggest decline among Asian markets. The Taiwan dollar weakened by the most since March 26.Elsewhere in Asia, cases are also coming back, with India now the epicenter of the global crisis, recording more than 329,000 new cases Tuesday. Malaysia is tightening curbs on people’s movements across the country after daily cases exceeded 3,000 this month for the first time since February. The detection of the one case with Indian Covid-19 variant has added to the risk, and Malaysia is struggling with the pace of vaccinations. Less than 3% of the population had completed their vaccination series as of May 9, data compiled by Bloomberg show. That tally trails Indonesia and Singapore, and puts Malaysia at risk of falling short of its vaccination target for the year.Read more: Malaysia Stocks, Currency Decline After Nationwide Virus CurbsThe absence of widespread infections and an export-driven economy meant Taiwan avoided the impact seen in most of the rest of the world from the pandemic. The economy grew 3.1% last year, driven by a surge in demand for Taiwan’s computer chips but also supported by a rebound in consumer spending. The government has hinted in recent weeks it may raise its 2021 gross domestic product forecast to above 5% from its current estimate of 4.6%.For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIRENS, EXPLOSIONS, JERUSALEM</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/world-news-hamas-middle-east-israel-ad7d5a99e382dcdd3e5df45f33be1b43</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — Israel unleashed new airstrikes on Gaza early Tuesday, hitting the high-rise home of a Hamas field commander and two border tunnels dug by militants, as Hamas and other armed groups fired dozens of rockets toward Israel...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9-year-old DJ scratches her way to fame...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/dubai-middle-east-entertainment-music-hip-hop-and-rap-a0052f93dd950ae60373cf3c9278f79f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Michelle Rasul had just learned to read and write and was already spinning turntables, scratching hip-hop records and making the beats drop. Four years later, at the age of 9, she’s one of the world’s top DJs and competed in this year’s global championship...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of fake fans boosts China messaging on TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/asia-pacific-china-europe-middle-east-government-and-politics-62b13895aa6665ae4d887dcc8d196dfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — China’s ruling Communist Party has opened a new front in its long, ambitious war to shape global public opinion: Western social media. Liu Xiaoming, who recently stepped down as China’s ambassador to the United Kingdom, is one of the party’s most successful foot soldiers on this evolving online battlefield...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Secretive Swiss Bank for World's Richest...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/inside-pictet-secretive-swiss-bank-040126749.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- In the mythology of private banking, Banque Pictet &amp; Cie SA stands apart. Over the course of more than two centuries, the Swiss institution has discreetly tended to the assets of the very rich, led by a small crop of partners who form the most exclusive men-only club anywhere outside the Vatican.In its entire history, only 43 individuals — all men, all white — have risen to the rank of Pictet managing partner, creating a bond more enduring than your typical marriage. From their Geneva perch, they oversee more than 600 billion francs ($662 billion) in assets under management and a level of profitability far beyond larger, publicly-listed peers, often rewarding each of them with more than 20 million francs a year. But in recent years, an unsettling new trend crept into Pictet, cracking the façade of corporate cohesion: key employees began leaving. Over the course of 2019, a dozen long-tenured relationship managers at the wealth unit departed. Within days in September of that year, four leading bankers from the team looking after Russian clients handed in their resignations. Bankers for Scandinavia and Israel followed, putting billions in assets under management at stake.At the heart of the exodus lies a culture clash. Longtime employees were bristling at the brash style of the flood of recent hires brought on to manage the money of the ultra rich, particularly the explosive growth of new wealth in Asia that has set off an aggressive race for assets and talent with bigger rivals like UBS Group AG and HSBC Holdings Plc.Yet for others, change wasn’t happening fast enough; some newcomers who had signed up to the promise of the rejuvenated Pictet were departing again in frustration.Interviews with a dozen people familiar with Pictet’s private-wealth arm reveal a business at a crossroads, confronted with the reality that, in order to stay ahead, Switzerland’s preeminent private bank must adapt. That means embracing more risk and changing the client relationship — away from the concierge-like approach that endured for generations toward a more transactional model.That can be tough for employees accustomed to the principle of caution and secrecy that guided Pictet through the centuries. But change has also brought opportunity to rethink old habits and expand the bank on the global stage.The people asked not to be identified discussing the bank’s inner workings. Pictet declined to comment for this story.While overall attrition at Pictet Wealth Management stands at an all-time low of 2.8%, the evacuation of longtime talent has reverberated through the corridors of the five-story modernist headquarters. The departures startled the partners, who viewed the outflow as an assault on an institution priding itself in flat fluctuation. So late in 2019, they gathered in a spartan conference room for what the partners call their salon meeting to learn more about what was behind the defections.Sitting in tiered formation at the large conference table, much in the same way they congregate several times a week to discuss the order of business, the men heard of tensions, a dispute over restraint and renewal rippling through the bank’s private wealth subsidiary. “Pictet is in between two worlds,” says Pedro Araujo, a senior researcher at the University of Fribourg, who has studied Switzerland’s elite families. “They are in the old world of Geneva private bankers, and the new world of globalized finance, where they want to be present internationally, they want to grow, they want to present themselves as modern, but not too much. Two worlds that are on a collision course.”For all its tradition, Pictet has become more attuned to change in recent years. The company transformed its legal status after the end of banking secrecy in 2014, disclosing more performance metrics as a result. One of its partners, Rémy Best, had already made his mark revamping the asset-management unit. Next, he turned his attention to the wealth division, long the beating heart of Pictet. It turned out that the operation required fresh blood. And the bank found it in Boris Collardi, who performed one of the most audacious maneuvers in Swiss banking in 2018 when he abruptly left as CEO of Zurich private-banking nemesis Julius Baer and decamped to the shores of Lake Geneva to join Pictet.On the face of it, Collardi is everything that the typical Pictet stakeholder is not. More bonvivant than ascetic financier, Collardi, 46, stands apart as the first outside partner in decades. He also brought serious star power and a dose of bonhomie to the Pictet franchise that values uniformity over individualism, down to the subdued color palette of the partners’ perfectly tailored suits.Collardi, by contrast, is known to greet close colleagues with a hug or a peck on the cheek; in meetings, he is the first to take off his suit jacket and jokingly complains about having to wear a tie. His ascent to the Pictet partnership not only made him one of the youngest people in recent history to hold that title, it also tipped the scale for the first time to a majority of members in the group who aren’t descendants of the founding families.In Collardi, the partners identified a peer who could pick up from Best, a longtime acquaintance who had introduced the new hire to the other partners. And Collardi was already well versed in Asia, where Pictet was keen to tap into an affluent class of newly minted billionaires preparing to pass on their wealth to the next generation.But Collardi also had to adjust to the new reality of no longer being the undisputed leader. Instead, he is now one voice among seven, where every decision is made in unison. The weekly meetings are presided over by senior partner Renaud de Planta, who declined to comment for this story. Given that the average tenure of an active partner is 20 years, collegial harmony is the glue that holds together the senior team. That hasn’t stopped Collardi from moving swiftly in his new role. Within a year, more than 100 of his loyalists had followed him to Pictet, including close to the complete teams for the Middle East and Latin America.Collardi also accelerated an overhaul of the investment and trading platforms, replacing some of the longest-serving portfolio managers with investment advisers half their age. By the end of 2020, Pictet's wealth bankers had swelled to 1,098 from 740 just five years earlier, an expansion not dissimilar to absorbing a full-blown acquisition. The changes echo the overhaul that Collardi enacted at Julius Baer. Over the course of a decade, he turbo-charged the storied private bank, sending it on a breakneck expansion from Sao Paulo to Singapore, doubling assets under management as a result. But despite his meteoric rise, Collardi remained, by his own account at the time of the move, “only an employee.” Pictet, by contrast, offered a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to become an entrepreneur with extra financial legroom but without the daily grind of running a publicly-listed company. Making Pictet partner brings a stake in a steady business whose owners share in more than 500 million francs in annual profit. Up until a few years ago, the firm was so old-fashioned that managing partners were expected to be addressed as Notre Sieur, a formal French title for sire. The challenge facing the partners is that in order to grow, they need to aggressively target Asia, the epicenter of wealth creation. But that requires the embrace of new — and potentially riskier — investment assets, chief among them structured products, which use derivatives to track the performance of an underlying asset.Collardi spent more than a year trying to win backing from the other partners to push Pictet to sell its own products in that asset class. The others weren’t convinced, priding themselves in their track record of never having endured a defaulted loan. The project was watered down in early 2020 and Pictet settled for the less-risky option of being a broker selling other bank’s structured products.Asia has nevertheless remained an important focus for Collardi’s reorganization, where he wants to break into the ranks of the top 10 private banks. For now, Pictet is willing to wait for clients to come to the bank once they are ready for a risk-averse approach to wealth management. Collardi appointed Fong Seng Tee, a banker he knew from his time at Credit Suisse Group AG, as the head for the wealth arm’s Asia division, pushing the existing leader into a more ceremonial chairmanship position. He also brought an ally over from Baer to run a new Middle East region, stripping the territory from the longtime banker who oversaw the wealth business for Greece, Turkey and the Middle East.While Pictet has steadily grown over the years, it has so far avoided the tense transitions to a modernized corporate structure embraced by other well-known former partnerships, notably Goldman Sachs Group Inc. and Lazard Ltd. Pictet may still be much smaller than publicly-listed wealth managers, but the bank packs a punch when it comes to profitability. Pictet long managed to achieve a return on equity above 40%, a number that's unheard of for any modern bank. While the figure has come down to between 16% and 21% in the past half decade, it's still a cut above UBS, Credit Suisse and Julius Baer.The transformation in 2014 into a limited partnership removed the risk of the partners bearing the full brunt of losses. As a result of the change in legal status, Pictet began publicly disclosing performance data. Suddenly, Pictet was forced to reckon with its haphazard organization that often put personal relationships before a systematic structure. Until then, it wasn’t unusual for bankers to act independently with no uniform approach to clients, for example sending out correspondence using their own fonts and letterheads. Among historic quirks, some employees didn’t have a formal work contract — joining the bank was a social compact with a benevolent patriarchy holding a protective hand over its flock. Pictet embarked on a long march into the 21st Century, guided by one of its partners. A former McKinsey executive, Rémy Best was attuned to performance metrics and organizational optimization. Fresh from turning Pictet’s asset management arm into a metric-minded profit generator, Best next set his eyes on wealth management, long a protected sanctuary at Pictet because it used to bring in the bulk of money.The bank took a hard look at which private wealth customers were bringing in the lion’s share of revenue, realizing that some were costing Pictet too much, while others still should be targeted more aggressively to buy more services.Best’s forensic approach caused a stir among employees. Pictet’s private bankers hadn’t previously been required to disclose their clients, or say how much money they were making for the bank. Personal customer relationships gave way to faceless scorecards measuring net new money, return on assets, and whether bankers met growth targets.The details were made available to an army of internal business managers poring over the numbers, often re-assigning clients by funneling them into categories based on wealth, location and level of activity with the bank. Some individual bankers lost coveted clients to new teams with regional focuses, and others bristled at what they saw as an unvarnished style of the newer hires. Still others threw up their hands and decided to leave.The tone of modern corporate efficiency can grate in a firm where former managing partner Nicolas Pictet once told his employees that retaining a client was more important than making a profit. The company has also grown past the point where partners could regularly act as rainmakers on a hard-fought deal or bringing on a big client.But as owners of a private partnership, they still stand apart from the rank-and-file. After all, a confidential calculation determines how much profit is kept for the partners and how much is distributed to the rest of the bank to support the firm’s entire equity structure. Each time a partner joins the reigning fellowship, he is required to purchase a substantial stake of the company. To finance the transaction, existing partners provide a loan to their newest member, who pays them back over time. A departing partner must start selling his share back to the bank. To support this ebb and flow of stakes, the bank aims for a minimum 20% return on equity.Maintaining that level has become harder amid mounting competition and higher compliance costs. When profitability has dropped below 20%, employees have felt the pain in their personal compensation, which contains a variable component tied to the annual results. That, in turn, has led to the perception of a growing divide between average workers and the partners, who have continued to enjoy their healthy share of profits. When employee profit participation drops, so does that of the partners, Pictet said after the article was published. During a presentation in February, a cherished Pictet ritual held online for the first time this year, de Planta laid out last year’s key numbers. The bank was buoyed like many others by the market volatility the pandemic provided — from the boom in investing revenue to a rebound in variable compensation for employees and a record number of assets under management as clients sought safety.But while the partners spoke at length about performance, charitable efforts or Pictet’s gleaming new building slowly rising on the outskirts of Geneva, one member from their group remained conspicuously absent: Collardi didn’t speak or show once during the presentation.Instead, the man most associated with Pictet’s turbulent last years had slipped into the background. (updates with company response on compensation in fourth-from-last paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans Have Been Sharing Food With Animals for Centuries. Why Is That?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/11/humans-have-been-sharing-food-with-animals-for-centuries-why-is-that/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In England and America, selling bird seed for feeders is a big business. In Delhi, people toss bits of meat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Have More Than 150 Friends?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/11/can-you-have-more-than-150-friends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Just how many friends can one person have? In a 1993 study, Robin Dunbar, a British anthropologist, theorized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24 other businesses targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9564961/Hackers-launched-cyberattacks-24-companies-Colonial-Pipeline-shutdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least two dozen other victims - who have not been named - were also affected by the ransomware attack, Bloomberg reported. The Colonial Pipeline was shut down on Friday,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF releases footage of retaliatory strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/idf-releases-footage-of-strike-on-hamas-members-launching-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC limits reviews of vaccinated but infected, spurring concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/cdc-limits-review-of-vaccinated-but-infected-draws-concern/ar-BB1gx1au?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Federal health officials this month decided to limit how they monitor vaccinated people who have been infected with Covid-19, drawing concern from some scientists who say that may mean missing needed data showing why and how it happens. At the end of April, more than 9,000 Americans were reported to be infected after being vaccinated, according to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. While that’s a tiny percentage...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tel Aviv opens up citywide bomb shelters...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/tel-aviv-opens-up-citywide-bomb-shelters-following-rockets-launched-667800</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The cities of Givatayim, Ramat Gan and Bnei Brak have made similar announcements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hamas fires over 150 rockets into Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/cogat-announces-closure-of-gaza-border-crossing-over-rocket-fire-667730</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of roads and train lines in southern Israel were closed due to security concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tinderbox burst into flames...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/arab-israeli-conflict/dont-let-the-jerusalem-tinderbox-become-an-inferno-analysis-667763</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rockets will pound Israel, and a Hamas or PIJ cell in the West Bank or from Gaza could attack the IDF or Israeli civilians.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 other businesses targeted...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9564219/Gas-stations-begin-run-fuel-cyberattack-Colonial-Pipeline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Motorists in Atlanta on Monday night were complaining that gas stations were empty, as a consequence of the shutdown of the 5,500-mile Colonial Pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Resistance Is Ready'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/israel-jerusalem-violence-palestinians-wounded-2021-05-10/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel's army said it launched airstrikes on Gaza, in response to rockets fired by Hamas militants after hundreds of Palestinians were hurt in clashes at a religious site.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis to hold NEWSMAX town hall...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/552717-desantis-to-hold-newsmax-town-hall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax announced Monday that Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) will hold a town hall on the channel later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly contagious variant emerges in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/highly-contagious-brazilian-covid-19-variant-emerges-in-florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new mutation of the highly-contagious Brazilian COVID-19 variant, dubbed P2 or P.1.1, has emerged in Florida, health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOCK:  NBC will not air GOLDEN GLOBES...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/05/golden-globes-canceled-nbc-2022-hfpa-1234753314/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There will be no Golden Globes on NBC in 2022, as the besieged Hollywood Foreign Press Association continues to falter in reforming itself to the satisfaction of Hollywood studios and stakeholders.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endangered wolves to be housed at Ted Turner ranch in New Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nm-state-wire-ted-turner-new-mexico-wolves-lifestyle-c0e4fd9d9ef2b74f5ad8eb78fecf1046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBUQUERQUE, N.M. (AP) — One of Ted Turner’s ranches in southern New Mexico will be the new home for a pair of Mexican gray wolves and their pups as federal wildlife managers look at more options for boosting the genetic diversity of the endangered species...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy set to rout Cheney and move past 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2021/05/10/mccarthy-needs-to-rout-cheney-to-move-past-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANALYSIS — McCarthy hopes that ousting Cheney will satisfy pro-Trump GOP voters and allow him to move on to attacking Democrats’ failings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime becomes defining issue of NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-crime-mayoral-race-defining-issue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some candidates for mayor of New York are making crime above and below ground in the city a campaign issue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech's next move: Private cities without govt control...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/tech-bros-next-move-private-cities-without-government-control/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After dominating Silicon Valley in the past two decades, hiking up rent prices in the area and filling the streets with flannel vests and wool sneakers, they’re now spreading into other regio…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALLAHAN: Hollywood just now realizes the awards are ridiculous?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/10/hollywoods-hypocritical-protest-of-the-golden-globes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Such perfect timing, now that viewership has tanked and there is seemingly no awards show — not the Oscars or the Grammys or the CMAs or the SAGs or anything, really — that America wants to see.…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN 63% APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/biden-coronavirus-approval-rating-efcc859a21a0ab6c43dfb4157987bf80</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden is plunging into the next phase of his administration with the steady approval of a majority of Americans, according to a new poll from &lt;a href="https://apnorc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ground-breaking AI now predicting earthquakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/groundbreaking-ai-used-predict-earthquakes-24080538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tool, called DeepShake, is being developed in the US to give several seconds of advance notice that earthquakes are on the way. It uses a deep neural network, a form of AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Man attacked mom with taser on Mother's Day...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/mothers-day-shocker-521903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAY 10--The most shocking Mother’s Day gift this year was the handiwork of a Wisconsin man, records show. During a disturbance yesterday afternoon, a 43-year-old woman was tased in the neck by her s</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
