<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Weightlifter wins gold on ONE LEG!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/tokyo-olympics-2020/3348040/weightlifter-li-fabin-flamingo-gold-tokyo-2020-olympics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEIGHTLIFTER Li Fabin blew away the competition in the men’s 61kg weightlifting category using a bizarre ONE-LEGGED lift to win gold at the Tokyo Olympics. Li used a unique stance to correct …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL:  APPLE AirDrop causes chaos on board packed flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3348557/apple-airdrop-threat-united-flight-passengers-photo-gun/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PASSENGERS of a United flight were left terrified due to ”threat on board” after they received a photo of a gun via Apple’s AirDrop. The bizarre incident took place on Thursday wh…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron pushes for Israeli inquiry into spyware...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/25/emmanuel-macron-pushes-for-israeli-inquiry-into-nso-spyware-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French president reportedly spoke to Naftali Bennett to ensure ‘proper investigation’ after Pegasus project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They had a date to kill the cow. So I stole her': How vegan activists are saving farm animals...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/24/how-vegan-activists-are-saving-spains-farm-animals</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spain may be famous for its love of meat – but sanctuaries across the country are coming to the rescue of its doomed cows, bulls, pigs, sheep and geese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hospitalized radio host was outspoken skeptic...</title>
      <link>https://www.tennessean.com/story/news/2021/07/25/wtn-radio-host-phil-valentine-knows-he-very-sick-covid-19/8086143002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tennessean.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nashville radio host Phil Valentine, who in the past has been skeptical about vaccination against COVID-19, is now hospitalized with the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers link 'heavy wildfire smoke' to increased risk of contracting covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.rgj.com/story/news/2021/07/25/wildfire-smoke-increased-risk-contracting-covid-19/8086294002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rgj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are proposing that there is a link between air pollution and an increased risk of contracting COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump encourages MAGA to boo US women's soccer...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/sports/tokyo-summer-olympics/trump-encourages-gop-crowd-to-boo-u-s-womens-soccer-team/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics crossed over with a Donald Trump rally Saturday night, as the former president encouraged a hyped-up Phoenix crowd to boo the U.S. Women’s soccer team. The political action committee Turning Point Action sponsored the “Protect Our Elections Rally,” which turned into a wide-ranging attack on fellow Republicans, the military, the press, “woke” culture — and eventually U.S….</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASKETBALL ROBOT STEALS SHOW AT OLYMPICS</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/25/scary-looking-robot-steals-the-show-at-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maybe all Team USA basketball needs is a robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pollution turns Argentina lake bright pink...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pollution-turns-argentina-lake-bright-210112998.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lagoon in Argentina's southern Patagonia region has turned bright pink in a striking, but frightful phenomenon experts and activists blame on pollution by a chemical used to preserve prawns for export.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crist rips DeSantis over spike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/broward-charlie-crist-rips-gov-234400087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic gubernatorial hopeful Charlie Crist attacked Gov. Ron DeSantis on Sunday, accusing him of playing Republican presidential politics on the Texas border — while COVID-19 infections are rising and people are dying in Florida. During a campaign appearance in Broward County, Crist pointed to the recent increase in COVID-19 infections, hospitalizations and deaths. “You know what’s ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California man who mocked vaccine dies of virus...</title>
      <link>https://nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/california-man-who-mocked-covid-19-vaccine-dies-of-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man who mocked COVID-19 vaccinations has died at a Los Angeles-area hospital after contracting the virus. Stephen Harmon was 34.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster shots on horizon...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/commentary-covid-vaccine-booster-shot-pfizer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In today’s pharmaceutical universe, a simple “safe and effective” determination by the Food and Drug Administration to approve a drug can be manipulated to sell products of questionable value. And …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci warns going in wrong direction...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-anthony-fauci-masks-70585010748808ce2284cfc19b608e47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — The United States is in an “unnecessary predicament” of soaring COVID-19 cases fueled by unvaccinated Americans and the virulent delta variant, the nation’s top infectious diseases expert said Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swimming team does just fine without Phelps...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-entertainment-sports-coronavirus-pandemic-99835fa2a33934f84035d1e7f225366f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Michael Phelps was up in his broadcast seat, a mere observer rather than the driving force of U.S. swimming. No need to fret about what he left behind. The Americans are off to a flying start at the Tokyo Aquatics Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ggymnasts, tired of sexualization, wears 'unitards'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-gymnastics-germany-unitard-7f5adad73b0a75d263b5d3f57c2f9bd0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The team’s outfits looked similar to the others in the room as the arena lights gleamed off crystals crisscrossing their chests and down their crimson and white sleeves. But the German gymnastics team’s new Olympic suits didn’t stop at their hips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF Bars Now Requiring Proof of Vaccination...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/san-francisco/sf-bars-now-requiring-proof-of-vaccination/2604682/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcbayarea.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The majority of bar owners in San Francisco are in favor of requiring proof of vaccination for indoor customers to keep both staff and patrons safe as coronavirus continues to spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan beheaded by Taliban for brief stint as US Army translator....</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/afghan-beheaded-by-taliban-for-brief-stint-as-us-army-translator-report-674816</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Taliban promised that no harm will come to the tens of thousands of Afghans who cooperated with foreign forces, but many in the country do not feel safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police trace everyone who broke rules, fine for 'filthy, risky behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jul/25/covid-sydney-police-punish-anti-lockdown-protesters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime minister denounces ‘selfish’ protesters who marched against coronavirus measures as police taskforce traces everyone who broke rules</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Wants to Add Rep. Kinzinger to Jan. 6 Committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-nancy-pelosi-says-shes-speaking-to-gop-rep-kinzinger-about-joining-january-6-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi said on Sunday her plan is to name Congressman Adam Kinzinger (R- IL) to the January 6 select committee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious life of Bay Area's 82-year-old bodybuilding cowboy...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/characters/article/bay-area-bodybuilder-cowboy-artist-16304506.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His story begins on a 300-acre farm in San Luis Obispo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ declines to investigate Cuomo's handling of Covid in nursing homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/doj-declines-to-investigate-cuomo-s-handling-of-covid-19-in-nursing-homes/ar-AAMwGwL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Justice has turned down a request from several Republican Congressmen to open a civil investigation into New York and three other states that admitted patients to nursing homes at the start of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Wants You to Connect With God. On FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/25/facebook-wants-you-to-connect-with-god-on-facebook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Months before the megachurch Hillsong opened its new outpost in Atlanta, its pastor sought advice on how to build a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly white supremacist prison gangs rise on feds' radar...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/doj-charges-against-unforgiven-show-110137191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside the public eye on Oath Keepers and Proud Boys, feds are trying to stem a deadlier threat: white supremacists operating in and out of prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly 'untreatable fungus' resistant to all medication spreading rapidly...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/deadly-untreatable-fungus-resistant-medication-24610928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 'deadly fungal infection' that can be resistant to all existing treatments has been worrying health officials following recent outbreaks in hospitals and care homes around the USA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploited Hollywood Assistants Fed Up, Fighting Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/youre-dying-for-your-dream-exploited-hollywood-assistants-are-at-their-breaking-point-and-fighting-back</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No movie or TV show could function without assistants, yet many are stuck making minimum wage. Enough, they say. “If you’re not gonna promote us, you’ve got to pay us.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands defy Orban with festive Pride parade backing gay rights in Hungary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/hungary-gay-pride-parade-2021-lgbtq-budapest-viktor-orban/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEPs and embassies express support to community targeted by new legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's Gymnasts Have Surprisingly Rough Start...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/sections/tokyo-olympics-live-updates/2021/07/25/1020328400/u-s-womens-gymnasts-have-a-surprisingly-rough-1st-day-of-olympic-competition</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few stumbles from U.S. gymnasts – including from star Simone Biles – allowed Russia's team to take the lead. The U.S. is the heavy favorite. Russia came out one point ahead with the total team score</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's Great Salt Lake drops to lowest level ever recorded...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/utahs-great-salt-lake-drops-lowest-level-recorded/story?id=79037767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USGS said Saturday it was about an inch below the previous record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free money for all? Mayors hope local tests bring big change...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/free-money-for-all-mayors-hope-local-tests-bring-big-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In experiments across the country, dozens of cities and counties and the state of California are giving some low-income residents a guaranteed income of $500 to $1,000 each month to do with as they please, and tracking what happens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India expected to seek new Russian stealth fighter to counter China...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/military/article/3142369/india-expected-seek-new-russian-stealth-fighter-amid-ongoing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fifth-generation Checkmate is likely to offer advanced stealth capability but will sell at a much lower cost than the US’ F-35.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany warns unvaccinated may face restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-germany-a46d18ff239dcbc71973cd1052c3866b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — German Chancellor Angela Merkel’s chief of staff has warned that restrictions for unvaccinated people may be necessary if COVID-19 infection numbers reach new heights in the coming months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEDIAN JACKIE MASON DEAD AT 93...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/jackie-mason-who-turned-kvetching-into-comedy-gold-dies-at-93/600081181/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former rabbi, Mason made comic capital as a Jew feeling his way — sometimes nervously, sometimes pugnaciously — through a perplexing gentile world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z 'nowstalgia' leading to thrifting explosion...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/pop-culture/pop-culture-news/gen-z-s-nowstalgia-y2k-fashion-leading-thrifting-explosion-n1274720</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iconic fashion trends of the early 2000s like bucket hats, low-rise jeans, and babydoll T-shirts are all having a resurgence among younger consumers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelans Enduring Day-Long Waits to Fill Gas Tanks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/venezuelans-enduring-day-long-waits-220448641.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Venezuela’s capital city is once again rationing gasoline after output at state-owned refineries slumped, forcing motorists to endure day-long queues to top off tanks.Shortages have returned to Caracas, prompting drivers to prowl the streets for open filling stations as lines stretch for blocks in some areas. Because of breakdowns at Petroleos de Venezuela SA fuel-making plants, gasoline output has crashed by more than 40% since the end of June, according to two sources with knowl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASK MANDATES RETURN...</title>
      <link>https://www.insider.com/cities-revive-covid-19-mask-mandates-sparking-backlash-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mask mandates have provoked outrage. One town councilman in California even called the policy "BS" and vowed not to enforce it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man used AI to bring back deceased fiance. Tech creators freak...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/man-used-ai-to-talk-to-late-fiance-experts-warn-tech-could-be-misused-2021-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man used artificial intelligence (AI) to mimic speaking to his late fiancé. The creators of the technology warn that it could be used for misinformation campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politicians threaten to prolong...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/australians-may-face-longer-lockdown-022624032.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MELBOURNE (Reuters) -Australia's New South Wales logged its second-highest daily increase of the year in locally acquired COVID-19 cases on Sunday amid fears of a wave of new infections after thousands of people joined an anti-lockdown protest. There were 141 COVID-19 cases reported, down from 163 a day earlier. Under fire for a slow vaccine rollout, Prime Minister Scott Morrison said more vaccine supply was not going to ensure New South Wales gets out of lockdown, but what was needed was an effective, properly enforced lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Pyramid-sized asteroid to fly close to Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-science/great-pyramid-sized-asteroid-to-fly-close-to-earth-674818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The asteroid is considered potentially hazardous, with a possible height of 220 meters (720 feet), but it is expected to fly safely without impacting the planet.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
