<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Unvaxxed Bolsonaro appears to break 'honor system' during address...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-e2-80-99s-unvaccinated-bolsonaro-appears-to-break-un-vaccine-e2-80-98honor-system-e2-80-99-during-address/ar-AAOFq3J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nations claimed there was an "honor system" to ensure vaccination among world leaders. Bolsonaro spoke anyway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jon Stewart returns with APPLE news show...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/the-problem-with-jon-stewart-trailer-1235017441/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer is teasing its forthcoming "The Problem With Jon Stewart," which will apparently include the former "Daily Show" host grilling U.S. Secretary of the Treasury Janet Yellen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BIDEN APPROVAL 50%...</title>
      <link>https://americanresearchgroup.com/economy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;americanresearchgroup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States embrace vaccine mandates despite potential worker exodus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/states-embrace-vaccine-mandates-despite-potential-worker-exodus/article_a6da7691-849f-5bbe-b949-bf9efe0bd5b6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden soon will require millions of workers to get vaccinated against COVID-19 or be tested weekly. But before Biden's announcement earlier this month, 18 states and the District</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WORLD AT INFLECTION POINT'</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/united-nations-general-assembly-joe-biden-6dd0382e93987500d714f9fa497602af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UNITED NATIONS (AP) — President Joe Biden used his first address before the U.N.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keys To Happy Life = Exercise, Eating Fruits &amp; Veg?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fruit-vegetables-happy-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These lifestyle changes make people happier in comparison to individuals who are already eating lots of healthy produce or those keeping their same old diet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGH STAKES AT UN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/world/live-news/un-general-assembly-09-21-21/h_d360a50408be147a7b3d200be7552fd6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World leaders are gathering in New York City for the 76th session of the UN General Assembly. Follow here for the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memo shows Donald lawyer six-step plan for Pence to overturn election...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/20/politics/trump-pence-election-memo/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A conservative lawyer working with then-President Donald Trump's legal team tried to convince then-Vice President Mike Pence that he could overturn the election results on January 6 when Congress counted the Electoral College votes by throwing out electors from seven states, according to the new book "Peril" from Washington Post journalists Bob Woodward and Robert Costa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Americans Leaving Country To 'Reclaim Destiny' In Ghana...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/black-americans-leave-racism-in-us-to-reclaim-destiny-in-ghana/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sonjiah Davis had a good life in Washington D.C., but she "never felt safe." Like many others, she's discovered that "home is not a place. It's how you feel where you are."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Far-Right Pundit Surges in Polling for Presidential Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/french-far-right-pundit-surges-in-polling-for-presidential-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Far-Right Pundit Surges in Polling for Presidential Race</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Humans Lost Their Tails...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/21/how-humans-lost-their-tails/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For half a billion years or so, our ancestors sprouted tails. As fish, they used their tails to swim through</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iPhone 13 Review: The Most Incremental Upgrade Ever...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/21/apple-iphone-13-review-the-most-incremental-upgrade-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The truth is that smartphones peaked a few years ago. After so many advances, the miniature computers have reached incredible</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Some wanted me dead:' Pope acknowledges critics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-religion-pope-francis-slovakia-bratislava-f018aeb6e5d420703822ef75aed6272c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Pope Francis has acknowledged his increasingly vocal conservative critics, saying their “nasty comments” were the work of the devil and adding that “some wanted me dead” after his recent intestinal surgery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shocking scenes from Del Rio tent camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/on-the-ground-at-the-del-rio-migrant-tent-camp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas — Yellow police tape is all there is holding back a small city’s worth of migrants from escaping the underbelly of an international bridge where they have camped out for days and become increasingly on edge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will efforts to cheat death benefit humanity -- or elite few?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/21/silicon-valleys-quest-to-live-forever-could-benefit-the-rest-of-us.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of tech billionaires have decided they want to use their enormous wealth to try and help humans "cheat death."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How pandemic helped scatter $1-million homes across LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/business/story/2021-09-21/covid-changed-la-real-estate-making-one-million-homes-common-place</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 unleashed new demand for homes, made the well-off wealthier, and fueled extreme bidding wars. The result? The $1-million home is everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Fran mayor blasted for dancing maskless at club. She called critics 'fun police'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/san-francisco-e2-80-99s-mayor-blasted-for-dancing-maskless-at-a-crowded-club-she-called-her-critics-the-e2-80-98fun-police-e2-80-99/ar-AAOEFpf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Like, we don’t need the fun police to come in and try and micromanage and tell us what we should or shouldn’t be doing," San Francisco Mayor London Breed said after being recorded at a club maskelss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLErs Protest Removal of Russian App as Bend to Govt...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/googlers-protest-removal-of-russian-app-as-bend-to-government/ar-AAOEECw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google employees have joined the slew of politicians and activists blasting the internet giant for pulling a voting app from Russia’s opposition leader, a move critics say showed the company was caving in to the Kremlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LYFT built brand on being nice gig work app clad in pink. Its drivers paint different picture...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/lyft-built-a-brand-on-being-the-nice-gig-work-app-clad-in-pink-its-drivers-paint-a-different-picture/ar-AAOF3Ja</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyft has taken a different approach than its rival to driver accommodations. Critics say it reflects a more relaxed attitude toward drivers’ concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-intelligent sex robots will make owners 'slaves'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/sex-robots-ai-become-super-24932155</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE Pricier sex robots have already been equipped with a range of artificial intelligence features, with customers shelling out thousands on groundbreaking synthetic companions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne police fire pepper balls, pellets to break up protest...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210921102347-qwxze</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/AUSTRALIA (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-Melbourne police fire pepper balls, pellets to break up COVID-19 protest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border crossers on school buses? TX town caught in middle...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210921075936-58tyv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/BORDERTOWN (PIX):Migrants on school buses? Texas town feels caught in the middle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German officials fear anti-mask radicalization after killing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-arrests-germany-5c853b4e068e1203b890652cc96e8a5c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Senior politicians in Germany expressed shock over the weekend killing of a young gas station clerk who asked a customer to wear a face mask, and they warned Tuesday against the radicalization of people who oppose the country's pandemic restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of Pilots Looms as Next Challenge for Airlines...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/a-shortage-of-pilots-looms-as-the-next-challenge-for-airlines/ar-AAOEuZV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being thrust into crisis by the coronavirus, the aviation industry faces yet more trouble as the world emerges from the worst of the pandemic to find there’s now likely to be a shortage of pilots after thousands were laid off or decided to retire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People worried about going back to office because don't want to poo at work...</title>
      <link>https://www.indy100.com/news/return-to-office-poo-survey-b1923859</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indy100.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “pan-xiety” of going back into the office is real, and there is one symptom that some people are particularly worried about as a result... poo paranoia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi 15-week abortion ban gets trial date...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/573033-supreme-court-to-hear-mississippis-15-week-abortion-ban-case-dec-1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court announced Monday it will hear arguments Dec. 1 on a Mississippi abortion restriction that poses a direct challenge to the landmark 1973 ruling in Roe v. Wade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock-market fall may be sign of more serious trouble ahead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/20/mondays-stock-market-fall-may-be-a-sign-of-trouble-ahead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow dropped 614 points yesterday, its worst day since October 2020 — and most analysts blamed worries about Chinese real estate. That would seem an odd thing to be causing such fear and loathin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their Baby Died in Hospital. Then Came $257,000 Bill...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/21/their-baby-died-in-the-hospital-then-came-the-257000-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brittany Giroux Lane gave birth to her daughter, Alexandra, a few days before Christmas in 2018. The baby had dark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Begin Effort to Curb Post-Trump Presidential Powers...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/21/democrats-begin-effort-to-curb-post-trump-presidential-powers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — House Democrats are planning to introduce a package of proposed new limits on executive power on Tuesday, beginning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand Cops Arrest Men Entering Locked-Down City With 'Large Amounts' of Illicit KFC...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-zealand-cops-arrest-men-entering-locked-down-city-with-large-amounts-of-illicit-kfc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they found at least three buckets of chicken, 10 tubs of coleslaw, and a big stash of fries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Member of CIA chief's team reports Havana syndrome symptoms...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/20/politics/cia-director-havana-syndrome-india-trip/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When CIA Director Bill Burns traveled to India earlier this month a member of his team reported symptoms consistent with Havana syndrome and had to receive medical attention, according to three sources familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden steps onto global stage with high-stakes UN speech...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/573117-biden-steps-onto-global-stage-with-high-stakes-un-speech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden faces high stakes on the global stage as he takes his plea for international cooperation on pressing issues like climate change and the coronavirus to the United Nations General Assembly on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Afghans fell from plane, families live with horror...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/soccer-sports-afghanistan-middle-east-kabul-58a4e0a9c6343ab78a1985df31e2d729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — It’s a scene that has come to symbolize the chaotic end to America’s 20 years of war in Afghanistan: A lumbering U.S. Air Force cargo plane takes off from Kabul airport, chased by hundreds of desperate Afghan men scrambling to get on the aircraft.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew served sex assault suit in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/uk/prince-andrew-is-served-accusers-sexual-assault-lawsuit-united-states-lawyers-2021-09-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain's Prince Andrew has been served with a sexual assault lawsuit in the United States by lawyers for a woman who says she was forced to have sex with him at the London home of a friend of convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein, court papers show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigation launched into agents on horseback chasing migrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/20/investigation-border-agents-horseback-migrants-513237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security has also sent extra personnel to oversee the situation in Texas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Options shrink for Haitians straddling Texas border...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mexico-texas-caribbean-united-states-immigration-931593e957bf0a8a4cfd691ecedd8211</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DEL RIO, Texas (AP) — The options remaining for thousands of Haitian migrants straddling the Mexico-Texas border are narrowing as the United States government ramps up to an expected six expulsion flights to Haiti Tuesday and Mexico began busing some away from the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nerves on edge on Spanish island as quakes, lava threaten...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-africa-environment-and-nature-canary-islands-european-union-431141b6d75824e6480d2be30ed1eee6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL PASO, Canary Islands (AP) — Several small earthquakes shook the Spanish island of La Palma off northwest Africa in the early hours of Tuesday, keeping nerves on edge as rivers of lava continued to flow toward the sea and a new vent blew open on the mountainside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big gamble pays off... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/federal-general-election-results-2021-1.6182364</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbc.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liberal Leader Justin Trudeau will win enough seats in this 44th general election to form a government, the CBC News decision desk has projected. It's still too early to say whether it will be a minority or majority government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden UN speech will try to world that 'America is back'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/20/biden-un-speech-multilateral-diplomacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But president will contend with skepticism in wake of Aukus, disagreements over Israel and the chaotic Afghanistan withdrawal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK:  Zuckerberg agreed not to fact-check Trump posts in exchange for lenient regulation...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10009669/Peter-Thiel-said-Zuckerberg-agreed-Trump-push-state-sanctioned-conservatism-new-book-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Max Chafkin's new book 'The Contrarian: Peter Thiel and Silicon Valley's Pursuit of Power,' writes that Thiel attended the meeting then told an associate of the alleged deal between Zuckerberg and Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org Prosecutors Find New Evidence in a Basement...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/new-york-prosecutors-find-new-evidence-in-donald-trump-organization-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lawyer for Trump Organization chief financial officer Allen Weisselberg revealed in open court that prosecutors have found more evidence and that more indictments are expected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Targets 'Effeminate' Men in Xi's Mounting Push for Conformity...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-20/china-slams-effeminate-men-in-xi-s-mounting-push-for-conformity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a low-cut midriff top, butt-hugging pants and a bold red lip, Beijing photographer Alain would be hard to miss even in the most crowded party. People stare, he said, and he loves it: “It’s totally a rebellion against conservative culture.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Deserted Factories Show How China Electric Car Boom Went Too Far...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/deserted-factories-show-how-china-electric-car-boom-went-too-far</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big gamble... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/canada-health-elections-toronto-coronavirus-pandemic-ddfc4d35fb45559f096bc76f7106949b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Canadians voted Monday in a pandemic election that could weaken Prime Minister Justin Trudeau or reward his government’s handling of the pandemic. Trudeau gambled on an early election to try to capitalize on the fact that Canada is now among the most fully vaccinated countries in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Lindsey Graham, Mike Lee vetted Trump fraud claims. They were unpersuaded...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/lindsey-graham-and-mike-lee-personally-vetted-trump-e2-80-99s-fraud-claims-new-book-says-they-were-unpersuaded/ar-AAOCY9m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Peril,” by Bob Woodward and Robert Costa, reveals how far the two Republicans went in examining the president’s fraud claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE REVOKES COVID TRAVEL BAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/us-to-ease-travel-restrictions-for-foreign-visitors-who-are-vaccinated-against-covid.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration will also require unvaccinated U.S. citizens to test a day before departure and after they return home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TIKTOK Challenge Inspires Students To Steal From And Vandalize Schools...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/09/20/tiktok-devious-licks-viral-challenge-vandalism-stealing-in-schools/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The challenge has spread here locally, with districts from New Jersey to Connecticut reporting thousands of dollars in damage while issuing warnings to students and parents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to lift refugee cap to 125,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/20/biden-administration-us-refugee-cap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plan comes as tens of thousands of Afghan refugees are on military bases awaiting resettlement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salvadoran president declares himself 'dictator' in apparent joke...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210920211837-pke2l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EL SALVADOR-BUKELE/:Salvadoran president declares himself 'dictator' in apparent joke</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago mayor pitches $500 monthly payments to poor families...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-chicago-lori-lightfoot-43f3d6583e4dbf1ceae98bcc23220ee5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Chicago Mayor Lori Lightfoot pitched a pilot program Monday giving $500 monthly payments to 5,000 low-income households, part of the city's proposed $16.7 billion spending plan that relies on an infusion of federal relief funds to close budget gaps for several years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Deaths Than Births In Alabama In Grim First...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/20/1038950564/alabama-deaths-births-2020-coronavirus-surge-vaccination-rate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama's top health official says the state has "literally shrunk." According to preliminary data, it saw 64,714 total deaths and 57,641 births in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House: Border Patrol with whip 'obviously horrific'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/white-house-says-images-border-patrol-whip-obviously-horrific-n1279663</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Press secretary Jen Psaki called the images "horrible," but said she could not yet address what the consequences would be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Dating App Launches 'Pro-Choice Badge'...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/culture/top-dating-app-launches-pro-choice-badge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top dating app will donate to Planned Parenthood for every user who promotes abortion on its platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter coming -- again...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2021/09/20/winter-is-coming-again-what-to-expect-from-covid-19-as-the-season-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some see hope for the Delta surge to wane, but a rebound of the flu this winter could bring other complications, experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American death toll surpasses Spanish Flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/covid-is-americas-deadliest-pandemic-as-us-fatalities-near-1918-flu-estimates.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reported U.S. deaths due to Covid crossed 675,000, Johns Hopkins data shows, and is still increasing at an average of more than 1,900 fatalities per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington gridlock, debt-ceiling showdown weigh on market...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/20/washington-gridlock-and-a-debt-ceiling-showdown-are-weighing-on-the-market.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Strategists say the renewed sell-off in U.S. markets on Monday is in part thanks to partisan gridlock in Congress over the debt ceiling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Pleads Not Guilty To Sexually Assaulting 5 Women In LA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/09/20/harvey-weinstein-pleads-not-guilty-to-sexually-assaulting-5-women-in-la/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former movie mogul is charged with sexually assaulting five women at L.A. area hotels from 2004 to 2013.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Vax Eric Clapton Breaks Vow, Plays Venue With Vaccine Mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/eric-clapton-vaccine-mandate-show-smoothie-king-1229285/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musician who swore never to play a vaccine-mandate show goes ahead and does just that in New Orleans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL-ERIAN: Crackdowns shaking notion that it's 'investable market'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/the-evergrande-crisis-and-china-s-regulatory-crackdowns-are-shaking-the-notion-that-china-is-an-investable-market-says-mohamed-el-erian/ar-AAODLGg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The potential collapse of homebuilder Evergrande "is shaking key tenants of this global investment theme," renowned economist El-Erian said on CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON AI Cameras Punishing Drivers for Mistakes They Didn't Make...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/88npjv/amazons-ai-cameras-are-punishing-drivers-for-mistakes-they-didnt-make</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon delivery drivers say surveillance cameras installed in their vans have made them lose income for reasons beyond their control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Burns Says Current Times 'Equal' to Civil War...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/one-of-the-worst-times-ever-in-american-history-ken-burns-says-current-times-equal-to-civil-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documentary filmmaker Ken Burns said that the present day is one of the worst times in American history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver debates civilians be given law-enforcement powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.westword.com/news/homeless-denver-hancock-street-enforcement-team-city-county-12359179</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.westword.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Street Enforcement Team will hit the streets in October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALMART worker quits in profanity-laced tirade over loudspeakers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/walmart-worker-resigns-over-store-loudspeakers-f-k-this-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Walmart worker quit in a profanity-laced tirade over the Louisiana store’s loudspeakers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovered from virus and traveling to Israel? No test required...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/recovered-from-covid-and-traveling-to-israel-no-pcr-test-required-679867</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To qualify, travelers must have tested positive between 11 days and three months prior * Health Ministry drops Mexico from list of red countries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of bees kills dozens of endangered penguins...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/world/2021/09/swarm-of-bees-kills-dozens-of-endangered-african-penguins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A swarm of bees has killed 63 endangered African penguins on a beach outside Cape Town, the Southern African Foundation for the Conservation of Coastal Birds said on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Fundraising at Record-Breaking Pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-fundraising-at-record-breaking-pace-ahead-of-midterms/ar-AAODAZA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Democratic National Committee raised $9.9 million in August bringing its 2021 total to $110 million, both record amounts for a year before an election, according to a person familiar with the party’s fundraising. More than half of the haul in August, traditionally a slow month for raising money, came from small-dollar donors, who gave $5.2 million. So far this year, grassroots contributors have combined to give $58.4 million,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Hanks fights to survive with dog and robot in sci-fi thriller...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/tom-hanks-finch-trailer-1235017014/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hanks is the survivor of an apocalypse with his trusty dog and robot in this Apple TV+ film from director Miguel Sapochnik.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student in Canada had 2 followers. Didn't escape Beijing threats over online activity...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestar.com/news/canada/2021/09/18/a-chinese-student-in-canada-had-two-followers-on-twitter-he-still-didnt-escape-beijings-threats-over-online-activity.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monitoring of Chinese nationals abroad, and other people of Chinese origin, is posing a challenge that many western countries have been slow to face, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuPaul sets record for most Emmys by Black artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/rupaul-emmy-record-most-wins-black-performer-1235015916/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picking up another Emmy for competition program for 'RuPaul's Drag Race,' the 60-year-old host has surpassed Donald A. Morgan with the most awards from the TV Academy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emmys:  A Thoroughly Modern Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/2021-emmys-were-thoroughly-modern-052449185.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Fury/GettyEnd all awards show bits. That’s the lesson.The Emmys winners did the show for them. They were all (mostly) great. There were surprises sprinkled throughout, the kind of fun that shocks TV critics watching alone on their couch with some rosé and makes them stand up reflexively and start clapping about.(That was me, when Mare of Easttown’s Julianne Nicholson deservedly won, Olivia Colman’s Queen Elizabeth reigned over Emma Corrin’s Princess Diana, and Hacks creator/writer/director</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
