<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER RESTRICTS DON JR</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/twitter-partially-suspends-donald-trump-jr-for-sharing-hydroxychloroquine-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media giant Twitter suspended the account of Donald Trump Jr. after he shared a video of doctors talking about the controversial anti-malarial drug hydroxychloroquine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Favorite Doctor Believes in Demon Sperm...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/stella-immanuel-trumps-new-covid-doctor-believes-in-alien-dna-demon-sperm-and-hydroxychloroquine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president is pushing the coronavirus theories of a Houston doctor who also says sexual visitations by demons and alien DNA are at the root of Americans’ common health concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King dollar's decline ripples across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-dollar-analysis/king-dollars-decline-ripples-across-the-globe-idUSKCN24T1G5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An accelerating decline in the U.S. dollar is reverberating around the world, adding fuel to a global momentum rally that has boosted prices for everything from technology stocks to gold.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'It looks like downtown Baghdad'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8563241/On-Portlands-streets-Anger-fear-fence-divides.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal officers who are protecting Portland's courthouse under the orders of the Trump administration have revealed that they 'fear for their lives' after the 61 nights of protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Spends 9-in-10 Ad Dollars Defending States He Won...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/trump-spends-9-in-10-advertising-dollars-defending-states-he-won</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paradise lost: Eviction looms for hermit living alone on Italian island...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/travel/article/budelli-hermit-eviction-morandi/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 30 years, Mauro Morandi has been the sole inhabitant of Budelli, an Italian island in the Mediterranean Sea. As the global coronavirus crisis unfolds, he now faces eviction from "the safest place on Earth"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer confidence tumbles...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f7141aab14400d4fcd7f47a88e3b8e44</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — U.S. consumer confidence tumbled in July to a reading of 92.6 as coronavirus infections spread in many parts of the country. The Conference Board, a New York research...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President seeks political shot in arm in vax push...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7cc45cdcb3e53515b8ff4304a4ae5c06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s handling of the coronavirus pandemic put his political fate in grave jeopardy. Now he’s hoping to get credit for his administration’s aggressive push for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Merkel and waning global clout of USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2020/07/28/trump-merkel-us-waning-global-clout/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The image of the U.S. began the new decade in a weaker position globally than at most points in the previous two presidential administrations."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Bob Ross Still So Popular?</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/culture/archive/2020/07/why-bob-ross-still-so-popular/614431/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty-five years after his death, the painter who gave us “happy little trees” is more ubiquitous than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Of Pleasure: Hedonism Key To Happier Life, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/power-of-pleasure-hedonism-key-to-living-happier-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds people who take the time for hedonism are living happier lives and suffer less depression.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI REBUKES TRUMP</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/dr-fauci-rebukes-trumps-tweetstorm-against-him-i-have-not-been-misleading-the-american-public/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci shrugged off Donald Trump's attacks against him in light of the president's new tweetstorm against his medical recommendations regarding the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE OVER 'CURE'</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8566907/Donald-Trump-goes-Twitter-binge-retweets-posts-praising-hydroxychloroquine.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump retweeted a slew of posts praising controversial drug hydroxychloroquine for treating COVID-19 on Monday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'CALL THAT LIVING?' HOCKNEY RIPS BORIS OVER HEALTH PLANS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8566333/Artist-David-Hockney-lays-bossy-boots-Boris-Johnsons-anti-obesit-crackdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artist David Hockney has branded Boris Johnson and Matt Hancock 'bossy boots' over the government's attempts to crack down on obesity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stakes high as Depp's libel case against tabloid closes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fade699882c0208520fa3622c4c7f437</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Johnny Depp’s libel case against a British tabloid that accused him of abusing ex-wife Amber Heard was wrapping up Tuesday, with the star's lawyer insisting Depp had never hit a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil rights icon Rep. John Lewis lies in state at Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/31d9efec950ba0d69bb17c88fd48ab2c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — In a solemn display of bipartisan unity, congressional leaders praised Democratic Rep. John Lewis as a moral force for the nation in a Capitol Rotunda memorial service rich with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm Isaias likely to form in Atlantic, adding to record-breaking season...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-tropical-storm-isaias-tuesday-update-hurricane-center-20200728-43kkadvmavgerkrzbvla4a74je-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A low-pressure system with disorganized showers in the Atlantic could form into the next tropical depression or Tropical Storm Isaias with long-range forecasts bringing it close to Florida, according to the National Hurricane Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE ON MARS? ROVER SET FOR LAUNCH...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/space/os-bz-mars-rover-launch-preview-20200728-zztbqp2hbzaklgjofjpsamd3py-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In early March, when out of thousands of name ideas for NASA’s new Mars rover 13-year-old Alexander Mather’s suggestion of “Perseverance” was chosen, no one foresaw the prescient message it would carry as the coronavirus pandemic capsized American life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Do We Believe in UFOs? That's Wrong Question...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/28/insider/UFO-reporting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting on the Pentagon program that’s investigating unidentified flying objects is not about belief. It’s about a vigilant search for facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluffy the Human Slayer? FORD Unleashes Robot Dogs...</title>
      <link>https://www.motortrend.com/news/ford-boston-dynamics-robot-dog-spot-fluffy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motortrend.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ford just sourced two of Boston Dynamics' robot dogs to help scan the Blue Oval's Van Dyke transmission plant as it gears up for a retooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escape America? 12 Countries Where Can Buy Citizenship...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/laurabegleybloom/2020/07/28/escape-america-countries-buy-citizenship-second-passport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In many countries, you can live the dream and live abroad by buying residency and dual citizenship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Mystery seeds from China landing in Americans' mail boxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/seeds-from-china-mysterious-seed-landing-american-mail-boxes-usda-investigating-do-not-plant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The USDA is investigating, and state agriculture officials are warning residents not to plant, or even touch the unsolicited seeds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamptons Concert With Goldman CEO, CHAINSMOKERS Faces Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/hamptons-concert-with-goldman-ceo-chainsmokers-faces-n-y-probe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hamptons Concert With Goldman CEO, Chainsmokers Faces N.Y. Probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Senator Criticized for Ad Enlarging Jewish Opponent's Nose...</title>
      <link>https://time.com/5872563/georgia-senate-race-ad-jewish-nose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;time.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is the oldest, most obvious, least original anti-Semitic trope in history,” Democrat Jon Ossoff said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's 1980 -- in reverse...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/509275-its-1980-in-reverse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today, as in 1980, the United States is a profoundly unhappy country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran targets dummy US aircraft carrier in Gulf exercises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-targets-dummy-us-aircraft-carrier-gulf-exercises-114815827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran&amp;#39;s Revolutionary Guards blasted a mock-up of a US aircraft carrier with missiles on Tuesday during military exercises in sensitive Gulf waters, state television said. Footage of the war games broadcast on state television showed the Guards&amp;#39; air and naval forces readying for an attack off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clue to Van Gogh's Final Days Found in His Last Painting...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/28/a-clue-to-van-goghs-final-days-is-found-in-his-last-painting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMSTERDAM — One hundred and thirty years ago, Vincent van Gogh awoke in his room at an inn in Auvers-sur-Oise,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He got $4 million in relief loans. Then bought LAMBORGHINI...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/first-got-4-million-covid-210256806.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the first things David T. Hines bought when he got $4 million in COVID-19 relief loans from the feds for his supposedly ailing South Florida moving business was a super-luxury Lamborghini Huracan Evo, authorities say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baseball players express fear, uncertainty in wake of MARLINS outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/mlb/baseball-players-express-fear-and-uncertainty-in-the-wake-of-marlins-coronavirus-outbreak/ar-BB17fyyB?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barr plans to mount defiant defense of Trump in showdown with House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/What-to-expect-when-Barr-is-questioned-by-the-15438189.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Attorney General William Barr will tell the House Judiciary Committee on Tuesday that President Donald Trump has not inappropriately intervened in Justice Department business - even though Barr has more than once moved in criminal cases to help the president's allies - and he will defend the administration's response to civil unrest in the country, according to a copy of his opening statement.  Barr, according to the statement, will take a defiant posture as he testifies before the panel for the first time since Democrats took control of it, alleging that they have attempted to "discredit" him since he vowed to investigate the 2016 FBI probe of possible coordination between Russia and the Trump campaign, and that the media has been unfair in covering unrest. He is expected to face critical questioning on his response to anti-police-brutality protests across the nation, his controversial interventions in high-profile cases involving allies of Trump and many other matters.  According to a Democratic committee counsel, lawmakers will ask Barr about his role in dispatching federal agents to respond to police-brutality protests that have at times grown violent - first in the District of Columbia and, more recently in Portland, Ore. Several Democratic leaders - including House Judiciary Committee Chairman Jerrold Nadler, N.Y. - have asked the Justice Department and Homeland Security inspectors general to probe the federal government's actions in those cities and raised questions about whether they were legal.  "Citizens are concerned that the Administration has deployed a secret police force, not to investigate crimes but to intimidate individuals it views as political adversaries, and that the use of these tactics will proliferate throughout the country," Nadler and others wrote earlier this month.  Barr will...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROTESTERS SURROUND DHS CHIEF'S HOUSE...</title>
      <link>https://www.alxnow.com/2020/07/27/activists-protest-at-alexandria-home-of-acting-dhs-chief-chad-wolf/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.alxnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of protestors demonstrated outside the Alexandria home of acting Department of Homeland Security Secretary Chad Wolf on Sunday, and called for him to end actions against protestors throughout the country by federal agents. "We live among the people who are wreaking havoc on this country,"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA INFECTED</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200727140344-dkmrl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-O'BRIEN (UPDATE 3):UPDATE 3-Trump national security adviser O'Brien tests positive for coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As virus threatened invasion, 'Red Dawn' team tried to save America...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/coronavirus-threatened-invasion-red-dawn-team-save-america/story?id=72000727</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Red Dawn" pandemic experts on early email chain with government officials break their silence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Wealthy Men Twice As Likely To Develop High Blood Pressure...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/wealthy-men-twice-as-likely-to-develop-high-blood-pressure-than-those-with-low-income/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study reveals that men with a higher income have a greater risk of developing high blood pressure versus those with a lower income.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More federal agents sent to reinforce courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/trump-administration-sending-more-federal-agents-to-reinforce-portland-courthouse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Trump administration is sending more federal agents to Portland, Ore., as officials consider pushing back harder and farther against the growing crowds and nightly clashes with protesters, vandals and rioters, The Washington Post has learned. To strengthen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First debate moved to Cleveland amid pandemic concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/27/presidential-debate-moved-to-cleveland-382960</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate, which is in just over two months, was originally scheduled to be hosted by the University of Notre Dame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis Lies in State in Capitol Rotunda...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/07/27/895150700/watch-civil-rights-icon-john-lewis-honored-at-capitol-hill-ceremony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The late Georgia congressman's body will lie in state in the Capitol Rotunda. A public viewing for the "conscience of the Congress" will be held outside due to the ongoing coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard major disputes top admin officials over clearing White House protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/27/politics/white-house-protest-church/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top National Guard official will tell Congress that the widely criticized decision to forcefully clear protesters from a park outside the White House last month was made even though demonstrators were acting peacefully, a view at odds with public comments by top Trump administration officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gym owners who defied gov arrested on contempt charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/27/ian-smith-and-frank-trumbetti-atilis-gym-owners-wh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owners of a New Jersey gym that has repeatedly defied Gov. Phil Murphy’s executive order to remain closed during the COVID-19 pandemic were arrested Monday on contempt charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Seeks Criminal Referral Related To Zuckerberg...</title>
      <link>https://www.projectveritas.com/news/veritas-video-heartens-congressman-to-solicit-ag-barr-for-criminal-referral/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.projectveritas.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigating and exposing corruption in both public and private institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists growing miniature human organs to test drugs...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/927696/scientists-are-3d-printing-miniature-human-organs-test-coronavirus-drugs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether the goal is to find a treatment for COVID-19 or another disease, scientists often have to conduct preliminary tests on animals to determine whether the drug is safe or effective in people. It's not always a one-for-one comparison, but The New York Times reports there may be a new way around that step going forward: 3-D printing. For example, Anthony Atala, the director of the Wake Forest Institute for Regenerative Medicine, and his team are using 3-D printers to create tiny replicas of human organs, including miniature lungs and colons, which are particularly affected by the coronavirus. They send them overnight for testing at a biosafety lab at George Mason University. The idea predated the coronavirus â€” Atala said he never thought 'we'd be considering this for a pandemic' â€” but it could come in handy and help expedite the experimental drug process, especially since Atala said his Winston-Salem, North Carolina-based lab can churn out thousands of printed organs per hour. 'The 3-D models can circumvent animal testing and make the pathway stronger from the lab to the clinic,' said Akhilesh Gaharwar, who directs a lab in the biomedical engineering at Texas A&amp;M University. Read more at The New York Times. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shark of 'significant size' closes down Long Island beaches...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/27/shark-of-significant-size-closes-down-some-li-beaches/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A shark of “significant size” was spotted off Hempstead, LI, on Monday — prompting local beach closures, officials said. The town tweeted out an alert in the early afternoon sayin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Hermain Cain STILL hospitalized...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/12240930/herman-cain-hospital-coronavirus-president-trump-rally-tulsa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HERMAN Cain is at an Atlanta hospital receiving coronavirus treatment, according to a statement posted to his Twitter account. The former 2012 Republican presidential candidate developed symptoms &amp;…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA to fly helicopter over Mars: 'Wright brothers' moment'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/nasa-rover-perseverance-helicopter-flight-mars/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The helicopter, Ingenuity, will travel to Mars clutching the rover's belly and, a few months after touchdown, attempt to fly solo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Cops Setting Up 'Mask Traps'...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/27/miami-police-setting-up-mask-traps-issuing-100-fines-to-people-wearing-masks-improperly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The theoretical case for government mask mandates has to be weighed against the reality of their enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antitrust fever rises...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/antitrust-fever-rises-big-tech-ceos-set-testify-152450617.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antitrust fever hits a peak in Washington this week with lawmakers set to grill top executives of four of the biggest US technology firms in what promises to be a rare political spectacle for the digital era. The showdown Wednesday in the House of Representatives comes amid rising concerns over Big</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drugmakers refuse White House meeting after executive orders on costs...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/27/drugmakers-trump-meeting-canceled-382847</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top pharma executives were supposed to meet with the president on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO Takes Turntable as Hamptons Gets Back to Partying
...</title>
      <link>https://www.fa-mag.com/news/goldman-ceo-takes-the-stage-as-hamptons-gets-back-to-partying-57087.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fa-mag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A couple of thousand people showed up for Safe &amp; Sound, the Hamptons' first drive-in concert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases hit record highs in more than DOZEN states...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8564627/New-COVID-19-cases-hit-fresh-highs-DOZEN-states.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of coronavirus cases are now spiking in more than a dozen states, including Oklahoma, Missouri and Mississippi as the virus shows signs it is moving North.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firing of Hungarian Newspaper Editor Stokes Press Freedom Fears...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/07/27/firing-of-hungarian-newspaper-editor-stokes-press-freedom-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another blow to the country's few remaining independent news outlets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Anxiety props up Joe, Donald voters fervent...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f4ca81c007504ca97ff1feb0b5a56bcd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Murtice Sherek is not excited about Joe Biden. The Minnesota Democrat, a 79-year-old retired nurse, preferred another candidate in the presidential primary. She also...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More federal agents sent to reinforce courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national-security/portland-protests-trump-federal-agents-reinforcements/2020/07/27/e8a943ae-d023-11ea-8d32-1ebf4e9d8e0d_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Marshals Service is sending 100 deputies while Customs and Border Protection contemplates deploying 50 agents amid concerns about losing control of the conflict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: 6 Ways Trump Could Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2020/07/how-trump-could-win-reelection/612205/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polling could be wrong. The economy could recover just enough. He could announce his own October surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends fighter jet to intercept US spy plane over Black Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/russia-sends-su-27-fighter-jet-to-intercept-us-spy-plane-over-black-sea-636512</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly HALF of Miami Marlins players test positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1207057/nearly-half-miami-marlins-test-positive-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Miami Marlins home opener was canceled on Monday after nearly half of the team’s roster tested positive for the coronavirus. The COVID-19 outbreak, which has since affected 12 of the team…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Glass puts computer on your eyes!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1206929/apple-glass-headset-ar-augmented-reality-design-concept-video-leak-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FUTURISTIC “Apple Glass” headset could totally replace your iPhone – by giving you augmented reality cyber-vision. Amazing concept footage of the rumoured headset has been mocked up b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New app tells South Floridians if they've been exposed. Will anyone use it?</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/fl-ne-contact-tracing-app-south-florida-20200726-n64qojstmnchxfz52iwdvbrbiu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new app called CombatCOVID is offering South Floridians a chance to see what has been invisible until now: whether they crossed paths with someone who has the new coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans look to virus relief to avert economic and electoral disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/07/27/republicans-look-to-virus-relief-to-avert-economic-and-electoral-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key aid programs are expiring, but Republicans and Democrats remain miles apart on whether they should continue or, if not, what should replace them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At prisons without AC, masks add discomfort to unbearably hot summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-florida-prisons-heat-masks-20200722-bbe4hatmffgb7aqdofhmnffdvi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blistering heat in Florida’s state prisons — some of which lack air conditioning in living spaces — is always concern for family members and advocates during the summer months, but this year it’s compounded by a recent mandate that all inmates wear masks most of the day as COVID-19 cases continue to rise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Lewis to Lie in State in the Capitol Rotunda...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/john-lewis-is-the-first-black-lawmaker-to-lie-in-state-in-the-capitol-rotunda/ar-BB17eTVY?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 Million Evictions Coming over Next Four Months?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90532305/11-million-households-could-be-evicted-over-the-next-four-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new tool helps you see the contours of the approaching housing disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: 'Most severe emergency'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8564379/Covid-19-severe-emergency-declared.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global tally has risen by a million in just four days, led by massive outbreaks in the United States, India and Brazil which are each piling up tens of thousands of new cases per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLEFACEBOOKAMAZONGOOGLE Reckoning?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/apple-facebook-amazon-google-are-headed-to-congress-an-event-years-in-the-making/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The four tech giants are headed to Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One question still dogs Trump: Why not try harder to solve crisis?</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/One-question-still-dogs-Trump-Why-not-try-harder-15436174.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both President Donald Trump's advisers and operatives laboring to defeat him increasingly agree on one thing: The best way for him to regain his political footing is to wrest control of the coronavirus.  In the six months since the deadly contagion was first reported in the United States, Trump has demanded the economy reopen and children return to school, all while scrambling to salvage his reelection campaign.  But both allies and opponents agree he has failed at the one task that could help him achieve all of his goals - confronting the pandemic with a clear strategy and consistent leadership.  Trump's shortcomings have perplexed even some of his most loyal allies, who increasingly have wondered why the president has not at least pantomimed a sense of command over the crisis or conveyed compassion for the millions of Americans impacted by it.  People close to Trump, many speaking anonymously to share candid discussions and impressions, say the president's inability to wholly address the crisis is due to his almost pathological unwillingness to admit error; a positive feedback loop of overly rosy assessments and data from advisers and Fox News; and a penchant for magical thinking that prevented him from fully engaging with the pandemic.  In recent weeks, with more than 146,000 Americans now dead from the virus, the White House has attempted to overhaul - or at least rejigger - its approach. The administration has revived news briefings led by Trump himself and presented the president with projections showing how the virus is now decimating Republican states full of Trump voters. Officials have also set up a separate, smaller coronavirus working group led by Deborah Birx, the White House coronavirus response coordinator, along with Trump son-in-law and senior adviser...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Player Excused from Bubble to Attend Funeral -- Goes to Strip Club...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2020/07/26/nba-investigating-lou-williams-strip-club-trip-despite-quarantine-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Basketball Association is investigating why Los Angeles Clippers guard Lou Williams was seen in a strip club Thursday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millions of Americans 'hanging by thread' as aid expires...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-53534435</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A $600 boost to unemployment benefit is set to expire soon, leaving many people worried about money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both campaigns build legal armies for electoral battlefield...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/508962-trump-biden-build-legal-armies-for-electoral-battlefield </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine put to final test in thousands of volunteers...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d9150647d677cd036c03b8d0ab52358b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s biggest COVID-19 vaccine study got underway Monday with the first of 30,000 planned volunteers helping to test shots created by the U.S. government -- one of several candidates in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Portland's streets: Anger, fear, and fence that divides...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1dd1bb39093a3691f4e78093787ab877</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — The party at the Salmon Street Springs fountain, a riverfront landmark in the heart of Portland, was just getting started. Dozens of drummers beat out entrancing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover why patients lose sense of smell...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1207221/why-coronavirus-patients-lose-sense-smell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE KEY symptoms of coronavirus are now widely known as a new and persistent cough, a high temperature and a loss of taste and smell. But many have been left mystified as to why the respiratory inf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identical twins plan to get pregnant together -- with same man!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/1207183/worlds-most-identical-twins-plan-pregnant-same-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE “world’s most identical twins” Anna and Lucy DeCinque have revealed that they are planning to get pregnant at the same time with their shared boyfriend. The sisters, who live in Perth with thei…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IS IT SPREADING WITH AIR CONDITIONING?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/other/can-covid-spread-with-air-conditioning-hvac-makers-plan-upgrades/ar-BB17eMF8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED SOX Pitcher Confirms He's Dealing With Heart Issue From Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/mlb/news/red-sox-pitcher-eduardo-rodriguez-confirms-hes-dealing-with-heart-issue-stemming-from-covid-19-infection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodriguez will be shut down for at least a week with the hope that his heart inflammation goes away</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New travel curbs imposed as world tackles second wave...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200727131711-r13h9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ (WRAPUP 4, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 4-New travel curbs imposed as world tackles second COVID-19 wave</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
