<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Fears for Merkel's health after she violently shakes during ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/462140-merkel-zelensky-shaking-ill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel was spotted visibly unsteady and shaking when she met Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky. The 64-year-old politician later said she recovered from the sickly condition after drinking water.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KICKOFF:  FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/whitehouse/trump-targets-floridas-electoral-haul-orlando-campaign-kick-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expect a show Tuesday when President Trump announces his reelection campaign in Florida, a state that holds 29 precious electoral votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  SAVAGE DOUBTS TRUMP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/18/us/politics/michael-savage-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Savage was one of the first radio hosts to endorse Mr. Trump. Now he thinks the president’s fans are too uncritical. But his listeners aren’t so sure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover video gives gruesome look at Florida dog-fighting ring...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/undercover-video-offers-gruesome-look-florida-dog-fighting-ring-n1018496</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage, shot by a confidential government informant, was obtained by NBC News after eight people were indicted on federal dogfighting charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARTING NEXT WEEK!</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/zz/news/20190617/trump-vows-removal-of-millions-of-illegal-aliens-starting-next-week</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump said in a tweet Monday night that U.S. immigration agents are planning to make mass arrests starting "next week," an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW RACES TOWARD 27,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/18/stock-market-wall-street-monitors-federal-reserve-meeting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks surged after President Donald Trump said he will be meeting with his Chinese counterpart, Xi Jinping, at the upcoming G-20 summit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  First thing I would do is eliminate tax cuts!</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-first-thing-i-would-do-president-eliminate-president-s-tax-cut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Joe Biden said Monday that the first thing he’d do as president is “eliminate” the Tax Cuts and Jobs Act:&amp;#13;&amp;#13;“First thing I would do as president is eliminate the president’s tax cut,” Biden said during the Poor People's Forum in Washington, D.C. on Monday.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;[Click here for video]&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Biden’s promise to repeal the tax cuts is a promise to raise taxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Ants Pour Out From Passenger's Carry-On Bag On Flight...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/06/18/ants-that-spill-out-from-carry-on-bag-force-united-plane-out-of-service/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A passenger on the Venice-to-Newark flight Monday described the scenario in a series of tweets and photos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booker adds anti-Trump anger to message of love...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/booker-adds-dash-anti-trump-181322935.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Cory Booker spent the first five months of his presidential bid dispensing a message of love and unity. But it hasn’t caught on with a Democratic electorate that is seething with anger toward President Donald Trump and desperate to throw him out of office.The New Jersey senator long seen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE BLITZ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e32b4a65baf74afab5bb5b2aa061f734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUR MORE YEARS?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5916483b100f4c02be2b22155308dc5a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP VOWS TO DEPORT 'MILLIONS'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190618011308-vmh1j</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/TRUMP (URGENT):Trump says U.S. agency will begin removing millions of illegal immigrants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK unveils 'most dangerous form of surveillance yet' with launch of cryptocurrency...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9319668/facebook-launch-libra-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FACEBOOK is launching cryptocurrency next year that will allow people to move money from their smartphone into a digital “wallet”. The currency is known as Libra, which the social netwo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'killing prisoners and harvesting organs for transplants'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/786329/china-organ-harvesting-london-tribunal-falun-gong</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libra: FACEBOOK Crypto Trojan Rabbit...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2019-06-18/libra-facebooks-crypto-trojan-rabbit</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Echoes of 'JAWS' as Cape Cod learns to live with rise of great white shark...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/jun/18/great-white-shark-cape-cod-massachusetts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A booming seal population is drawing the apex predator to the Massachusetts peninsula where contact with humans follows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'THE ROCK': I WASN'T GOING TO CONFORM TO HOLLYWOOD...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/dwayne-the-rock-johnson-mtv-generation-award</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dwayne “The Rock” Johnson is officially an icon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears for Merkel health after seen violently shaking at ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7154083/Fears-Angela-Merkels-health-seen-violently-shaking-minute-Berlin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German Chancellor Angela Merkel appeared unsteady and was shaking as she stood in the midday sun in Berlin. She visibly shook for around a minute but said she was just dehydrated in the heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6.5 mag quake strikes off coast of Japan...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190618132141-8z9vp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JAPAN-QUAKE/ (URGENT):Magnitude 6.5 earthquake strikes off coast of Japan -USGS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSIDE BACKPAGE.COM VICIOUS BATTLE WITH FEDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/inside-backpage-vicious-battle-feds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For years, it was the largest portal for sex on the internet. Now its fate could shape the future of Silicon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New robotic dishwasher for restaurants taking dirty work out of kitchen...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/18/robotic-dishwasher-for-restaurants-taking-dirty-work-out-of-kitchen.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants have a hard time hiring and retaining dishwashers, but now there's a robot for that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand man jailed for sharing mosque shooting video...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-48671837</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philip Arps had also made a modified version of the video that he intended to share as a meme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia: Stop provoking...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-nuclear-usa-russia/russia-to-washington-drop-middle-east-troop-plan-and-stop-provoking-iran-idUSKCN1TJ0UF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia told the United States on Tuesday to drop what it called provocative plan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norway island wants to be world's first time-free zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/norway-sommaroy-island-time-free-zone/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The locals on Sommaroy, an island in northern Norway, make the most of their precious summer sun with no regard to conventional timekeeping. Now they want to be world's first time-free zone officially.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porous border could hinder efforts to stem spread of Ebola...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/ebfa128638c74de1838a9508a8f7dc79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel unsteady, whole body shaking at ceremony...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/963b2962aea54de499025e866a1ebe92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRID HACK IN SOUTH AMERICA?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/60ecd65067ec43c28c29a412f452b488</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro looking for safe exit?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7153177/Maduro-no-longer-feels-safe-looking-exit-army-turns-Colombian-leader-claims.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivan Duque said Maduro's family and inner circle were looking to find sanctuary before the eventual collapse of his grip on Venzuela's military, following an attempted coup in April.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela's misery doesn't even spare the dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/cadb01f1c0ca4012ae17c46c0a240061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Tests USA Appetite for Fight...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/u-boosts-pressure-iran-tests-042158206.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Donald Trump’s campaign vow to get the U.S. out of costly foreign entanglements is colliding with the messy reality of America’s commitments in the Middle East, where tensions are rising between Washington and Tehran after attacks on two tankers last week.The dilemma emerged</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four More Years? Trump Has Reasons to Fear...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/four-more-years-trump-reasons-095536363.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Want to receive this post in your inbox every day? Sign up for the Balance of Power newsletter, and follow Bloomberg Politics on Twitter and Facebook for more.It's been 27 years since an incumbent U.S. president lost re-election, and judging by the health of the economy and other traditional</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investors Haven't Been This Bearish Since '08 Financial Crisis...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/investors-haven-t-bearish-since-080212229.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Investors haven’t been this pessimistic since the global financial crisis of 2008.That’s according to a Bank of America Merrill Lynch survey of money managers with $528 billion between them. Equity allocations saw the second-biggest drop on record, while cash holdings jumped by the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chaos at RAPTORS championship rally after shooting...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7149701/Raptors-victory-parade-draw-TWO-MILLION-celebrate-NBA-title.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Four people were shot following Monday's parade in Toronto, celebrating the Raptors' first NBA title. As police told the Daily Mail, both victims sustained serious, but not life-threatening injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LORAX' tree said to be Dr. Seuss' muse topples in San Diego...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article231646633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World population projected to STOP growing by end of century...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2019/06/17/worlds-population-is-projected-to-nearly-stop-growing-by-the-end-of-the-century/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewresearch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in modern history, the world’s population is expected to virtually stop growing by the end of this century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Manafort Seemed Headed to Rikers. Then the Justice Deprt Intervened... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/06/17/nyregion/manafort-rikers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decision came after Attorney General William Barr’s top deputy sent a letter to state prosecutors. Mr. Manafort will now be held in a federal lockup while he faces state charges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: J.J. Abrams Nears $500 Million Deal With WARNERMEDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/jj-abrams-bidding-war-won-by-warnermedia-as-bad-robot-nears-500m-partnership-1207800 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bad Robot, the famed production company Abrams runs with his wife and co-CEO Katie McGrath, had been fielding offers from pretty much every major media company at one point or another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior trip descends into disaster... </title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/17/senior-trip-to-dominican-republic-descends-into-disaster-after-group-falls-ill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of Oklahoma teens’ senior trip to the Dominican Republic was ruined when they fell sick with a mysterious illness. The recent Deer Creek High School graduates flew on June 8 to the em…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OJ TWITTER account threatens man with knife emojis...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/17/o-j-simpsons-twitter-account-threatens-man-with-knife-emojis/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shocking threats were contained in a pair of videos posted on the “@KillerOJSimpson” Twitter page on Monday, which also marked the 25th anniversary of the infamous slow-speed police…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Buffett fan club falls ill on Dominican Republic trip...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/54-jimmy-buffett-fans-from-us-fell-ill-during-group-trip-to-dominican-republic-travel-agent-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About half the members of a Jimmy Buffett fan club from Oklahoma who traveled to the Dominican Republic in April got sick, the group&amp;#39;s travel agent confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Would become 'Trump's war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/06/war-with-iran-would-become-trumps-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump cannot want war with Iran. Such a war, no matter how long, would be fought in and around the Persian Gulf, through which a third of the world’s seaborne oil travels. It could trigger a worldwide recession and imperil Trump’s reelection. It would widen the “forever war,” which Trump said he would […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Melania aide favorite to become new White House press sec...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/white-house/top-melania-trump-aide-stephanie-grisham-emerges-as-favorite-to-become-new-white-house-press-secretary  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephanie Grisham, spokeswoman for first lady Melania Trump, is emerging as the top candidate to replace outgoing White House press secretary Sarah Sanders, according to sources familiar with the selection process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRAN THREAT: 10 DAYS TO SAVE NUKE DEAL...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9311290/iran-uranium-limits-nuclear-pact/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN announced today it intends to smash the strict uranium stockpile limits set under the nuclear deal it struck with the world’s leading powers. The hardline country’s shock statement…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway 'HILLARY AND CLINTON' to Close Early Amid Poor Ticket Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/hillary-clinton-close-one-month-early-broadway-1218946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The play is the third Scott Rudin production of the 2018-19 season to move up its closing date following soft ticket sales.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump supporters line up 40 HOURS before Orlando rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/politics/president-trump-supporters-line-up-37-hours-before-orlando-rally</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supporters of President Donald Trump are already lined up outside Orlando&amp;#39;s Amway Center for his big rally Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE TROOPS TO MIDDLE EAST</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/us-send-1000-additional-troops-middle-east-tensions/story?id=63772858</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is sending 1,000 additional troops to the Middle East, amid rising tensions between the U.S. and Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Along Unexpected Lines In 3 Cases...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/06/17/733408135/supreme-court-justices-split-along-unexpected-lines-in-three-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court decided four cases Monday, and three defied the usual ideological fissures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robocalls overwhelm hospitals, patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2019/06/17/robocalls-are-overwhelming-hospitals-patients-threatening-new-kind-health-crisis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For most Americans, robocalls are a nuisance. For hospitals, spam calls can be a life-or-death threat in a setting where every second counts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  70-Somethings Holding Party Back...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2019/06/there-should-be-age-limit-presidents/591724/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic Party’s gerontocracy is holding back the political causes it claims to want to advance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masters of manipulation: Evolution of 'puppy dog eyes'...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190617-masters-manipulation-evolution-puppy-dog-eyes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Masters of manipulation: the evolution of 'puppy dog eyes'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested at JFK for 34 singing finches hidden in plastic hair curlers...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/06/17/politics/man-arrested-smuggling-finches-jfk-guyana/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man attempting to smuggle a flock of singing finches was caught in customs on Sunday at John F. Kennedy International Airport in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA restores some Central American aid but vows no more without action...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/0eaa42865d974e46ba04a51e21e1a81b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK porn block is 'privacy timebomb,' experts warn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/9313115/uk-porn-block-is-privacy-timebomb-for-20million-brits-experts-warn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE UK porn blocker will be coming into effect next month but the age verification restrictions could become a data protection nightmare, according to concerned experts. The Open Rights Group, a co…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legend Of Florida's Skunk Ape Lives On...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/06/17/florida-skunk-ape-legend/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sunshine State has beautiful beaches, thrilling theme parks, and great nightlife; but did you know we are also home to the elusive and mysterious Skunk Ape?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists take peek behind sad puppy dog eyes...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/scientists-take-a-peek-behind-those-sad-puppy-dog-eyes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOMO 4 TV provides news, sports, weather and local event coverage in the Seattle, Washington area including Bellevue, Redmond, Renton, Kent, Tacoma, Bremerton, SeaTac, Auburn, Mercer Island, Bothell, Shoreline, Lynnwood, Mill Creek and Everett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ranted About Govt: 'Storm Coming'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/06/17/a-storm-is-coming-guns-and-threats-highlight-alleged-dallas-shooter-brian-clydes-social-media/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social media posts by the man who officials say opened fire at the Earle Cabell Federal Building in downtown Dallas give insight into the alleged shooter's state of mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Expected To Have 400 Million Fewer People By 2100...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/06/17/china-population-fall-2100/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is expected to lose nearly 400 million people by the end of the century, according to a Pew Research Center report based on United Nations projections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRBUS ready for pilotless jets -- are passengers?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d8d911a9f1844df1a314a42c346e74a4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/suspected-gunman-shot-after-opening-fire-outside-dallas-court-building-n1018251</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brian Isaack Clyde was seen on video near the doors to the Earle Cabell Federal Building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted Egyptian President 'collapses and dies in court'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-ousted-egyptian-president-mohammed-16532353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 67-year-old, who was overthrown in July 2013, was facing espionage charges when he reportedly fainted in court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ginsburg, Gorsuch dissent; Supreme Court deals big blow to Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/supreme-court-ruling-deals-potential-blow-to-paul-manafort-as-he-battles-state-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Supreme Court ruling in the case of an Alabama man who pleaded guilty to a gun charge could have major implications for the unrelated white-collar case against former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort in New York -- by keeping him exposed to another set of charges, even if he ultimately wins a presidential pardon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutilated sharks branded like cattle...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/south-carolina/article231625233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The sexbot apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://spectator.us/sexbot-apocalypse/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectator.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunman shot dead after opening fire on Dallas federal courthouse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/crime/2019/06/17/shots-fired-federal-courthouse-downtown-dallas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shots were fired Monday morning at the Earle Cabell federal courthouse in downtown Dallas Monday morning, officials said.A Dallas Morning News...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US to question Assange pal jailed in Ecuador...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/09ac93b95bbe46d7b90a73c73fda6389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
