<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>2,100 mostly unarmed Guard troops on border...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-military/2018/10/23/2000-unarmed-guard-troops-on-border-as-trump-vows-to-send-more-to-stop-migrant-caravan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Guard could send 2,000 more troops to border, if governors OK the deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple narrowly escape death after beaver topples 65-ft tree onto yacht!</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/germany-beaver-couple-tree-yacht-muritz-elde-a8597841.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rodent causes thousands of euros in damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Speeding escalator at metro goes haywire, piles dozens on floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/rome-subway-escalator-out-of-control-video-2018-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An escalator malfunctioned at a Rome metro station and injured at least 10 people. A video of the event shows people being spit out onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy expert quits GOOGLE-backed 'smart city'...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/privacy-expert-resigns-from-alphabet-backed-smart-city-1829934748</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A privacy expert tasked with helping a new smart city development protect the data privacy of residents has resigned over concerns that her guidelines would be largely ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City bans clowns on Halloween...</title>
      <link>https://www.ksat.com/news/no-clowns-allowed-michigan-city-bans-clowns-on-halloween</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ksat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you plan to attend the Boo Bash in the Detroit suburb of Oak Park on Halloween, you can be a ghost, goblin, zombie, vampire or any other character that you wish, but you can't be a clown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON futuristic cashierless convenience store coming to NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/amazon-go-cashierless-store-reportedly-opening-in-new-york-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Go stores use "Just Walk Out" technology so shoppers can skip the wait to pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GILLUM HOT IN FLORIDA</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/florida-governor-election-2018-andrew-gillum-leads-desantis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto bets big on FACEBOOK ads...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-10-23/facebook-ad-report-puts-o-rourke-as-top-spender-after-facebook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP 6</title>
      <link>https://poll.qu.edu/florida/release-detail?ReleaseID=2582</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.qu.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gillum Leads In Tight Florida Governor's Race, Quinnipiac University Poll Finds; Dem Boosted By Independents, Women, Non-White Voters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 MILES AWAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/honduran-migrant-caravan-resumes-march-mexico-us-142832691.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of mainly Honduran migrants heading to the United States -- a caravan President Donald Trump has called an "assault on our country" -- stopped to rest Tuesday after walking for two days into Mexican territory. "They're exhausted," said migrant rights activist Rodrigo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS AT FACILITY</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/adenovirus-wanaque-center-for-nursing-and-rehabilitation-new-jersey-outbreak-children/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A strain of adenovirus is affecting "medically fragile children with severely compromised immune systems," health officials say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  ILLEGALS TO VOTE IN SAN FRAN...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/san-francisco-allow-noncitizens-vote-school-board-184120600--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco will become the largest city in the United States and one of only a handful nationwide to allow noncitizens, including people in the country illegally, to vote in a local election in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gillum ahead by 6 points in Florida gov's race...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2018/10/23/poll-andrew-gillum-leads-ron-desantis-by-6-in-florida-governors-race/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most recent governor's race poll shows what every independent general election survey has shown: Andrew Gillum is winning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEOs give employees time off to vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/ceos-give-employees-time-off-to-vote-in-hotly-contested-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CEOs Give Employees Time Off to Vote in Hotly Contested Midterms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service cancels controlled burn near Earth's largest tree...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-prescribed-fire-sequoias-20181023-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Park Service plan to set fire to an ancient sequoia grove in the western Sierra Nevada has been canceled for the second time this year, further delaying a delicate forestry operation aimed at triggering new growth near the world’s largest tree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENCE:  Nuke Weapons in Space Possible...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Pence-leaves-open-the-possibility-of-nuclear-13330288.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Vice President Mike Pence on Tuesday declined to rule out the idea of deploying nuclear weapons in space, saying the current ban on their use is "in the interest of every nation" but the issue should be decided on "the principle that peace comes through strength." "What we need to do is make sure that we provide for the common defense of the people of the United States of America and that's the president's determination here," Pence said in an interview with The Washington Post, when asked if nuclear weapons should be banned from orbit. Pence added, "What we want to do is continue to advance the principle that peace comes through strength.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper whose lyrics reflected Baltimore's pain fatally shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/rapper-whose-lyrics-reflected-baltimores-pain-fatally-shot-151532492.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — A rising Baltimore rapper who advocated for nonviolence and whose lyrics often reflected the city's trauma has been shot and killed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein, Accusers in Early Talks to Settle Civil Claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/harvey-weinstein-accusers-insurers-in-early-talks-to-settle-civil-claims-1540319930</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for Harvey Weinstein and women who have accused him of sexual misconduct are working with insurance companies and the New York attorney general’s office in an attempt to reach a sweeping settlement of all civil suits pending against the disgraced producer and his former film studio.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams's Burning of Georgia Flag Surfaces on Eve of Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/abrams-role-in-burning-georgia-flag-is-revealed/17938592/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — At a protest on the steps of the Georgia Capitol in 1992, Stacey Abrams, now the Democratic candidate for governor, joined in the burning of the state flag, which at the time incorporated the Confederate battle flag design and was viewed by many as a lingering symbol of white supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS KILLS 6 KIDS</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/health/6-kids-dead-12-sick-in-viral-outbreak-at-nj-rehab-center/4542019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state Department of Health on Tuesday confirmed 18 cases of adenovirus at the Wanaque Center for Nursing and Rehabilitation in Haskell, Passaic County.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US stealth bomber makes emergency landing in CO...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-stealth-bomber-lands-colorado-emergency-152740438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLORADO SPRINGS, Colo. (AP) — The Air Force says a Missouri-based B2 stealth bomber landed in Colorado Springs after an unspecified emergency, but neither of the pilots was injured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Records Support Claims Rep. Married Her Brother...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/davidsteinberg/official-school-records-support-claims-that-rep-ilhan-omar-d-mn-married-her-brother/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is implicated in multiple felonies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKorea says it will arrest citizens who smoke weed in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/oct/23/bong-arm-of-the-law-south-korea-says-it-will-arrest-citizens-who-smoke-weed-in-canada</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seoul reminds 23,000 South Korean students in Canada that domestic law applies to them no matter where they are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100,000 in rare emeralds taken in brazen NC mine heist...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article220452165.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An emerald mine in the foothills of North Carolina was the scene of an old fashioned jewel heist, with thieves making off with more than $100,000 in rare gems and gold jewelry, says the mine owner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of control subway escalator injures 10 in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/738264/roma-vs-cska-moscow-russia-football-fans-injured-escalator-rome-video-latest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue wave? First clues coming in...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article220437025.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California election will be in the national spotlight, as it could shape whether Republicans or Democrats control the U.S. House Representatives. Initial mail ballot returns cast doubt on whether a ‘blue wave’ is forming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China 'flaunt wealth' socials craze: Elites post photos surrounded by luxury goods...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/10/23/chinas-rich-post-photos-lying-face-surrounded-luxury-goods-flaunt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of people lying face down on the ground surrounded by luxury goods have gone viral on Chinese social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JUDGE JERRY': Springer Working On Daytime Courtroom Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/jerry-springer-daytime-courtroom-show-judge-jerry-development-nbcuniversal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jerry Springer has a syndicated courtroom show focused on small-claims cases in the works at NBCUniversal, called "Judge Jerry," of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest amphibious plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/china-ag600-worlds-largest-amphibious-plane-does-first-water-takeoff-test-2018-10</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AG600, said to be the world's largest amphibious aircraft, is designed for civil aviation and operations like firefighting, but experts believe it could be repurposed for military uses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profanity Used In Ads...</title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/politics/ct-met-illinois-governors-race-bruce-rauner-ad-profanity-20181022-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican Gov. Bruce Rauner is launching a new TV ad on Tuesday that’s provocative for its use of a bleeped-out profanity to describe the future of Illinois if Democratic challenger J.B. Pritzker wins and serves in government alongside House Speaker Michael Madigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School cancels 'ALADDIN' over Arab stereotypes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wbaltv.com/article/school-cancels-production-of-aladdin-jr-for-complaints-of-stereotyping-arab-culture/24086346</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wbaltv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Baltimore County elementary school has stopped plans for a school play because of complaints of negative stereotyping of Arab culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa to recover 'looted' cash after bank collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/south-africa-recover-looted-cash-bank-collapse-161650904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Africa said Tuesday it would seek to recover millions of dollars stolen from a local bank that subsequently collapsed owing substantial sums to creditors. A central bank report, titled "The Great Bank Heist", into the failure of VBS Mutual bank said $130 million (112 million euros) was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackouts force Venezuelans to perform surgery in darkness...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article220464510.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelans have learned to live by candlelight during electrical blackouts. Commerce and education are paralyzed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook shifts 8 MORE House races toward Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cookpolitical.com/analysis/house/house-overview/ten-rating-changes-democrats-enthusiasm-edge-narrows-and-fundraising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cookpolitical.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SILVER:  86% DEMS TAKE HOUSE</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2018-midterm-election-forecast/house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight's predictions for the 2018 House elections</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Bring me the head of the dog'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7559690/how-saudi-crown-prince-aide-ordered-jamal-khashoggis-murder-via-skype-as-journalists-severed-fingers-sent-back-to-royal-as-trophy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE dismembered body of Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi has been found near where he is believed to have been tortured and killed, it’s been claimed today. Reports say the butchered remains …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Son Glares at MBS During Meet...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6306539/Saudi-hit-squad-deliberately-disabled-CCTV-consulate-Turkeys-president-Erdogan-reveals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Salah bin Jamal Khashoggi was pictured shaking hands with the powerful heir to Saudi Arabia's throne in Riyadh during a meeting also attended by King Salman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowner Turns Heads With Vicious Trump-Themed Halloween Display...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/10/23/alameda-halloween-display-takes-aim-trump-administration/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An East Bay homeowner's elaborate Halloween decorations are drawing a lot of curiosity from neighbors with a clearly anti-Trump political theme that satirizes the current administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Outraged After Drag Queen 'Jessica L'Whor' Speaks At Middle School...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2018/10/22/adams-county-career-day-drag-queen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A school district has apologized to parents, after hosting a drag queen as part of a career day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOT LYIN' TED ANYMORE!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/apos-beautiful-ted-apos-trump-024209079.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cruz is coming under extreme pressure from his Democratic challenger, Beto O’Rourke, while Trump, troubled by the prospect of a blue wave in November’s midterm elections, is trying to shore up Republican control of Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Cat 4 Hurricane Willa closes in on Mexico coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/news/storms/hurricane/news/2018-10-22-hurricane-willa-pacific-ocean-mexico-landfall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Weather Underground provides local &amp; long range weather forecasts, weather reports, maps &amp; tropical weather conditions for locations worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX New $2B Borrowing Sparks Fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/netflixs-additional-2-billion-borrowing-raises-wall-street-eyebrows-1154325</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The streamer's long-term debt has soared north of $10 billion, though Moody's says ratings and outlook remain stable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC attorney general launches investigation of clergy sex abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/10/23/us/dc-catholic-investigation/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C., Attorney General Karl Racine announced Tuesday that he has launched a civil investigation into whether the Archdiocese of Washington violated the law by covering up the sexual abuse of minors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC FOX-TV break-in suspect shot by guard had history of 'irrational' lawsuits...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2018/10/fox-break-in-suspect-shot-by-guard-said-microchip-was-implanted-in-head/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who was shot by a security guard after kicking his way through two plexiglass doors Fox 5’s D.C. television station Monday has a history of filing “irrational” lawsuits — including one that alleged he had a microchip implanted in his head that controlled his thoughts and actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 DAYS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dec537c487da4dbab9d2212940c8a69a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is battling Democrats for control of Congress. But you might think it's 2016 all over again. As the 2018 midterms shifted to the final two weeks of campaigning, Trump staged a large Monday night rally in Houston, Ted Cruz's hometown, to help the Texas senator and his 2016 presidential rival fend off a tough challenge from Democratic Rep. Beto O'Rourke. During the 2016 primaries, Trump mocked Cruz as "Lyin' Ted," insulted his wife's appearance and suggested Cruz's father played a role in the Kennedy assassination. Cruz assailed Trump as a "sniveling coward" and told Trump to leave his wife alone. But campaigns have a way of letting bygones be bygones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Device Found Near George Soros Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/explosive-device-found-ny-home-billionaire-soros-141259535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI on Tuesday was investigating an explosive device found in the mailbox at the New York home of US billionaire and liberal donor George Soros, a target of right-wing groups, officials confirmed. An employee of the residence in Bedford, north of Manhattan, found the suspicious package in the mailbox</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SPOOKED!</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/index/djia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump Lawyer: There's No 'Witch Hunt,' Mueller 'Is American Hero'...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/news-and-politics/former-trump-lawyer-ty-cobb-no-witch-hunt-mueller-is-an-american-hero/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It was important to me not to have criticism widely thrown back-and-forth and turn it into a Ken Starr-like process, the way that ended up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Buying of Treasurys Softens...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/foreign-buying-of-u-s-treasurys-softens-unsettling-financial-markets-1540303515</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overseas investors, traders and central bankers are buying fewer Treasurys, which helped fuel a bond selloff this fall, pushing yields up and shaking stocks. Foreign buyers now hold 41% of outstanding Treasury debt, their lowest share in 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Turns Over Identities of Bloggers on Soccer Team...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/23/sports/benfica-bloggers-google.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anonymous writers who disclosed proprietary information about the storied club may not be able to remain anonymous for much longer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcker thinks 'we're in hell of mess'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/former-fed-chairman-paul-volcker-thinks-were-in-a-hell-of-a-mess.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Federal Reserve Chairman Paul Volcker, who has reached legend status in the world of central banking, isn't optimistic about current conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New TITANIC to set sail...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5ny.com/news/new-titanic-will-sail-from-dubai-in-2022</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans are continuing to launch a new Titanic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA shares rocket as short seller reverses position...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-shares-rocket-5-as-short-seller-citron-reverses-position-2018-10-23</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cook shifts 8 toward Dems...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412700-cook-shifts-8-house-races-toward-dems</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook Political Report on Tuesday shifted eight House races toward Democrats and two in favor of Republicans with 14 days to go before the midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 relatives of GOP Nevada gov candidate pen op-ed opposing him...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412694-12-family-members-of-gop-nevada-governor-candidate-pen-op-ed-opposing-him</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A dozen relatives of a Republican running for governor in Nevada</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Ellison falls behind in bid to become Minnesota AG...</title>
      <link>http://www.startribune.com/minnesota-poll-doug-wardlow-leads-keith-ellison-in-attorney-general-s-race/498264151/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republican gained ground since last month's poll; about one in six Minnesota voters still undecided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECOND migrant caravan heads for USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6307043/SECOND-migrant-caravan-1-000-heading-following-first.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The second caravan is believed to have started near the site of the first, in Honduras, and has already crossed into Guatemala, spending Monday night near the town of Chiquimula.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can rodeo legend win SDakota?</title>
      <link>http://theweek.com/articles/803164/democratic-rodeo-legend-become-south-dakotas-next-governor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the most inspiring governor's race in America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candidate Arrested For Stealing Rival's Campaign Signs...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/10/22/buena-park-candidate-steals-campaign-signs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Youngsun “Sunny” Park was arrested at about 10 a.m. Friday in a residential neighborhood near Malvern Avenue and Dale Street on reports that a man and a woman were removing campaign signs from people’s lawns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise and rise of mega yacht: Billionaires play one-upmanship...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-6306281/The-rise-rise-mega-yacht-Billionaire-one-upmanship-high-seas.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Global yacht management company Hill Robinson says demand for mega yachts has surged over recent years, with the vessels decked out with extreme toys, from submarines to helicopters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Swedes getting microchips inserted into bodies...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6306569/Thousands-Swedes-getting-microchip-IDs-inserted-hands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Swedes have been implanted with a microchip that allows them to replace cash, tickets and access card with a chip the size of a grain of rice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathing through nose boosts memory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6306249/Breathing-nose-BOOSTS-memory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts from the Karolinska Institute in Sweden found participants in their test who were exposed to certain odours were better at recalling them if their mouths had been taped over.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identical twins born female -- now brothers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-6306369/Identical-twins-born-girls-brothers-transitioning-came-transgender.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jack and Jace Grafe, 23, originally from Baltimore, Maryland, were born female but are now transitioning together. The brothers are now both in happy relationships with women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The squadron of ex-military men behind Bolsonaro's rise in Brazil...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-election-generals-insight/the-squadron-of-ex-military-men-behind-bolsonaros-rise-in-brazil-idUSKCN1MX1QX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man who will likely be Brazil's next Defense Minister greeted two repor...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overuse of antibiotics 'risks return to dark ages of life-threatening surgery'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/oct/23/overuse-of-antibiotics-risks-return-to-dark-ages-of-life-threatening-surgery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warning comes as report shows 3 million common surgical procedures could be hazardous if infections become resistant to antibiotics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETAILS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPEP4+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boise, Reno Capitalize on California Real Estate Exodus...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/boise-and-reno-capitalize-on-the-california-real-estate-exodus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boise and Reno Capitalize on the California Real Estate Exodus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLEFACEBOOKTWITTER staffs splurge on Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/google-facebook-and-twitter-staffs-splurge-on-democrats-ahead-of-midterms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google, Facebook and Twitter employees have donated substantially more to Democrats than Republicans with the 2018 midterms less than three weeks away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1,000 smart glasses appeal to masses?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/norths-focals-smart-glasses-first-look.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A start-up called North, formally Thalmic Labs, is introducing a pair of smart glasses that it thinks will appeal to the masses because the design looks so similar to normal glasses. They're called Focals, and they cost around $1,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto dealers see slowing sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/auto-dealerships-see-sharp-decline-in-sales-in-october.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of auto dealers around the country is seeing a noticeable drop in retail sales and customer traffic, raising the possibility that a long-anticipated slowdown in auto sales has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter Registration Application Sent To Woman Who Died 29 Years Ago...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2018/10/22/voter-registration-application-dallas-woman-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official voter registration applications have been showing up in the mailboxes of thousands of Texans. The problem is some applications were sent to people who have been dead for decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Heartbreak Can Kill You...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/how-heartbreak-can-kill-you-grief-causes-deadly-inflammation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from Rice University say that people who struggle to overcome grief caused by loss of a loved one are at greater risk of suffering from potentially deadly levels of inflammation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTOS: NUMBERS AT TRUMP RALLY DWARF THOSE AT OBAMA EVENT...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/photos-numbers-at-trump-rally-dwarf-those-at-obama-event/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Second angle at Obama rally shows miniscule crowd</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Company Helps People Flee San Francisco...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/10/22/high-housing-costs-are-pushing-people-ou</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaving The Bay Area is a real estate brokerage that helps people decamp for cheaper, greener pastures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brothers face $450,000 fine for removing trees from THEIR property...</title>
      <link>https://www.mlive.com/news/detroit/index.ssf/2018/10/brothers_could_pay_nearly_half.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They believed they were in the clear with the township's "exemption for farming."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youth Hostels Expand in USA by Shedding Old Identity...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/youth-hostels-expand-in-u-s-by-shedding-old-identity-1540292401 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Traditional hostels are adding more private rooms while some established hotel brands are shrinking their room size and putting more focus on bars and food to target millennials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 hot races...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/elections/2018/10/23/midterm-elections-5-hot-races-could-help-decide-house-control/1683472002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While red rural states will likely decide whether Senate Republicans keep the majority, House Republicans are on defense in suburban swing districts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican 'suffragettes' want vote, change, in a man's Church...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-pope-synod-women/vatican-suffragettes-want-vote-change-in-a-mans-church-idUSKCN1MX1GS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Catholic women say there's a clerical stained glass ceiling in the Vatican,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China to clone humans...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/738153/china-dog-cloning-mass-human-cloned-clones</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World markets tumble...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/asian-shares-tumble-chinese-growth-063909004.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE (AP) — Global shares were broadly lower on Tuesday as investors focused on geopolitical worries in Italy, China and beyond.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UN: France ban on full-body Islamic veil illegal...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6306593/Frances-ban-body-Islamic-veil-violates-human-rights-U-N-rights-panel.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.N. Human Rights Committee said on Tuesday that France's ban on the niqab, the full-body Islamic veil, was a violation of human rights and it would be reviewing French legislation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOW set for steep triple-digit losses...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/23/dow-set-for-triple-digit-losses-at-the-open-amid-rising-global-tensions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stock futures pointed to a negative open on Tuesday as investors looked past solid earnings and continued to dump major technology and financial shares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ojeda: Out of Appalachia pain, a tough-as-nails Dem emerges...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/ojeda-appalachia-pain-tough-nails-democrat-emerges-021152477.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Part GI Joe, part steadfast advocate for West Virginia's working poor, Richard Ojeda is pursuing the near-impossible: flipping one of America's most conservative congressional districts and reclaiming corners of Trump country for Democrats. Two weeks before midterm elections that will determine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO to show muscle in massive Norway exercises...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181023-nato-show-military-muscle-massive-norway-exercises</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Seizes on Saudi Murder as Chance to Upend Middle East...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/erdogan-seizes-on-saudi-murder-as-chance-to-upend-middle-east#gs.IhZNfOY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Erdogan is trying to turn a horrific murder into a catalyst for regaining influence across the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cocaine Deaths Hit Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/cocaine-deaths-hit-record-in-u-s-as-opioid-overdoses-level-off#gs.4ApLf3w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cocaine Deaths Hit Record in U.S. as Opioid Overdoses Level Off</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Woman demands to see passports of Spanish-speaking family at Virginia restaurant...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/412647-woman-demands-to-see-passports-of-spanish-speaking-family-at</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A white woman confronted a Spanish-speaking family last week at a Virginia restaurant and demanded that they "show me your passports" in video that has since gone viral.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT: Secret Service had to break up fight between Kelly and Lewandowski...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/the-day-the-west-wing-boiled-over-just-steps-from-the-oval-office/17938561/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An argument in February between White House chief of staff John F. Kelly and Corey Lewandowski, an informal adviser to President Donald Trump, turned into a physical altercation that required Secret Service intervention just outside the Oval Office, according to a half-dozen people familiar with the events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PET SHOP BOY:  'Where's the art, the poetry in all this?'</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2018/oct/21/neil-tennant-pet-shop-boys-collection-lyrics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With his collection of Pet Shop Boys lyrics about to be published, the musician talks about songwriting through the Thatcher era, the Aids crisis and the age of Brexit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stacey Abrams's Burning of Georgia Flag Surfaces on Eve of Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/22/us/politics/abrams-flag-burning-georgia.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As a college student, more than a quarter-century ago, Ms. Abrams joined in the burning of the state flag, which at the time was viewed by many as a lingering symbol of white supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive Device Found Near George Soros Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/10/22/nyregion/george-soros-explosive-device.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bomb squad technicians “proactively detonated” the device, a law enforcement official said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SILENT</title>
      <link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/article/Divided-Democrats-struggle-to-answer-Trump-s-13328112.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mysanantonio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are struggling to respond to President Donald Trump and his Republican allies, who are casting the caravan of thousands of migrants headed toward the U.S.-Mexico border as a failure of Democrats to help enact immigration policy in the GOP-controlled Congress. Some Democrats said Trump is vulnerable to a counterattack on his core campaign issue given that his policies failed to reduce the number of unauthorized immigrants. Yet party leaders and Democratic candidates have largely been silent ahead of the midterm elections, refusing to engage with Trump. The Democratic and Republican strategies reflect the path each party has charted with two weeks till Nov. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling Farmer Charged With Animal Abuse in Deaths of 27 Cows...</title>
      <link>https://lightlynews.com/2018/10/22/nyregion/a-struggling-new-york-farmer-is-charged-with-animal-abuse-within-the-deaths-of-27-cows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lightlynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Struggling New York Farmer Is Charged With Animal Abuse within the Deaths of 27 Cows - LIGHTLYNEWS.COM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vandals Throw Giant Boulder Through McCarthy Office Window...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/22/kevin-mccarthy-office-vandalized/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racial tension divides town after black, gay mayor elected...</title>
      <link>http://www.post-gazette.com/news/state/2018/10/22/Racial-tension-divides-Pennsylvania-Bridgeport-Mark-Barbee-black-openly-gay-mayor-election/stories/201810220092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.post-gazette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mark Barbee says Bridgeport, near Philadelphia, needs to fight racism. Others say race only became an issue when Barbee made it one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge bars New Hampshire proof of residency requirement for new voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-new-hampshire/judge-bars-new-hampshire-proof-of-residency-requirement-for-new-voters-idUSKCN1MW2Y8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New Hampshire judge on Monday put on hold a law requiring some voters to prese...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala makes big first impression in Iowa...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/10/22/kamala-harris-2020-iowa-923968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California senator previews her likely 2020 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teen accused of beheading his mother found not guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article220431740.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Franklin County teen charged with beheading his mother in 2017 has been judged not guilty by reason of insanity and committed to state psychiatric care.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Closes NY Stock Exchange...</title>
      <link>https://www.machinedesign.com/motion-control/groundbreaking-moment-robot-closes-ny-stock-exchange</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.machinedesign.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UR5e robot arm from Universal Robots is the first “cobot” to ring the NYSE bell, marking the rapid growth of collaborative robotics within the industrial automation market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Previously Deported Join Caravan......</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/10/22/previously-deported-illegal-aliens-join-caravan-its-time-for-me-to-go-back/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously deported illegal aliens are joining the migrant caravan headed to the U.S.-Mexico border to inundate the immigration system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeBron to Produce 'FRIDAY THE 13TH' Reboot...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/friday-the-13th-vertigo-entertainment-and-lebron-james-springhill-entertainment-1202988428/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following “Halloween’s” massive success at the box-office this weekend, another slasher franchise is looking at a rebirth as Roy Lee’s Vertigo Entertainment and LeBron James…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When you hear economy improving, 'remember who started it'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/412617-obama-when-you-hear-economys-improving-remember-who-started-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Obama on Monday urged a crowd in Las Vegas to "remember who started" the current economic boom, reminding them that the country recovered from the Great Recession during his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Scores Plummet for Class of 2018, Lowest in DECADES...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/trending/thanks-common-core-act-scores-for-class-of-2018-worst-in-decades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's not like we weren't warned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VB6SNVajb74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live coverage of Trump campaigning for Ted Cruz at â€˜Make America Great Againâ€™ rally in Houston, TX. Â» Subscribe to NBC News: http://nbcnews.to/Subscrib...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STUMPS FOR CRUZ...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/houston/article/Abbott-fires-up-rally-crowd-ahead-of-Trump-13327847.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Monday called Rep. Beto O'Rourke "a stone-cold phony" and took some sharp jabs at Sen. Ted Cruz's Democratic opponent, but otherwise focused on national issues while praising Cruz and a laundry list of Texas Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1000 MILES AWAY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c3eaa50bbf8a4cdf9fc5c0952225e1bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAPACHULA, Mexico (AP) — Thousands of Central American migrants resumed an arduous trek toward the U.S. border Monday, with many bristling at suggestions there could be terrorists among them and saying the caravan is being used for political ends by U.S. President Donald Trump. The caravan's numbers have continued to grow as they walk and hitch rides through hot and humid weather, and the United Nations estimated that it currently comprises some 7,200 people, "many of whom intend to continue the march north."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest shipwreck discovered; 2,400 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2018/oct/23/oldest-intact-shipwreck-thought-to-be-ancient-greek-discovered-at-bottom-of-black-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Archaeologists say the five-metre vessel has lain undisturbed for more than 2,400 years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How govt policies, taxpayer money helped Musk...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/10/21/how-government-policies-and-taxpayer-money-have-helped-musk-and-tesla.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla is not alone in going after government dollars, but Elon Musk's major companies have gotten significant government support in different forms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Judge upholds MONSANTO verdict, cuts award to $78M</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5c872e3fadfa41aeaf635c99a7629ba5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — A Northern California judge on Monday upheld a jury's verdict that found Monsanto's weed killer caused a groundskeeper's cancer, but she slashed the amount of money to be paid to the man from $289 million to $78 million. In denying Monsanto's request for a new trial, San Francisco Superior Court Judge Suzanne Bolanos cut the jury's punitive damage award from $250 million to $39 million. The judge had earlier said she had strong doubts about the jury's punitive damage award.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK: Government bans phrase 'fake news'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2018/10/22/government-bans-phrase-fake-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The government has banned the term &amp;ldquo;fake news&amp;rdquo; after urging ministers to use &amp;ldquo;misinformation&amp;rdquo; or &amp;quot;disinformation&amp;quot; instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston area smashes cast ballots record...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/politics/horseshoe/article/Harris-County-smashes-early-voting-record-13327145.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harris County voters on Monday set a new record for the first day of early voting in a midterm election, County Clerk Stan Stanart said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Your poop is probably full of plastic...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/your-poop-is-probably-full-of-plastic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study suggests that microplastics routinely show up in our food—and our digestive tracts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe quest to build 'unhackable' quantum internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.technologyreview.com/s/612327/europes-quest-for-an-unhackable-quantum-internet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.technologyreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An ambitious project in the Netherlands aims to use quantum technology to foil hackers who try to spy on data flowing through the internet’s pipes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA difficulty recovering lost, taken artifacts...</title>
      <link>https://www.theverge.com/2018/10/22/18009414/nasa-lunar-rover-historical-artifacts-lost-space-shuttle</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theverge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lunar soil bag and Apollo 11 hand controllers have slipped through the cracks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX accused of deceiving black users with manipulative artwork...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/tv/netflix-accused-of-deceiving-black-users-with-manipulative-personalised-artwork-2392085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix has been criticised for appearing to deceive black users with the use of 'intrusive' and 'manipulative' advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot baths improve depression as much as exercise?</title>
      <link>https://www.newscientist.com/article/2183250-hot-baths-could-improve-depression-as-much-as-physical-exercise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newscientist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking a hot bath twice a week may help relieve mild depression. It may work by resetting circadian rhythms, which are often disrupted in people with depression</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: WIKILEAKS CLAIM BASED IN PART ON REPORTER EMAIL...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/10/22/roger-stone-wikileaks-claim-reporter-email/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Second source'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychic busted for witchcraft fraud; 'Cleansing' jewels, cash from 'evil'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/ontario-psychic-charged-with-pretending-to-practice-witchcraft</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police say she told highly vulnerable customers she needed to ‘cleanse’ their cash and jewellery of ‘evil spirits’ in order to cure their ailments</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE warns EU 'meme ban' threatens open internet...</title>
      <link>https://mashable.com/article/youtube-ceo-meme-ban-eu-article-13/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mashable.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Article 13 is a threat to millions of YouTube creators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama compares Trump to 'tin pot dictatorship'...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/bensmith/obama-midterm-elections-vegas-jacky-rosen-senate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“That is not how America works. That is how some tin-pot dictatorship works."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Willa becomes Category 5 storm off Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.wunderground.com/cat6/Hurricane-Warnings-Mexico-Hurricane-Willa-Intensifies-Category-5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wunderground.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurricane warnings were flying for the Pacific coast of Mexico from San Blas to Mazatlán as extraordinarily fast-intensifying Category 5 Hurricane Willa headed north at 7 mph towards the coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas crowd in line 24 hrs before event...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/politics/article/Trump-supporters-line-up-24-hours-ahead-of-Toyota-13325410.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glen Collins and his fiancee, DeeJay Miller, are among the supporters flocking to the Houston area to see the president. The couple left their 5-month-old baby with a relative in Waco to see Trump stump for Cruz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODWIN: Count on Hillary running...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/10/20/count-on-hillary-clinton-running-again-in-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is beyond odd, but here goes. I rise to defend Hillary Clinton. She is under attack and this time, the long knives are wielded by members of her own clan. Suddenly, after two years of indulgin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama: Remember who started 'economic miracles!'</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/congress/obama-downplays-economic-miracles-under-trump-remember-who-started-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama told Nevada voters Monday that they should not give President Trump credit for the current state of the economy and said they should "remember who started it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUDY: Manafort said nothing damaging...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-giuliani/trump-lawyer-manafort-said-nothing-damaging-in-mueller-interviews-idUSKCN1MW2U8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Under an unusual arrangement, Paul Manafort's attorney has kept Donald Trum...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
