<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Possible Shift in Aim...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/russia-says-donbas-is-ukraine-focus-in-possible-shift-in-aim/ar-AAVuCWq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scary twist in 'Frankenstein' variant...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/health/health-problems/emergence-of-deltacron-variant-exposes-scary-new-supervirus-threat/news-story/f35c37c83fca7f5e9092f76c94295171</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The arrival of the new Deltacron variant sent shockwaves across the globe – and experts say there’s a good reason why we should be concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  BLACK NEWS CHANNEL shutting...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/life/radiotvtalk-blog/black-news-channel-is-shutting-down/KQULTBFPYZHY7PNK3H4I7UVJYM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black News Channel, which has dozens of employees in Atlanta, is closing down after two years on air.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists figure out how vampire bats got taste for blood...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vampire-bats-blood-diet-313676c715465fd48192fa9f8ce2c39d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Scientists have figured out why vampire bats are the only mammals that can survive on a diet of just blood. They compared the genome of common vampire bats to 26 other bat species and identified 13 genes that are missing or no longer work in vampire bats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right to Film Police Under Attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/g5qn57/filming-police-legality</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans in several states have introduced legislation—and in some cases, passed it—that could ultimately punish people for recording the police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Revealed Nation of Rulers, Not Laws...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2022/03/25/covid-revealed-america-to-be-a-nation-of-rulers-not-of-laws/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The United States is a nation of laws, badly written and randomly enforced," noted the late musician and satirist Frank...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cleveland Wants to Become 'Kindest Place in Country'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/interactives/2022/magazine-cleveland-kindland-just-be-kind-politics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is politics getting in the way?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin backs Ketanji Jackson for Supreme Court, all but ensuring confirmation...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/25/joe-manchin-to-vote-for-ketanji-brown-jackson-to-supreme-court/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderate Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin announced Friday that he intended to vote to confirm Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson to the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, drugs, dry wall: Inside last artist communes on San Fran's Market Street...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sf-culture/article/SF-artist-commune-on-Market-17026538.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Acid proms,” Day of the Dead parties and live music once dominated the intersection...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid cases in UK rocket by million in week...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/03/25/coronavirus-uk-almost-one-million-people-test-positive-in-a-week-16344224/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Infections are nearing record levels in England, while both Scotland and Wales have reached the highest amount since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambulance Companies Sound Alarm on Workers in Short Supply...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloomberglaw.com/daily-labor-report/u-s-ambulance-companies-sound-alarm-on-workers-in-short-supply</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloomberglaw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambulance companies are warning they face a major worker shortage that could slow emergency response times across the country if nothing is done to help them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating Seafood Immoral? Octopuses, Squid, Crabs Have Emotions, Feel Pain!</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/octopuses-squid-crabs-emotions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers argue that octopuses, crabs, lobsters, crayfish, and other invertebrates are indeed sentient and can feel pain, anger, fear, and happiness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL HELL:  War in Ukraine nearing more dangerous phase...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenation.com/article/world/exclusive-ukraines-defense-intelligence-chief-warns-of-real-hell-for-russians/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenation.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brig. Gen. Kyrylo Budanov’s warning that Russia was about to invade his country was widely dismissed—until the war began. So his latest predictions about the course of what is turning out to be a surprisingly long war are probably worth taking more seriously.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOMAS RELEASED FROM HOSPITAL AFTER WEEK; MYSTERY INFECTION...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/supreme-court/justice-clarence-thomas-discharged-dc-hospital-rcna21559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas was admitted last Friday after experiencing flu-like symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUOTA PLAN MAY DESTROY OSCARS</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/culturefiles/are-the-oscars-over-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinking ratings, shrinking movie stars, boring broadcasts, not to mention battles over its controversial new museum. And now a quota system that threatens to tear the Oscars apart. How the Academy Awards are struggling to get on with the show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Map: Americans Fleeing Los Angeles And Flocking To Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90735184/where-did-americans-move-in-2021-this-population-map-will-show-you</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Los Angeles County was the biggest loser, while five counties in Texas were among the biggest gainers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More women becoming storm chasers, defying convention and breaking barriers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/more-women-are-becoming-storm-chasers-defying-convention-and-breaking-barriers/ar-AAVuAjP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin: J.K. Rowling and Russia Victims of Western 'Cancel Culture'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/general-news/jk-rowling-russia-putin-cancel-culture-1235118555/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian leader made an unexpected reference to the 'Harry Potter' author, who, he said, was canceled because she "didn't satisfy the demands of gender rights."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to host 'historic summit' of US, Arab diplomats...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220325-israel-to-host-historic-summit-of-us-arab-diplomats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel said it will host a "historic summit" from Sunday of top diplomats from the United States and three Arab states with which it has normalised ties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man caught with dozens of lizards in his clothes charged with smuggling 1,700 reptiles...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/man-caught-dozens-lizards-clothes-120003489.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 30-year-old Oxnard man was indicted on federal charges of wildlife trafficking, smuggling and conspiracy, prosecutors say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Riskiest Oscars Ever...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/riskiest-oscars-ever-academy-awards-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody's inclined to give this year's ceremony the benefit of the doubt, which means the stakes are huge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery of Queen Elizabeth and the Wheelchair...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-mystery-of-queen-elizabeth-and-the-wheelchair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Queen Elizabeth is rumored to be using a wheelchair, and determined not to be seen doing so during public appearances, such as Prince Philip’s memorial service next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brutally Honest Ballot No. 3...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/brutally-honest-oscars-ballot-3-1235117324/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A member of the Academy's directors branch, granted anonymity to speak freely, shares which films and people earned his precious vote (and why).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas discharged from hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/25/supreme-court-justice-clarence-thomas-discharged-from-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas was discharged from the hospital, a week after being admitted with an infection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin will vote for nominee Jackson, essentially ensuring her seat...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/25/politics/joe-manchin-ketanji-brown-jackson-vote/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Virginia Democratic Sen. Joe Manchin announced on Friday that he plans to vote for President Joe Biden's Supreme Court nominee Ketanji Brown Jackson, a move that all but guarantees she will be confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black TESLA employees describe culture of racism: 'Breaking point'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/black-tesla-employees-describe-culture-120007146.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In their own words, former Tesla employees describe what they call a racist work environment that led California to file a civil rights lawsuit against the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abramovich Eyes Sanction-Free Dubai Property...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/sanctioned-russian-billionaire-house-hunting-102600697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chelsea FC owner Roman Abramovich is looking for a house on a luxury manmade island in Dubai, sources told Bloomberg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSRPs Have Whole New Meaning in Upside-Down Car Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/in-upside-down-u-s-car-market-msrps-have-a-whole-new-meaning/ar-AAVulnl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THEME PARK HORROR: Boy, 14, dies after slipping out of 430ft drop tower ride at 75mph...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10651331/Teen-dies-fall-Florida-amusement-park-ride.html?ito=social-twitter_dailymailus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unnamed 14-year-old fell from the plunging ride - the world's tallest free-standing drop tower - at ICON park in Orlando, Florida, just after 11pm on Thursday, police and emergency services said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid runs riot with key nominees infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/tv/4970724/oscars-crisis-covid-best-picture/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS weekend’s Oscars are in crisis — with half of the Best Picture films battling Covid scares. Nominees have dubbed the panic “swab sweat” — as they nervously await two mandatory PCR tests 48 hou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Can Detect Heart Problems -- By Sound Of Voice...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/artificial-intelligence-heart-voice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers at the Mayo Clinic say people who have a high voice biomarker score are more than twice as likely to suffer major heart problems related to clogged arteries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China and Solomon Islands Draft Secret Security Pact, Raising Alarm in Pacific...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/24/china-and-solomon-islands-draft-secret-security-pact-raising-alarm-in-the-pacific/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY, Australia — A leaked document has revealed that China and the Solomon Islands are close to signing a security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson faces growing Republican opposition...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/599689-jackson-faces-growing-gop-opposition-on-supreme-court</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Ketanji Brown Jackson is facing a shrinking pool of potential GOP supporters for her Supreme Court confirmation, as Republicans harden their opposition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long on Europe's Fringe, Poland Takes Center Stage...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/25/long-on-europes-fringe-poland-takes-center-stage-as-war-rages-in-ukraine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW — After the White House announced this week that President Biden would visit Poland, the Kremlin let rip with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primaries Testing Trump Role as the GOP 'Kingpin'...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/25/how-the-2022-primaries-are-testing-trumps-role-as-the-g-o-p-kingpin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald J. Trump has sought to establish himself as the Republican Party’s undisputed kingmaker in the 2022 midterms, issuing more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado mountain project offers vision of green housing future...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/colorado-mountain-project-offers-vision-of-green-housing-e2-80-99s-future/ar-AAVu1GT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Tense Oscars race nears end as show aims to win back fans...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220325-tense-oscars-race-nears-end-as-show-aims-to-win-back-fans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood is anxious to find out if "CODA," "The Power of the Dog" or "Belfast" will be named the year's best film at the Oscars on Sunday -- and whether audiences will actually tune in to see it hap…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea goes Hollywood with dramatic missile launch footage...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220325-north-korea-goes-hollywood-with-dramatic-missile-launch-footage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leather jacket, sunglasses and a gigantic missile: North Korean state media announced the launch of Pyongyang's largest-ever intercontinental ballistic missile with an attempt at old school Hollywood…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel war rocks Mexico's Baroque jewel Zacatecas...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220325-cartel-war-rocks-mexico-s-baroque-jewel-zacatecas</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Escorted by heavily armed soldiers, a Mexican farmer returns to his ransacked ranch house near the front line of a war between drug cartels, whose acronyms are scrawled on bullet-pocked walls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: BRONCOS stadium fire torches seats, suite area...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/nfl-sports-fires-denver-b1d6fd0ebbcc9cbe67b05a023a3f432f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DENVER (AP) — Firefighters extinguished a blaze that torched several rows of seats and a suite area at the Denver Broncos' stadium on Thursday. The fire broke out on the fourth level at Empower Field at Mile High just after 2 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California groundbreaking set for largest wildlife crossing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/mountains-environment-california-los-angeles-canada-b641c9aacaa098a044cc8410f41af72f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Groundbreaking is set for next month on what's billed as the world's largest wildlife crossing — a bridge over a major Southern California highway that will provide more room to roam for mountain lions and other animals hemmed in by urban sprawl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts watching for potential new virus surge in USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-science-health-pandemics-wastewater-9b6589e908c8532db0922cc4ed3f3910</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — As coronavirus infections rise in some parts of the world, experts are watching for a potential new COVID-19 surge in the U.S. — and wondering how long it will take to detect. Despite disease monitoring improvements over the last two years, they say, some recent developments don't bode well:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Crash Mystery Deepens As Evidence Suggests Mid-Air Breakup...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/china-plane-crash-china-crash-mystery-deepens-as-evidence-suggests-mid-air-breakup-2842114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least one piece of the Boeing Co. 737-800 that crashed in China appears to have broken loose well before impact, a finding that adds mystery to the plane's fatal dive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA weighs engagement with Venezuela, Russian foothold in America's backyard...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-weighs-engagement-with-venezuela-a-russian-foothold-in-america-e2-80-99s-backyard/ar-AAVts35</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines alter uniform regulations, including maternity wear, manicure options, hairstyle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/marines-alter-uniform-regulations-including-maternity-wear-manicure-options-and-hairstyle/ar-AAVsLOC</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers push historic wave of bills targeting rights of LGBTQ teens, children, families...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gop-lawmakers-push-historic-wave-of-bills-targeting-rights-of-lgbtq-teens-children-and-their-families/ar-AAVu0u7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD: Influx of migrants at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/biden-faces-influx-of-migrants-at-the-border-amid-calls-to-lift-limits-that-aided-expulsions/ar-AAVqHUo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group hopes to use Constitution's ban on 'insurrectionists' to disqualify Marjorie Taylor Greene from reelection...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/washington/group-hopes-to-use-constitution-s-ban-on-insurrectionists-to-disqualify-marjorie-taylor-greene-from/article_7ea8f48c-e15e-5e1b-a3dc-287048712573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA — A group of Georgia voters has filed a challenge to U.S. Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s reelection bid, saying her actions leading up to the Jan. 6 Capitol attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Californians find bargain gas prices in Tijuana...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2654074?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TIJUANA, Mexico — Claudia Jessica Villarreal used to fill up her gray Nissan Pathfinder near her home in Chula Vista, California. Then Russia invaded Ukraine and gasoline prices went bonkers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX investigates 'off-label' use of puberty blockers amid ongoing fight over care...</title>
      <link>https://theeagle.com/texas-investigates-off-label-use-of-puberty-blockers-amid-ongoing-fight-over-transgender-care/article_4311c68a-abe8-11ec-b23c-4f8613ffc257.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton is investigating two pharmaceutical companies to determine whether they marketed certain drugs to treat transgender youth experiencing gender dysphoria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid 'RUST' tragedy legal drama, Baldwin back to work shooting Christmas movies in Rome...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amid-rust-tragedy-legal-drama-023500611.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s beginning to look a lot like Christmas for Alec Baldwin — even though the “Rust” tragedy still looms over his head. The beleaguered actor and producer is reportedly in Rome, working on his first movie projects since his involvement with last year’ fatal shooting on the New Mexico set of “Rust.” According to the Italian news service ANSA, Baldwin has two Italian Christmas-themed movies: ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kansas nuke plant was hacking target...</title>
      <link>https://lmtribune.com/nation/kansas-nuclear-plant-was-hacking-target-of-russian-spies-department-of-justice-says/article_19af1d08-3036-577f-8aad-7ffe14f95170.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lmtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A nuclear power plant in eastern Kansas was one target of computer hackers organized by Russia's spy agency as part of a large-scale international operation to seize control over critical</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's war in Ukraine nearing possibly more dangerous phase...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-europe-nato-971463587011b3bf19dde7abb35889ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Vladimir Putin's war in Ukraine is approaching a new, potentially more dangerous phase after a month of fighting has left Russian forces stalled by an outnumbered foe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN:  EXPECT REAL FOOD SHORTAGES</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-says-expect-real-food-175308088.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden said that the world will experience food shortages as a result of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, and production increases were a subject of discussions at a Group of Seven meeting on Thursday.Most Read from BloombergPutin Adviser Chubais Quits Over Ukraine War, Leaves RussiaChina Plane Crash Update: Second Black Box Found, Regulator SaysRussia Central Banker Wanted Out Over Ukraine, Putin Said NoWall Street Is Scrambling For the Exits in Moscow — and Billions Ar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notorious Hollywood P.I. Pellicano Off Probation, Years After Celebrity Wiretapping Scheme...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/private-investigator-anthony-pellicano-off-probation-birthday-wiretapping/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Radar has confirmed that Hollywood's favorite fixer is officially off probation, more than a decade after being sentenced for wiretapping, fraud, racketeering, and conspiracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines approve two-tone NAIL POLISH for troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10649095/Marines-approve-two-tone-nail-polish-troops-longer-hair.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US Marine Corps will allow service members to wear longer hair, two-tone nail polish for female Marines, and black or olive drab socks with their combat utility uniform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Week after hospitalization, Supreme Court still silent on Justice Thomas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/24/supreme-court-silent-on-justice-clarence-thomas-hospitalization.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News of Thomas' hospitalization came before confirmation hearings for Ketanji Brown Jackson, President Joe Biden's pick to replace Justice Stephen Breyer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILE HIGH STADIUM CATCHES FIRE...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/24/denver-broncos-mile-high-stadium-catches-fire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Empower Field at Mile High Stadium, the home of the Denver Broncos, caught on fire Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spies indicted in worldwide hacks of energy industry, including Kansas nuke plant...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/24/russian-spies-indicted-hack-nuclear-plant-00020217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their targets worked at more than 500 different entities, including the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission, according to the indictment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Marilyn Monroe movie gets rare NC-17 rating for sex content...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/movies/movie-news/netflix-marilyn-monroe-blonde-nc17-1235118236/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MPAA has given the biopic 'Blonde,' starring Ana de Armas as the celebrity icon, an adults-only rating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan 6 committee has Ginni Thomas, Mark Meadows texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/24/politics/ginni-thomas-mark-meadows-text-messages/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky Oscar Appearance In Works, Producer Hints...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/oscars-hosts-what-to-expect-wanda-sykes-regina-hall-1234986399/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a year of controversy and a self-described untypical Oscars, co-host Wanda Sykes today promised there would be some jabs in the March 27 ceremony but no one will get hurt. “We’re trying stayed a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin the tiger dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4965967/putin-tiger-dead-minnesota-zoo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TIGER named Putin has died while undergoing a medical procedure. Minnesota Zoo said that the big cat passed away during the procedure on Wednesday. Putin was said to have experienced cardiac fail…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France probes Interpol president for alleged torture, barbarism...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220324-france-probes-interpol-president-for-alleged-torture-barbarism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French anti-terror prosecutors have opened a preliminary inquiry into torture and acts of barbarism allegedly committed by Emirati General Ahmed Nasser Al-Raisi who in November became president of In…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurs far from USA inflaming political division on FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/Facebook-GearLaunch-17024417.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chronicle found that fake Facebook groups supporting the anti-vaccine “Freedom...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
