<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Drops VIKINGS QB As Spokesman Over Anti-Vax Stance...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/08/06/kirk-cousins-temporarily-loses-sponsorship-deal-with-michigan-hospital-over-covid-vaccine-stance/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Vikings quarterback Kirk Cousins has lost a sponsorship with a hospital in Michigan, as a result of what the hospital calls his stance on COVID-19 vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Story of Secret IRS Files...</title>
      <link>https://www.propublica.org/article/the-inside-story-of-how-we-reported-the-secret-irs-files</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.propublica.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ProPublica journalists who obtained the secret tax documents of thousands of America’s richest people share how they conceived of their stories, what readers should understand about the tax system and where they’re taking these stories next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHATSAPP Boss Blasts: Easily used to search for anything govt decides to control...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/whatsapp-head-apple-child-safety-surveillance-system-201956787.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook’s head of WhatsApp says he is “concerned” by Apple's child safety plans, calling it a "surveillance system.".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 people injured in stabbings on Tokyo train...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/06/asia/tokyo-train-stabbing-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people were stabbed on a train in Tokyo by a man with a knife Friday night, according to the Tokyo Fire Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Volcanic eruptions at Vesuvius, Santorini could trigger 'world crippling' tsunamis...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3425288/vesuvius-santorini-volcanic-eruptions-tsunamis/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VOLCANIC eruptions in Italy and Greece could trigger tsunamis that cripple world trade. Experts fear minor blasts at Vesuvius and Santorini could be just as if not more dangerous than colossal expl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cabin where 'River Dave' squatted for 27 years burns on day he appeared in court
...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/flooding-woodland-hermits-cabin-burns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An off-the-grid New Hampshire hermit known to locals as “River Dave” whose cabin burned down on wooded property where he was squatting for 27 years has been inundated with offers from as far away as California for a new place to live.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressman Suing Pelosi Over Mask Fines Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ralph-norman-congressman-covid-19-positive-test-vaccinated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Congressman Ralph Norman attributed his mild symptoms to his fully vaccinated status.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70% of New York voters say resign, majority thinks he should be charged...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/06/cuomo-should-resign-over-sexual-harassment-claims-new-yorkers-say-in-poll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden and other top Democrats say New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo should resign due to sexual harassment claims. He also faces potential impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONTIER Turns Away Booked Travelers Due To Staffing...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/this-is-outrageous-frontier-airlines-turn-away-booked-travelers-due-to-understaffing-issues/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passengers say it was a scene of wall-to-wall people and much frustration trying to get aboard Frontier Airlines flights Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban parade in US Humvees, chant 'Allahu Akbar...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3426213/taliban-parade-humvees-chant-capture-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICTORIOUS Taliban militants today paraded through the streets in captured US Humvees while chanting “Allahu Akbar”. The gloating gunmen flew the group’s white flag as they captur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreaks Tied to Concerts Raise Outdoor Transmission Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/music/music-news/pendleton-whisky-music-faster-horses-covid-outbreaks-outdoor-transmission-1208842/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts say closely packed crowds are likely responsible for cases tied to Oregon’s Pendleton Whisky Music Fest and Michigan’s Faster Horses Festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA Speeding Up Extra Doses...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fda-aiming-to-speed-extra-vaccine-doses-for-immunocompromised-patients/ar-AAN1LYi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration is speeding efforts to authorize extra doses of the coronavirus vaccines for Americans with weakened immune systems, a change that reflects a growing concern within the Biden administration about these vulnerable patients as the contagious Delta variant surges nationwide. The regulatory move would mean that people with impaired immune responses who need an extra shot, such as certain cancer patients, would be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Cares About Privacy -- But Only If You're an Advertiser...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/facebook-cares-about-privacy-e2-80-94but-only-if-you-e2-80-99re-an-advertiser/ar-AAN1ac5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The social giant kicked off researchers studying how political ads can encourage targeted voter suppression, leaving citizens with little insight into how they’re manipulated on the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US drops plan to vacate troop bases in Germany, Belgium...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210806-us-drops-plan-to-vacate-troop-bases-in-germany-belgium</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US drops plan to vacate troop bases in Germany, Belgium</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service Presses Forward With Plan to Slow Mail Delivery...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/06/1025488630/the-postal-service-presses-forward-with-unpopular-plan-to-slow-some-mail-deliver</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New members of the U.S. Postal Service Board of Governors expressed concerns with the plan, but it's moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil Political Crisis Grows as Bolsonaro, Top Court Bicker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/brazil-political-crisis-grows-as-bolsonaro-top-court-bicker/ar-AAMZzP1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Jair Bolsonaro’s relentless attack on Brazil’s voting system soured his relationship with the Supreme Court, leaving the country on the brink of an institutional crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILLS Ink QB Allen To 6-Year, $258 Million Extension...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/bills-josh-allen-agree-to-terms-on-six-year-extension-worth-reported-258-million-150-million-guaranteed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Allen will be under contract through 2028</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA shuts major hydroelectric plant amid record-low water levels at Lake Oroville...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/06/california-shuts-down-major-hydroelectric-plant-amid-severe-drought.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The loss of power could fuel rolling blackouts as the state struggles with a historic drought and record-breaking heat waves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pediatric patients scaring doctor...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/opinion/article/I-treat-pediatric-covid-patients-What-I-m-seeing-16362541.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Throughout the pandemic, I have cared for kids admitted with covid-19 to the children's...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon Decriminalized All Drugs. Will It Work?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/video/2021/08/06/oregon-decriminalized-all-drugs-to-stop-overdoses-will-it-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small-scale drug possession is now a $100 infraction that can be dismissed with a call to a drug abuse assessment hotline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police Draw Guns, Handcuff Black Realtor Showing House To Client...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/news/national/2021/08/05/black-realtor-client-handcuffed-during-home-showing-break-in.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They believe they were racially profiled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OUT BY FALL?</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/cuomo-sexual-harassment-assembly-deadline/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for the Legislature's impeachment probe gave the state's chief executive one week to provide them with reasons why he thinks he should keep his job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE FOUNDER FLEES TO NEW ZEALAND</title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/national/health/coronavirus/300373505/google-billionaire-larry-page-is-an-nz-resident-government-confirms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Google co-founder and the sixth-richest person in the world, Larry Page, is a New Zealand resident, the Government has confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teenagers dominate games...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcolympics.com/videos/teen-takeover-next-generation-dominates-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcolympics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teenagers have made their mark in the 2020 Tokyo Olympic Games, winning medal after medal across various sports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Churches left out of construction boom...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/construction-spending-churches-religion-f3e6fcbe-755d-40e8-b198-e47753aa5af2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It bucks the trend of construction booms in other sectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo Pleads Ignorance on Missing Whiskey...</title>
      <link>https://whiskeyraiders.com/article/pompeo-pleads-ignorance-in-the-case-of-the-missing-whiskey-i-wouldnt-know-the-difference-between-a-58-bottle-and-a-5800-bottle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whiskeyraiders.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Fasting Best Way To Fight Off Infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fasting-food-poisoning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After being infected with Salmonella, fasting eliminated almost all of the tissue damage and inflammation in the mice's intestines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Goldmine' asteroid headed for solar system full of metals worth quadrillions...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/goldmine-asteroid-headed-solar-system-24705236</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 124 mile-wide space rock is heading towards our solar system and scientists believe it could be worth more than $10,000 quadrillion (£8,072 quadrillion), and NASA is planning to visit it by 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DELTA PLUS' Variant Detected In San Francisco...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/new-delta-plus-coronavirus-variant-detected-in-bay-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Delta variant of the coronavirus fuels an ongoing COVID wave, Bay Area health experts are keeping a close eye on yet another variant: Delta Plus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE FOUNDER FLEES TO NEW ZEALAND</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/larry-page-revealed-as-another-tech-billionaire-with-se-1847434522</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ultra-wealthy are buying residency and citizenship in New Zealand to hedge against the apocalypse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto brawl bogs down infrastructure bill, as Yellen and White House fight changes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cryptocurrency-brawl-bogs-down-infrastructure-bill-as-yellen-and-white-house-fight-off-changes/ar-AAN0HPH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senators are at odds over how to handle taxation related to cryptocurrencies, setting off a fierce lobbying war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRINCESS CRUISES tightening restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/transportation/566687-cruise-lines-tightening-restrictions-as-delta-variant-spreads</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Princess Cruises is announced Thursday that the company will take measures to curb the spread of the coronavirus on its ships as the delta variant continues to surge across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Does Bezos Want NASA Moon Lander Contract So Badly?</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/08/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-fight-nasa-moon-lander-contract-spacex/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Bezos believes that space is the railroads and highways of the future.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Bikers Expected in Sturgis...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/06/hundreds-of-thousands-of-bikers-expected-in-sturgis-despite-delta-variant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although most large events shut down last summer because of the coronavirus pandemic, the Sturgis Motorcycle Rally forged ahead, panicking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAX evacuated after 'bomb threat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3425327/lax-airport-terminal-five-bomb-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAX Airport was evacuated after a “suspicious vehicle” prompted a security concern. Travelers said that they were evacuated from Terminal 5 early on Friday morning. Both levels of the t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Springsteen, US team qualify for equestrian jumping final...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-entertainment-great-britain-olympic-team-germany-olympic-team-cbb34f12fa48df3b9e0d6498ceff891f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Jessica Springsteen and the U.S. equestrian jumping team earned an encore performance in qualifying Friday night. Springsteen and gold medal-winning teammates Laura Kraut and McClain Ward secured a spot in Saturday night's team jumping final with a trio of nearly perfect trips around the Equestrian Park course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record Drug Busts and Illegal Raves: Summer on Spain's Party Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avpvp/record-drug-busts-and-illegal-raves-welcome-to-summer-on-spains-party-islands</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people party on despite club closures, police are battling to stem the tide of drugs heading to the Balearics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Mission Over Baltic Sea By Air Force Nuke Sniffing Plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/41850/curious-mission-flown-over-the-baltic-sea-by-u-s-air-force-nuke-sniffing-plane</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Air Force only has one Constant Phoenix jet, which is used to collect air samples that could show evidence of nuclear testing or accidents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perfect Storm Battering DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-perfect-storm-battering-ron-desantis-in-florida</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record high COVID numbers, fallout from the Surfside collapse, a horrific red tide—on the latest New Abnormal, it’s getting harder for the governor to claim everything’s just fine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truthers Demanding Horse Medicine Instead of Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/demon-sperm-doctors-new-bogus-cure-has-covid-truthers-eating-horse-paste</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These geniuses have been convinced to pass on the vaccine and raid rural farm stores so they can suck down “sheep drench” and take swine injections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BROKEN SPIRIT: Meltdown will go into next week with 50% of flights canceled Friday...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3422428/spirit-airlines-disruption-continues-cancellations-fifth-day/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE meltdown at Spirit Airlines will continue into next week, the travel giant’s CEO admitted Thursday – as a sixth day of chaos will see more than 50 per cent of its scheduled flights …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eastwood Finds Redemption in 'CRY MACHO' Trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollingstone.com/movies/movie-news/clint-eastwood-cry-macho-trailer-1208486/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eastwood stars in and directed the film</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents Refusing To Evacuate Pulling Guns On Firefighters!</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/firefighters-getting-guns-pulled-out-on-them-some-dixie-fire-residents-refusing-to-evacuate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters working the massive Dixie Fire burning in several Northern California counties are having to deal with another challenge: residents who refuse to evacuate and are brandishing guns at fire crews.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese uproar as state TV host calls gold-medal winner 'manly woman'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/aug/06/chinese-uproar-as-state-tv-host-calls-gold-medal-winner-a-manly-woman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shot put champion Gong Lijiao quizzed about boyfriends and settling down into ‘a woman’s life’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene suggests Southerners could 'welcome' Biden 'police state friends' with guns...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/congress/marjorie-taylor-greene-suggests-southerners-could-welcome-biden-s-police-n1276152</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We all love our Second Amendment rights," she said, adding, "They might not like the welcome they get.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Tourist Bites Man's Ear Off At Florida Keys Hotel...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/05/florida-man-altercaiton-man-loses-part-of-ear-in-keys/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Port St. Lucie man is facing serious charges after being accused of biting part of a man’s ear off during an altercation at a Stock Island hotel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NJ Gov Orders Masks in Schools...</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/school-masks-mandate-required-in-murphy/10934204/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the COVID numbers in the Garden State are not as bad as many other states, cases here are five times higher than they were a month ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID renews interest in radiation, but doctors caution against pilgrimages to radon-filled mines...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/living/lifestyle/2021-08-03/COVID-renews-interest-in-radiation-but-doctors-caution-against-pilgrimages-to-radon-filled-mines-2432072.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The travelers view the radon exposure as low-dose radiation therapy for a long list of health issues. But the Environmental Protection Agency and the World Health Organization, among others, blame the gas as the second-leading cause of lung cancer and caution against its use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban kill head of govt media dept...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-taliban-94face0f6d0cabcc3896ef6f33d03bea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan (AP) — The Taliban shot and killed the director of Afghanistan's Government Information Media Center on Friday, the latest killing of a government official and one that comes just days after an assassination attempt on the acting defense minister.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He put off getting shot. Now, he's in ICU pleading others avoid mistake...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/he-put-off-getting-the-vaccine-now-he-e2-80-99s-in-the-icu-pleading-others-avoid-his-mistake-e2-80-98i-messed-up-e2-80-99/ar-AAN0LZd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I could have done research. I could have gotten the vaccine. I could have gotten my kids vaccinated, but I was negligent," Travis Campbell told The Washington Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Prosecutors Could Do...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/2021/08/what-could-prosecutors-do-to-andrew-cuomo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A veteran of the Manhattan DA’s office on the new danger to the governor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expats to Be Locked In on Return as Australia Ups Border Curbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/expats-to-be-locked-in-on-return-as-australia-ups-border-curbs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expats to Be Locked In on Return as Australia Ups Border Curbs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ leader entangled in report under fire...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566638-lgbtq-leader-entangled-in-cuomo-report-comes-under-fire</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president of the nation’s largest LGBTQ advocacy organization is under fire from activists and some of his own employees over his role in the sexual harassment controversy surrounding New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurses' grief pours out online...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210806100011-hbgiq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-NURSES (PIX, GRAPHICS):U.S. nurses' COVID-19 grief pours out online: 'I just don't want to watch anyone else die'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE founder gets New Zealand residency, raising questions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-lifestyle-travel-new-zealand-immigration-b7184a3296dea7c8c276232d615da0ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — Google co-founder Larry Page has gained New Zealand residency, officials confirmed Friday, stoking debate over whether extremely wealthy people can essentially buy access to the South Pacific country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lake Powell dips to historic low...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-science-business-environment-and-nature-lakes-b5e987404cbb8ca59c1bac2907522ef5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PAGE, Ariz. (AP) — A thick, white band of newly exposed rock face stretches high above boaters’ heads at Lake Powell, creating a sharp contrast against the famous red desert terrain as their vessels weave through tight canyons that were once underwater.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS WINNING</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/we-are-backsliding-our-pandemic-momentum-has-been-squandered-002145298.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top U.S. public health officials are warning about an alarming rise in coronavirus cases, hospitalizations and deaths, figures that represent a bitter setback in the fight to end the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COWBOYS remain NFL's most valuable team at $6.5 billion...</title>
      <link>https://cowboyswire.usatoday.com/2021/08/05/dallas-cowboys-jerry-jones-forbes-nfl-franchise-value/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cowboyswire.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the 15th straight year, the Dallas Cowboys are the NFL’s most valuable franchise. To put it lightly, they’ve enjoyed one heck of a hot girl summer. | From @CDBurnett7</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden considers withholding funds to spur vaccinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Biden-administration-considers-withholding-funds-16368208.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The Biden administration is considering using federal regulatory powers and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital admissions, deaths rise 40% in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/white-house-pushes-student-vaccinations-as-hospital-admissions-deaths-rise-about-40-in-a-week/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daily new cases, hospitalizations and deaths from the delta variant of the coronavirus are all surging as millions of Americans remain unvaccinated, federal health officials warned Thursday. "Across the board, we are seeing increases in cases and hospitalizations in all...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA turns aggressive on requirements...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/la-gets-aggressive-on-vaccine-requirements-as-delta-surges-how-it-affects-you/ar-AAMYNUT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;L.A. County has taken aggressive actions to fight the Delta variant, and officials in the county and city are considering more. How it will affect you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire devastates California Gold Rush town...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/weve-lost-everything-survivors-reeling-as-downtown-greenville-leveled-by-dixie-fire/ar-AAMZ1WT?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'We've lost everything': Greenville's historic downtown leveled by Dixie fire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighter sues after pulling daughters body from Surfside rubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.firehouse.com/rescue/technical-rescue/structural-collapse/news/21233300/firefighter-sues-after-pulling-daughter-from-collapsed-fl-condo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.firehouse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his wrongful death lawsuit, a Miami firefighter who searched the wreckage for his 7-year-old daughter for days claims Surfside condo officials knew about “deplorable conditions" at the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA MAKES BILLIONS; STOCK DOUBLES...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/articles/moderna-earnings-stock-vaccine-covid-variants-51628160919</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The mRNA specialist reported a larger-than-expected profit, but that wasn't enough for investors following a 141% gain over the past three months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRGIN GALACTIC prices space tickets at $450,000...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/virgin-galactic-restarting-space-tickets-212051932.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After flying its founder Richard Branson to space, Virgin Galactic is restarting ticket sales beginning at $450,000, the company announced Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starving cows. Fallow farms. The Arizona drought worst in country...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/starving-cows-fallow-farms-arizona-090031813.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly all of Arizona is in drought, with large swaths in extreme drought. Experts say the picture may well get worse in a state where more than a third of its water comes from Lake Mead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census probes sexual orientation, gender identity...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/5/census-breaks-new-ground-questions-about-sexual-or/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau has begun asking Americans about sexual orientation for the first time as part of a battery of surveys it is doing to measure social changes during the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picture of Micky Mouse fools NYC's vax passport...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/ny-vaccine-passport-apps-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NYC COVID Safe app allows users to upload a photo of their vaccine card and then flash the image in the app to enter a vaccine-requiring establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan to 'Think Different' About Encryption Opens Backdoor to Your Private Life...</title>
      <link>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/08/apples-plan-think-different-about-encryption-opens-backdoor-your-private-life</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eff.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple has announced impending changes to its operating systems that include new “protections for children” features in iCloud and iMessage. If you’ve spent any time following the Crypto Wars, you know what this means: Apple is planning to build a backdoor into its data storage system and its messaging system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAUCI:  WORSE THAN DELTA COMING...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fauci-delta-variant-covid-d1c0d550-6624-417d-bde6-33c8f56deaba.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People who are not getting vaccinated mistakenly think it’s only about them. But it isn’t."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Secretary Warns of School Closures...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/education-secretary-warns-de-santis-abbott-on-masks-dont-be-the-reason-why-schools-are-interrupted-224307858.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of Education Miguel Cardona said Thursday that while the Delta variant is “providing new challenges,” he expects children to return to in-class instruction this fall.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
