<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Men at ad agency win sex discrimination case...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9817847/Two-men-win-sex-discrimination-payout-female-director-vowed-obliterate-JWTs-reputation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chas Bayfield (left) and Dave Jenner, in their fifties and creative directors at JWT, were axed from the leading ad agency because bosses 'urgently' wanted to address its poor gender pay gap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typhoon threatens to derail...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/23/olympics-threatened-by-typhoon-that-could-hit-tokyo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The storm is forming in the Philippine Sea and will head dangerously close to Japan’s capital city on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Box Office Plunges 70% Due to New Entry Rules...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/film/global/france-vaccination-mandatory-b-o-drop-1235026283/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French box office has taken a big hit and dropped 70% this week due to the new sanitary measures enforced on July 21 which require a proof of vaccination or a recent negative PCR test to enter …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since restaurants reopened, customers have been 'unbearable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/food/article/SF-Bay-Area-restaurants-customers-rude-Yelp-review-16333535.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the June 15 reopening, customers have gotten … a little difficult.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA BECOMES NATION'S HOTSPOT, AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/coronavirus/article252960743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surgeon general called it an “all-in moment” for the nation as the coronavirus pandemic becomes a more regional phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump friend Barrack ordered released on $250 million bond...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/trump-ally-tom-barrack-spac-pulled-bail-hearing-in-uae-case-changed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thomas Barrack, a close friend of Donald Trump, is accused of illegally lobbying for the United Arab Emirates during Trump's campaign and presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL COACH FIRED FOR REFUSING VAX</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2021/07/23/report-vikings-coach-rick-dennison-gone-coronavirus-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Vikings have reportedly cut ties with assistant coach Rick Dennison after he refused to take the coronavirus vaccine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrack Reaches Bail Deal With Prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/tom-barrack-reaches-bail-deal-with-prosecutors-in-uae-case-1.1632353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump ally Thomas J. Barrack Jr. and U.S. prosecutors have reached agreement on a bail package that will allow the founder of Colony Capital Inc. to be freed ahead of a trial on charges that he illegally lobbied the government on behalf of the United Arab Emirates, according to people familiar with the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Herschel Walker eyes Senate run, turbulent past emerges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-sports-nfl-college-football-coronavirus-pandemic-5e2875eec11e93f9a3bf1fc859137ff8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATLANTA (AP) — At first glance, Herschel Walker has a coveted political profile for a potential Senate candidate in Georgia. He was a football hero at the University of Georgia before his long NFL career.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellen urges Congress to raise debt limit now...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/yellen-urges-congress-to-raise-debt-limit-by-aug-2-or-treasury-will-take-extraordinary-measures-to-prevent-default.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER just 39% effective as delta spreads; Still prevents severe illness...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/delta-variant-pfizer-covid-vaccine-39percent-effective-in-israel-prevents-severe-illness.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer's and BioNTech's Covid-19 vaccine is just 39% effective against delta in Israel, but still provides strong protection against severe illness and hospitalization.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests break out at Haiti president's funeral, guests run for cover...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723161436-btoxn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-PRESIDENT/FUNERAL (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-Protests break out at Haiti president's funeral, guests run for cover</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX begins to arrest and jail crossers on trespassing charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-begins-to-arrest-and-jail-border-crossers-on-trespassing-charges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas is beginning to arrest migrants on trespassing charges along the U.S.-Mexico border as part of Republican Gov. Greg Abbott's actions that he says are needed to slow the number of border crossings, jailing at least 10 people so far with more on the way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye debuts album in bizarre, wordless appearance...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/music/2021/07/22/kanye-west-debuts-donda-west-album-atlanta-listening-party/8062969002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West debuted "Donda," named for his late mother, to a crowd of more than 40,000 fans in Atlanta. The new album arrives Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA rules change means Bezos may not get 'Astronaut wings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/US/2021/07/23/faa-rules-wings-spaceflight/4631627040412/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal aviation regulators have made a rare change to the requirements for its Commercial Astronaut Wings Program, meaning Blue Origin founder Jeff Bezos may not officially be recognized for his spaceflight this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA BECOMES NATION'S HOTSPOT, AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article252960743.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surgeon general called it an “all-in moment” for the nation as the coronavirus pandemic becomes a more regional phenomenon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singer Morgan Wallen says issue of race stretches across industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.goodmorningamerica.com/culture/story/morgan-wallen-speaks-racial-slur-gma-interview-michael-78989332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goodmorningamerica.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morgan Wallen spoke out in an exclusive interview with "Good Morning America" co-host Michael Strahan that aired Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden installing federal judges at blistering pace...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-judicial-federal-court-ffac832c-131d-4285-bc1a-3c1de9709463.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;: Biden has had eight federal judges confirmed since taking office on Jan. 20.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body Preserved in Bog Since IRON AGE Contains Undigested Last Meal...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/body-preserved-in-a-bog-since-the-iron-age-still-contai-1847343217</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dubbed "Tollund Man," the natural mummy offers a window into what life was like in Europe 2,400 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET THE COVID GAMES BEGIN!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9817335/Tokyo-Olympics-Protesters-gather-hours-opening-ceremony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tokyo Olympics is finally underway in Japan after a year of Covid delays, with Naomi Osaka given the honour of lighting the Olympic cauldron to start the sporting spectacular.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPOST MEDIA GURU EXITS...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/a-fond-farewell-from-keith-j-kelly-as-media-ink-comes-to-an-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keith J. Kelly’s farewell column gives a snapshot of his most memorable behind-the-scenes moments and the larger-than-life characters he experienced in his 23 years writing Media Ink for The …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening Ceremony Review: Lackluster Affair, Weak Start...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/tokyo-olympics-opening-ceremony-review-nbc-naomi-osaka-savanah-guthrie-mike-tirico-1234798669/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPOILER ALERT: This story contains details of this morning’s Tokyo Olympics Opening Ceremony live on NBC. Ever imagine what it would be like if they held an Olympics and almost nobody came? W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics convene amid disbelief in much of Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-opening-ceremony-8b75b92f36477af48612c70a2b7104e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Belated and beleaguered, the virus-delayed Tokyo Summer Olympics finally opened Friday night with cascading fireworks and made-for-TV choreography that unfolded in a near-empty stadium, a colorful but strangely subdued ceremony that set a striking tone to match a unique pandemic Games.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon's people line up in 'queues of humiliation' as country unravels...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/lebanons-people-line-queues-humiliation-090043959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortages of basic goods have hit Lebanon as its leaders do little to resolve a long-running currency crisis that has sparked despair and desperation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC FACES OBSTACLES</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/olympics/for-nbc-the-covid-olympics-will-be-a-feat-of-strange-movements-and-remote-mystery/ar-AAMtJwW</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storage spaces as broadcast booths, Orlando hotels as family-cheering sections and other oddities mark the broadcast of the 2021 improvisational Games, being called the 2020 Tokyo Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addict who spent $40,000 on tickets left on sidelines...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210723-olympics-addict-who-spent-40-000-on-tickets-left-on-the-sidelines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olympics addict who spent $40,000 on tickets left on the sidelines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archer faints in heat...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/russia/564505-russian-archer-faints-in-heat-at-olympics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian archer fainted at the Olympics due to the heat on Friday during a qualifying round.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country singer Morgan Wallen says issue of race stretches across industry...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/564509-country-singer-morgan-wallen-says-issue-of-race-stretches</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was caught on camera using racist language, but Morgan Wallen says a race issue extends beyond him, perhaps stretching across the country music industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti's murdered president laid to rest with tensions high...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723125416-qft87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAITI-PRESIDENT/FUNERAL (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Haiti's murdered president laid to rest with tensions high</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Like horror film': Revisiting disaster of Woodstock 99...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/tv-and-radio/2021/jul/22/woodstock-99-peace-love-and-rage-documentary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new documentary surveys the mess of Woodstock 1999 – a disaster of poor planning and a microcosm of toxic masculinity, raunch culture and entitlement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Too Much Coffee Shrinks Brain; Raises Dementia Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/coffee-can-shrink-brain-raise-dementia-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you find yourself repeatedly heading over to the coffee pot for refills, you may be actually putting your brain health at risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside The Don's intense search for Cheney challenger...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/07/23/trump-cheney-challenger-500599</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president's team has been interviewing Republicans running against Rep. Liz Cheney. Two of them have interviews with Trump up next.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amsterdam's oldest sex workers have 'serviced 335,000 men'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/meet-amsterdams-oldest-sex-workers-24601851</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twin sisters Louise and Martine Fokken are Amsterdam's oldest sex workers and have more than a century of experience in the sex industry between them - servicing more than 335,000 men over the years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: World's most dangerous roads...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/travel/travel_news/article-9809519/The-worlds-dangerous-roads-revealed-A1010-deemed-worst-UK.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers used information from government websites, news reports and transport associations to produce infographics showing the deadliest roads around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE co-founder Larry Page 'living off-grid in Fiji'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9816787/Google-founder-Larry-Page-grid-hiding-Fijian-islands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google co-founder Larry Page has reportedly been living off the grid for more than a year, and hiding out in Fiji on isolated islands away from tourists as the pandemic swept the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man nearly masturbates to death...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-9810615/Japanese-man-masturbates-death.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Doctors at Nagoya City University Hospital revealed the man suffered a life-threatening stroke caused by a blood vessel in his brain rupturing when masturbating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nightclubs new battleground -- but young yearn for freedom...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/23/nightclubs-are-the-new-covid-battleground.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The night time economy is re-opening just as coronavirus cases soar, particularly among the young.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials warn of 'superbug' outbreaks in Dallas, DC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/564489-health-officials-warn-of-fungus-superbug-outbreaks-in-dallas-dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health officials are warning of a fungus “superbug” outbreak in Dallas and Washington, D.C., that seem to be resistant to treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free money for all? Mayors hope local tests bring big change...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-9d956a91ae436e5fbbfd349673f7166a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By triggering $1,400 stimulus checks for millions of people and expanding the child tax credit for many families, the pandemic offered a clear takeaway for some officials: That putting tax dollars in people’s pockets is achievable and can be a lifeline to those struggling to get by.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANGER AT UNVAXXED...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/jul/23/ala-gov-kay-ivey-fumes-over-worst-vaccination-rate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alabama Gov. Kay Ivey said people are “supposed to have common sense” as she unloaded on unvaccinated people for driving coronavirus outbreaks and hospitalizations in her state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves in CA stealing scarce water amid extreme drought...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/07/22/us/california-water-thieves-drought/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As an extreme drought grips California, making water increasingly scarce, thieves are making off with billions of gallons of the precious resource, tapping into fire hydrants, rivers, and even small family homes and farms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unarmed 75-year-old Tasered without warning by Colorado officer: 'What did I do?'</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Unarmed-75-year-old-Tasered-without-warning-by-16334698.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When police knocked on Michael Clark's door in Idaho Springs, Colo., in May, he emerged...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>England quarantine rules relaxed to avoid shortages...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-0aa163de10d84559aebdcea83d8e8907</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The British government has sought to ease food supply pressures in England by exempting more than 10,000 workers from quarantine rules that led to staff shortages and empty shelves and fears of panic-buying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING 20S: Americans spending again and AMEX booming...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-879a94ac579792e7021d31dab9bee477</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Spending at restaurants, shops and entertainment venues has come back in force as vaccines become more common and it fueled a revenue surge at American Express during the second quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan 'rising sun' flag provokes ire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-japan-japan-olympic-team-south-korea-olympic-team-5a50f35230a3330226cdc92bf4abc66d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEOUL, South Korea (AP) — Japan considers the “rising sun” flag part of its history. But some in the Koreas, China and other Asian countries say the flag is a reminder of Japan’s wartime atrocities, and is comparable to the Nazi swastika.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel Nightmares May Scrub August Vacation Plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/travel-nightmares-may-scrub-your-august-vacation-plans/ar-AAMt8zK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans have waited more than a year to get away, but a host of pandemic-related factors are conspiring to make another staycation the smart move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak pops travel bubble between Australia, New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/delta-variant-outbreak-pops-travel-bubble-between-australia-and-new-zealand/ar-AAMsVck </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Explodes in Cancun and Los Cabos as Third Wave Hits Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/covid-explodes-in-cancun-and-los-cabos-as-third-wave-hits-mexico/ar-AAMtzWj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third coronavirus wave fueled by the highly contagious delta variant is battering two of Mexico’s most popular tourist destinations on opposite coasts, Los Cabos in the Pacific and Cancun on the Caribbean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ Rights Force Hungary Into Moment of Reckoning at Pride March...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/lgbtq-rights-force-hungary-into-moment-of-reckoning-at-pride-march</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How LGBTQ Rights Forced Hungary Into a Moment of Reckoning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 100 US athletes unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/564488-at-least-100-us-olympic-athletes-are-unvaccinated-as-2020-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 100 U.S. Olympic athletes that are set to compete in Japan remain unvaccinated as the Games begin on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrack Heads Back to Court to Learn If He Wins Bail... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/564486-ex-trump-adviser-barrack-set-for-bail-hearing-friday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former campaign adviser to former President Trump is set to go back to court on Friday for a bail hearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq war Marine walks U.S.-Mexico border to protest deportation of vets...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723104729-jwolx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IMMIGRATION/VETERAN (PIX, TV):Iraq war Marine walks U.S.-Mexico border to protest deportation of veterans</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From 'congratulations' to 'fully canceled': CA cafe owners hit roadblock...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723084719-snmck</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-CAFES (PIX):From 'congratulations' to 'fully canceled': California cafe owners hit roadblock</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Americans navigate conflicting mask advice, 'everyone confused'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210723084719-qjmjj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-MASKS (PIX, GRAPHICS):As Americans navigate conflicting COVID-19 mask advice, 'everyone is confused'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats rattle PA county targeted in election audit...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722222805-zzf1l</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/PENNSYLVANIA (PIX):Threats rattle Pennsylvania county targeted in election audit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QAnon Shaman' in plea negotiations after mental health diagnosis...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/exclusive-qanon-shaman-plea-negotiations-after-mental-health-diagnosis-lawyer-2021-07-23/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The participant in the Jan. 6 U.S. Capitol riots nicknamed the "QAnon Shaman" is negotiating a possible plea deal with prosecutors, after prison psychologists found he suffers from a variety of mental illnesses, his attorney said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro once said he'd stage military takeover. Now Brazilians fear laying ground for one...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/bolsonaro-once-said-he-e2-80-99d-stage-a-military-takeover-now-brazilians-fear-he-could-be-laying-the-ground-for-one/ar-AAMtihe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro's increasingly brazen comments have escalated a months-long campaign to erode faith in the electoral system of Latin America's largest democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two shot outside of popular restaurants in DC...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/564476-two-shot-outside-of-restaurants-in-dc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two men were shot outside restaurants on 14th street in Washington, D.C. Thursday evening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORIDA HOTSPOT...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/564470-florida-reports-highest-daily-covid-19-cases-since-january</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida on Wednesday reported 12,647 new cases of COVID-19, the highest daily number of cases since late January, according to data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Nomads: Surfing World for Risk and Profit...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/crypto-nomads-surfing-the-world-for-risk-and-profit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is just after midnight in Hong Kong, and Sam Bankman-Fried stares at the trading data on his six monitors,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burned by Hot Housing Market, Some Buyers Back Off...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/burned-by-hot-housing-market-some-buyers-back-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first house was in Midvale, Utah — a three-bedroom, just over 2,100 square feet, listed for $479,000. Rob Ettaro</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Haitian President's Funeral Nears, Anger Burns in Streets...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/23/as-haitian-presidents-funeral-nears-anger-burns-in-the-streets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CAP-HAÏTIEN, Haiti — Hours before mourners were due to pay tribute to the assassinated President Jovenel Moïse at a state</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire at mansion owned by Beyoncé, Jay-Z investigated as possible arson...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/fire-at-mansion-believed-to-be-owned-by-beyonc-c3-a9-and-jay-z-investigated-as-possible-arson/ar-AAMtprz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Orleans fire department said the property had been vacant for some time and that 22 responders attended the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL TESTS ORAL VAX...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/07/22/oral-covid-vaccine-set-to-begin-trials-in-israel/?sh=7254f9021ba5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avoiding needles, oral vaccines are much easier to store, transport and administer, possibly helping to ease disparities in vaccine access around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: LeBron first in NBA history to make $1 billion while playing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-becomes-first-player-in-nba-history-to-make-1-billion-in-earnings-while-still-playing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James' earnings on and off the court have made him a ridiculous amount of money</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAMES LIKE NO OTHER</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-swimming-soccer-sports-tokyo-8b75b92f36477af48612c70a2b7104e1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Disputed, locked down and running a year late, the Tokyo Games begin at last on Friday night, a multinational showcase of the finest athletes of a world fragmented by disease — and an event steeped in the political and medical baggage of a relentless pandemic whose presence haunts every Olympic corner.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>911 outages along East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3331697/fedex-ups-airbnb-delta-airlines-website-down-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MULTIPLE major US companies have been knocked offline today due to a nationwide outage, including Airbnb, FedEx, Delta Airlines, and HBO Max. Downdetector also flagged issues with Fidelity, USAA, U…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread Internet outage briefly disrupts retail, financial, travel sites worldwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/widespread-outage-disrupts-major-retail-financial-travel-websites-worldwide/3168859/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A widespread disruption caused severe outages for some of the world’s biggest websites on Thursday afternoon – and it was all caused by a software update gone horribly wrong. DownDetector.com showed a sharp and simultaneous spike in outage reports for prominent travel, retail, financial and gaming websites globally. In most cases, the spike in outage reports appeared to start around…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DNS failure'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/22/several-major-websites-go-down-in-widespread-internet-outage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several of the affected services blamed Akamai, a content delivery network.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia disconnected from global internet in tests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722094330-21wee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tests were carried out between June and July to test the ability of the 'Runet', as part of Russia's cybersecurity efforts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pingdemic' grips Britain as fears of food shortages grow...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210722050900-pa20w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record numbers of people were 'pinged' by the NHS COVID-19 contact tracing app asking them to isolate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware victim gets master key to unlock networks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-technology-joe-biden-europe-business-bb7298b31b7157640fbd5f90fc19c224</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON (AP) — The Florida company whose software was exploited in the devastating Fourth of July weekend ransomware attack, Kaseya, has received a universal key that will decrypt all of the more than 1,000 businesses and public organizations crippled in the global incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buses leaving Texas border town packed with illegals...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/07/22/buses-leaving-texas-border-town-packed-with-illegal-migrants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buses leaving the Texas city at the heart of the border crisis are struggling to keep up with business — because they’re full of illegal immigrants released into the US, The Post has le…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly It's Bare Season...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/22/suddenly-its-bare-season/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who hasn’t had the nightmare? It’s the one about being caught in public dressed in your undies. Therapists and dream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi Brief in Crucial Supreme Court Abortion Case: Overturn 'Roe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/mississippi-brief-in-crucial-supreme-court-abortion-case-overturn-roe-and-casey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi attorney general Lynn Fitch filed a brief in the most important Supreme Court abortion case in three decades.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC: 'ANOTHER PIVOTAL POINT'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-director-warns-us-at-another-pivotal-point-in-pandemic/ar-AAMrGDD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention struck a new tone of urgency on Thursday about the coronavirus pandemic, warning that the United States is “not out of the woods yet” and is once again at “another pivotal point in this pandemic” as the highly infectious Delta variant rips through communities with low rates of vaccination. The warning from the director, Dr. Rochelle Walensky, during a briefing by members of the White...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy to require 'pass' for many activities...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-government-and-politics-coronavirus-pandemic-6e5ba18d35f3ac40d4f34e6b3b22d58d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — With daily COVID-19 cases sharply rising again, Italy will soon require people to have passes reflecting their health status to access gyms, museums, movie theaters, the inside of restaurants and other venues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
