<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>MLB Network Cuts Top Reporter Over Criticism of Commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/mlb-network-cuts-ties-with-ken-rosenthal-over-criticism-of-commissioner-rob-manfred/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ken Rosenthal, one of baseball's most prominent reporters, is out at MLB Network, stemming from criticism of commissioner Rob Manfred. Rosenthal, 59, had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA to stop seeking prison for many...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/04/manhattan-da-alvin-bragg-to-stop-seeking-prison-in-some-cases/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In his first memo to staff on Monday, Alvin Bragg said his office “will not seek a carceral sentence” except for in homicide and a handful of other cases</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panel Quietly Ramps Up Inquiry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-the-capitol-s-shadow-the-jan-6-panel-quietly-ramps-up-its-inquiry/ar-AASpMyZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Behind closed doors inside a nondescript office building at the foot of Capitol Hill on a recent chilly morning, the House inquiry into the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol was in full swing. As congressional staff aides shuffled through the halls going about their normal business, investigators quietly pulled shades over the windows in conference rooms on several different floors and posted “Do Not Disturb” signs. In one such room sat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMTRAK passengers trapped 30-plus hours on train...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/neighborhoods/north-fulton/atlanta-amtrak-passengers-trapped-30-plus-hours-on-train/77QSQTWQDNEW5F7WEC6KCIDR6M/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A midnight train from Georgia has been trapped on the tracks in Virginia for more than 30 hours. They are not alone, the rail provider is reporting delays of several hours for trains across the East Coast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police called out to break up fights at testing centers...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/milwaukee-covid-testing-sites-security-increased-due-to-altercations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Milwaukee Police Department will be present at testing facilities to assist with the line and keep everyone safe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health experts criticize TSA security checks as virus spreads...</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/2022/01/04/ignoring-omicron-risk-tsa-still-requires-travelers-remove-masks-airport-checkpoints/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mask-wearing on planes reduces the risk of Covid infection, but in airports every traveler is still required to remove their mask during security screening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Defy God, Teach Goldfish to Drive on Land...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7v7g4/scientists-defy-god-teach-goldfish-to-drive-on-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goldfish were pretty good at piloting a Fish-Operated Vehicle, or FOV, the scientists report in a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Backdoored Phones Secretly Harvested GPS Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/93b3ay/fbi-backdoor-anom-phones-gps-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Documents reviewed by Motherboard, including thousands of pages of Anom messages, show that the FBI's backdoored Anom phones collected more data than the content of messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religous Sect, Burning Shed Focus of Deadly Colorado Fire Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/christian-sect-burning-shed-focus-of-deadly-colorado-fire-investigation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people are missing and presumed dead in a fire that sent 10,000 people from their homes and appears to have started on land owned by the Twelve Tribes group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida train kills 5th person in month...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-florida-fort-lauderdale-7dd0e7ec2435468d685918b92a0d2bf2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — A Brightline higher-speed train fatally struck a pedestrian who walked into its path Tuesday, the fifth death involving the railroad since it recently resumed operations after being shutdown because of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood trade wars heat up...</title>
      <link>https://www.lamag.com/culturefiles/hollywood-trade-wars-heat-up/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Noah's Ark' underground doomsday bunker on moon could save humanity in apocalypse...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/noahs-ark-underground-doomsday-bunker-25852569</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A storage unit on the moon could work as a 'global insurance policy' says Professor Jekan Thanga who believes 250 rocket launches are needed to complete the project</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan ER doc:  Omicron making people really sick in different way...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/coronavirus/omicron-variant-symptoms-latest-covid-making-people-really-sick-in-a-different-way/3477882/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As COVID-19 infections with the omicron variant of the virus surge out of control nationwide, emergency rooms are filling up again — and one well-known New York City doctor says what they’re seeing now is much different than the last two years of the pandemic. Manhattan emergency room physician Dr. Craig Spencer took to Twitter late Monday night to explain…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC cuts subway service...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/some-nyc-subway-service-suspended-due-to-crew-shortage</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The MTA has suspended multiple subway lines through Friday, Jan. 7, 2022, because COVID-19 is hitting the workforce hard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECORD 4.5 MILLION QUIT JOBS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/04/economy/us-job-openings-november/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A record 4.5 million Americans voluntarily left their jobs in November, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon declares enough room in space for billions of satellites!</title>
      <link>https://spacenews.com/op-ed-is-there-enough-room-in-space-for-tens-of-billions-of-satellites-as-elon-musk-suggests-we-dont-think-so/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spacenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's stance is overly optimistic. Space is big, but LEO is not big enough to safely accommodate tens of billions of satellites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence flares at protests in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-europe-pandemics-germany-ac28ee41bfe23856bd3f8df7f070fbca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Police in Germany have reported sporadic violence at demonstrations against the country’s pandemic restrictions, with one protester in the eastern town of Lichtenstein biting an officer and another attempting to steal a service weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Life-Changing Realizations People Have on Psychedelics...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/5dg9a5/the-life-changing-realisations-that-people-had-on-psychedelics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New year, new you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Damon Viral Crypto Ad Is Embarrassing Cash Grab...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/matt-damons-viral-crypto-ad-is-an-embarrassing-cash-grab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor’s commercial for Crypto.com (tagline: “fortune favors the brave”) compares investing in crypto to the bravery of space exploration or summiting Mount Everest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top suspect in Haiti assassination probe in custody in Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/haiti/article257029817.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A key suspect in the assassination of Haitian President Jovenel Moïse is in U.S. custody in Miami after being arrested Tuesday morning by Homeland Security agents upon arrival from Panama, multiple U.S. government sources familiar with the matter told McClatchy and the Miami Herald.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump 'needs to be in prison' for Jan. 6 riot, says partner of fallen Capitol Police officer Sicknick...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Trump-needs-to-be-in-prison-for-Jan-6-riot-16748063.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The partner of Capitol Police officer Brian Sicknick, who died after trying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN TO ADDRESS NATION</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/588146-biden-to-address-nation-on-omicron-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden will address the nation on Tuesday afternoon about the current wave of the omicron coronavirus variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARLINK Internet Dishes Attracting Cats...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/the-byte/starlink-dishes-cats</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk's Starlink internet dishes are attracting local cats on cold days, apparently to stay warm and take advantage of the heat it produces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leftists Ascendant in Latin America as Key Elections Loom...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/04/leftists-are-ascendant-in-latin-america-as-key-elections-loom/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO — In the final weeks of 2021, Chile and Honduras voted decisively for leftist presidents to replace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo artist anger over new EU rules goes beyond skin deep...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-lifestyle-amsterdam-european-union-tattoos-7cd5d66056cbd1d8405f41238a4946f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — Tattoo parlors say their art will lose a lot of its vibrancy after European Union rules banning thousands of chemicals in their coloring ink kick in on Wednesday. The 27-nation bloc answers back that public health will be much better served with tougher restrictions on elements in ink that may cause cancer or allergies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAN DIES AFTER FALLING INTO HAWAII VOLCANO...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4393808/hawaii-kilauea-volcano-man-dead/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 75-YEAR-old man has died after he plunged 100ft into Hawaii’s Kilauea volcano. The man, who has only been identified as a Hilo resident, disappeared at the Hawaii Volcanoes National Park la…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Cybermen: Nimble robot can open bottle, give injection, lift 65lbs...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10366023/his-hi-tech-invention-looks-just-like-Doctor-villain-dont-worry-help.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beomni 1.0, is set to be unveiled for the first time in public at the 2022 Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas this week. It is so nimble it can pick up a pinch of salt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS SET NEW RECORDS...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/03/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow Jones Industrial Average and S&amp;P 500 closed at records on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER DRONE ATTACK ON AMERICAN FORCES IN IRAQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4389676/us-stops-second-armed-drone-iran-revenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE US stopped a second armed drone attack on its forces in Iraq after Iran vowed revenge for the 2020 killing of Qasem Soleimani. A similar attack was attempted on Monday after two armed drones we…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZONGOOGLE deploy armies to thwart antitrust bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/04/amazon-google-thwart-antitrust-bills-526460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small businesses that rely on the tech giants are signing petitions and joining Zoom calls with lawmakers to warn against legislation aimed at promoting competition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Epstein settlement with accuser bail him out?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/investigations/article257015497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein paid Virginia Roberts Giuffre $500,000 in November 2009 to dismiss a lawsuit she had brought against him alleging that that he and Ghislaine Maxwell had sexually abused her and directed her to have sex with their powerful friends, according to a newly unsealed settlement document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New variant NOT 'worth worrying about; Fails to take off...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10367101/French-Covid-variant-NOT-worth-worrying-scientists-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Virologists say the strain predates Omicron but has yet to cause chaos, bolstering hopes that it may fade into the background.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden disapproval hits new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/biden-disapproval-rating-high-voters-blame-him-on-economy-cnbc-poll.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden's disapproval rating reached a new high in December as more voters signaled their unhappiness with his handling of the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan Raises Coup Clashes in Warning Rivals Against Protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-04/erdogan-raises-coup-clashes-in-warning-rivals-against-protests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of prayer site in doubt under Israel's fragile govt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-religion-jerusalem-israel-prayer-04a68f9f0baafa813fb0dfab3485e896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — When Israel's new government took office last June, it indicated it would press ahead on an egalitarian prayer site at Jerusalem's Western Wall — a sensitive holy site that has emerged as a point of friction between Jews over how prayer is conducted there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarkets Shelves Bare in Sydney as Virus Isolates Staff...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/supermarkets-shelves-bare-sydney-covid-053706230.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Sydneysiders are facing empty shelves at some supermarkets as exploding coronavirus cases force a range of staff from truck drivers to warehouse workers into isolation. Most Read from BloombergOmicron Cases Are Hitting Highs, But New Data Put End in SightU.S. Sets Global Daily Record of Over 1 Million Virus CasesPolice Pinpoint Starting Point of Historic Colorado WildfireIvanka Trump, Donald Trump Jr. Subpoenaed in Asset ProbeU.S. Catches Kremlin Insider Who May Have Secrets of 20</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBOTS FILL IN FOR STAFF</title>
      <link>https://abc7news.com/robots-robot-hotel-silico-valley/11421841/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7news.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, customers say they like it, especially now while COVID anxiety is high. It's one less person to make contact with as a robot brings room service orders to your door, instead of a person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Grapes Key To Healthy Heart? 'Cleans Up' Cholesterol...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/grapes-heart-attack-cholesterol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study found just four weeks of eating grapes led to significant health boosts among people who rarely eat fruit and vegetables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ:  Republicans Will Impeach Biden If Win House...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/podcasts/ted-cruz-says-republicans-will-likely-impeach-biden-over-border-policy-if-they-win-house-majority/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Weather it's justified or not, the democrats weaponized impeachment. They used it for partisan purposes to go after Trump because they disagreed with him."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Superyacht Dispute Pits CREDIT SUISSE Against Gulf Prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/saudi-superyacht-dispute-pits-credit-suisse-against-gulf-prince</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Superyacht Dispute Pits Credit Suisse Against Gulf Prince</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Meme Twin Brothers Die Days Apart From COVID...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/french-tv-star-igor-bodganoff-dies-from-covid-19-complications-days-after-twin-brother-grichkas-death</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grichka Bogdanoff reportedly succumbed to complications from COVID-19. Six days later, so did Igor Bogdanoff. Both had refused to get vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew set for court showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/prince-andrew-set-court-showdown-25845863</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawyers for the 61-year-old Duke of York will argue that the lawsuit should be dropped due to a secret deal Victoria Guiffre made with billionaire paedophile Jeffrey Epstein in 2009</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motorists trapped overnight on I-95 as winter storm causes icy, snowy havoc...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/04/weather/winter-weather-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drivers have been stranded for hours on a major interstate in eastern Virgina -- some stuck from Monday into Tuesday morning -- after a severe winter storm caused massive backups, sending authorities scrambling to clear a path.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News engagement fell off cliff in '21...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/media-ratings-traffic-2021-a6be4d72-ba5f-4f8a-ae3e-0872ecd87677.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It doesn't look like 2022 will be much better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In historic first, aircraft carrier Abraham Lincoln deploys under command of female captain...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/military/story/2022-01-03/abraham-lincoln-strike-group-deploys</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The strike group's deployment to the western Pacific comes amid hostile rhetoric between China and Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown remains on BUCS roster as Tampa Bay discusses next steps with NFL...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/antonio-brown-remains-on-buccaneers-e2-80-99-roster-as-tampa-bay-discusses-next-steps-with-nfl/ar-AASoLFg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech, finance firms buying up homes doesn't bode well for everyone else...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/opinions-tech-and-finance-firms-buying-up-homes-doesn-t-bode-well-for-everyone-else/ar-AASpXOc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew launches legal gambit to derail sex suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/prince-andrew-launches-legal-gambit-derail-virginia-giuffre-sex-abuse-rcna10751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew’s lawyers tried again Monday to block a lawsuit by Virginia Giuffre who says he sexually assaulted her when she was 17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Catches Kremlin Insider Who May Have Secrets of 2016 Hack...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2022/01/03/world/crime-legal-world/us-kremlin-insider-secrets-2016-hack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extradited from Switzerland in December, Vladislav Klyushin has been accused of illegally making millions of dollars trading on hacked corporate-earnings information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA MILLION CASES IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/04/us-counts-over-1-million-new-daily-covid-cases-in-global-record-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. also has the highest 7-day average of new cases in the world, according to Johns Hopkins University's rankings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betty White agent denies she died from booster...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2022/01/03/betty-whites-cause-of-death-revealed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The “Golden Girls” and “Mary Tyler Moore Show” star died at the age of 99 on Dec. 31 at her home in Brentwood, Calif.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE RELAXES</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/economy/france-relaxes-quarantine-rules-as-europe-adapts-to-omicron-s-spread-11641224120777.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European countries try to avert the threat of labor shortages resulting from mass self-isolation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1918 flu even more relevant in 2022 thanks to omicron?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/opinions-the-1918-flu-is-even-more-relevant-in-2022-thanks-to-omicron/ar-AASnEOY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How safe are indoor gyms?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/wellness/how-safe-are-indoor-gyms-during-omicron-surge-what-experts-say/ar-AASoa9k</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames feds for shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/desantis-blames-feds-for-covid-treatment-testing-shortages-as-omicron-spreads/ar-AASoigB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark Silicon Valley case...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/elizabeth-holmes-theranos-trial-verdict-guilty-fraud-001725594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elizabeth Homes, the former CEO and founder of Theranos, has been found guilty on charges of wire fraud and conspiracy to commit wire fraud..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell Attended 'VANITY FAIR' Party After Editor Graydon Carter Killed Damning Exposé...</title>
      <link>https://radaronline.com/p/ghislaine-maxwell-vanity-fair-party-photos-graydon-carter-killed-jeffey-epstein-farmer-sisters-expose/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The convicted sex trafficker enthusiastically attended the magazine's parties after getting her way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron upends return to schools and workplaces...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-new-york-education-milwaukee-dce5cae3226eb78ebf074383a2d8135b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some school systems around the U.S. extended their holiday break Monday or switched back to online instruction because of the explosion in COVID-19 cases, while others pressed ahead with in-person classes amid a seemingly growing sense that Americans will have to learn to co-exist with the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG:  Ivanka Trump, Don Jr. Subpoenaed in Asset Probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-new-york-donald-trump-subpoenas-ivanka-trump-072e02a5bf16faa89a7f496d16536893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The New York attorney general’s office confirmed Monday that it has subpoenaed former President Donald Trump and his two eldest children, Ivanka and Donald Trump Jr., demanding their testimony in an investigation into the family’s business practices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Slams 'Hysteria' as Florida Shatters Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/florida-governor-ron-desantis-blames-the-feds-slams-hysteria-as-florida-shatters-covid-records-with-omicron</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Florida governor gave his first press conference in weeks, railing against COVID mitigation measures like masking, which he erroneously claimed “hasn’t worked period.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the influencer scam crimewave flooding INSTAGRAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4386757/inside-influencer-scam-crimewave/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A SHOCKING crimewave is flooding social media – with celebs plugging scams where Brits are conned out of thousands of pounds of their hard-earned cash. Celebs including Joey Essex, Katie Pric…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine camps...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4386697/chinese-authorities-raid-homes-midnight-quarantine-camps-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINESE authorities reportedly raided dozens of homes in the middle of the night and forced people onto buses to quarantine camps under the world’s strictest lockdown. The country is racing t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Final' interview faked?</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/03/exclusive-people-magazines-betty-white-cover-story-final-interview-conducted-by-email-no-one-spoke-to-her</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLIGHTMARES CONTINUE... THOUSANDS STRANDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10363979/Flightmare-slows-2-680-flights-canceled-270-delayed-Monday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Southwest was the hardest hit of all US airlines on Monday with 481 cancellations. By late morning, 2,133 domestic flights or international ones starting or finishing in the US had been canceled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds THERANOS founder Elizabeth Holmes guilty on multiple charges in criminal fraud trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/03/jurors-in-holmes-trial-remain-deadlocked-on-three-of-11-fraud-counts.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jurors reached a verdict in the Elizabeth Holmes criminal trial after seven days of deliberations. They found the Theranos guilty on four counts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=81KiNoKJkCQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Credit: Two Oceans Digital via StoryfulTo download this video for news use you must go to: http://newswire.storyful.com To obtain a Storyful subscription, co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$29,000 for Average Used Car? Would-Be Buyers Aghast...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2022-01-03/29-000-for-an-average-used-car-would-be-buyers-are-aghast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prices for used cars are soaring so high, so fast, that buyers are being increasingly priced out of the market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro rushed to hospital with intestinal blockage...</title>
      <link>https://www.thejournal.ie/bolsonaro-rushed-to-hospital-5644847-Jan2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thejournal.ie&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctor Antonio Luiz Macedo told news site UOL that the president would undergo several tests to examine his abdomen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew accuse's legal deal with Epstein released...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/03/jeffrey-epstein-prince-andrew-virginia-giuffre</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unsealing stems from Giuffre’s sexual abuse lawsuit against duke, filed in Manhattan federal court in August</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archivist Says Donald Hiding Records to Avoid 'Prison Time'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/donald-trump-is-hiding-his-january-6-records-to-avoid-prison-time-says-former-national-archivist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There are things in those records that are going to make real trouble.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden stranded on AF1 at Andrews...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4387106/biden-whipped-snow-stuck-air-force-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOE Biden was whipped with snow and wild winds after getting stuck on Air Force One. The president was forced to stay on board the plane for around 30 minutes on Monday at Joint Base Andrews, Maryl…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Dying chimp says goodbye to human best friend for last time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4385451/dying-chimpanzee-meets-beloved-trainer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT the ripe old age of 59, Mama had defied the average life expectancy of a chimpanzee by all accounts. But as she was hit by a lengthy illness, the elderly chimp was refusing food and stayed curle…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artist claims tried to pimp her out at Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4384277/artist-jeffrey-epstein-ghislaine-maxwell-tried-to-pimp-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN artist claims Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell tried to pimp her out to older men at Donald Trump’s Mar-a-Lago members’ club. Rina Oh, 42, has been accused of recruiting girls for Epstein b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Maricoin' world's first LGBT...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/money/4370697/cryptocurrency-price-live-maricoin-launches-bitcoin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACTOR Matt Damon is being resoundingly mocked on Twitter for being featured in a Crypto.com commercial. In the ad, “Fortune Favors the Brave,” Damon talks about risk-takers “who embrace the m…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only 1 in 10 teens getting enough exercise...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/teens-exercise-during-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say that number has fallen significantly from the already paltry 16 percent getting enough exercise prior to COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Ketamine Reduces Depression, Suicidal Thoughts Within Hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/ketamine-reduces-depression-suicidal-thoughts-within-hours/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New research out of England shows the drug ketamine effectively reduces depression and suicidal thoughts shortly after being taken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems brace for post-Pelosi era...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/House-Democrats-brace-for-the-post-Pelosi-era-16743053.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - House Democrats are bracing for a turnover in leadership next year that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene chopped from TWITTER, suspended by FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/03/marjorie-taylor-greene-facebook-suspension-526398</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Facebook has joined Twitter in censoring me,” Greene (R-Ga.) wrote on Gettr, a social media platform favored by some right-wing conservatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could it happen again?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/03/could-january-6th-happen-again-526167</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Capitol Police has made progress under a new chief. But many on the Hill don't have an easy answer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hockey fan spotted staffer's suspicious mole from stands, saving his life...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/01/03/1069935191/canucks-manager-skin-cancer-fan-scholarship</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kraken fan and future medical student Nadia Popovici alerted Canucks staffer Brian Hamilton to a suspicious mole, which turned out to be cancerous. The teams surprised her with a $10,000 scholarship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  NFL PLAYER STRIPS, GETS TOSSED FROM TEAM...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/antonio-brown-buccaneers-wr-removes-uniform-exits-field-jets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Tampa Bay’s offense in the midst of a third-quarter drive, Antonio Brown pulled off his helmet, jersey and pads, waved to the fans at MetLife Stadium and ran into the tunnel. Following the game, head coach Bruce Arians said Brown is "no longer a Buc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab shuts testing due to overwhelming demand...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/nsw-act/news/major-pathology-lab-shuts-covid19-testing-clinics-due-to-overwhelming-demand/news-story/3a5181a2ee5e14277b843c808abf1e53</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A major pathology lab has temporarily shut 28 Covid-19 testing clinics across NSW as it struggles to keep up with demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sneak attack storm bringing heavy snow, severe weather to East...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/sneak-attack-storm-bringing-heavy-snow-severe-weather-to-eastern-u-s/ar-AASo3fK?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railing collapses at FEDEX Field, causing fans to fall and narrowly miss EAGLES QB...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/railing-collapses-at-fedex-field-causing-fans-to-fall-and-narrowly-miss-eagles-e2-80-99-jalen-hurts/ar-AASmKZd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even in tumultuous season, Rodgers and PACKERS are NFC No. 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/even-in-a-tumultuous-season-aaron-rodgers-and-the-packers-are-the-nfc-s-no-1-seed/ar-AASmRNN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coaches forced teen to eat pizza against his religion, he says. Now he's suing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/sports/nfl/coaches-forced-a-teen-to-eat-pizza-against-his-religion-he-says-now-he-s-suing/ar-AASn4OM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump offers unusual endorsement of Hungarian Prime Minister Viktor Orban ahead of vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/trump-offers-unusual-endorsement-of-hungarian-prime-minister-viktor-orban-ahead-of-parliamentary-elections/ar-AASo286?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing harvests masses of data on Western targets, documents show...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/china-harvests-masses-of-data-on-western-targets-documents-show/ar-AASk8e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrong People Hoarding Tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-wrong-people-are-hoarding-covid-tests/ar-AASooBl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DATA:  Southeast poised for big surge of covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/southeast-us-poised-for-a-firestorm-of-omicron-cases-with-few-safeguards-in-place/ar-AASmFKE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More People Getting Unapproved 4th Doses of Vaccine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/more-people-are-getting-unapproved-fourth-doses-of-the-covid-19-vaccine/ar-AASnzWw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depositions sought...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-york-attorney-general-seeks-depositions-from-ivanka-trump-donald-trump-jr/ar-AASocce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of flu dubbed 'Flurona'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/mixture-covid-flu-dubbed-flurona-25826601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The young woman, a patient in Beilinson Hospital in Petach Tikva., was unvaccinated and results from the hospital detected the co-presence of both the flu and the Covid 19 pathogens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Set for Record Start to New Year After Blowout Deliveries...</title>
      <link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/business/tesla-set-for-record-start-to-new-year-after-blowout-deliveries-101641214700648-amp.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hindustantimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Inc. is set to start the new year on the highest of high notes after the firm reported a historic quarter for deliveries that smashed its previous record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Since Jan. 6, MAGA internet has descended into infighting over money and followers...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Since-Jan-6-the-pro-Trump-internet-has-16745294.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The far-right firebrands and conspiracy theorists of the pro-Trump internet have a new...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French election year kicks off with EU flag fracas at Paris landmark...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/france/20220103-french-election-year-kicks-off-with-eu-flag-fracas-at-paris-landmark</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;France’s far right claimed a victory on Sunday after officials took down the EU flag from the Arc de Triomphe following outrage expressed by President Emmanuel Macron’s right-wing rivals for the Elys…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD having trouble covering shifts...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/highest-rate-of-sick-nypd-officers-hes-ever-seen-says-outgoing-commissioner-shea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surge in positive COVID cases across New York has caused major staffing shortages due to sick employees within the NYPD and FDNY.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twins born in different years!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/california-twins-born-15-minutes-apart-but-in-different-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twins Aylin and Alfredo Trujillo entered the world just 15 minutes apart in Salinas, California, but they were born on different days, months and years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Week That Could Destroy Him...</title>
      <link>https://www.firstpost.com/world/crucial-week-ahead-for-prince-andrew-as-new-york-judge-set-to-hear-virginia-giuffres-civil-lawsuit-against-him-tomorrow-10252951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.firstpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge will also make public today a confidential agreement between Jeffrey Epstein and Giuffre, who has claimed the former lent her out for sex with his associates, including Prince Andrew</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese 'starving to death' as millions forced into lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1544098/china-covid-news-lockdown-xian-starving-residents-zero-covid-policy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RESIDENTS in the locked down city of Xi'an have claimed they risk starvation as they contend with China's zero-Covid policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microchip developer says there's no stopping roll-out...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1542866/covid-microchip-developer-rollout-vaccine-passport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE DEVELOPER of a controversial new Covid microchip that is embedded in the skin has hit back at critics who slammed the project in an exclusive interview with Express.co.uk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 2021, Police Took Page Out of NSA Playbook...</title>
      <link>https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2021/12/2021-police-took-page-out-nsas-playbook</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eff.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While dragnet searches were once thought to be just the province of the NSA, they are now easier than ever for domestic law enforcement to conduct as well. This is because of the massive amounts of digital information we share—knowingly or not—with companies and third parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kimberly Guilfoyle Engaged...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10365275/Don-Jr-Kimberly-Guilfoyle-ENGAGED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DailyMail.com can reveal that Donald Trump Jr. and Kimberly Guilfoyle are engaged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW VARIANT SPARKS FEARS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10365005/Covid-tracking-scientists-France-spot-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some 12 infections have been spotted so far near Marseille, with the first linked to travel to the African country Cameroon. But there is little sign that it is outcompeting the Omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE becomes first $3 trillion company...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/03/apple-becomes-first-us-company-to-reach-3-trillion-market-cap.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple's cash flow also makes the stock a safe haven during times of market uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74.5 inches of snow? Multiple records smashed in Alaska...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article256992622.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Journal:  'End Of Pandemic Won't Be Televised'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bmj.com/content/375/bmj-2021-068094 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bmj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dashboards of pandemic statistics have dominated screens and helped to track covid-19, but David Robertson and Peter Doshi explain why they might not be enough to define its end  As the year 2021 started, the covid-19 pandemic seemed to be receding. Discussions and predictions about “opening up,” a return to “normal,” and achieving herd immunity were in the air.1234 But for many, optimism receded as cases and deaths surged in India, Brazil, and elsewhere. Attention turned to SARS-CoV-2 virus variants—most recently, the emergence of omicron. Just as the end seemed to be on the horizon, it was interrupted by a foreboding that the pandemic could be a long way from over.56 Unlike any previous pandemic, covid-19 has been closely tracked through dashboards that aim to show the real time movement and effect of coronavirus; they track laboratory testing metrics, hospital and intensive care admissions, transmission rates, and, most recently, vaccine doses delivered. These dashboards—with their panels of numbers, statistics, epidemic curves, and heat maps—have dominated our televisions, computers, and smartphones. At their core is the allure of objectivity and data to grasp onto in the midst of uncertainty and fear. They have helped populations conceptualise a need for rapid containment and control,7 directing public sentiment, fuelling pressure for countermeasures, and maintaining an aura of emergency.7 They offer a sense of control when cases are coming down following certain countermeasures but can also drive a sense of helplessness and impending catastrophe when cases rise. There is no universal definition of the epidemiological parameters of the end of a pandemic. By what metric, then, will we know that it is actually over? The World Health Organization declared the covid-19 pandemic, but who will tell us when it’s over? The ubiquity of dashboards has helped …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab-Grown Shrimp Price Tag Shows Long Way Ahead to Mass Market...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/lab-grown-shrimp-s-price-tag-shows-long-way-ahead-to-mass-market</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lab-Grown Shrimp’s Price Tag Shows Long Way Ahead to Mass Market</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Africa parliament fire flares up again; Suspected arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-africa-59861556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters are trying to douse the blaze which reignited hours after it was said to be under control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  All the Celebs Who Moved to Miami...</title>
      <link>https://www.architecturaldigest.com/story/celebrity-real-estate-hot-spot-2021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.architecturaldigest.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karlie Kloss, Serena Williams, Cindy Crawford, and more A-listers bought property here this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWER OUT...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/southeast-mid-atlantic-snowstorm-cuts-power/1119160</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A quick-hitting blast of winter weather left several inches of snow blanketing parts of the Southeast, before spreading into the mid-Atlantic, where it shut down much of the nation’s capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JANET JACKSON TO BREAK SILENCE WITH DOC...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/lifetimetv/status/1477372159655698432</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto Shuts Restaurants, Schools; Limits indoor gatherings to five people...</title>
      <link>https://torontosun.com/news/local-news/premier-ford-to-make-11-a-m-announcement</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;torontosun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUTUBE removes Rogan  with vax skeptic...</title>
      <link>https://thepostmillennial.com/youtube-removes-joe-rogan-interview-with-dr-robert-malone-from-youtube</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thepostmillennial.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big Tech site YouTube has removed podcaster Joe Rogan's interview with Dr. Robert Malone from its video-sharing platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nurse reportedly recovers from coma after receiving VIAGRA...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/03/uk-nurse-recovers-from-covid-19-after-being-given-viagra/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monica Almeida spent 28 days in a coma after contracting COVID-19 and was just 72 hours from her ventilator being turned off when she was saved by a “large dose of Viagra.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man self-immolates after ranting against jabs...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/02/australian-man-self-immolates-after-ranting-against-covid-vaccines/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Australian man was critically injured after he doused himself in gasoline and lit himself on fire in public on New Year’s Day after ranting against vaccines, according to local reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fatal shark attack alarms surfers...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/weve-lost-tom-fatal-shark-140023157.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A family grieves and a surfing community is wary after a great white shark kills a 42-year-old body boarder in Morro Bay on Christmas Eve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should police arrest sex workers for standing around? Thorny question lands on Newsom's desk...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-arrest-sex-workers-standing-130048877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sex workers say a loitering law that targets them for their hangouts and appearance is discriminatory, especially for transgender and Black people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid pandemic, a rise in gambling addiction emerges...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/invisible-addiction-amid-pandemic-rise-120021499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sports betting is on the rise in recent years. So are calls to gambling help hotlines. Then there's the pandemic: 'People are alone and struggling'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashli Babbitt: Rorschach test for attack on Capitol...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ashli-babbitt-rorschach-test-attack-023200543.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A conspiracy-spouting extremist or a patriotic martyr? Ashli Babbitt, who was shot dead a year ago during the invasion of the US Capitol, is a Rorschach test for the deep political fault line that runs through the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BANNON BENEFACTOR PRAISES COMMUNIST PARTY MEMBERS...</title>
      <link>https://mobile.twitter.com/JMichaelWaller/status/1411351785437007879</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;mobile.twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patton Oswalt apologizes for being friends with Dave Chappelle...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/john-s-2/2022/01/03/patton-oswalt-apologizes-for-being-friends-with-dave-chappelle-n439018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I’m sorry, truly sorry, that I didn’t consider the hurt this would cause."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Brown on Crime and Street Conditions in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/03/willie-brown-on-crime-and-street-conditions-in-san-francisco/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;San Francisco is starting the new year at a gloomy time: fearful of the latest wave of coronavirus infections, seemingly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress May Be Heart's Worst Enemy...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/03/stress-may-be-your-hearts-worst-enemy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re probably familiar with these major risk factors for heart disease: high blood pressure, high cholesterol, smoking, diabetes, obesity and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY AG:  Ivanka Trump, Don Jr. Subpoenaed in Asset Probe...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/03/new-york-a-g-seeks-to-question-trump-children-in-fraud-inquiry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New York State attorney general’s office, which last month subpoenaed Donald J. Trump as part of a civil investigation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA Top Scientist Says We Can Terraform Mars. Venus Too?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/02/nasas-retiring-top-scientist-says-we-can-terraform-mars-and-maybe-venus-too/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since joining NASA in 1980, Jim Green has seen it all. He has helped the space agency understand Earth’s magnetic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC shuts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/storms-weather-district-of-columbia-f43f3a379e6ed05e726348891c0b68e7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A winter storm packing heavy snow blew into the nation's capital Monday, closing government offices and schools and grounding the president's helicopter as 6 to 11 inches (15 to 28 centimeters) of snow ringed the area around Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Series of attacks highlights reach of Iran-allied militias...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-iran-jerusalem-israel-media-01bcc885cb5e064af64656e81c33ef89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Yemen’s Houthi rebels seized a ship in the Red Sea, armed drones targeted Baghdad's international airport, and hackers hit a major Israeli newspaper Monday — a string of assaults that showed the reach of Iran-allied militias on the second anniversary of America’s killing of a top Iranian general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hedge fund CEO resigns ahead of anticipated Senate run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-pittsburgh-pennsylvania-senate-elections-connecticut-093fa1305465242644127d7289fb2c74</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — David McCormick has resigned as CEO of one of the world’s largest hedge funds, Connecticut-based Bridgewater Associates said Monday, as McCormick moves closer to declaring his candidacy for U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thune mulls retirement...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/elections-campaigns-south-dakota-sioux-falls-john-thune-d77c0282509b0174786d58c0d0e5ccd9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIOUX FALLS, S.D. (AP) — South Dakota political candidates are revving into full campaign mode this week with one big exception: Republican Sen. John Thune, who has delayed a reelection announcement as he considers retirement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron clouds future forecasts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-health-pandemics-591db0701abcb31c2459b7a98a46e2b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pandemics do eventually end, even if omicron is complicating the question of when this one will.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK RESISTS MORE MEASURES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-london-europe-england-d0c46533c0f56fc58e709616d7716348</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British Prime Minister Boris Johnson warned on Monday that the country's health system will remain under strain for weeks amid the current surge in coronavirus infections, but suggested there would be no tightening of measures soon to slow the spread.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress' doctor urges 'maximal telework'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-seoul-europe-fcd5b5fe538e4d3da81bc0b903127820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW ORLEANS — Costumed revelers will mark the beginning of New Orleans’ annual Carnival season this week with a ride on a historic streetcar — carrying out a cherished tradition despite recent surges in COVID-19 infections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital workers sidelined as patient numbers rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-kansas-city-kansas-1afb326090f0d34f5cdd564d7730d138</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSION, Kan. (AP) — Kansas on Monday reported a record seven-day average for new confirmed and probable COVID-19 cases, as one of the state's largest hospitals struggled to treat an influx of patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death threats over vax pass...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220103145905-j7e8z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-"We will not yield," French lawmaker says after death threats over COVID vaccine pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRAEL REOPENS TO FOREIGNERS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220103134902-vz8vo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/ISRAEL-FOREIGNERS (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Israel to start reopening to foreigners, reviews quarantines and tests as Omicron surges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPOST hacked on Soleimani assassination anniversary...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220103014239-8ru91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-INTERNET/NEWSPAPER:Israel's Jerusalem Post website hacked on Soleimani assassination anniversary</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
