<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Half Dems don't think he'll serve all four years...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/short-timer-half-of-democrats-dont-think-biden-will-serve-all-four-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A majority of voters, including half of Democrats, do not think that 77-year-old Democrat Joe Biden will serve all four years as president, putting added pressure on who he plans to choose as vice president, and potential successor, according to a new survey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaramucci Swaps Insults With President: 'The Loser Is You'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/anthony-scaramucci-swaps-insults-with-donald-trump-over-his-presidency-the-loser-is-you/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POTUS said his former communications director "made a fool of himself" in Fox News appearance on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resignations as anger mounts...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-lebanon-security-blast-idUSKCN2560XY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebanon's cabinet faced rising pressure on Monday to step down after a devastating explosion that has stirred public outrage and prompted resignations of several ministers, with the justice minister the latest to go and the finance minister set to quit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/chicago-riots-woman-shouts-i-cant-breathe-as-she-loots-luxury-clothing-store/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looters hit high end luxury stores in response to armed criminal being shot by police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Le Mans to be raced behind closed doors...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200810-le-mans-to-be-raced-behind-closed-doors-due-to-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Le Mans to be raced behind closed doors due to virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff on Virus Relief Package Leaves Damage All Around...</title>
      <link>https://news.bloombergtax.com/daily-tax-report/standoff-on-virus-relief-package-leaves-damage-all-around</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.bloombergtax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were plenty of casualties left in the rubble of failed negotiations on another trillion-dollar-plus rescue package for a U.S. economy mired in a historic, pandemic-induced recession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHOTO: 75-Mile Long Shadow From Storm Blocks Sunrise In Kansas...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/08/09/sunrise-shadow-goodland-kansas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The isolated storm was about 35,000 feet tall and roughly 75 miles to the northeast of weather observers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100 arrests, 13 officers hurt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a105a525e52c3447d506216048aa3c40</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — More than 100 people were arrested Monday following a night of looting and unrest that left 13 officers injured and caused damage in the city's upscale Magnificent Mile shopping...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAGLES linebacker abruptly retires at 26...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2020/08/10/eagles-lb-jatavis-brown-retires-26-after-signing-free-agent/3333388001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eagles linebacker Jatavis Brown retired after four NFL seasons. He had just signed with the Eagles in March and was expected to be in mix to start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN RAISES MOST CASH FOR BIDEN AMONG HOPEFULS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/10/biden-vice-president-fundraising-392948</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden first and foremost wants a governing partner. But fundraising prowess is unquestionably a plus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost 100K kids infected in last two weeks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/10/almost-100k-us-kids-infected-with-covid-19-in-last-2-weeks-of-july/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Almost 100,000 American children tested positive for the coronavirus in the last two weeks of July — an alarming 40 percent rise, according to new data. As officials continue to wrestle over …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Raises Bridges After Unrest, Looting Batter Downtown...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/10/chicago-raises-bridges-after-unrest-and-looting-batters-downtown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago officials raised bridges and suspended some train and bus service Monday morning after unrest and looting caused widespread damage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's biggest pop star -- future president?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/aug/09/brazilian-pop-superstar-anitta-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Born in Rio’s favelas, Anitta became Brazil’s biggest pop star. Then a political awakening made her even more influential. She talks Bolsonaro, Black Lives Matter and bisexuality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance, sunset: Death of indie cinema imminent?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2020/aug/10/sundance-sunset-is-the-death-of-indie-cinema-imminent</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With blockbusters filling up the big screen and streaming giants dominating the small, independent film-makers are running out of options</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest Fires Setting Chernobyl Radiation Free...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/science/archive/2020/08/chernobyl-fires/615067/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trees now cover most of the exclusion zone, and climate change is making them more likely to burn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unusual Strikes Stump Experts...</title>
      <link>http://endoftheamericandream.com/archives/why-have-so-many-enormous-earthquakes-hit-the-united-states-in-recent-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;endoftheamericandream.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unusually large earthquakes have been striking diverse locations all over the United States in recent months, and experts are not exactly sure why this is happening.  On Sunday, a very strange magnitude 5.1 earthquake that hit North Carolina made headlines all over the nation.  In fact, when I check</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon government on brink over blast fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200810-lebanon-government-on-brink-over-blast-fallout</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lebanon government on brink over blast fallout</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots 'redefining human existence'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-redefining-human-existence-22494715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In her new book Sex Robots &amp; Vegan Meat, journalist Jenny Kleeman has explored the fast-growing world of sex dolls and has visited the elite Abyss factory in San Diego</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump paints Biden in picture many don't recognize...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Trump-paints-Biden-in-a-picture-many-don-t-15471574.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump is increasingly trying to run against a Joe Biden of his own making.  Rather than look for campaign ammunition in the former vice president's long track record of politically vulnerable votes and policy proposals, Trump has instead chosen to describe Biden as a godless Marxist bent on destroying the country with a radical agenda that would make Che Guevara blanch.  The caricature is one that neither Biden's critics nor supporters recognize - but it's one Trump continues to promote.  To hear Trump tell it, the former vice president and longtime U.S. senator is "the most extreme left-wing candidate in history." Biden is going to "abolish the police" and "abolish the suburbs." Biden is even "against God."  In lobbing such extravagant attacks on Biden, Trump has concocted a profile of the presumptive Democratic nominee at odds with much of Biden's personal and professional life - a cartoonish depiction so distant from the reality of Biden that the hits don't always resonate.  "Generically, can you successfully paint a caricature of your opponent and be rewarded at the polls? Yes," said Pia Carusone, a Democratic ad maker. "But you can't just do that without understanding the greater context that the attack is falling in, and we're in the middle of a heath and economic catastrophe and people are very pessimistic about what they're hearing from candidates and elected leaders."  The most effective political attacks, said Ken Goldstein, a professor of politics at the University of San Francisco, are often the ones that heighten an existing concern or voter perception about an opponent.  "There is certainly this notion that a bunch of wizards sit around and come up with this caricature and then spend hundreds of millions of dollars to drive the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looters, vandals sweep through Chicago after police shooting...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/10/looters-vandals-sweep-through-chicagos-magnificent-mile/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hours after Chicago police shot a young man who turned and fired at them, hundreds of people went on a looting and vandalism spree in various parts of the Windy City early Monday, according to repo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Flexes Military Muscle in Maritime Feud With Greece...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/turkey-flexes-military-muscle-in-mediterranean-feud-with-greece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updates...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/08/10/live-updates-looting-unrest-overnight-across-downtown-chicago-the-loop-shut-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of stores, banks and other businesses were broken into across downtown Chicago overnight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Satellites Add to Astronomers' Worries About Night Sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.rjrempires.com/amazon-satellites-add-to-astronomers-worries-about-the-night-sky/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rjrempires.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Welcome to the age of the satellite tv for pc megaconstellation. Inside the subsequent few years, huge networks, containing tons of and even 1000's of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold rally could forge ahead to $4,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/10/gold-prices-amid-coronavirus-pandemic-and-us-elections.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold prices could forge ahead to $4,000 per ounce in the next three years, but factors such as the development of a coronavirus vaccine and the November U.S. elections could change the fortunes of the precious metal, analysts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choice of running mate matters more than usual?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d53a5543177d6ab91d0a0fb517f834f8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — For all the secrecy and speculation that typically surrounds the search for a vice presidential candidate, the decision rarely sways an election. But ahead of Joe Biden's imminent...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme poverty rises; Generation sees future slip away...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/727c2dea29daed6e226b964f8caadfcf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ADDIS ABABA, Ethiopia (AP) — As a domestic worker, Amsale Hailemariam knew from the inside out the luxury villas that had grown up around her simple shelter of raw metal and plastic sheeting. And...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong media tycoon Jimmy Lai arrested, newsroom searched...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2ce4e0aac2bbb360f06e481dffaf5149</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — Hong Kong authorities broadened their enforcement of a new national security law on Monday, arresting media tycoon Jimmy Lai, searching the headquarters of his Next Digital group...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students suspended for posting pictures of packed halls --  now high school is closing after 9 people infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/students-get-suspended-for-posting-pictures-of-schools-crowded-halls-now-several-people-have-been-infected-2020-08-09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, pictures of maskless students crowding the hall of Georgia’s freshly reopened North Paulding High School went viral and raised questions all over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House reached out to South Dakota governor about adding Trump to Mount Rushmore... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8610013/White-House-reached-South-Dakota-governor-adding-Trump-Mount-Rushmore.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A White House aide contacted the office of Governor Kristi Noem of South Dakota (pictured) to ask about adding a president to Mount Rushmore, the New York Times reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STATE OF 2020 RACE...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/polls/president-general/national/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest political polls collected by FiveThirtyEight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly all major moves by Trump admin have been via executive orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Trump-s-legally-dubious-executive-actions-are-15470685.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEDMINSTER, N.J. - Already largely absent from intense negotiations for a coronavirus stimulus package, President Donald Trump fully distanced himself from the thorny legislative process by leaving Washington on Thursday for a weekend at his private golf resort in New Jersey.  After talks on Capitol Hill collapsed, Trump assembled some of his dues-paying club members to watch him complete the final step of what has become a familiar routine in his turbulent presidency: signing a legally dubious executive order after failing to reach a deal with Congress.  The president who pitched himself to voters as the consummate negotiator and ultimate dealmaker has repeatedly found his strategies flummoxed by the complexities and pressures of Washington lawmaking. In response, he has frequently relied on showmanship and pageantry to try to turn negotiating failures into victories.  "We're going to be signing some bills in a little while that are going to be very important, and will take care of, pretty much, this entire situation," Trump said Saturday from his club's grand ballroom, surrounded by presidential seals, American flags and news cameras.  He was greeted with raucous applause by dozens of supporters as he posed for pictures in a simulation of a White House signing ceremony after major legislation is passed.  But the four documents the president signed Saturday were neither "bills" nor "acts" despite his comments referring to them as such, and their effectiveness and legality are already being called into question by Democrats and some Republicans in the Congress he is attempting to bypass.  Trump said the executive actions he signed would provide economic relief to millions of Americans by deferring payroll taxes and provide temporary unemployment benefits by repurposing unspent dollars. But whether that relief will ever...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARGEST SINCE 1916</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article244835022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTTEST SUMMER:  Phoenix surpasses most days at or over 110&amp;deg;...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/a-record-nobody-really-wants-phoenix-surpasses-most-days-at-or-over-110-degrees/ar-BB17LlQm?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not everyone is thrilled about proposed rocket launch site in Michigan's Upper Peninsula...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2020/08/08/michigan-spaceport-marquette-aerospace-manufacturers-association-wurtsmith-oscoda-airport/3323976001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal for a Michigan spaceport in the Upper Peninsula that was greeted with enthusiasm weeks ago is seeing concerns raised about the impacts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School year like no other launches with chaos coast to coast... </title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/School-year-like-no-other-launches-with-chaos-15470902.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - It's going to be screen time all the time for kindergartners and graduate students alike. Teachers are threatening strikes. And students are already coming home infected with the coronavirus, which has upended American education.  The 2020-21 school year has dawned, and it's more chaotic than any before it.  Plans are changing so fast that students and parents can hardly keep up. Districts that spent all summer planning hybrid systems, in which children would be in school part of the week, ditched them as coronavirus cases surged. Universities changed their teaching models, their start dates and their rules for housing, all with scant notice.  And many districts and colleges have yet to make final decisions, even now, with the fall term already underway in some of the country.  "Plans are changing right up till the moment that schools open," said Michael Casserly, executive director of Great City Schools, a lobbying group for large districts.  Chicago Public Schools announced last week that, after planning a hybrid system, its classes would begin the year online. Districts across the country have pushed back their opening dates. Last week, the first week of school in Georgia's Cherokee County School District, administrators sent 14 letters to parents, each disclosing new cases of the novel coronavirus, which causes the disease covid-19. They included 13 students ranging from first to 12th grades, and a few teachers. More than 300 students who had been in contact with them were directed to quarantine for 14 days.  "Our parents wanted a choice for their children, and we delivered - it is not perfect, and we all know that, but perfection is not possible in a pandemic," Superintendent Brian Hightower said Friday in a message to the community.  Another Georgia high school, in Paulding County, drew national...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President vows permanent cut to payroll tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Democrats-assail-Trump-actions-on-payroll-tax-and-15470397.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - President Donald Trump's new executive actions to disburse coronavirus relief without Congress sparked confusion and frustration Sunday among businesses, Democrats and state officials, some of whom lamented the moves would not deliver the necessary relief to cash-strapped Americans.  Trump's directives were aimed at offering new unemployment benefits, protecting renters from eviction and postponing the payment of a federal tax. But an array of economists and lawmakers depicted these policies as incomplete, unworkable or legally questionable - raising the prospect that the president's attempt to boost the economy may have a muted impact.  One of the orders allows employees making less than $104,000 to delay until January payment of a payroll tax that funds Social Security and Medicare. Trump added that he would try to change federal rules next year to make the deferred payments into a permanent tax cut - but only if he is reelected.  The tax typically is taken out of paychecks by employers. And businesses, payment processors and economists signaled Sunday, in the absence of a guarantee, that the payroll taxes actually will be absolved, businesses would be unlikely to alter worker paychecks.  "It's a little bit of a leap of faith on an employer's part," said Pete Isberg, the vice president of government affairs for ADP, which processes payments for 40 million workers and 800,000 businesses.  Isberg said it may take months for some businesses to implement a system that can defer payroll taxes for a few months, delaying any potential boost to the economy. "It's not clear employers broadly will adopt this," he added. "It's not clear employees will want to take it even if they qualify."  Unable to swing a deal with Democrats, Trump resorted to executive actions as concerns in Washington intensified about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Leads in Battlegrounds Wisconsin, Pennsylvania...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/biden-leads-wisconsin-pennsylvania-opinion-poll-covid-countrys-direction-09-08-2020/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vast majority of voters in these two states say things in the U.S. are going badly. They think Joe Biden would do a better job of handling coronavirus by significant margins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven dead as floods hit Greek island...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/five-dead-one-missing-floods-165104894.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A baby was among seven people who died as torrential rains and floods swept the Greek island of Evia, damaging dozens of houses and blocking roads, authorities said Sunday. The eight-month-old baby was found dead in a house in the village of Politika on Sunday, said a spokesman for firefighters involved</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of motorcyclists flood into small town... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/defying-virus-thousands-motorcyclists-flood-194101612.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shrugging off the five million coronavirus cases now tallied on US soil, thousands of motorcyclists are converging this weekend on a small South Dakota town for what is billed as the biggest cycle gathering in the world. In past years, the 10-day rally in the town of Sturgis has drawn hundreds of thousands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro assails Brazil network blaming him for deaths... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/bolsonaro-assails-brazil-network-blaming-202900816.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Jair Bolsonaro lashed out Sunday at the &amp;quot;cowardice&amp;quot; of Brazil&amp;#39;s most widely viewed TV network for suggesting he bore heavy blame for the nation&amp;#39;s more than 100,000 coronavirus deaths. The far-right president accused TV Globo of treating the death milestone as if it were &amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boycotted. Criticized. But FOXNEWS Leads Pack in Prime Time...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/09/boycotted-criticized-but-fox-news-leads-the-pack-in-prime-time/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one sense, this has been a difficult period for Fox News: a star anchor fired after being accused of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator: 'Unconstitutional Slop'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/96a1c20494cc9ebb547a44aa60406168</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRIDGEWATER, N.J. (AP) — President Donald Trump’s end run around Congress on coronavirus relief is raising questions about whether it would give Americans the economic lifeline he claims and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starvation Looms for Morocco's Horses as Tourism Collapses...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/moroccos-carriage-horses-suffer-covid-101509593.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abdenabi Nouidi sold his favorite horse for $150 to help feed the others on the team that pulls tourists in carriages through the buzzing streets of Marrakech. The prospect of starvation looms for carriage horses and other animals normally used in Morocco’s tourist mecca. The Society for the Protection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand reaches 100-day milestone without a single transmission!</title>
      <link>https://www.tvnz.co.nz/one-news/new-zealand/significant-milestone-new-zealand-hits-100-days-without-community-transmission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tvnz.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There were no new cases confirmed today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class in session -- at YMCA, roller rink...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/california/story/2020/08/07/shadow-schools-class-is-in-session-at-the-ymca-and-roller-rink-1304829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For working parents, it brings much-needed relief to the exhausting months since coronavirus began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortages threaten plan for rapid tests...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/09/coronavirus-test-shortages-trump-plan-rapid-392520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manufacturers of antigen tests say they are nowhere near able to meet demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Worry Attorney General Has 'October Surprise'...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/08/07/900279687/barr-promises-doj-wont-try-to-influence-2020-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General William Barr says he won't take any action to influence the presidential election, but looming in the background is a probe apparently focused on the Obama administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Iowa is the most important state...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationaljournal.com/s/709019?unlock=4CXARIFP2VST86TK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationaljournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The predominantly white working-class state voted for Trump by 9 points and elected a Republican governor in 2018. If Republicans can’t win here, it’s going to be a long Election Night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia Reports Deadliest Day...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/australia-reports-17-coronavirus-fatalities-in-its-deadliest-day/ar-BB17JVPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump promises permanent cut to payroll tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-promises-permanent-cut-to-payroll-tax-funding-social-security-and-medicare-if-he-s-reelected/ar-BB17JIZa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia Turns Off America's Oil Taps Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/saudi-arabia-turns-off-america-s-oil-taps-again/ar-BB17KnvY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No keg parties, no road trips: Colleges set rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/no-keg-parties-no-road-trips-colleges-set-coronavirus-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As they struggle to salvage some semblance of a campus experience this fall, U.S. colleges are requiring promises from students to help contain the coronavirus — no keg parties, no long road trips and no outside guests on campus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago uses social media to track quarantine violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/chicago-to-use-social-media-to-track-tourists-violating-quarantine-city-dismisses-comparison-to-big-brother</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago is doubling down on efforts to enforce its emergency coronavirus travel order, as officials will now be reviewing the social media posts of possible violators as the pandemic continues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outrage as Manhattan DA drops charge against BLM leader accused of assaulting officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8608583/Manhattan-district-attorney-DROPS-felony-charge-against-BLM-leader-accused-assaulting-NYPD-cop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DA Cyrus Vance personally ordered the charges against Derrick Ingram, 28, from felony assault in the second degree to misdemeanor assault, a law enforcement source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Italy turned disaster around...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/09/europe/italy-coronavirus-return-normal-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A horrifying moment in the Covid-19 pandemic hit Italy on March 27, 2020, when the civil protection authorities announced that 969 people had died in just 24 hours. In the weeks before that, images of coffins stacked up in church parlors and being driven down the streets of the northern Italian town of Bergamo in a caravan of military trucks poured into the homes of Italians, by then locked down for nearly three weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronic fatigue syndrome long-term effect...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/07/health/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-covid-19-survivors-wellness/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The long-term effects of Covid-19 aren't completely known, but experts say many who survive the disease could develop chronic fatigue syndrome, also known as myalgic encephalomyelitis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKES HIT NORTH CAROLINA</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/article244834402.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus outbreak at crowded Georgia high school...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/education/9-cases-of-covid-19-reported-at-north-paulding-high-school/OWH6MN7DZ5A2XDQMXX337AQEWI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Georgia school that became infamous for hallways crowded with unmasked students reported a half-dozen students and three staffers with coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator: 'Unconstitutional Slop'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/511202-some-gop-lawmakers-express-discomfort-with-trump-executive-orders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several GOP senators voiced discomfort regarding President Trump's decision Saturday to sign four executive orders meant to address the economic fallout of the coronavirus pandemic and bypass Congress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden says 'reckless war on Social Security'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/511197-biden-says-trump-executive-orders-are-a-reckless-war-on-social-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden on Saturday called President Trump’s executive order to cut payroll taxes “a reckless war on Social Security.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeschooling Hits Mainstream...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/08/07/once-marginalized-homeschooling-hits-the-mainstream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DIY approaches to education—including homeschooling, learning pods, and microschools—are gaining popularity as public schools fold under pressure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMON COWELL BREAKS BACK...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/08/09/simon-cowell-recovering-from-near-six-hour-surgery-after-scary-bike-crash/?_ga=2.66987110.930761471.1596989387-660223987.1594701572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was a long surgery, they had to fuse his bones and implant a rod,” a source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They tweeted, retweeted photo of cop. Then came felonies...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tweeted-retweeted-photo-cop-black-100037519.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legal experts say charging Twitter users with felonies over posts of a New Jersey cop during a Black Lives Matter protest is &amp;quot;a bit of a stretch.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanese call for an uprising after protests rock Beirut...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200809112016-w3cmu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEBANON-SECURITY/BLAST (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Lebanese call for an uprising after protests rock Beirut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How COVID-19 brought 'largest criminology experiment in history'...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/paranoid-about-the-pandemic-how-covid-19-brought-the-largest-criminology-experiment-in-history/wcm/964870a2-86c8-4814-a34f-edf1bc76417e/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE MAP</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/map/?extent=20.67391,-471.70898&amp;extent=52.45601,-401.39648&amp;listOnlyShown=true&amp;timeZone=utc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service emerges as flash point heading into election...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fadfb69ba83bf83875fee42ce323a27c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Mail piling up. Constant attacks from the president. Cuts to overtime as record numbers of ballots are expected to pass through post offices this fall. The success of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARGEST SINCE 1916</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e9c431febbeb3e4fb4f7685abc315f51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPARTA, N.C. (AP) — The most powerful earthquake to hit North Carolina in more than 100 years shook much of the state early Sunday, rattling homes, businesses and residents. The National...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA tops 5 million confirmed virus cases, to Europe's alarm...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2a03a4e685316eb7d5a6e7181000fbfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — With confirmed coronavirus cases in the U.S. hitting 5 million Sunday, by far the highest of any country, the failure of the most powerful nation in the world to contain the scourge...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
