<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>1,000 people aim to smash record for world's largest ORGY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7773652/world-largest-orgy-sex-party-colorado-polyamorous-derrier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A POLYAMOROUS events planner has revealed her quest to organise the world’s largest orgy – inviting 1,000 to the marathon sex party. Pearl Derrier, 29, from Denver, Colorado, goes to or…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homebuilder confidence plummets...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/homebuilder-confidence-plummets-to-the-lowest-level-in-more-than-two-years-as-demand-stalls.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising mortgage rates and continued home price growth are hurting affordability and fast becoming a toxic cocktail for the nation's homebuilders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air pollution shaving years from lives. Where is it claiming most?</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/policy/environment/article221668390.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study examines how much longer people could live if particulate pollution — such as soot from cars and trucks — was reduced to levels recommended by the World Health Organization. In Fresno, people could live a year longer, on average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars: Christian Bale Leaps Into Lead Actor Race With 'VICE'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/in-contention/oscars-christian-bale-leaps-into-the-lead-actor-race-with-adam-mckays-sobering-vice-1203031566/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;’Tis the season for latter-year revelations. With Adam McKay’s new film “Vice,” a follow-up to his 2015 Oscar winner “The Big Short,” a major one has landed, though it’s hardly a surprise: Christia…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensual goddess fresco discovered in ancient Pompeii bedroom...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/2566d74abc7d4995bbc1dc9c0f5a0b62</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Archaeologists have found in an ancient Pompeii bedroom a fresco depicting a sensual scene of a goddess and swan. Pompeii archaeological park director Massimo Osanna told Italian news agency ANSA on Monday that the figure of goddess Leda being impregnated by a swan representing Roman god Jupiter is a fairly common theme in Pompeii home decoration. But he praised this fresco as exceptional since the goddess appears to look at whoever's looking at the fresco. Osanna said "Leda watches the spectator with a sensuality that's absolutely pronounced."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi king urges action against Iran...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181119123649-vxsmr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-KING/ (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-Saudi king urges action against Iran, backs Yemen peace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threaten To Devastate Black Friday Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-11-18/brutally-cold-temperatures-could-stifle-black-friday-sales</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN Warning: Economy will slow to crawl next year...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/19/goldman-sachs-believes-the-us-economy-will-slow-to-a-crawl-next-year.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman sees economic growth slowing to below 2 percent in the second half of 2019 as the Fed continues to raise rates and the effects of the tax cut wear off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlook for Traditional TV Goes From Bad to Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/outlook-for-traditional-tv-goes-from-bad-to-worse-1542632401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cord-cutters continue to chip away at cable and satellite providers’ dominance of the living room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Ousted Trump Aide Nabs Seven-Figure Advance For Tell-All...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/print/team-of-vipers-ousted-trump-aide-reportedly-nabs-seven-figure-advance-for-tell-all-about-white-house/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil price now controlled by just three men...</title>
      <link>https://www.worldoil.com/news/2018/11/18/bloomberg-opinion-the-oil-price-is-now-controlled-by-just-three-men</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.worldoil.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beto blows up 2020 Dem primary...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/19/beto-orourke-2020-democratic-primary-995353</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top party donors and operatives are eager to see the Texas congressman jump into the presidential race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 5 generals can't deploy for medical reasons...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/11/19/one-five-army-generals-were-not-cleared-combat-2016/2029702002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One in five Army generals could not deploy in 2016 for medical reasons. Overdue medical and dental exams were the main culprits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth Eating Its Oceans...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/42470-earth-is-eating-its-oceans.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three times more water than previously estimated gets dragged into subduction zones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 people aim to smash record for world's largest ORGY...</title>
      <link>/https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7773652/world-largest-orgy-sex-party-colorado-polyamorous-derrier/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University lecturers told DON'T USE CAPS as it frightens students...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/1046977/university-lecturers-not-to-use-cap-letters-student-failure</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(It might upset the snowflake students)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbulent stock market spooks older workers, retirees...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c96eb2f4b5c54449b13c95e841f89dab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — The recent turbulence in the U.S. stock markets is spooking some older workers and retirees, a group that was hit particularly hard during the most recent financial crisis. There's no indication, though, that the recent volatility has brought about large-scale overhauls in retirement planning. "There's a lot of fear that if you have another event like 2008 and you retire the year before or the year after, you're screwed. I'm not taking that risk," says Mark Patterson, a recently retired patent attorney from Nashville, Tennessee. "There's a huge fear of folks my age that they're going to run out of money and they're going to need to rely on the government for help."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red alert after Guatemala volcano erupts again; 3,000 flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-red-alert-after-guatemala-volcano-erupts-again-200-flee</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French fuel depots targeted as 'yellow vest' protesters persist...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-french-fuel-depots-targeted-yellow-vest-protesters-persist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese homoerotic writer gets 10 year jail term...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181119-chinese-homoerotic-writer-gets-10-year-jail-term</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biting winds to grip Macy's Parade in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-news/bundle-up-biting-winds-to-grip-macys-thanksgiving-day-parade-in-nyc/70006658</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gruesome discovery of tiger farm exposes illegal trade in heart of Europe...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/nov/19/gruesome-discovery-of-czech-tiger-farm-exposes-illegal-trade-in-heart-of-europe </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gruesome haul of fresh pelts and rotting remains marks the end of a five-year probe into an international crime ring, that authorities fear points to a wider problem in Europe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Victims may never be found...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-casualties/some-california-wildfire-victims-may-never-be-found-searcher-idUSKCN1NO16X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Searchers looking for the remains of victims of the wildfire that destroyed the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK CHAOS CONTINUES...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-britain-eu-may-lawmaker-challenge/uk-conservative-lawmaker-says-pm-may-faces-day-of-reckoning-on-monday-idUSKCN1NO0LX?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Theresa May faces a day of reckoning on Monday as mutinou...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder rate soars in Venezuela...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6405051/Murder-rate-soars-Venezuela-forcing-population-extreme-precautions-amid-shortages.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South American nation registered 26,000 homicides last year, 89 per 100,000 inhabitants and a figure 15 times the global average, according to the Venezuelan Observatory of Violence, an NGO.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temps 25 degrees below average...</title>
      <link>https://www.wusa9.com/article/weather/weather-blog/coldest-thanksgiving-in-years-when-it-will-feel-like-the-10s-20s/65-615665921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wusa9.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanksgiving Day will be unseasonably cold across the Northeast and Mid-Atlantic -- temperatures in some areas will drop 15° - 25° below average. This is what it means for DC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial Recognition Goes Mainstream, Drawing Concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/facial-recognition-goes-mainstream-drawing-concerns-1542623401 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facial recognition is increasingly used by law-enforcement agencies and in schools, retail stores and other venues, spurring privacy concerns. In this episode of Moving Upstream, we test out the technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northeast Coldest Thanksgiving on Record?</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/forecast/regional/news/2018-11-18-thanksgiving-day-record-cold-northeast/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'll need to bundle up on Turkey Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE CUTS PRODUCTION ORDERS FOR 3 NEW IPHONE MODELS...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-suppliers-suffer-as-it-struggles-to-forecast-iphone-demand-1542618587 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lower-than-expected demand for Apple’s new iPhones and the company’s decision to offer more models have created turmoil along its supply chain and made it harder to predict the number of components and handsets it needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak 11: Empty Seats Abound As Season Enters Final Stretch...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2018/11/18/weal-11-empty-seats-abound-nfl-season-enters-final-stretch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL season is nearly coming to its end, with only six more weeks of regular season play left. Which has caused many fans on social media</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As tech booms, Bay Area worker wages drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/11/18/silicon-valley-wages-have-dropped-for-all-except-highest-paying-jobs-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nine out of every 10 Silicon Valley jobs pays less now than when Netflix first launched in 1997, despite one of the nation’s strongest economic booms and a historically low unemployment rate …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Berkeley Cancels Classes Over Poor Air...</title>
      <link>https://news.berkeley.edu/2018/11/18/classes-canceled-monday-tuesday/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.berkeley.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selfie evidence saves man facing 99 years in prison...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox32chicago.com/news/national/selfie-saves-texas-man-from-serving-up-to-99-years-in-prison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox32chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They say a picture is worth a thousand words, but a selfie turned out to be priceless for one Texas man.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-injured Canadian diplomats say silent govt afraid to upset Havana...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/world/article-canadas-brain-injured-cuba-diplomats-speak-out-about-ottawas-silence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The diplomats say duty of care for their concussion-like injuries has been trumped by the federal government’s political interests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Navy ship gives Venezuelan refugees free medical care, stokes tensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2018/nov/18/usns-comfort-us-navy-hospital-ship-venezuelan-refugees-tension</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USNS Comfort, moored off Colombia, will help patients as pressure builds on relationship between Washington and Caracas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE News may shut over EU 'link tax' plans...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2018/nov/18/google-news-may-shut-over-eu-plans-to-charge-tax-for-links</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Search engine is lobbying hard to stop proposed tax, aimed at compensating news publishers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: A lot of horrible decisions led to 'kidnapped' man running naked around neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://kfor.com/2018/11/16/allegedly-kidnapped-man-found-naked-in-norman-neighborhood-police-call-the-result-of-bad-decisions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOORE, Okla. - A man found running through the street naked in Norman claims he was one of two people kidnapped in Moore and dropped off there. Now police are looking for the two men responsible. But police say a lot of bad decisions on both sides led up to the bizarre scene. William Trites and Phillip Tullis are both charged with two counts of kidnapping, and one count of robbery. A warrant has been issued for their arrest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bernstein suggests media edit WH pressers before airing...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/carl-bernstein-suggests-media-should-edit-white-house-pressers-before-airing-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Veteran journalist Carl Bernstein said cable news networks should stop broadcasting White House press conferences and briefings in their entirety because they have become "propagandist exercises."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg gives Johns Hopkins record $1.8 billion for student financial aid... </title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/michael-bloomberg-to-give-johns-hopkins-record-1-8-billion-1542575094</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York City Mayor and possible 2020 Democratic presidential candidate Michael Bloomberg is giving $1.8 billion to Johns Hopkins University. The gift is believed to be the largest ever to an academic institution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR:  Redskins QB Alex Smith breaks two bones in leg...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/25312926/redskins-qb-alex-smith-breaks-two-bones-leg-texans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington Redskins quarterback Alex Smith suffered a right leg injury and was carted off the field in the third quarter of Sunday's game vs. the Houston Texans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEARCH BEFORE RAIN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/74cf4da585f6459c82474439ca7a4fe3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICO, Calif. (AP) — Volunteers in white coveralls, hard hats and masks poked through ash-covered debris Sunday, searching for the remains of victims of the devastating Northern California wildfire before rains that are forecast for this week complicate their efforts. While the rain could help tamp down the blazes that have killed 76 people so far, it also could wash away telltale fragments of bone, or turn loose, dry ash into a thick paste that would frustrate the search. A team of 10 volunteers went from burned house to burned house Sunday in the devastated town of Paradise, accompanied by a cadaver dog with a bell on its collar that jingled in the grim landscape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers say FACEBOOK can cause depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/new-study-claims-facebook-instagram-and-snapchat-are-linked-to-depression-2018-11-09</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The findings are published in the December Journal of Social and Clinical Psychology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French fuel tax revolt simmers...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/macrons-popularity-dips-french-fuel-tax-revolt-simmers-112456225.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emmanuel Macron's popularity took a further hit in recent weeks, according to a poll on Sunday, as fuel tax protests rumbled on across France in the latest sign of discontent with the president's economic reforms. Only 25 percent of those questioned in an Ifop poll between Nov. 9 and 17 said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coalition in Turmoil...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/netanyahus-coalition-in-turmoil-as-he-rejects-partners-demand-1542569719</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Sunday appointed himself defense minister, rejecting a coalition partner’s key demand in a move that could collapse the government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters Battle Exhaustion From Perpetual Blazes...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/california-firefighters-battle-exhaustion-from-perpetual-blazes-1542556801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Many firefighters battling California’s deadliest wildfire in Paradise have spent the past year hopping from one major blaze to another—each worse than the last.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico considers legalizing marijuana during its war on drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.pressdemocrat.com/business/8972460-181/mexico-considers-legalizing-marijuana-during</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pressdemocrat.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legislation submitted to Congress this month would regulate cannabis, allowing it to be grown, sold and consumed for recreational use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikely to Sit for Mueller Interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-says-whitaker-right-about-russia-probe-won-t-sit-n937671</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"There is no collusion," Trump said. "He happened to be right. I mean, he said it."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What started as tiny brush fire became California's deadliest...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/what-started-as-a-tiny-brush-fire-became-california-s/article_9b32290d-1cb4-554b-a984-ef7ae358b189.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PULGA, Calif. — Before there was a spark, there was the wind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FIRE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/often-divisive-trump-switches-consoler-chief-role-095635338.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even the bright lights on Donald Trump's motorcade grew dim as "the Beast" limousine and the rest of the presidential procession slid into the haze covering the fiery inferno of northern California. All along the route to the town of Paradise stretched blackened fields. California is</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINALLY:  Senator Scott!</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/scott-wins-florida-u-senate-seat-manual-recount-184729779.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the recount of the Nov. 6 election, Scott won by 10,033 votes out of 8.19 million cast statewide, Florida elections officials said on Sunday. Scott took 50.05 percent, compared with 49.93 percent for Nelson, the officials added. Nelson, first elected to the Senate in 2000, became the latest incumbent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIM SEARCH FOR 1000 MISSING</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181118161838-scn0u</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Besides the toll on human life, property losses from the blaze make it the most destructive in California history</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protest greets Champs Elysees Store...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/protest-greets-apples-champs-elysees-launch-170010411.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The launch of an Apple store on the Champs Elysees in Paris was greeted Sunday by a protest against the US multinational's controversial fiscal practices. The group had staged a sit-in at Apple's flagship Paris store in December 2017, and in February a French court declined to approve a ban</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says calling Israeli election now would be 'irresponsible'...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/netanyahu-says-calling-israeli-snap-polls-now-irresponsible-185850422.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said Sunday calling snap elections now would be "irresponsible" as he vowed to push on despite a coalition crisis. Speaking in an impassioned televised address to the nation, Netanyahu also said he would retain the defence ministry portfolio at least</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Moral panic' targets Indonesia's LGBT community...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/moral-panic-targets-indonesias-lgbt-community-024855676.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indonesian Budi Ahmad used to live openly as a gay man without fear of becoming a target for violence in the world's biggest Muslim-majority nation. The country of 260 million is in the grip of a moral panic, with critics saying the vulnerable LGBT minority is being used as a political punching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron's popularity falls to 25%...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/macrons-popularity-falls-25-percent-poll-231241851.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The popularity of French President Emmanuel Macron has dropped to just 25 percent, according to a major tracker poll published on Sunday. The poll by research group Ifop was published in the Journal du Dimanche a day after a nationwide "yellow vest" protest against high fuel prices that analysts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading Australia wedding magazine shuts over gay snub...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/leading-australia-wedding-magazine-shuts-over-gay-snub-083643654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A leading Australian bridal magazine has shut after being ditched by advertisers for refusing to feature same-sex couples, one year after the country changed its marriage laws. The Christian founders of "White", Luke and Carla Burrell, said they did not feature gay weddings in their magazine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS FLIP ANOTHER SEAT!</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/democrat-cisneros-nabs-gop-house-seat-southern-california-021426659--election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrat Gil Cisneros captured a Republican-held U.S. House seat in Southern California on Saturday, capping a Democratic rout in which the party picked up six congressional seats in the state. In what had been the last undecided House contest in California, Cisneros beat Republican Young Kim for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEGGY NOONAN</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/news/types/declarations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID IGNATIUS</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/people/david-ignatius/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ignatius writes a twice-a-week foreign affairs column.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nothing on this page is real': How lies become truth in online America ...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/nothing-on-this-page-is-real-how-lies-become-truth-in-online-america/2018/11/17/edd44cc8-e85a-11e8-bbdb-72fdbf9d4fed_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Facebook, he writes America’s Last Line of Defense. She likes and shares.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Works to Avoid His Govt Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.voanews.com/a/netanyahu-works-to-avoid-his-government-collapse/4663454.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.voanews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister save his coalition by how he fills the defense minister job</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GABRIEL SHERMAN</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/contributor/gabriel-sherman</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EL AL diverts flight after religious passengers become violent in Shabbat scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/el-al-diverts-flight-after-religious-passengers-become-violent-in-shabbat-scare/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ultra-Orthodox accused of violence on two planes from New York due to fears they would arrive after sundown Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson attacked by mob during livestream... </title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7770954/tommy-robinson-mob-attack-facebook-live-stream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FAR-right activist Tommy Robinson has been attacked while livestreaming a video in Luton. The 35-year-old, whose real name Stephen Yaxley-Lennon, was on his way to watch Luton Town when the inciden…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target Mississippi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/mississippis-gop-senator-is-tripping-all-over-herself-and-dems-are-starting-to-see-an-opportunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the last Senate contest of the cycle with a high degree of uncertainty. Democrats want to help but not mess things up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School bans 'expensive' jackets due to 'poverty shaming'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/school-bans-expensive-jackets-due-to-poverty-shaming-of-students/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most of the public supports the move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could you fit in this airplane bathroom? </title>
      <link>https://www.stuff.co.nz/travel/news/108684430/its-a-struggle-to-fit-into-shrinking-airplane-bathrooms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stuff.co.nz&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola response suffers another setback...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2018/11/17/ebola-response-setback-attack-who/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WHO evacuated 16 people working to contain the outbreak after an attack in the area, Director General Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said in an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALZ:  What has President Trump learned from defeat? </title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/What-has-President-Trump-learned-from-defeat-13401267.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All presidents suffer defeats and setbacks, whether through elections, legislative battles, international events or scandals. Most learn from them and adapt. Will President Donald Trump be an exception? That's the question ahead for the president: Will the second two years of his first term be any different from the first two years? His actions and words in the days following the midterm elections indicate things actually could get worse rather than better. He has never been a gracious winner. In defeat, he has shown worse: ill-tempered, withdrawn, even more unpredictable. Trump was elected in 2016 to lead a divided country. The midterm results, however, make clear the degree to which he has widened those divisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescuers search for pet owners...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article221803670.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The San Francisco SPCA and UC Davis vets are working to reunite pets rescued from the Northern CA Camp Fire with their owners. The animals’ burns are mild to severe, and most are unclaimed after the wildfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire refugees create new town of 'Wallywood'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article221775730.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How will California find housing for the Camp Fire evacuees and where will they go? As the search continues in Paradise for the dead and missing, CA officials struggle to find homes for victims of the wildfire. Some people are making their own town of “Wallywood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rain storms could bring more misery...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires-shelter/rain-storms-could-bring-more-misery-for-california-fire-evacuees-idUSKCN1NM0HA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people displaced by California's most destructive wildfire, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Left Get Revenge on Assange?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2018/11/17/julian-assange-robert-mueller-222608</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mysterious court filing hints the Wikileaks maestro, blamed by many for Hillary’s defeat, has already been secretly charged. But for what?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA: The Land That Failed to Fail...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2018/11/18/world/asia/china-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West was sure the Chinese approach would not work. It just had to wait. It’s still waiting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RONAN FARROW</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/contributors/ronan-farrow</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREW MCCARTHY</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/author/andrew-c-mccarthy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> Mocks 'Little Adam Schitt'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/trump-slimes-rep-adam-schiff-as-little-adam-schitt/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS MAKES HIS MOVE?</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/1046795/brexit-news-theresa-may-confidence-vote-boris-johnson-jacob-rees-mogg-david-davis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA OPENS CUBA 'SPY BASE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/742951/world-war-3-putin-soviet-military-base-cuba-donald-trump-usa-russia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog accused of a HATE CRIME...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6401779/The-DOG-accused-hate-crime-fouling-outside-home-just-one-2-500-cases-probed.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police notes recorded: 'An unknown dog has fouled outside of victim address and victim perceived this to be a racial incident.’ The Met had more than 2,500 complaints for hate crime in 2015 and 2016.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCHOOL WITH 17 CHILDREN CHANGING GENDER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6401593/Whistleblower-teacher-makes-shocking-claim-autistic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mail on Sunday can reveal that 17 pupils at a single British school are in the process of changing gender. According to a whistleblower most of the youngsters have autism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kevin Spacey vanished off face of the earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6401449/How-Kevin-Spacey-not-seen-YEAR.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following the allegations against Kevin Spacey nothing has been seen or heard of the double Oscar-winning actor. He was last spotted exercising at the Meadows Rehab Centre in Arizona, last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of Witches in USA on Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/blog/michael-w-chapman/number-witches-us-rise-may-outnumber-presbyterians</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GE, once America's most valuable company, fights junk-bond status...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/16/ge-once-elite-is-now-fighting-to-avoid-becoming-a-junk-bond-name.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GE's stock is a sliver of its former self, and its bonds are now trading as if they are already junk-rated, putting pressure on new CEO Larry Culp to quickly raise cash and cut debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BREITBART</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syndicated news and opinion website providing continuously updated headlines to top news and analysis sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living together becoming more popular than marriage...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/modern-love-cohabitation-on-rise-in-u-s-demographic-trends</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Living together is become more popular than marriage for young American couples, according to Census Bureau data.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence-Xi Showdown at APEC Shows Divide Only Widening...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/pence-slams-china-says-u-s-offers-countries-better-option</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pence Slams China, Says U.S. Offers Countries `Better Optionâ€™</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAY:  Getting rid of me won't help Brexit...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-politics-46250607</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The PM says next week will be "critical" and that progress in talks on the UK-EU future relationship could win over Tory rebels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE CEO Cook: New Regulations 'Inevitable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-on-hbo-tim-cook-interview-apple-regulation-6a35ff64-75a3-4e91-986c-f281c0615ac2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This is not a matter of privacy versus profits, or privacy versus technical innovation. That's a false choice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIKE ALLEN</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/axios-am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Allen, the world’s most-wired reporter, narrates the ten most important stories of the day. Daily</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL OF ORANGE COUNTY TURNS BLUE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/2018-midterms-california-gil-cisneros-young-kim-1542508058-d32b1cf0-8ee8-411d-92d9-209346c2022b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats flip the last remaining Republican seat in Orange County</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AXIOS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Smart, efficient news worthy of your time, attention, and trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman sues hospital for resuscitating her...</title>
      <link>https://www.abqjournal.com/1247179/woman-sues-hospital-for-resuscitating-her-ex-patient-alleges-her-dnr-directive-was-ignored-after-drug-allergy-caused-her-to-have-a-cardiac-arrest-2.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abqjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARRY ELDER</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/larryelder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;conserative columnist, conservative blogger, political commentary, political news, conservative column, GOP, conservatives, issues, opinion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLENN GREENWALD</title>
      <link>https://theintercept.com/greenwald/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theintercept.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al-Qaeda Threatens More Infernos...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/homeland-security/having-long-promoted-arson-tactic-al-qaeda-now-touts-california-burning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"They will question you about the mountains. Say: 'My Lord will scatter them as ashes,'" says the text citing the Quran, imposed over news photos from the blazes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Screams Of Terror Fill Philly Restaurant After Stabbing Prank...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/11/16/screams-of-terror-fill-philly-restaurant-after-stabbing-prank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrorized patrons took cover and ran for their lives after a man who appeared to be wearing a blood-soaked t-shirt walked into Terakawa Ramen screaming for help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamas 'Becoming' a billion-dollar brand...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/11/17/the-obamas-are-becoming-a-billion-dollar-brand/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Obamas are “Becoming” — billionaires. The launch of Michelle Obama’s cross-country book tour for her new memoir, “Becoming,” last week is just the latest marker on the road to fabulous wealth f…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE PAPERS</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/topic/newspapers-5993</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sky News - First for Breaking News, video, headlines, analysis and top stories from business, politics, entertainment and more in the UK and worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL SAVAGE</title>
      <link>https://michaelsavage.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;michaelsavage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MichaelSavage.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With hospitalization losing favor, judges order outpatient mental health treatment...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/with-hospitalization-losing-favor-judges-order-outpatient-mental-health-treatment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly every state in the country allows courts to force people with severe mental illnesses into treatment against their will. But critics argue these controversial intervention programs fail to a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERCEPT</title>
      <link>https://firstlook.org/theintercept/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;firstlook.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fearless, adversarial journalism that holds the powerful accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers Trapped After Elevator Plunges In Chicago's Hancock Skyscraper...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2018/11/16/hancock-elevator-fail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It took nearly three hours to rescue six people stuck in an elevator in Chicago’s fourth-tallest building early Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope decries that 'wealthy few' feast on what belongs to all...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c183ed8b9269499ea0f537d9e8a9f2b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VATICAN CITY (AP) — Championing the cause of the poor, Pope Francis on Sunday lamented that "the wealthy few" enjoy what, "in justice, belongs to all" and said Christians cannot remain indifferent to the growing cries of the exploited and the indigent, including migrants. Francis invited about 6,000 poor people as well as some of the volunteers who help them to the splendor of St. Peter's Basilica where he celebrated Mass on a day the Catholic Church dedicates to the needy. Later, he sat down with 1,500 of the indigent for a lunch of lasagna, chicken, mashed potatoes and tiramisu in a Vatican auditorium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP FIRE ZONE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/39609613ada445ffb135e53b9c577a50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump isn't committing to a previous pledge to keep chief of staff John Kelly for the remainder of his term, part of widespread speculation about staffing changes that could soon sweep through his administration. Trump, in a wide-ranging interview that aired on "Fox News Sunday," praised Kelly's work ethic and much of what he brings to the position but added, "There are certain things that I don't like that he does." "There are a couple of things where it's just not his strength. It's not his fault. It's not his strength," said Trump, who added that Kelly himself might want to depart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP TOP</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Associated Press delivers in-depth coverage on today's Big Story including top stories, international, politics, lifestyle, business, entertainment, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZERO HEDGE</title>
      <link>http://www.zerohedge.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XINHUA</title>
      <link>http://www.xinhuanet.com/english/world/index.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.xinhuanet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID LIMBAUGH</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/authors/dlimbaugh/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD NET DAILY</title>
      <link>http://www.wnd.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOL</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/william-kristol</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPHEN HAYES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/stephen-f.-hayes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRED BARNES</title>
      <link>http://www.weeklystandard.com/author/fred-barnes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.weeklystandard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANA MILBANK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonpost.com/2010/07/06/AB2i8vO_linkset.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BYRON YORK</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/author/byron-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH EXAMINER</title>
      <link>http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VANITY FAIR</title>
      <link>http://www.vanityfair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Entertainment, TV, politics, celebrity, fashion, and beauty news and commentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPI</title>
      <link>http://www.upi.com/NewsTrack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIZARRE [SUN]</title>
      <link>http://www.thesun.co.uk/sol/homepage/showbiz/bizarre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Best for News, Sport, Showbiz, Celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRONT PAGES UK</title>
      <link>http://www.thepaperboy.com/uk/front-pages.cfm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thepaperboy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLOYD GROVE</title>
      <link>http://www.thedailybeast.com/author/lloyd-grove/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAZE</title>
      <link>http://www.theblaze.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theblaze.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authentic. Unfiltered. Fearless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTIC</title>
      <link>http://www.theatlantic.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Atlantic covers news and analysis on politics, business, culture, technology, national, international and life on the official site of The Atlantic Magazine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DER SPIEGEL</title>
      <link>http://www.spiegel.de/international</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV RATINGS</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER FRIEDMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.showbiz411.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Hollywood News in Movies, Music, Broadway and Celebrity Headlines</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAN FRAN CHRON</title>
      <link>http://www.sfgate.com/chronicle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive Bay Area and San Francisco breaking news, sports, tech, and food and wine coverage, plus enhanced coverage of Giants, 49ers and Warriors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALON</title>
      <link>http://www.salon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.salon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROLLING STONE</title>
      <link>http://www.rollingstone.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollingstone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music, Film, TV and Political News Coverage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REUTERS</title>
      <link>http://www.reuters.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reuters.com brings you the latest news from around the world, covering breaking news in markets, business, politics, entertainment, technology, video and pictures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRUDGE REFERENCE DESK</title>
      <link>http://www.refdesk.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.refdesk.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESS TRUST INDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.ptinews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ptinews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO PLAYBOOK</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/playbook/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POLITICO's must-read briefing on what's driving the day in Washington</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO MORNING MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://www.politico.com/media/tipsheets/morning-media</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Your guide to the media circus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRUGMAN</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/paulkrugman/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Krugman, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about macroeconomics, trade, health care, social policy and politics. In 2008, he received the Nobel Prize in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY TIMES WIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.nytimes.com/timeswire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORKER</title>
      <link>http://www.newyorker.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting, Profiles, breaking news, cultural coverage, podcasts, videos, and cartoons from The New Yorker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSMAX</title>
      <link>http://www.newsmax.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsmax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsmax.com reports today’s news headlines, live news stream, news videos from Americans and global readers seeking the latest in current events, politics, U.S., world news, health, finance, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WORLD HEADLINES</title>
      <link>http://www.newseum.org/todaysfrontpages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newseum.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every morning, more than 800 newspapers from around the world electronically submit their front pages to the Newseum to be part of Today’s Front Pages online exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.nbcnews.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to NBCNews.com for breaking news, videos, and the latest top stories in world news, business, politics, health and pop culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTOR DAVIS HANSON</title>
      <link>http://www.nationalreview.com/author/victor-davis-hanson</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID CORN</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/author/david-corn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTHER JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.motherjones.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.motherjones.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 AM GIRLS</title>
      <link>http://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDIAITE</title>
      <link>http://www.mediaite.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCCLATCHY [DC]</title>
      <link>http://www.mcclatchydc.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARK LEVIN</title>
      <link>http://www.marklevinshow.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marklevinshow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mark Levin Show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFEZETTE</title>
      <link>http://www.lifezette.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lifezette.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From pop culture to faith, parenting to politics, LifeZette delivers a compelling mixture of stories, commentary, video and graphics designed to inform and entertain — and to help all of us live our lives to the fullest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAURA INGRAHAM</title>
      <link>http://www.lauraingraham.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lauraingraham.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Taken gloves off' in thefts of U.S. tech secrets...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-china-economic-espionage-20181116-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was the great microchip heist — a stunning Chinese-backed effort that pilfered $8.75 billion in secret American technology. But the real secret is it wasn't unusual. After a lull under President Obama, Chinese economic espionage is soaring again as U.S. relations with Beijing worsen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JERUSALEM POST</title>
      <link>http://www.jpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ITAR-TASS</title>
      <link>http://www.itar-tass.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itar-tass.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY POLICY...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/privacypolicy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BE SEEN!   RUN ADS ON DRUDGE REPORT...</title>
      <link>http://www.intermarkets.net/drudgereport.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.intermarkets.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERFAX</title>
      <link>http://www.interfax.com/news.asp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.interfax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALEX JONES</title>
      <link>http://www.infowars.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Jones' Infowars: There's a war on for your mind!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDO-ASIAN NEWS SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.ians.in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ians.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUGH HEWITT</title>
      <link>http://www.hughhewitt.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hughhewitt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A broadcast pro who has informed and entertained on radio and television for over a decade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUFFINGTON POST</title>
      <link>http://www.huffingtonpost.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.huffingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the latest headlines, news stories, and opinion from Politics, Entertainment, Life, Perspectives, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOT AIR</title>
      <link>http://www.hotair.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world’s first, full-service conservative Internet broadcast network</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEFF WELLS</title>
      <link>http://www.hollywood-elsewhere.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywood-elsewhere.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HELLO!</title>
      <link>http://www.hellomagazine.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hellomagazine.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News and pictures from the world of celebrity, royalty, entertainment, film and music; fashion trends and videos, health and beauty, celebrity profiles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY</title>
      <link>http://www.hannity.com/main.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hannity.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official Website of The Sean Hannity Show. Sean Hannity is a multimedia superstar, spending four hours a day every day reaching out to millions of Americans on radio, television and the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL TIMES</title>
      <link>http://www.ft.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ft.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;News, analysis and comment from the Financial Times, the world's leading global business publication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE REPUBLIC</title>
      <link>http://www.freerepublic.com/home.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freerepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRANCE 24</title>
      <link>http://www.france24.com/en/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking news and world news from France 24 on Business, Sports, Culture. Video news. News from the US, Europe, Asia Pacific, Africa, Middle East, America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  CLEVELAND BROWNS want to interview Condoleezza Rice for head coaching job...</title>
      <link>http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/25310452/cleveland-browns-want-interview-condoleezza-rice-head-coaching-job</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Browns would like to interview former Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice for their head-coaching job, a league source told ESPN. If they follow through, it would make her the first woman in NFL history to interview for such a position.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARCHIVES</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereportArchives.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereportArchives.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEUTSCHE PRESSE-AGENTUR</title>
      <link>http://www.dpa-international.com/news/international/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dpa-international.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLINE HOLLYWOOD</title>
      <link>http://www.deadline.com/hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood Entertainment Breaking News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY RECORD</title>
      <link>http://www.dailyrecord.co.uk/news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailyrecord.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA DAILY NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.dailynewslosangeles.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynewslosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAZ BAMIGBOYE</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/columnist-1000601/Baz-Bamigboye.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baz Bamigboye for the Daily Mail Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIERS MORGAN</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/columnist-1096452/Piers-Morgan-MailOnline.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Piers Morgan for MailOnline Columnist Archive for MailOnline</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL FEED</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/headlines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check out latest UK and world breaking news and headlines from the Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday. Visit our website to always stay informed on the latest news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UK] DAILY MAIL</title>
      <link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MailOnline - get the latest breaking news, showbiz &amp; celebrity photos, sport news &amp; rumours, viral videos and top stories from MailOnline, Daily Mail and Mail on Sunday newspapers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNBC</title>
      <link>http://www.cnbc.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get latest business news on stock markets, financial &amp; earnings on CNBC. View world markets streaming charts &amp; video; check stock tickers and quotes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELEBRITY SERVICE</title>
      <link>http://www.celebrityservice.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.celebrityservice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS</title>
      <link>http://www.cbsnews.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS News is dedicated to the best in journalism under standards it pioneered at the dawn of radio and television and continues to set in today’s digital age.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED</title>
      <link>http://www.buzzfeed.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeed.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BuzzFeed has breaking news, vital journalism, quizzes, videos, celeb news, Tasty food videos, recipes, DIY hacks, and all the trending buzz you’ll want to share with your friends. Copyright BuzzFeed, Inc. All rights reserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUSINESS INSIDER</title>
      <link>http://www.businessinsider.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest news from Business Insider</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON GLOBE</title>
      <link>http://www.boston.com/globe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boston.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILL PRESS</title>
      <link>http://www.billpress.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thought-provoking insights from the left side of the political aisle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BILD</title>
      <link>http://www.bild.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bild.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BILD.de: Die Seite 1 für aktuelle Nachrichten und Themen, Bilder und Videos aus den Bereichen News, Wirtschaft, Politik, Show, Sport, und Promis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV NEWSER</title>
      <link>http://www.adweek.com/tvnewser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The President [doesn’t] get to decide what’s fair and what’s not."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMZ</title>
      <link>http://www.TMZ.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.TMZ.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADWEEK</title>
      <link>http://www.Adweek.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.Adweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breaking News in Advertising, Media and Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAUL BEDARD</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/politics/washington-secrets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHAEL BARONE</title>
      <link>http://washingtonexaminer.com/author/michael-barone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRIAN STELTER</title>
      <link>http://us11.campaign-archive1.com/home/?u=47c9040f6ff957a59bd88396e&amp;id=e95cdc16a9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;us11.campaign-archive1.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JIM RUTENBERG</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/reference/timestopics/people/r/jim_rutenberg/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent and archived work by Jim Rutenberg for The New York Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRISTOF</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/nicholasdkristof/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicholas Kristof, a New York Times Op-Ed Columnist, writes about human rights, womenâ€™s rights, health, global affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAUREEN DOWD</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/maureendowd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maureen Dowd, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about American politics, popular culture and international affairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVID BROOKS</title>
      <link>http://topics.nytimes.com/top/opinion/editorialsandoped/oped/columnists/davidbrooks/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;topics.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Brooks, a New York Times Op-Ed columnist, writes about politics, culture and the social sciences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOKING GUN</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILL: JUST IN</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY BEAST</title>
      <link>http://thedailybeast.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A smart, speedy take on the news from around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALKING POINTS MEMO</title>
      <link>http://talkingpointsmemo.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER STONE</title>
      <link>http://stonezone.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;stonezone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAL CLEAR POLITICS</title>
      <link>http://realclearpolitics.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radaronline.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radaronline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check back often for the most up-to-the-second gossip, news and Hollywood happening anywhere. Follow stories as they happen &amp; see what's happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PJ MEDIA</title>
      <link>http://pjmedia.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PJ Media is a leading news site covering culture, politics, faith, homeland security, and more. Our reporters and columnists provide original, in-depth analysis from a variety of perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RICHARD JOHNSON</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/richard-johnson/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CINDY ADAMS</title>
      <link>http://pagesix.com/author/cindy-adams/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL STREET JOURNAL</title>
      <link>http://online.wsj.com/home-page</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;online.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WSJ online coverage of breaking news and current headlines from the US and around the world. Top stories, photos, videos, detailed analysis and in-depth reporting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEITH J. KELLY</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/keith-j-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANDREA PEYSER</title>
      <link>http://nypost.com/author/andrea-peyser/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW YORK</title>
      <link>http://nymag.com</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Guide to Restaurants, Fashion, Nightlife, Shopping, Politics, Movies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEWSBUSTERS</title>
      <link>http://newsbusters.org/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsbusters.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1200+ STILL MISSING</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181118030334-ckup2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRES/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 5-Search on for 1,276 now missing after California's deadliest wildfire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOU DOBBS</title>
      <link>http://loudobbs.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;loudobbs.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATIE HOPKINS</title>
      <link>http://hopkinsworld.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hopkinsworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE BEACON</title>
      <link>http://freebeacon.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YONHAP</title>
      <link>http://english.yonhapnews.co.kr/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.yonhapnews.co.kr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yonhap news articles produced by building a network covering domestic supplies in various newspapers, broadcasting and government departments, major institutions, major corporations, media ,K-pop, K-wave, Hallyu, Korean Wave, Korean pop, Korean pop culture, Korean culture, Korean idol, Korean movies, Internet media and international agreements of the Republic of Korea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAVDA</title>
      <link>http://english.pravda.ru/allnews_en.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;english.pravda.ru&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAILY CALLER</title>
      <link>http://dailycaller.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's entertainment gossip and chatter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS NEWS LOCAL</title>
      <link>http://cbslocal.com/2015/08/31/daily-news-tips-from-cbs-local-sites/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE</title>
      <link>http://boxofficemojo.com/daily/chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boxofficemojo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOWIE CARR</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news_opinion/columnists/howie_carr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOSTON HERALD</title>
      <link>http://bostonherald.com/news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVE BARRY</title>
      <link>http://blogs.herald.com/dave_barrys_blog/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;blogs.herald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEATHER ACTION</title>
      <link>/wx.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHEET</title>
      <link>/quake.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
