<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon Flies Plane Over Ukraine in Warning to Russia...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-military-plane-flies-over-ukraine-in-warning-to-russia-1544136754</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pentagon said it carried out a rare flight over Ukraine under the international Open Skies Treaty to “reaffirm U.S. commitment to Ukraine” amid heightened Russia-Ukraine tensions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  Making President's Bed, A Housekeeper Without Papers... </title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/making-president-trump%E2%80%99s-bed-a-housekeeper-without-papers/ar-BBQAYz2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I'm tired of being humiliated and treated like a stupid person'...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-trump-housekeeper-new-jersey-golf-club-immigration-20181206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman working as a housekeeper at President Trump's golf club in Bedminster, New Jersey revealed that she is an unauthorized immigrant in a NYT interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation-hit Chernobyl wolves 'spreading mutant genes across Europe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911846/the-european-grey-wolf-population-has-boomed-at-the-site-since-the-human-population-moved-out-and-it-became-a-virtual-wildlife-preserve/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS fear wolves living in Chernobyl’s radioactive forbidden zone may be spreading mutant genes across Europe. The European grey wolf population has boomed at the site since the human p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President lawyers, Special Counsel in talks following written submission...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/trump-lawyers-special-counsel-discussions-following-written-submission-president-s-n945061</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s lawyers have resumed discussions with the office of special counsel Robert Mueller in recent days, the first time that's been acknowledged since President Donald Trump submitted written responses to questions regarding the possibility of collusion between his 2016 campaign and Russia, two people familiar with the matter told NBC News on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNOPES Fact-Checker Botches Fact Check...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2018/12/06/snopes-facebook-google-fact-check/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'This is quite literally insane fake news'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STONE: Legal 'proctological examination' hell...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/roger-stone-gripes-about-legal-proctological-examination-this-has-been-hell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCAR DRAMA: HOST HOMOPHOBIA HEADACHE</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/kevin-harts-past-anti-gay-tweets-creates-problem-academy-1167191</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next Oscars host faces a backlash over hundreds of homophobic jokes. Said Billy Eichner: "There's real truth, anger &amp; fear behind these."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'They're All Too Old': Dems Face Generational Reckoning...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/12/democrats-face-a-generational-reckoning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The choice in the 2020 primary ultimately comes down to one thing: who is best prepared to beat Trump at a time when Trump owns the culture? Someone who actually understands culture would be a start.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smugglers who ingested Mexican cartel cash profits busted...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-colombia-crime/smugglers-ingested-mexican-cartel-cash-say-colombia-police-after-arrests-idUSKBN1O600D</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombia has arrested 27 people accused of belonging to four smuggling networks ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: Heather Nauert Next UN Ambassador...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-07/trump-to-pick-heather-nauert-as-next-un-ambassador-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Keep in mind, I'm not homophobic'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/kevin-hart-deletes-old-anti-gay-tweets-after-landing-oscar-hosting-gig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin Hart has been busy scrubbing his Twitter account of his old anti-gay tweets since he was tapped as Oscar host earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gig in jeopardy?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/should-the-oscars-fire-host-kevin-hart-over-his-homophobic-jokes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Past homophobic and anti-gay jokes and tweets the comedian made, including calling someone’s picture a “gay billboard for AIDS” have resurfaced. Are they a fireable offense?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Hart Scrambles to Delete Anti-Gay Tweets After Being Named OSCARS Host...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/michaelblackmon/kevin-hart-homophobic-tweets-gay-oscars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a since-deleted tweet, Hart joked that he would break a dollhouse over his son’s head if he were caught playing with the toy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecuador: Enough UK guarantees for Assange to leave embassy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0b95cddbe0614d47b71c07c827710210</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;QUITO, Ecuador (AP) — Ecuador's president has ramped up pressure on Julian Assange to leave his country's embassy in London, saying that Britain had provided sufficient guarantees that the WikiLeaks founder won't be extradited to face the death penalty abroad. Lenin Moreno's comments in a radio interview Thursday suggest that months of quiet diplomacy between the U.K. and Ecuador to resolve Assange's situation is bearing fruit at a time when questions are swirling about the former Australian hacker's legal fate in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doorstop vigilantes fight porch pirates with booby traps, dog poop...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/porch-pirates-are-trying-to-steal-christmas-but-doorstep-vigilantes-are-on-high-alert/2018/12/06/cbf694ea-f966-11e8-8c9a-860ce2a8148f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans fight back with booby traps, hidden cameras and even dog poop against the scourge of online commerce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Ready for 'Inevitable' Clampdown on Tech, Media?</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/blog/2018/12/06/are-you-ready-for-the-clampdown-on-tech</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Apple's CEO Tim Cook says "the free market is not working," bad things are coming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lena Dunham lied to discredit alleged rape victim...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/ct-life-stevens-thursday-how-not-to-apologize-lena-dunham-1206-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The "Girls" actress and director should be better at apologizing by now, but her Hollywood Reporter note to Aurora Perrineau is little more than terrible performance art.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuns embezzle $500,000 from school to gamble, take trips...</title>
      <link>https://www.presstelegram.com/2018/12/05/nuns-improperly-took-as-much-as-500000-from-torrance-catholic-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.presstelegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were an ATM and people know it and they won’t ask for justice,” one parent said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sits on victim naked, bashes with brass plate...</title>
      <link>https://www.komu.com/news/columbia-woman-arrested-for-domestic-assault-sexual-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.komu.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police arrested Amy Parrino after an incident in northeast Columbia on Sunday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman chases, beats man who refused to perform oral sex...</title>
      <link>https://www.columbiatribune.com/news/20181204/columbia-woman-charged-with-sex-abuse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbiatribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Columbia woman is accused of attempting to force a man to perform oral sex on her.Boone County prosecutors on Monday charged 43-year-old Amy Nicole</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC election fraud probe shines light on 'ballot harvesting'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsoctv.com/news/north-carolina/north-carolina-race-shines-light-on-ballot-harvesting/884597359</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsoctv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELENA, Mont. (AP) - An investigation into whether political operatives in North Carolina illegally collected and possibly stole absentee ballots in a still-undecided congressional race has drawn attention to a widespread but little-known political tool called ballot harvesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firms in China vulnerable after HUAWEI arrest...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/us-firms-in-china-vulnerable-after-huawei-arrest-ex-us-trade-advisor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's a good chance the Chinese will retaliate for the arrest of Huawei CFO Meng Wanzhou by targeting American businesses in China, says former assistant U.S. trade representative Jeff Moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE AirDrop Assaults On Rise As Criminals 'Cyber Flash' Strangers...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2018/12/05/airdrop-assaults-on-the-rise-as-criminals-cyber-flash-strangers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As technology infiltrates every aspect of our lives criminals and creeps are figuring out creative ways to abuse it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ride from Hell': Carpooling in Age of UBER...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/ride-from-hell-carpooling-in-the-age-of-uber-can-beawkward-1544112559</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As shared ride services become more popular, passengers clash over music, temperature and talking. Exasperated drivers try to referee; ‘They had no shame.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIATCHRYSLER to open new Detroit factory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/fiat-chrysler-reportedly-plans-to-open-new-assembly-factory-in-detroit-to-build-suv.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REDSKINS QB facing 'devastating complications' after surgery...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2018/12/06/reports-alex-smith-dealing-with-post-op-infection-in-leg/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington quarterback Alex Smith’s recovery from the broken tibia and fibula he suffered last month is reportedly being complicated by an infection. Eric Bickel of 106.7 The Fan reports that…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDNY Chief removed over 'inappropriate behavior'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/12/06/fdny-chief-james-leonard-removed-from-post-over-inappropriate-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FDNY’s top uniformed member was removed from his post Thursday amid a probe into his alleged mistreatment of the department’s highest-ranking woman, the FDNY and sources said. Chief of Departme…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece plans crowdfunding for new warships...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1845b762915c4de7bb71d6568fb73d51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATHENS, Greece (AP) — Greece's defense minister is appealing to his austerity-battered countryfolk for a crowdfunding effort to raise money for new warships, promising to donate part of his own salary. Panos Kammenos says he will open a bank account on Jan. 1 where members of the public can make donations "for new frigates and a flagship." He addressed his appeal to Greece's wealthy shipowning industry, as well as ordinary Greeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>89,000 security forces deployed...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-protests-security/france-to-deploy-89000-security-personnel-ahead-of-saturday-protests-idUSKBN1O52BS</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French Prime Minister Edouard Philippe said 89,000 members of the security force...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay Conversion Exorcisms on the Rise in Indonesia...</title>
      <link>https://pjmedia.com/faith/islamic-exorcisms-aim-to-cast-out-lgbt-demons-in-worlds-largest-muslim-country/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pjmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's even a TV show...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Republicans following Wisconsin's lead in curbing Democrats' power...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-politics-states/michigan-republicans-following-wisconsins-lead-in-curbing-democrats-power-idUSKBN1O5289</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A day after Wisconsin Republicans approved a package of bills intended to restri...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next big security risk: Children's video-game habit...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-next-big-risk-to-your-security-is-your-kids-video-game-habit-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hackers are increasingly targeting video games, new report finds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRIDAY:  3 new docs may show what ex-Trump aides told Mueller...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/justice-department/friday-3-new-documents-may-show-some-what-ex-trump-n944801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two sentencing memos for Michael Cohen and a document detailing Paul Manafort's alleged "crimes and lies" are due to be filed Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eiffel Tower to close...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/eiffel-tower-close-saturday-due-planned-paris-protests-n944876</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several other cultural sites and attractions will also close.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi rejects funding wall...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e3fd315c66554c22bfdf97710e0df711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — House Democratic Leader Nancy Pelosi is rejecting the idea of paying for President Donald Trump's border wall in exchange for a deal to help hundreds of thousands of young immigrants avoid deportation. Pelosi said Thursday that wall funding and legal protections for so-called "Dreamers" should not be linked, saying "they're two different subjects." Pelosi, who is seeking to become House speaker in January, said Congress should pass appropriations bills that key committees have already agreed on, along with a separate measure funding the Department of Homeland Security, which oversees the border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Marriage Easiest In Old Age...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/marriage-easier-old-age-laughter-replaces-bickering/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ever feel like your marriage is losing its luster and all the romance is being replaced with petty bickering? Don't worry, there's light -- and lightheartedness -- at the end of the tunnel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Net Oil Exporter for First Time in 75 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-12-06/u-s-becomes-a-net-oil-exporter-for-the-first-time-in-75-years</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTHWEST Flight Skids Off Runway At Burbank Airport... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/12/06/southwest-flight-skids-burbank-airport/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines flight arriving at Burbank Airport from Oakland skidded off the runway after landing Thursday morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Murder Rate on Track for Big Drop...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/upshot/us-murder-rate-for-2018-is-on-track-for-a-big-drop.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Murders are down so far in a sample of large American cities, typically a good indicator for national numbers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bones tossed like trash at cemetery...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fc144b8bb3c04f96b95634f7f645415e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the 1990s, Cheryl Jansen had noticed junk and tree limbs piling up at the once oasis-like Park Cemetery, just north of downtown Bridgeport, Connecticut, and wondered where the money families had paid for perpetual upkeep was going. What she learned after finally taking her case to a judge shocked the conscience. Gravestones and remains moved without permission to make way for the newly dead. New graves simply stacked on top of old ones, separated by a new layer of dirt. Worst of all, human bones, casket pieces and old headstones tossed in the woods like trash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65,000 security forces deployed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/edfebfba2beb486d8d1e48da4cb6834e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — France will deploy more than 65,000 security forces amid fears of new rioting at protests Saturday in Paris and around the nation, despite President Emmanuel Macron's surrender over a fuel tax hike that unleashed weeks of unrest. Police unions and local authorities held emergency meetings Thursday to strategize on how to handle the weekend protests, while disparate groups of protesters did the same thing, sharing their plans on social networks and chat groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photographer who documented dark side of communist state mysteriously vanishes...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7911948/chinese-photographer-dark-side-communist-state-vanishes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN award-winning Chinese photographer who candidly documented the dark side of the country’s booming economy has mysteriously vanished. Lu Guang, a three-time World Press Photo award winner, …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FX Lands Most TV Nominations... </title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/golden-globes-tv-fx-most-nominations-network-prime-video-streamers-hbo-netflix-1202515092/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FX is closing its chapter as a 21st Century Fox network on a high note, edging awards juggernauts HBO and Netflix to top the list of networks with most Golden Globes nominations, 10. It was a very …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encryption-busting powers...</title>
      <link>https://www.itnews.com.au/news/australia-gets-world-first-encryption-laws-as-labor-folds-516601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itnews.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Labor passes bill without changes it claimed were needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCASIO CORTEZ:  Climate Governance Will Create 'Economic, Social, and Racial Justice'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-ocasio-cortez-inevitable-global-warming-governance-will-crea </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘It’s inevitable that we can use the transition to 100% renewable energy as the vehicle to truly deliver and establish economic, social, and racial justice in the United States of America’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elementary school bans Santa, candy canes, red and green items...</title>
      <link>http://eagnews.org/elementary-school-bans-santa-candy-canes-reindeer-elf-on-the-shelf-red-green-items-to-be-inclusive-and-culturally-sensitive/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;eagnews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manchester Elementary School Principal Jennifer Sinclair just landed on Santa’s naughty list, which means she probably won’t get any presents from the big man this year. The Nebraska educator apparently tripped on a “big rock” and fell on her face, all the while attempting to rob her students of the joyous Christmas season. It’s like a bad Hallmark movie come to life, happy ending and all. “It seems that I have stumbled upon a ‘big rock’ that I hadn’t anticipated,” Sinclair wrote to her legion of teachers in her “week ahead” newsletter for Dec. 3-7. “I know that you are</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest snubs, surprises...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/golden-globes/2018/12/06/golden-globes-nominations-snubs-4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 2019 Golden Globes nominations are out. Let's first hit some surprises, because there were some rather huge ones on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>http://dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6467875/Elizabeth-Warrens-advisers-want-APOLOGIZE-DNA-stunt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats blasted the liberal Massachusetts senator in October for drawing attention to her biggest political liability in the middle of a tense midterm election cycle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approval rating crashes to 18%...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7915541/emmanuel-macron-predicts-violence-france-weekend-approval-rating/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL Macron’s approval rating has crashed below 20 per cent today as he predicts more “major violence” across France this weekend. The beleaguered head of state is locked in a law and order cri…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNITY, ZUCKER, DRUDGE NAMED 'MOST INFLUENTIAL'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/mediaites-most-influential-in-news-media-2018/8/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDEN GLOBES CHAOS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d47620b3896e4f47b82aac1ec5069554</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Adam McKay's Dick Cheney biopic "Vice" seized control of the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards with a leading six nominations, narrowly edging Bradley Cooper's tear-jerking revival "A Star Is Born," the interracial road-trip drama "Green Book" and the period romp "The Favourite." "Vice" topped all contenders Thursday, in nominations announced at the Beverly Hilton Hotel in Beverly Hills, California, including best picture, comedy and best actor nominations for Christian Bale's nearly unrecognizable performance as the former vice president. It also earned nominations for Amy Adams' Lynne Cheney, Sam Rockwell's George W. Bush and both the screenplay and direction by McKay, the veteran comedy filmmaker who once skewered politicians as a "Saturday Night Live" writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amal Clooney accuses Trump of 'giving green light' to autocratic regimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/amal-clooney-accuses-trump-giving-green-light-autocratic-regimes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amal Clooney has claimed Donald Trump gives the &amp;quot;green light&amp;quot; to autocratic regimes during a speech in which she warned against the US president's attacks on the press.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.wral.com/elizabeth-warren-stands-by-dna-test-but-around-her-worries-abound-/18043961/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wral.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — The plan was straightforward: After years of being challenged by President Donald Trump and others about a decades-old claim of Native American ancestry, Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., would take a DNA test to prove her stated family origins in the Cherokee and Delaware tribes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student protests intensify alongside tax revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181206-french-student-protests-intensify-alongside-yellow-vest-revolt</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French student protests intensify alongside 'yellow vest' revolt</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump Spoilers?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/811016/5-republicans-who-could-challenge-trump-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of them can win. But they could play spoiler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shatters Diversity Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/golden-globes-shatters-diversity-record-4-10-best-picture-nominees-non-white-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Crazy Rich Asians," "BlacKkKlansman," "Black Panther" and "If Beale Street Could Talk" all break into the top categories</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The College Guys Trying to Ban Porn on Campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/these-college-guys-are-trying-to-ban-porn-on-campus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movement started at Notre Dame but has quickly spread to other universities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stair test may predict risk of dying of heart disease, cancer, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/health/how-live-longer-stair-test-may-predict-longevity-death-risk-t144556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you can do this simple test, it's a good sign of your exercise capacity. If not, you may need to exercise more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Generation Xanax...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/06/generation-xanax-doubling-children-treated-addiction/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New figures reveal the rise of &amp;ldquo;generation Xanax&amp;rdquo; - with a doubling in young people being treated for addiction to anti-anxiety drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bannon grilled by Senate Intel Committee...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/senate-intelligence-committee-grilled-steve-bannon-about-cambridge-analytica </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The notorious “psychographic” data firm remains of interest to Senate investigators—as does the former Trump strategist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Watch can now detect irregular heart rhythms, other problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/apple-watch-ecg-sensor-review.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We tried out the new ECG app and irregular heart rate notification for Apple Watch ahead of its release on Thursday. Here's how to use it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Claims Chased U.S. Destroyer Out Of Territorial Waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/news/2018-12-06/russia-claims-it-chased-us-destroyer-out-its-territorial-waters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Cheney Takedown 'VICE Tops With 6 Nominations...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/lists/2019-golden-globes-nominations-full-list-1165090</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ceremony is set for Jan. 6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz passes cyber snooping laws with global implications...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/australia-passes-cyber-snooping-laws-global-implications-103222310.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australia Thursday passed controversial laws allowing spies and police to snoop on the encrypted communications of suspected terrorists and criminals, as experts warned the "unprecedented powers" had far-reaching implications for global cybersecurity. There has been extensive debate about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's slow-motion staff 'shakeup'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/12/06/trumps-slow-motion-staff-shakeup-stunts-2019-planning-1046414</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president has left top officials in a state of limbo and top jobs without permanent occupants, creating &amp;quot;a sense of chaos.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade Gap Widens to 10-Year High...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-trade-deficit-climbs-to-10-year-high-despite-tariffs-tough-trump-stance-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trade deficit rose 1.7% in October to a 10-year high amid a record shortfall with China, keeping the U.S. on pace to record the largest gap in a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 9,000 counterfeit NIKES seized in New York...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/05/us/counterfeit-nikes-seized-new-york-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Can you spot a fake?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payroll growth slows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/06/payroll-growth-slows-in-november-as-labor-market-tightens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Private payrolls increased by 179,000, below the 195,000 growth expected by a Refinitiv survey of economists. The number also was a drop from the 225,000 in October and below the 203,000 prior monthly average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/golden-globe-nominations-2019-1203082075/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nominations for the 76th annual Golden Globe Awards will be announced Thursday morning show live from the Beverly Hilton Hotel. Actors Terry Crews, Danai Gurira, Leslie Mann and Christian Slate are…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Tanzania, Crackdown Sends LGBT People Into Hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/behind-the-curtain-in-tanzania-a-crackdown-sends-lgbt-people-into-hiding-1544101201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A crackdown on LGBT rights in Tanzania has forced people into hiding and sparked an international backlash.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro athletes say they will lose fortune under tax law...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/why-pro-athletes-may-lose-a-fortune-because-of-the-new-tax-law-2018-12-06</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPAs who work with athletes say they can no longer get full deductions for state and local taxes — or for itemizing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE: GOLDEN GLOBES NOMS</title>
      <link>https://www.goldenglobes.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goldenglobes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood awards season kicks off...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/12/how-to-watch-the-golden-globe-nominations-nbc-live-facebook-instagram-1202514901/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nominees for the 76th Annual Golden Globe Awards will be announced Thursday, Dec. 6 by Terry Crews, Danai Gurira, Leslie Mann, and Christian Slater. In addition to the nominees, the Hollywood F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of underground LSD guides...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2018/dec/06/lsd-guides-psychedelic-assisted-psychotherapy </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Americans searching for alternative paths to healing have turned to psychedelics. But how does one forge a career as a guide when the substances are illegal?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment/la-et-2019-golden-globe-nominations-how-to-watch-the-golden-globe-1544036969-htmlstory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everything you need to know about how to livestream Thursday's Golden Globe nominations announcement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron on brink...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1055152/Macron-news-france-crisis-protests-end-of-macron-no-confidence-vote</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EMMANUEL Macron’s leadership is hanging by a thread as left-wing groups within the French parliament discuss launching a no confidence vote against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honduran woman in migrant caravan gives birth in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3ca21d8faf414f639693f07fbf4bc7ea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — A Honduran woman affiliated with a caravan of Central American migrants gave birth on U.S. soil shortly after entering the country illegally amid growing frustration about a bottleneck to claim asylum at official border crossings. Border Patrol agents arrested the woman Nov. 26 after she entered the country illegally near Imperial Beach, California, across the border from Tijuana, Mexico, Customs and Border Protection said Wednesday. She was arrested with her 20-year-old husband and 2-year-old son.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Workers Get Just 1.25 Cents for Each DISNEY Doll Produced...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2018/dec/06/revealed-disney-ariel-doll-earns-chinese-worker-1p </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Undercover investigation exposes illegally long working hours and low wages for staff at factory producing toys for Disney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first bee vaccine seeks to save dying pollinators...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/World-s-first-honey-bee-vaccine-seeks-to-save-13446663.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A growing number of honey bees die each year due to pesticides, vanishing habitats, poor nutrition and climate change, with potentially disastrous consequences for agriculture and natural diversity. Now, scientists at the University of Helsinki have developed the first edible vaccine against microbial infections, hoping to save at least some of the pollinators. "We might be right now at a tipping point, without even realizing it," Dalial Freitak, the lead scientist on the project, said in an interview on Wednesday. "We've been taking the pollination services for granted for so long. These insects are not there, they are disappearing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chavez Bleak Legacy Keeps Venezuela Broken 20 Years After Rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2018/dec/06/on-the-road-venezuela-20-years-after-hugo-chavez-rise</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Guardian travels across the nation the late Hugo Chávez dreamed of transforming, to understand its collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Stands by DNA Test. But Around Her, Worries Abound...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/12/06/us/politics/elizabeth-warren-dna-test-2020.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since releasing the results in October, the ancestry issue clouding her possible presidential campaign has only intensified.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots will feel love, suffer pain when dumped...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7908769/sex-robots-will-soon-feel-love-and-suffer-devastating-pain-after-we-dump-them-expert-reveals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEX robots will soon feel love and suffer pain after being dumped, according to an expert. Professor Robin Mackenzie, director of Law and Medical Ethics and Kent Law School, claimed robotics will b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP: Deli Customer Attacks Worker for Wait Time Over Bagel Order...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/Angry-Deli-Customer-Attacks-Worker-Bacon-Egg-Cheese-Cinnamon-Raisin-Bagel-Brooklyn-502035522.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An irate deli customer is wanted for his violent tantrum in which he attacked a worker when he was told his wait time for a bacon, egg and cheese sandwich would take at least five minutes, police said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes noms... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181206-hollywood-awards-season-kicks-off-with-golden-globes-noms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood awards season kicks off with Golden Globes noms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emerging STDs pose serious public health threats...</title>
      <link>https://edition.cnn.com/2018/12/06/health/std-sexually-transmitted-diseases-partner/index.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;edition.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although gonorrhea, chlamydia and syphilis grab most of the headlines, public health officials are warily watching the emergence of other bacterial sexually transmitted infections.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
