<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOKer Rallies Fans to Bombard 'Whistleblower' Site With Fake Tips...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/tiktoker-creates-script-to-bombard-texas-abortion-whistleblower-site-with-fake-tips/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TikTok “hacktivist” has created a script to flood a Texas website used to solicit information on people seeking abortions with fake reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDI unveils new concept car as 'private jet for road'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/audi-unveils-grandsphere-concept-car-as-a-private-jet-for-the-road.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the vehicle can't fly, Audi said it designed the electric car with such luxury private travel in mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LISTEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/09/02/abba-drops-2-songs-announces-new-album-avatar-tour-now-look-like-steely-dans-becker-and-fagen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Benny and Bjorn from ABBA now look like Donald Fagen and Walter Becker from Steely Dan. Forty years later, they’re releasing a new album on November 5th called “Voyage.” Two of th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk declines to address law after Gov. suggests he supports...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/02/texas-abortion-law-elon-musk-reacts-to-gov-greg-abbotts-comments.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk declined to directly weigh in on Texas' abortion law after Gov. Greg Abbott said the Tesla CEO supported his state's "social policies."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel now world's Covid hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9951117/Israel-worlds-Covid-hotspot-0-2-population-catching-yesterday.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country recorded 1,892 cases per million people on Wednesday - nearly 0.2 per cent of the entire population in a single day - stats compiled by an Oxford University research team show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHARK TANK' stars sued for fraud...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2021/09/02/shark-tank-stars-kevin-oleary-kevin-harrington-sued-for-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twenty hopeful entrepreneurs claim the famed business investors manipulated them into paying their companies and received no help in return.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Brady Gets Jab...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/09/02/tom-brady-vaccinated-bruce-arians-buccaneers-100-percent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buccaneers head coach Bruce Arians told the media on Thursday that 100 percent of the team's players, coaches, and staff have been vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular surfing instructor, Q, and an unspeakable horror...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/popular-surfing-instructor-qanon-unspeakable-120045161.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Barbara residents are struggling to make sense of a tragedy involving Matt Coleman, head of a local surf school, and the killings of his two young children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning into landslide...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/gavin-newsom-recall/article/Newsom-recall-poll-election-California-yes-Elder-16430710.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's Newsom's most favorable recall poll in a while.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vows 'whole-of-government' response...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/unconstitutional-chaos-biden-vows-whole-government-response-after-texas-abortion-n1278380</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden called the U.S. Supreme Court’s 5-4 ruling “an unprecedented assault on a woman’s constitutional rights under Roe v. Wade."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma Company Ready to Jab Dogs, Cats, Zoo Animals...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2021/09/01/although-covid-19-rare-in-cats-dogs-pharmaceutical-company-says-theyre-ready-with-a-vaccine-if-needed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If or when cats and dogs need COVID vaccine, Zoetis pharmaceutical company is ready to provide. At this time the virus is rare in pets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OK to Want to Exterminate People, Greece's New Health Minister Once Argued...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/7kv3za/its-ok-to-want-to-exterminate-people-greeces-new-health-minister-once-argued</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanos Plevris, the man in charge of Greece's pandemic response, has apologised if comments he made about Auschwitz while defending his own dad from Holocaust-denial offended any Jewish people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaxxer's family ridiculed after 'begging' for money...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/world/coronavirus/global/antivaxxers-family-slammed-for-begging-for-money/news-story/6cb5726f9c1a9d03158c92c238c36f57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The family of a Covid-19 conspiracy theorist who ultimately died of the virus has been ridiculed for “begging” for money and launching a fundraising page — with strangers accusing them of “stupidity” and urging potential donors not “to help pay for the funeral of someone who caused others to die”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Must Face Claim That Siri Violates Privacy, Judge Rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-09-02/apple-must-face-claim-that-siri-violates-privacy-judge-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A federal judge allowed a lawsuit against Apple Inc. to proceed with a claim that its Siri voice assistant violates users’ privacy, but he dismissed part of the complaint under California’s Unfair Competition Law.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving workplace spawns new jobs: Social scientist, remote work evangelist, digital anthropologist....</title>
      <link>https://metropolismag.com/viewpoints/think-lab-future-now/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metropolismag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A ThinkLab report finds that if we adapt as we go, the workplace could become a practical extension of our present conditions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Digital Currencies to Be Tested in Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/central-bank-digital-currencies-tested-040000941.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Bank for International Settlements will test the use of central bank digital currencies with Australia, Malaysia, Singapore and South Africa in an experiment that could lead to a more efficient global payments platform.Codenamed “Project Dunbar,” the study aims to develop prototypes for a common platform that will enable international settlement in digital fiat currencies issued by central banks, BIS said in a release Thursday. The system would allow direct transactions in cen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Store requires customers present pic of horse to purchase Ivermectin...</title>
      <link>https://www.ktnv.com/news/coronavirus/las-vegas-feed-store-sells-out-of-ivermectin-blames-customers-trying-to-treat-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ktnv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At V &amp; V Tack and Feed, they normally stock and sell ivermectin for use on horses. But right now, they're completely sold out of the horse dewormer, and store associate Shelly Smith suspects a lot of her customers aren't using it as intended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL brings back 'social justice' decals...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/32132328/nfl-brings-back-social-justice-helmet-decals-end-zone-stencils-part-inspire-change-platform</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players can wear social justice messages on their helmets again this season and "It Takes All of Us" and "End Racism" will be stenciled in end zones for the second straight year as part of the league's Inspire Change platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why human beings are obsessed with status...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/09/life-is-one-big-status-game/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The battle to be virtuous inspires endless political cruelty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets Turned Into Raging Rivers...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/photo-galleries/2021/09/02/ida-remnants-batter-tri-state-with-historic-rain-tornado-reports/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The once category 4 hurricane passed through New York City, dumping 3.15 inches of rain in the span of an hour at Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIPER VENOM SHOWS PROMISE?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazilian-viper-venom-may-become-173012111.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian researchers have found that a molecule in the venom of a type of snake inhibited coronavirus reproduction in monkey cells, a possible first step toward a drug to combat the virus causing COVID-19. A study published in the scientific journal Molecules this month found that the molecule produced by the jararacussu pit viper inhibited the virus's ability to multiply in monkey cells by 75%. "We were able to show this component of snake venom was able to inhibit a very important protein from the virus," said Rafael Guido, a University of Sao Paulo professor and an author of the study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ Readying GOOGLE Antitrust Lawsuit Over Ad Business...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-doj-readying-google-antitrust-204728728.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. antitrust officials are preparing a second monopoly lawsuit against Alphabet Inc.’s Google over the company’s digital advertising business, according to a person familiar with the matter, stepping up the government’s claims that Google is abusing its dominance.The Justice Department has accelerated its investigation of Google’s digital advertising practices and may file a lawsuit as soon as the end of the year, said the person, who declined to be named because the investigati</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than dozen deaths after Ida remnants slam Northeast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/northeast-us-new-york-new-jersey-weather-60327279197e14b9d17632ea0818f51c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The remnants of Hurricane Ida inundated large swaths of the northeastern U.S. with historic and unanticipated fury Wednesday night, killing at least 14 people in flooding in New York, New Jersey and Pennsylvania as basement apartments suddenly filled with water, rivers and creeks swelled to record levels and roadways turned into car-swallowing canals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China bans 'sissy men' from TV in new crackdown...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-entertainment-business-religion-china-62dda0fc98601dd5afa3aa555a901b3f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — China’s government banned effeminate men on TV and told broadcasters Thursday to promote “revolutionary culture,” broadening a campaign to tighten control over business and society and enforce official morality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel prepares to step down...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-fb1b1e7e87232054548e7ab5d6a7d8a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Angela Merkel will leave office as one of modern Germany's longest-serving leaders and a global diplomatic heavyweight, with a legacy defined by her management of a succession of crises that shook a fragile Europe rather than any grand visions for her own country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/crazy-footage-shows-tornado-passing-over-burlington-bristol-bridge-in-new-jersey</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Burlington-Bristol Bridge appears to have stood up to the test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT LEAST 15 DEAD...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3583837/toddler-and-eight-others-dead-in-hurricane-ida-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORRENTIAL downpours and tornadoes have battered northeastern USA claiming the lives of at least 18 people, including a two-year-old boy. The powerful remnants of Hurricane Ida sparked chaos across…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  TWISTERS IN NJ...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/01/video-shows-tornadoes-tear-through-new-jersey-penn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple tornados swirled through New Jersey, ripping apart and flattening homes amid furious downpours and flash floods from the remnants of Hurricane Ida.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM, FORD halt some production as chip crisis grows...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-ed8ff73b019ccf0836f9032f2b02291e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DETROIT (AP) — The global shortage of computer chips is getting worse, forcing automakers to temporarily close factories including those that build popular pickup trucks. General Motors announced Thursday that it would pause production at seven North American plants during the next two weeks, including two that make the company's top-selling Chevrolet Silverado pickup.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candace Owens Says Testing Facility Refused Her for 'Spreading Misinformation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/candace-owens-covid-test/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Candace Owens said Wednesday that a private facility in Colorado refused to test her for COVID for "spreading misinformation."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Harms of Masking Young Students Are Real...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/09/school-mask-mandates-downside/619952/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The educational cost of face coverings for young students is far better established than the benefits of mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red Warning Light on Branson's Space Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.newyorker.com/news/news-desk/the-red-warning-light-on-richard-bransons-space-flight</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newyorker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The F.A.A. is investigating the ship’s off-course descent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARING: 'Broke' Mohamed Hadid builds NEW $250M hilltop mansion in Beverly Hills...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9949529/Mohamed-Hadids-latest-250M-hilltop-mansion-Beverly-Hills-blasted-local-residents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mohamed Hadid, the father of supermodels Gigi and Bella Hadid, has started construction on a new Beverly Hills property overlooking Coldwater Canyon with an asking price of $250 million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs Now Run Haiti, Filling Vacuum Left by Years of Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/gangs-now-run-haiti-filling-a-vacuum-left-by-years-of-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gangs Now Run Haiti, Filling a Vacuum Left by Years of Collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man facing charges after escaping quarantine hotel in New Zealand...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/570511-man-facing-charges-after-escaping-quarantine-hotel-in-new</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Zealand authorities said Thursday that a man who tested positive for COVID-19 could face a fine or jail time after he escaped a quarantine hotel to return home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL returns social justice helmet decals, end zone stencils...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/sports-nfl-c10867c92924cc9a59c99e220c8ee84e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NFL players can wear social justice messages on their helmets again this season and “It Takes All of Us” and “End Racism” will be stenciled in end zones for the second straight year as part of the league’s Inspire Change platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Florida Hospital Full of Dying, Unvaxxed Thirtysomethings...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-a-miami-florida-hospital-full-of-dying-unvaccinated-30-somethings-dying-of-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I’ve never bagged so many thirtysomething-year-olds, leaving behind young kids, pregnant wives,” one nurse said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A popular surfing instructor, QANON, and an unspeakable horror...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2021-09-02/did-qanon-inspire-santa-barbara-surfer-to-kill-his-kids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Barbara residents are struggling to make sense of a tragedy involving Matt Coleman, head of a local surf school, and the killings of his two young children.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear Of Fidgeting: 1 In 3 Suffers From 'Hatred Of Movements' By Others...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/fear-fidgeting-hatred-of-movements/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Misokinesia is a strong negative emotional response to viewing someone else's small and repetitive movements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNNING IMAGES</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/stunning-images-emerge-of-catastrophic-and-deadly-flooding-in-nyc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight individuals are dead, including one two-year-old, as the metropolitan area of New York City was ravaged by record rainfall, tornadoes, and flash flooding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank Digital Currencies to Be Tested in BIS Experiment...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/central-bank-digital-currencies-to-be-tested-in-bis-experiment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants include Singapore, Australia, South Africa. Experiment may lead to new global digital payments platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number of people with dementia set to jump 40%...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/number-people-with-dementia-set-jump-40-78-mln-by-2030-who-2021-09-02/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 55 million people worldwide are living with dementia, a neurological disorder that robs them of their memory and costs the world $1.3 trillion a year, the World Health Organization (WHO) said on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 panel taps Cheney as vice chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/02/jan6-panel-liz-cheney-508715</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move is likely to ignite further divisions among House Republicans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of Thousands Still Without Power...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/09/01/1033471531/ida-new-orleans-power-entergy-louisiana</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some progress is being made three days after Ida made landfall, but the region's utility company, Entergy, faces a slew of obstacles in restoring power throughout the region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas abortion ban opens up 'Wild West' of enforcement, critics say...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210902105929-ykfuv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/ABORTION-ENFORCEMENT (ANALYSIS):ANALYSIS-Texas abortion ban opens up 'Wild West' of enforcement, critics say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana towns still crawling out from Ida destruction...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210902095955-d4829</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ (PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):Louisiana towns still crawling out from Ida's destruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST RAIN IN HOUR</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/flash-flood-emergency-new-jersey-flooding-york-city-hurricane-ida/10993344/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a historic night as the National Weather Service Office in New York City issued its first ever Flash Flood Emergency - and had to do so more than once.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort to recall Newsom struggling, new poll shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/the-effort-to-recall-gov-gavin-newsom-is-struggling-new-california-poll-shows/ar-AAO0fQm </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIN CRIPPLES CITY...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/02/at-least-seven-people-killed-overnight-in-nyc-in-historic-flooding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service issued its first ever flash flood warning for the city, and said 3.15 inches of rain fell on Central Park in an hour, from 8:51 pm to 9:51 pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swedish superstars ABBA set to unveil 'sensational' musical comeback...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/swedish-superstars-abba-set-unveil-022049733.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They famously vowed never to reform, to the disappointment of their legions of fans. But nearly four decades after disbanding, Swedish superstars ABBA were on Thursday expected to announce a "sensational comeback" collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OZ WORLD'S LONGEST LOCKDOWN!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9949223/Victorian-Covid-outbreak-explodes-176-new-cases-Dan-Andrews-reveals-roadmap-lockdown.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victoria's dramatic surge in Covid infections reached new heights with 176 new cases recorded just as Dan Andrews abandons eliminating the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulator sues crypto lending platform over $2 BILLION fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.macaubusiness.com/us-regulator-sues-crypto-lending-platform-over-2bn-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.macaubusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX district closes schools after  two teachers covid dead in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/texas-school-district-closes-for-week-after-two-teachers-die-of-covid-19/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It wasn't clear whether either was vaccinated. And a second Waco-area district closed for four days starting Friday due to a COVID surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rogan covid infected, taking deworming medicine...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/joe-rogan-has-covid-19-is-taking-unproven-deworming-medicine/ar-AANZUBj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Rogan, who said he is doing well as of Wednesday, has used his popular podcast to question vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperation grows; One million still without power...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desperation-grows-as-new-orleans-residents-struggle-to-recover-from-ida/ar-AANZgi2?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 985,000 electric customers across Louisiana woke up Wednesday in the dark again, with complete power restoration potentially weeks away. More than 768,000 of those outages were from Entergy, the state’s largest power provider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security director agrees to talk...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-organization-e2-80-99s-security-director-agrees-to-testify-to-grand-jury/ar-AAO06AF?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matthew Calamari Jr., 28, is the son of Donald Trump’s longtime bodyguard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Cubans land on Key West beach as attempts to reach USA climb...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/community/florida-keys/article253885358.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Border Patrol on Tuesday took 13 Cuban migrants into custody after the group landed on a Key West beach in a homemade boat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested in Hawaii after showing vaccination card with misspelling...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/illinois-woman-arrested-hawaii-showing-224600300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — A suburban Chicago woman was arrested in Hawaii last week after, court records show, she entered the state with a fake COVID-19 vaccination card that misspelled drug company “Moderna” as “Maderna.” Chloe Mrozak, 24, was arrested Aug. 28 at Inouye International Airport in Oahu and faces a misdemeanor charge of falsified vaccination documents, according to court records. The arrest was ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even voters who like Kamala Harris worry about her future...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/even-voters-kamala-harris-worry-140845277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamala Harris struggles in public opinion polls. Voters in Pennsylvania locales essential in the Democratic Party electoral map help explain why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrack UAE Influence Case 'Involves National Security'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/barrack-uae-influence-case-involves-national-security-us-says/ar-AANZNj8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The criminal case against Tom Barrack, the businessman accused of acting as an unregistered agent of the United Arab Emirates, involves national security information, according to a court filing on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Tax Hike Largest Since 1968...</title>
      <link>https://www.atr.org/biden-impose-largest-tax-increase-1968</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.atr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The $3.5 trillion tax hike being pushed by President Biden and congressional Democrats would be the largest tax increase since 1968.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;In nominal dollars, Biden’s $3.5 trillion tax increase would be the largest in history. But even when comparing this tax as a percentage of the economy, this tax hike would be the largest in more than 50 years.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;While Democrats claim this tax increase will fall on “the rich," the proposal will raise taxes on small businesses and working families.&amp;#13;&amp;#13;Some of the tax increases proposed by Biden and Democrats include:  &amp;#13;&amp;#13;1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One million still without power...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210901195713-8bgf4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STORM-IDA/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 5-One million without power as Ida leaves trail of destruction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>72 HOURS LATER:  Ida's devastation shocks as fuel shortages hinder recovery...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/evacuees-urged-not-return-home-after-devastation-storm-ida-2021-09-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storm damage from Ida astounded officials on Wednesday a full three days after the powerful hurricane pounded southern Louisiana, as reconnaissance flights revealed entire communities devastated by winds and floods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crews save town near Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/evacuees-anxiously-follow-course-california-fire-near-lake-tahoe-2021-09-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Lake Tahoe stood smoke-filled and largely deserted on Wednesday after crews fought back a huge wildfire, leaving the California resort town unscathed as the flames raged toward Nevada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish woman stoned near Hebron saved by Palestinians...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jewish-woman-stoned-near-hebron-saved-by-palestinians-678330</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Palestinians saved a Jewish woman who was hit in the head in a rock-throwing attack near Hebron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest claims demons sending staff threatening texts...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/priest-claims-evil-demons-figured-24889559 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Rossetti says demons have now worked out how to taunt their victims, families and any priests trying to carry out exorcisms to save them through text messages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA seeks gender neutral displays in large stores...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-california-3270657e85f4b7c4bee79138ba056a28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — California could soon force large department stores to display some child products in gender neutral terms after the state Legislature passed a bill on Wednesday aimed at getting rid of traditional pink and blue marketing schemes for items like toys and toothbrushes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New ambassador goes full wolf...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/09/01/china-new-ambassador-speech-508465</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qin Gang warns of “disastrous consequences” if the U.S. seeks to suppress China using a “Cold War playbook.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Rogan Infected, Taking Ivermectin...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7e89m/joe-rogan-covid-19-ivermectin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I feel great,” the host declared, unconvincingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists increasingly targeted at LA protests...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/sep/01/los-angeles-protest-journalists-attacked-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporters covering rightwing protests have been assaulted, robbed and sprayed with mace as victims say police fail to enforce the law</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Safety mode' to block accounts for harmful language...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/twitter-launches-safety-mode-block-accounts-harmful-language-rcna1863</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twitter will launch a safety feature that would allow users to temporarily block accounts for seven days for using harmful language or sending uninvited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOS: Tornado Tears Through Annapolis...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/09/01/tracking-ida-confirmed-tornado-in-anne-arundel-county-caught-on-camera/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple Twitter users possibly caught footage of the tornado, and it's frightening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOST parents no longer want kids in school full time...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/education/worried-about-covid-most-parents-no-longer-want-kids-school-n1278128</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You want them back in the building, but at the same time, you want them safe,” one parent said. “You want them healthy.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario to require vaccine certificates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-canada-health-ontario-coronavirus-pandemic-25f590df3bb6ba612988d50d7da668d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TORONTO (AP) — Ontario on Wednesday became the fourth Canadian province to announce residents will have to show proof of vaccination against COVID-19 to enter restaurants, theaters, gyms and other indoor public venues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
