<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'ELVIS' biopic wows CINEMACON with 'superhero' story, rap remix...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/elvis-biopic-wows-cinemacon-superhero-073237650.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Doja Cat song sampling "Hound Dog" is just one of many ways that director Baz Luhrmann hopes to bring "Elvis" into the 21st century with new biopic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China reports first human case of H3N8 bird flu...</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/east-asia/china-reports-first-human-case-of-h3n8-bird-flu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The H3N8 variant has previously been detected elsewhere in the world in animals, but no human cases have been reported. . Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid talk of WWIII, diplomacy losing steam...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amid-talk-of-world-war-iii-diplomacy-is-losing-steam/ar-AAWDy5S </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis fight with DISNEY helps him break fundraising records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-fight-with-disney-helped-him-break-fundraising-records/ar-AAWBJpX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive TWITTER accounts lose followers, conservatives gain?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220427-progressive-twitter-accounts-lose-followers-conservatives-gain</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key figures on the American left, Barack Obama among them, have shed thousands of followers since Elon Musk's planned purchase of Twitter emerged, while numbers have soared for right-wing politicians…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manchin eyes tax hike to 'combat inflation'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/manchin-and-schumer-discuss-new-tax-hike-deficit-cut-proposal-1.1757248</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Key holdout Senator Joe Manchin said Tuesday he discussed a tax increase and deficit reduction bill with Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer as a way to reduce soaring inflation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World faces biggest price shock in 50 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-61235528</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine is pushing up prices of commodities including food, cotton and energy, the World Bank says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Giants Duped Into Giving Up Data Used to Sexually Extort Minors...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/tech-giants-duped-giving-data-173424811.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Major technology companies have been duped into providing sensitive personal information about their customers in response to fraudulent legal requests, and the data has been used to harass and even sexually extort minors, according to four federal law enforcement officials and two industry investigators.Most Read from BloombergRussia to Cut Gas to Poland and Bulgaria, Making Energy a WeaponRussia Warns of Nuclear War Risk as Ukraine Talks Go OnUkraine Latest: Russia Says It Cut G</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Feared Republicans Put 'People in Jeopardy' After Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/26/mccarthy-feared-g-o-p-lawmakers-put-people-in-jeopardy-after-jan-6/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Representative Kevin McCarthy, the House Republican leader, feared in the aftermath of the Jan. 6 attack that several far-right members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump drawn to celebrity in weighing midterm picks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-entertainment-business-pennsylvania-ohio-5adc976efa97debf1613f3eb13fa0cfd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBUS, Ohio (AP) — Republicans hoping to emerge from crowded primaries this year stacked up on operatives with ties to former President Donald Trump , betting those connections would give them a leg up on landing critical endorsements that would help them win.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily blood pressure pills could be replaced by injection...</title>
      <link>https://www.thenationalnews.com/health/2022/04/26/twice-yearly-injection-could-replace-daily-tablets-to-treat-high-blood-pressure/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thenationalnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UK scientists are running a trial to see effectiveness of managing hypertension through new injection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youth voters not pleased by EITHER party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2022/04/25/youth-voters-not-pleased-by-either-party-according-to-harvard-poll/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This edition shows significant concern, relative to our previous polls, about the motivation of elected officials, a growing disdain for our political discourse, and young people are seriously que…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci eyeing exit?</title>
      <link>https://www.audacy.com/1010wins/news/local/interview-anthony-fauci-birx-resignation-pact-covid-19-pandemic-new-york</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.audacy.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Anthony Fauci wouldn’t comment Tuesday when asked by 1010 WINS if he had a resignation pact with other doctors in Donald Trump’s White House.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oz flaunts Trump endorsement in PA showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/politics/politicalnews/s-2668662?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARRISBURG, Pa. — Pennsylvania Republican U.S. Senate candidate Mehmet Oz debuted a new Trumpian confidence inspired by the former president's endorsement, as the five candidates tried to set themselves apart as the "most Pennsylvanian" candidate in Monday's debate for ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis fight with DISNEY helps him break fundraising records...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ron-desantis-fight-with-disney-helped-him-break-fundraising-records/ar-AAWBJpX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDIDATE CARLSON?  Tucker named keynote speaker at Iowa conference...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/tucker-carlson-to-speak-at-iowa-summit-raising-eyebrows-and-speculation-of-a-presidential-run/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ox New’s top-rated host Tucker Carlson will headline the 2022 FAMiLY Leadership Summit in Des Moines, Iowa this July, the group announced Tuesday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FREE SPEECH' RECORD SKETCHY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/elon-musk-and-free-speech-track-record-not-encouraging.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk's free speech advocacy seems to apply mostly to his own speech or that of his fans and promoters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implanting microchip in dogs, cats to become mandatory in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://newsinfo.inquirer.net/1588233/implanting-microchip-in-pet-dogs-cats-to-become-mandatory-in-june-in-japan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newsinfo.inquirer.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO -- Implanting a microchip in pet dogs and cats and registering the owner’s contact information will become mandatory in June under the revised Law on Welfare and Management of</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YANKEES stole signs; Fined by MLB...</title>
      <link>https://www.houstonchronicle.com/texas-sports-nation/astros/article/New-York-Yankees-sign-stealing-2015-2016-fine-17125599.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.houstonchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MLB letter offers few details into New York's use of replay room to relay signs and led...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUDIO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2022/04/26/us/politics/mccarthy-republican-lawmakers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New audio recordings reveal Kevin McCarthy worried that comments by his far-right colleagues could incite violence. He said he would try to rein in the lawmakers, but has instead defended them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meadows' texts reveal new details about key role of little-known GOP congressman...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/26/politics/mark-meadows-texts-scott-perry-key-role-overturn-election/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newly obtained text messages and recent court filings fill in significant gaps about the key role a little-known Pennsylvania Republican congressman played at almost every turn in scheming to reverse or delay certification of the 2020 election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARBY'S employee threw hot grease on drive-thru customer in Alabama...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/arby-s-employee-threw-hot-grease-on-drive-thru-customer-in-alabama-cops-say/ar-AAWCngR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS RATTLE WALL STREET</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/stocks-sink-inflation-recession-fears-184011387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell Tuesday as a steep decline in technology stocks deepened Wall Street’s losses after a brutal start to 2022. The Dow Jones Industrial Average was down more than 600 points shortly after 2 p.m. Tuesday, a decline of 1.8 percent. The Nasdaq composite was down 3 percent and the S&amp;P 500 index had fallen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top lawyer cries...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/26/twitters-top-lawyer-reassures-staff-cries-during-meeting-about-musk-takeover-00027931</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vijaya Gadde, a key executive involved in decisions to remove former President Donald Trump and ban political advertising, expressed uncertainty about the future of the platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA WIPES OUT $114 BILLION</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/jonathanponciano/2022/04/26/tesla-stock-plunge-wipes-out-114-billion-in-value-as-twitter-deal-sparks-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Tesla shareholders can’t be happy" about the Twitter deal potentially diverting Elon Musk's attention, one analyst says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takeover sets up clash with Europe regulations...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/elon-musks-twitter-takeover-sets-up-a-potential-clash-with-europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Elon Musk's $44 billion deal to buy Twitter, EU officials have a message for the eccentric tech billionaire: follow the rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRESH LOW FOR '22</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/25/stock-market-futures-open-to-close-news.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks fell sharply on Tuesday continuing a vicious April sell-off after a one-day breather, as investors dumped shares on fears of an economic slowdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION! RECESSION!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/3464102-stocks-stink-as-inflation-recession-fears-rattle-wall-street/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks fell Tuesday as a steep decline in technology stocks deepened Wall Street’s losses after a brutal start to 2022. The Dow Jones Industrial Average closed with a loss of 809 points Tuesday, fa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison Cawthorn implicated in potential insider crypto scheme, experts say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/madison-cawthorn-implicated-in-potential-insider-trading-scheme-experts-say/ar-AAWCFZN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absent Dem lawmaker will 'absolutely' still work as HAWAIIN AIRLINES pilot...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/absent-democratic-lawmaker-returns-washington-bad-headlines</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Hawaii Democrat who hasn't reported to work in Washington in months has returned to Congress following a string of bad headlines about his absences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian foreign minister warns 'do not underestimate threat of nuclear war'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/russian-minister-warns-dont-underestimate-26798300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NATO is already effectively at war with Russia, warns Russia’s foreign minister, Sergei Lavrov, adding that there was a 'real danger' the conflict could trigger a third world war</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusted YELP Reviewers Sell 'ELITE' Reviews for Cash...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/qjbqvd/buy-yelp-elite-reviews</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yelp “Elite” reviewers are verified members of the site who are supposed to be more trustworthy than ordinary users. Some of them are selling their reviews to businesses around the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese police build Covid CAGES around homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/chinese-police-build-cages-around-26805381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;People living in the Chinese city woke up to 2-metre tall fences outside - and they aren't allowed to leave their homes even if they don't have Covid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Critic Says Musk Bullied Him Off TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tech/lawrence-fossi-speaks-out-on-elon-musk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That Monday would have been an otherwise unremarkable day at the office for Lawrence Fossi, but for a phone call from an irate Elon Musk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fort Worth is first city in U.S. to mine bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/fort-worth-tx-the-first-city-in-the-us-to-mine-bitcoin.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Bitmain Antminer S9 mining rigs will run 24 hours a day, seven days a week, in the climate-controlled information technology wing of Fort Worth City Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stirs the pot...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/04/26/manchin-bipartisan-climate-package-00027811</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The West Virginia centrist is "just starting" to gauge cross-aisle consensus on climate — while his party waits for his buy-in on bigger plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to send tanks in U-turn...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/26/europe/germany-weapons-ukraine-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany has agreed to deliver anti-aircraft tanks to Ukraine, the German Defense Ministry announced on Tuesday, a move that underscores a major shift in its approach to providing military help to Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blasts reported in Moldova...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-monitoring-blasts-reported-in-moldova-breakaway-region-bordering-ukraine/ar-AAWC6A0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top general: Greatest security threat since WWII...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/russia-ukraine-war-news-04-26-22/h_1f99b9e529be98578452193be3c752df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The UN chief is heading to Moscow to meet Russian President Vladimir Putin on Tuesday, as heavy fighting continues in Ukraine. Follow here for live news updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58% of U.S. population has antibodies from previous infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/at-least-58percent-of-us-population-has-natural-antibodies-from-previous-covid-infection-cdc-says.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly 58% of people in the U.S. now have antibodies from previous Covid infection, demonstrating how widespread the virus was during the winter omicron surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARVARD pledges $100 million to atone for role in slavery...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/nation/harvard-pledges-100-million-to-atone-for-role-in-slavery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvard University is vowing to spend $100 million to research and atone for its ties with slavery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA CATCHES COVID; NO CLOSE CONTACT TO BIDEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5206738/vice-president-kamala-harris-tests-positive-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;VICE President Kamala Harris has tested positive for Covid-19 but was not in close contact with President Joe Biden. Harris’ press secretary confirmed the news on Tuesday, saying the vice pre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wimbledon won't have vax requirement, allowing Djokovic to defend title...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/wimbledon-covid-vaccine-novak-djokovic-6e008927-c08a-455a-ba3f-999b976b9658.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Djokovic has won 20 grand slams, including six at Wimbledon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices jump another 20%...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/home-prices-jumped-20percent-in-february-slowdown-may-be-coming-sp-case-shiller.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Home prices continued to surge higher in February, but rising mortgage rates may make that kind of growth unsustainable in the months ahead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiation Level At Chernobyl 'Abnormal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/radiation-level-at-chernobyl-abnormal-iaea-chief-01650976208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The level of radiation at the Chernobyl nuclear disaster site is "abnormal", rising after Russian forces took over the area, the UN atomic watchdog's chief said while visiting Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: These companies paid little to no taxes last year...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/these-companies-paid-little-to-no-taxes-last-year-185d94c0-6f77-47f7-bd7f-ff5e2a061c8d.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"These are huge profitable corporations, and they hardly pay any taxes."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebellion brews...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10754055/Elon-Musks-Twitter-revolution-Rebellious-staff-claim-new-boss-dangerous-democracy.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Staff bombarded the US social media site and internal message boards with attacks on the controversial tycoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The man with nine wives...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10754177/A-man-nine-wives-admits-hes-sex-rota-tough-felt-sex-scheduled.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arthur O Urso, from Brazil, tried to balance the needs of his nine 'wives' but when he created a rota, he said it made sex 'a schedule not pleasure', and that it's better to let things flow naturally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK Doesn't Know What It Does With Your Data, Or Where It Goes?</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akvmke/facebook-doesnt-know-what-it-does-with-your-data-or-where-it-goes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We do not have an adequate level of control and explainability over how our systems use data,” Facebook engineers say in leaked document.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here's what world's first floating city could look like...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/26/worlds-first-floating-city-prototype-busan-south-korea.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United Nations, floating city developer Oceanix and the Korean shipping city of Busan have revealed a prototype for the first floating city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ether prepares for epic 'merge' in quest to eclipse bitcoin...</title>
      <link>https://money.usnews.com/investing/news/articles/2022-04-26/cryptoverse-ether-prepares-for-epic-merge-in-quest-to-eclipse-bitcoin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;money.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE $21 BILLION MYSTERY</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/companies/news/elon-musk-s-21-billion-mystery-where-will-tesla-ceo-get-cash-for-twitter-11650930991208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elon Musk has just about $3 billion in cash and somewhat liquid assets, according to Bloomberg estimates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin's alleged mistress sanctions target...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/putin-e2-80-99s-alleged-mistress-is-possible-us-sanctions-target/ar-AAWBxfQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nixon's message to McCarthy: The truth always comes out...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/richard-nixon-e2-80-99s-message-to-kevin-mccarthy-the-truth-always-comes-out/ar-AAWBPOg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple electrocuted to death making art hyped on TIKTOK, officials say...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/couple-electrocuted-to-death-making-art-hyped-on-tiktok-officials-say/ar-AAWBRvN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger Erupts at Xi's 'Big White' Army of Lockdown Enforcers...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/anger-erupts-at-xis-big-white-army-of-lockdown-enforcers/ar-AAWBKJL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Jack come back?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2022-04-26/with-musk-in-charge-at-twitter-could-jack-come-back </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy comment on Trump pardon could be key for Jan. 6 panel...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/3463142-mccarthys-comment-on-trump-pardon-could-be-key-for-jan-6-panel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House committee investigating the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol is scrutinizing one particular phrase from House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy’s (R-Calif.) leaked calls with other top Republica…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong-un parades 'hypersonic missiles'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5202968/kim-jong-un-hypersonic-nukes-build-arsenal-fastest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Jong-un has showcased deadly hypersonic missiles that are feared to be able to strike US bases in MINUTES as he vowed to build North Korea’s nuclear arsenal at its “fastest paceR…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antisemitic Incidents, Assaults Hit All-Time Highs in NY, NJ...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/antisemitic-incidents-assaults-hit-all-time-highs-in-new-york-and-new-jersey-adl-says/3662954/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antisemitic incidents in the United States hit an all-time high in 2021, and New York and New Jersey accounted for nearly 30% of the reported total, the Anti-Defamation League said Tuesday. Incidents (vandalism, harassment, assault) were up sharply last year, the ADL said in its annual summary – a function of pandemic restrictions decreasing, but also backlash to Israeli airstrikes…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lockdowns Behind Hepatitis Surge in Children?</title>
      <link>https://www.aol.com/could-covid-lockdowns-behind-hepatitis-081352286.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.aol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There have been 111 serious cases of hepatitis among children since the start of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding obscured: The family office behind buyout...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/rpt-focus-funding-obscured-family-100000208.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The small family office that is managing the wealth of the world's richest person and is helping put together the largest-ever acquisition to be carried out by one person is shrouded in secrecy. On Monday, Musk clinched a deal to buy Twitter Inc for $44 billion in a seminal moment for one of the world's most influential public forums. Musk - who is also the chief executive of electric car maker Tesla Inc and aerospace company SpaceX - revealed in a regulatory filing last week that the social media company should reach out to its family office as a point of contact regarding his proposed acquisition.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
