<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Hockney unveils new painting to lift gloom...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8128821/David-Hockney-unveils-new-painting-lift-nations-gloom-amid-coronavirus-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Hockney, 82, often dubbed Britain's greatest living artist, has unveiled a new painting which features bright yellow daffodils in front of a gloomy grey mass.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governor says 60,000 homeless in state could get virus...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-governor-says-60-000-010314386.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's governor said on Wednesday that modeling done by experts has shown that more than 60,000 homeless people could become ill with COVID-19 in the state over the next eight weeks, badly straining the healthcare system. "Over the next eight-week period, we have modeled that of the 108,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas strip club to offer drive-thru peep shows...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/business/las-vegas-strip-club-to-offer-drive-thru-peep-shows-1985402/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Little Darlings strip club will begin offering drive-thru strip shows for those who want to indulge in some adult entertainment, but do not want to enter the building.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis loses control...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/florida-governor-refuses-shut-down-beaches-amid-spread-coronavirus-n1162226</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis said it's "not uniform throughout the state that you're seeing massive crowds at beaches," despite videos of gatherings in Tampa Bay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newark orders mandatory curfew...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/newark-sets-nightly-curfew-non-essential-shops-must-close</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Ras Baraka announced several measures as part of an effort to slow the spread of the novel coronavirus in the Garden State's largest city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK STAYS LIT:  VIRUS DOESN'T STOP PARTYING...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8125045/Spring-breakers-partying-St-Patricks-Day-South-Beach.html'</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In South Beach, Miami - the most popular part of Miami Beach where thousands flock to spend spring break - an 11pm curfew was introduced and crowds were limited to no more than 250 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket superheroes!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8119443/The-heroic-supermarket-shelf-stackers-facing-customer-chaos-panic-buying-VIOLENCE.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Supermarket staff that have been working hard to restock shelves of toilet paper, frozen food and dry pasta that have been left empty due to panic-buying have become the unsung heroes of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refuses to shut down beaches...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-florida-beaches-ignore-social-distancing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring breakers are ignoring social distancing guidelines and flocking to some popular beaches.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians brace for worst...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/wary-official-virus-claims-russians-brace-worst-193056029.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While President Vladimir Putin has reassured the public that the virus pandemic is under control, many Russians instinctively distrust the official claims and fear the true situation is much worse. In this case, Russia reacted quickly in late January as the virus epidemic raged in China, closing its</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUAKE SHAKES SALT LAKE CITY...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2e022e9abcd7f093ee9dc8758e8e0849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A moderate earthquake Wednesday near Salt Lake City temporarily shut down a major air traffic hub, damaged a spire atop a temple and frightened millions of people already on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No layoffs, reduced rent: 'Italian cure' for pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/no-layoffs-reduced-rent-italian-cure-pandemic-000215042.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Companies are barred from laying off workers and rents have been reduced under Italy's economic survival plan for life at the European epicentre of the coronavirus pandemic. Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte hailed his 25-billion-euro ($28-billion) programme as the "Italian model" that the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL:  BIGGEST CHALLENGE SINCE WWII</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/merkel-calls-coronavirus-biggest-challenge-since-ww2-183130387.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany is facing its biggest challenge "since the Second World War" in the fight against the coronavirus, Chancellor Angela Merkel said Wednesday, in what observers called a "final warning" for citizens to heed sweeping confinement measures. Although her 15 years in office have</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Bangladesh prayer gathering sparks outcry...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/massive-bangladesh-coronavirus-prayer-gathering-sparks-outcry-193538973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A massive coronavirus prayer session with tens of thousands of devotees sparked an outcry in Bangladesh Wednesday as the South Asian nation reported its first death from the global pandemic. Local police chief Tota Miah said some 10,000 Muslims gathered in an open field in Raipur town in southern Bangladesh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIV drug combo fails as treatment...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200318231107-sqloz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/TREATMENT:HIV drug combo fails as treatment for severe COVID-19 in China study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loud protests ring out in Brazil over Bolsonaro response...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200318230135-xexq3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BOLSONARO-PROTESTS (URGENT):Loud protests ring out in Brazil over Bolsonaro's coronavirus response</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive-thru test sites popping up slowly across America...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200318223430-5l4za</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/USA-DRIVETHRU (PIX):Drive-thru coronavirus test sites popping up slowly across America</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer, heart surgeries delayed as virus alters care...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c161afff751e36d0cac4b59760288eb5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some cancer surgeries are being delayed, many stent procedures for clogged arteries have been pushed back and infertility specialists were asked to postpone helping patients get pregnant. Doctors...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP INVOKES WARTIME AUTHORITY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bd6d92f70e73276c74502fc18e663ae7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Describing himself as a “wartime president” fighting an invisible enemy, President Donald Trump on Wednesday invoked rarely used emergency powers to marshal critical medical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel starts surveilling virus carriers, sends 'nearby' to isolation...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/health-ministry-begins-controversial-tracking-of-coronavirus-patients/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As controversial tracking starts, people who were in close contact with those confirmed to have COVID-19 are informed by text message they must home-quarantine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC mayor pushes for 'shelter-in-place' order as cases surge to 1,900...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/nyc-mayor-pushes-for-shelter-in-place-order-as-coronavirus-cases-surge-to-almost-1900.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;De Blasio, speaking to NY1 local television station, said he had a "very good conversation" with Cuomo about an hour ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC suggests nurses use bandanas, scarves...</title>
      <link>https://rollcall.com/2020/03/18/cdc-suggests-nurses-use-bandanas-scarves-during-face-mask-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC says that option should be used “as a last resort” when the hospital nearly depletes its supply and experiences a crush of COVID-19 patients.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People Put Christmas Lights Back Up As A Sign Of Hope...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/people-put-christmas-lights-back-up-as-sign-hope-amid-coronavirus-fears/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With so many people isolated inside their homes, some residents are putting their Christmas lights back up as a sign of hope amid coronavirus fears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYSE closes trading floor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/nyse-to-temporarily-close-trading-floor-move-to-electronic-trading-because-of-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The closure was in part as a result of positive coronavirus tests of two people, Stacey Cunningham, President of the NYSE, told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How women could be uniquely impacted...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/how-the-coronavirus-could-impact-women-in-health-care.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now, women in the U.S. hold 76% of health-care jobs, according to the U.S. Census Bureau. In nursing, where workers are on the front lines of patient interactions, women make up more than 85% of the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can it spread through the mail?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/coronavirus-can-it-spread-through-the-mail-package-delivery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some people worry letters and packages could worsen the outbreak — here's what the United States Postal Service says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas man ARRESTED for lying about testing positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8127039/Texas-man-ARRESTED-lied-social-media-post-testing-positive-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Lane Brandin, 23, was charged with a class A misdemeanor charge of false alarm or report Tuesday after he made the false claim on social media about a hospital in Texas on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship of fools: Spring breakers party on booze cruise despite pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/18/spring-breakers-grind-and-party-on-booze-cruise-despite-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spring break … forever? College kids are bucking advice to practice social distancing amid the coronavirus pandemic and instead are partying in tight quarters aboard booze cruises. A Facebook…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orange County Bans ALL Public, Private Gatherings -- Including Work...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/03/17/oc-health-officials-set-to-close-dine-in-restaurants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The order does not prohibit members of any household or living unit from gathering and will remain in place through March 31.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wealthy hoping to buy their own ventilators...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/18/business/ventilator-shortage-coronavirus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States and other countries face a critical shortage of the lifesaving machines — and no easy way to lift production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus Plan Anticipates 18-Month Pandemic, Widespread Shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/us-virus-plan-anticipates-18-month-pandemic-and-widespread-shortages/ar-BB11ktjA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for love in the time of coronavirus...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/18/health/dating-during-coronavirus-wellness-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that dating during coronavirus seems so risky, millions of singles must reckon with a dilemma as they seek love in the time of pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest offers drive-through confessional...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/18/priest-offers-drive-through-confessional-amid-coronavirus-outbreak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He’s offering forgiveness — to go! A Maryland priest is running a drive-through confessional to help parishioners repent hygienically as the coronavirus pandemic rages, according to a report W…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Nightmare: Drug Shortage on Horizon...</title>
      <link>https://nationalinterest.org/feature/next-coronavirus-nightmare-theres-drug-shortage-horizon-134147</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalinterest.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Scott Gottlieb, the former commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration, weighs in on how to tackle the coronavirus pandemic and what the future holds for those Americans who haven't been infected by the virus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT INVOKES WARTIME AUTHORITY</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2020/03/18/coronavirus-senate-vote-expected-house-sick-leave-testing-bill/5076063002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump said he was invoking the Defense Production Act, which allows the president to require businesses to fulfill orders needed for national defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM, FORD, CHRYSLER close all US factories...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/general-motors-ford-and-fiat-chrysler-to-close-all-us-factories-due-to-the-coronavirus-sources-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Big Three automakers plan to close all U.S. auto factories as the coronavirus sweeps across the country, people familiar with their plans told CNBC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL:  Biggest Challenge Since World War II...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2020-03-18/merkel-urges-solidarity-in-biggest-challenge-since-world-war-ii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Millennials at higher risk?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/18/millennials-may-be-at-a-higher-risk-for-catching-coronavirus-official-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top official on the White House coronavirus task force issued an ominous warning on Wednesday, declaring that more millennials in Italy and France had gotten sick than anticipated. “There a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BALTIMORE: Mayor Begs Residents To Stop Shooting So Hospitals Can Be Used For Coronavirus Patients...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/we-need-those-beds-baltimore-mayor-urges-people-to-put-down-guns-after-violence-continues-during-covid-19-pandemic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Mayor Jack Young urged residents to put down their guns and heed orders to stay home after multiple people were shot Tuesday night amidst the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$2,000 FOR EACH AMERICAN</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/White-House-coronavirus-plan-aims-to-send-2-000-15140061.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - White House officials are working with congressional Republicans on an emergency stimulus package that could send two $1,000 checks to many Americans and also devote $300 billion towards helping small businesses avoid mass layoffs, according to two senior administration officials.  No final decisions have been made and talks with Republican leaders remain fluid, but the growing scale of the $1 trillion rescue plan is coming into sharper focus.  The White House will still need backing from Democrats before any plan can be pushed into law, but many Democrats have said they would support sending cash payments to Americans who are struggling to pay bills because of the virus's economic impact. Still, multiple levels of negotiations remain.  The White House's evolving spending plan could be unprecedented in its size and velocity, dwarfing the stimulus bill passed during the Obama administration and the Troubled Asset Relief Program passed during the Bush administration. The current $1 trillion Trump plan would seek to spend $500 billion towards the cash payments to individual Americans, though some people wouldn't qualify if their income is over a certain level.  The White House discussions with Republicans would aim to spend another $50 billion to help rescue the airline industry and $150 billion to prop up other sectors, which could include hotels, among others. Some Democrats have raised concerns about how these funds might be used and have called for putting restrictions on firms that receive emergency assistance to assure that employees aren't laid off while executives pocket large bonuses.  One of the goals of the White House's decision to seek $300 billion for small businesses in the plan would be to help firms continue paying employees, as there has already been a wave of layoffs, particularly at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>103-year-old Iran woman survives infection...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20200318-103-year-old-iran-woman-survives-coronavirus-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;103-year-old Iran woman survives coronavirus: report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas prices could drop below $1 gallon...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/gas-prices-could-hit-99-cents-in-some-states-due-to-coronavirus-and-supplies-expert-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One gas analyst says the national average price could soon dip below $2 a gallon, with some stations potentially charging as little as 99 cents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks wipe out all gains under Trump's presidency... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/dow-wipes-out-gains-under-trumps-presidency-still-slightly-positive-since-his-election.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dow's drop pushed the index below the level where it closed on Jan. 19, 2017, the day before Trump took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERN OUT:  SANDERS QUITS RACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/555984/bernie-sanders-suspends-campaign-joe-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERNIE Sanders has “SUSPENDED” his campaign after latest defeat to Joe Biden on Super Tuesday III, reports say – but his camp say the claims are false. The radical Democratic Soci…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Entirely Natural Origins Through Evolution'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/coronavirus-origins-covid-19-wasnt-produced-in-a-lab-scientists-conclude/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A team of international research have concluded that the novel coronavirus has entirely natural origins through evolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELEGATE COUNT...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-primary-elections/delegate-count</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment websites crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/coronavirus-state-unemployment-websites-crash-applications-surge-n1162731</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Totally broken," tweeted one person about their area's unemployment website. Trump administration officials have warned unemployment could reach 20 percent due to the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mnuchin warns jobless rate could hit 20%...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/mnuchin-warns-virus-could-yield-20-25-jobless-rate-without-action/ar-BB11kulX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Orphaned monkey cradles dog after humans killed mom...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/heartwarming-video-captures-orphaned-monkey-21712482</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The monkey has been 'adopted' by the dog after its mother was reportedly killed by humans in Himachal Pradesh, northern India, who blamed the animal for destroying crops</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ibuprofen may worsen effects! </title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/HEALTH-SCIENCE/World-Health-Organization-backs-call-to-avoid-ibuprofen-for-coronavirus-621408</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement supported a recent statement by the French health minister that ibuprofen may worsen the effects of Covid-19 and should be avoided.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis not allowed to leave homes...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Israelis-with-coronavirus-Health-Ministry-reports-304-patients-621258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Health Ministry reported 90 new patients on Wednesday morning from the 337 that were diagnosed with COVID-19 at press time the day before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists: Coronavirus NOT a bioweapon...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldscotland.com/news/18314818.coronavirus-not-bioweapon-created-lab-scientists-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldscotland.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research involving Edinburgh University academics dispels myths about the origins of Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,000 bed floating hospital to be deployed in NY harbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/floating-hospital-to-be-set-up-in-new-york-harbor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is going to deploy a Navy hospital ship for New York to use to treat coronavirus victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California considering martial law...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/california-preparing-for-worst-case-scenarios-martial-law-a-possibility</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Newsom also acknowledged much is unknown and so the state is preparing for frightening worst-case scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philly police delay arrests for crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox29.com/news/philadelphia-police-to-delay-arrests-for-certain-non-violent-crimes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox29.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philadelphia Police Commissioner Danielle Outlaw stressed Wednesday that the temporary policy does not mean the department is turning a blind eye to crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London shutting down...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/britain-braced-coronavirus-lockdown-london-21714296</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It comes as the Government prepares to close schools and restrict all but essential travel after realising their initial plan could have left 250,000 dead</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biohackers team up online to help develop coronavirus solutions...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/18/biohacking-online-forums-coronavirus-vaccines-testing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Students, scientists, developers and health professionals use forums to investigate potential vaccines and methods of testing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POWER OUTAGES, DAMAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2020/03/18/earthquake-hits-utahs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A magnitude 5.7 earthquake hit the Wasatch Front shortly after 7 a.m., shaking homes from Logan down to Utah County. It was the state’s largest earthquake since 1992.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunned world grapples with 'once-in-100-year' battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus/stunned-world-grapples-with-once-in-100-year-coronavirus-battle-idUSKBN21522O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hundreds of millions of people worldwide were adjusting on Wednesday to once-in-...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy will rush 10,000 student doctors into service, scrapping final exams...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-italy/italy-rushes-new-doctors-into-service-as-coronavirus-deaths-rise-above-2500-idUSKBN214245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Italy will rush 10,000 student doctors into service, scrapping their final exams...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreadful choice for global leaders: Wreck economy or lose millions of lives...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/story/2020-03-18/coronavirus-poses-dreadful-choice-for-global-leaders-wreck-your-economy-or-lose-millions-of-lives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After initially hesitating, most global leaders have decided they have no choice but to take the economic pain. In both directions, the costs are enormous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC LEADERS BATTLE OVER 'SHELTER IN PLACE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/cuomo-says-he-wont-approve-coronavirus-shelter-in-place-order-for-new-york-city.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cuomo said that such drastic policies would create more fear amid the COVID-19 outbreak, which has now infected more than 6,500 people across the U.S. and killed at least 115, according to Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NC police: Man shot to death -- inside ambulance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a99b0ae730773cd96ac6b8f9f1f479d4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — A suspect in North Carolina fatally shot a man while the victim was being treated inside an ambulance on Wednesday, police said. Charlotte-Mecklenburg officers were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get out of jail? Inmates argue for release...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/076cd5c4900c021ffddcc53b2a06f2af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Coronavirus has become a “get out of jail" card for hundreds of low-level inmates across the country, and even hard-timers are seeking their freedom with the argument that it's not...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising Porn Actor Accused of Abuse and Harassment: 'He Put Me in Suitcase'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/rising-porn-star-tommy-wood-accused-of-abuse-by-adult-actress-heather-vahn-who-says-he-put-me-in-a-suitcase</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The adult actress Heather Vahn opens up about the emotional and physical abuse she allegedly suffered at the hands of fellow porn actor Tommy Wood. And she’s not the only one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE WORLD BEFORE AND AFTER LOCKDOWN...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8126057/Pictures-public-spaces-emptied-countries-battle-contain-COVID-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A series of photographs taken in recent days from Libya to Singapore show deserted streets after governments across the world shut down borders to contain the deadly coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm will dump snow across USA on first day of spring...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/03/18/weather/spring-winter-storm-forecast/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A coast-to-coast storm with blizzard conditions, severe storms and flooding rains will barrel across the US Wednesday through Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA CLOSES BORDER WITH CANADA</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/18/trump-says-the-us-will-close-the-border-with-canada-to-non-essential-traffic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump on Wednesday said the United States would temporarily close its border with Canada to "non-essential traffic" due to the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCKS DIVE</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/17/stock-futures-fall-slightly-after-market-rebounds-on-hopes-for-1-trillion-stimulus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A violent reversal in bond yields was the latest move in the financial markets to unnerve investors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP...</title>
      <link>https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/uu60363602/executive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;earthquake.usgs.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARGEST SINCE 1992...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/57-magnitude-earthquake-strikes-salt-lake-city/story?id=69662609</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 5.7-magnitude earthquake struck just outside Salt Lake City, Utah, early Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRADY A BUC!</title>
      <link>http://www.nfl.com/news/story/0ap3000001106744/article/tom-brady-finalizes-agreement-to-join-buccaneers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New England Patriots quarterback Tom Brady has finalized an agreement to join the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, a source tells NFL Network Insider Ian Rapoport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel first ever TV address as infections soar in Germany...</title>
      <link>https://www.thelocal.de/20200318/merkel-set-to-give-first-tv-address-on-coronavirus-crisis-in-germany</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thelocal.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals straining. Big wave coming could break them...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-18/hospitals-are-straining-under-the-coronavirus-the-big-wave-coming-could-break-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the next two weeks, California will likely see a wave of serious coronavirus cases. That doesn't mean mitigation is failing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Human biosecurity emergency' declared in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/public-global-health/488178-human-biosecurity-emergency-declared-in-australia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “human biosecurity emergency” was declared on Wednesday in Australia and its prime minister urged citizens to refrain from traveling abroad for the next six months amid concerns that the coronavirus outbreak could exponentially wo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outbreak Hits NYPD...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/03/18/coronavirus-nypd-officer-tests-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police sources tell CBS2 at least one officer at the 1st Precinct has tested positive and more than two dozen others are out sick, many feeling symptoms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As world cowers, China glimpses coronavirus aftermath...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-cowers-china-glimpses-coronavirus-aftermath-074822309.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restaurants are reopening, traffic and factories are stirring, and in one of the clearest signs yet that China is awakening from its coronavirus coma, the country's "dancing aunties" are once again gathering in parks and squares. As the rest of the world runs for cover, China -- where</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Mexico, a cartel is taking over: Jalisco New Generation...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/mexico-cartel-taking-over-jalisco-050217156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico’s fastest-rising cartel, the Jalisco New Generation gang, has a reputation for ruthlessness and violence unlike any since the fall of the old Zetas cartel. In parts of the country it is fighting medieval-style battles, complete with fortified redoubts, to expand nationwide, from the outskirts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concerns rise for Florida's 'snowbirds'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-concerns-rise-floridas-snowbirds-020723509.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida, often called "the grayest state" in the US because so many elderly retire here, is facing up to the fact that it has an alarming concentration of the demographic most at-risk from coronavirus. "Everything is an uncertainty because we don't know how this is going to end, you</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanders to 'assess his campaign' after another round of bruising losses...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200318114835-pd5yz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/SANDERS (URGENT):Sanders to 'assess his campaign' after another round of bruising losses-statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rio's Christ the Redeemer statue closes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5ed1eee060942096c37238a2d4e4d19e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO (AP) — Rio de Janeiro’s Christ the Redeemer statue, which appears to balance improbably atop Corcovado mountain, has withstood the worst of what the elements could muster for nearly...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AP PHOTOS: Virus redefines respecting personal space...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/31eb77772a9904e6c141dac15c5696ae</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROME (AP) — Social distancing could qualify as an oxymoron in Italy, where walking arm-in-arm with friends, kissing neighbors in greeting and patting the heads of babies are part of the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American attitudes make virus response hard sell...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f800f38611f3fe95a309d607a24023a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Americans are summoned to deal with an attack or defy overwhelming odds, the response typically goes something like this: Fight. Hold the line. Stand together. This won’t stop us. Keep on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello from Italy. Your future grimmer than think...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Hello-from-Italy-Your-future-is-grimmer-than-you-15138082.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;My family lives in the Veneto, in Northern Italy, one of the regions worst-hit by the coronavirus. We are on lockdown. It's scary. It's lonely. It's uncomfortable. And did I mention scary?  I'll spare you the statistics and the sermons; both are already abundant. But I do want to make one thing clear: If you think that by stocking up your pantries you have absolved yourself from the responsibility of preparing for this virus, you are mistaken. This is a crisis like none before. Be skeptical of both naysayers and doomsayers; there's no way of knowing how this will end.  The restrictions came upon us slowly but steadily. Within two weeks, our old lives were gone. First the schools closed, then came social distancing. Then the government locked down the hardest-hit areas: no more going in and out of certain provinces; limited movements within the "red zones." Then the whole country shut down. Most stores closed their doors. People who could were asked to telework; those who could not, and did not have a job related to the continuation of essential services, were placed on part-time schedules or on unpaid leave. When we went out, we had to carry a pass explaining our reasons for being outside to show to the law enforcement officers patrolling the streets. The priority became keeping everyone inside, at all times.  For some people, the gradual rollout made these measures hard to accept: Skeptical observers questioned the seriousness of the disease, given that the restrictions were not draconian from the start. And yet without time to adjust to a progressive loss of freedom, we wouldn't have accepted it. We might have rebelled. Instead, we rallied, coming together as one - protecting one another's health, even as we could no longer socialize.  Living under these conditions is difficult to describe. We can leave the house only...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Our Children Will Starve'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/-our-children-will-starve-say-pakistan-farmers-as-locusts-breed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three swarms of locusts this year have destroyed crops on in the mountains of Pakistanâ€™s vast and arid Balochistan province.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there right to anonymity for carriers in America?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/civil-rights/488172-is-there-a-right-to-anonymity-for-coronavirus-carriers-in-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is time to examine medical privacy and public safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could Trump delay November election?</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/could-trump-delay-november-election-234714948.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The November election date is set by law, and the president can't postpone it or extend his term. But there are a lot of other questions about conducting an election in the midst of a pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French army flies patients to military hospital...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200318090958-zq5ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-ARMY (URGENT):French army flies coronavirus patients to military hospital</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First dog to catch bug dies after released from quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/health-environment/article/3075650/first-dog-found-coronavirus-has-died-after</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 17-year-old Pomeranian, which belonged to a now-recovered Covid-19 patient, had been under mandatory quarantine at a government facility since February 26, and returned home last Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists 'prove Darwin's survival of the fittest theory'...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-03-18/scientists-prove-darwins-survival-of-the-fittest-theory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACKING BRACELETS, INVISIBLE TATTOOS TO MONITOR?</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/covid-19-tracking-bracelets-invisible-tattoos-to-monitor-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Globalists like Bill Gates pushing Black Mirror-type tech on the masses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm a Doctor in Britain. We're Heading Into Abyss...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/18/im-a-doctor-in-britain-were-heading-into-the-abyss/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON — Ten days ago, I was asked to see a patient. I’m a respiratory specialist in an intensive-care unit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs Just Starting, and Forecasts Bleak...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/17/layoffs-are-just-starting-and-the-forecasts-are-bleak/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angela Gervasi was enjoying a day off on Thursday when she got a text from a co-worker: “Have you heard?”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom, daughter sold body parts from funeral home...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/national/article241289576.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
