<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Germany Sticks With Putin for 'Essential' Energy...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.eu/article/germany-putin-oil-gas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.eu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chancellor Olaf Scholz brushes off pressure from Ukraine and the US to stop pouring money into the Kremlin’s war coffers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials engage with Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/world/americas/venezuela/article259151443.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s opposition was caught off guard and angered as details emerged of a meeting between Biden and Maduro officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL suspends star for betting on games...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33446869/nfl-suspends-atlanta-falcons-wr-calvin-ridley-least-2022-season-betting-games</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL has suspended wide receiver Calvin Ridley for at least the 2022 season for betting on NFL games during the 2021 season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huge Cocaine Lab Found Inside World Heritage Site...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/z3n8zy/bolivia-world-heritage-site-cocaine-lab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The authorities have found drug labs in the Noel Kempff Mercado National Park before, and many more could still be operating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In S Korea, 'Squid Game Election' campaign gets ugly...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2022/03/07/1084874629/in-south-korea-the-squid-game-election-campaign-gets-ugly</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Negative campaigns are aggravating South Korea's already severe political divide as presidential elections approach on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside private company surveilling immigrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/07/us-immigration-surveillance-ice-bi-isap</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BI claims it provides immigrant tracking and ‘quality’ case management. A Guardian investigation paints a very different picture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fremont, CA Tops List Of 'Happiest Cities'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/money-americas-happiest-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The WalletHub study of the country's 182 largest cities finds Fremont, California tops the list as the happiest place in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winning the propaganda war...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/off-duty/military-culture/2022/03/03/how-ukraine-is-winning-the-propaganda-war/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Outside boots on the ground, this war is a battle for the world's hearts and minds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Love child' closes socials after wave of extreme trolling...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10586395/Putins-love-child-18-closes-social-media-wave-extreme-trolling.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since Putin ordered the invasion, Luiza Rozova, a student in St Petersburg, had been deluged with hostile posts from people angry at the Russian president's brutal actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Churchill? Zelensky praised as war communicator...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-volodymyr-zelenskyy-entertainment-media-social-media-896ac1afc240fdf349c0d4c96d5e2afc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To a watching world, his message is this, in both his words and his resolute, sometimes haggard appearance: He stands as a mirror to the suffering and spirit of his people. It appears to be getting through.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL becomes first state to recommend AGAINST vaccinating children...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-10586973/Florida-recommend-against-COVID-vaccines-healthy-kids.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Surgeon General Dr. Joseph Ladapo said Monday that the state will formally recommend against COVID-19 vaccinations for 'healthy; children, the first state to do such a move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S, COCA-COLA boycott calls grow...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-60649214</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Food and drink giants have been criticised on social media for failing to speak out on Ukraine's invasion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly discovered brain cells may be memory filing system...</title>
      <link>https://www.statnews.com/2022/03/07/newly-discovered-brain-cells-may-be-memory-filing-system-study-suggests/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.statnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists in a federally funded BRAIN Initiative consortium monitored electrical activity in patients' brains to find new groups of neurons involved in the creation of memories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Nearly 100%' of pre-staged combat power now moved in...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/europe/live-news/ukraine-russia-putin-news-03-07-22/h_2382a0569210f658ffb89bd569d5f7e4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukraine and Russia will hold a third round of talks Monday, according to negotiators as from on the ground in Ukraine as Ukrainian civilians are trapped in the cities of Mariupol, Volnovakha and Kyiv after evacuation efforts failed. Follow here for live news updates from on the ground in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controversial rock art may depict extinct giants of ice age...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/07/americas/rock-art-colombia-scn/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  AMAZON continues using Chinese suppliers linked to forced labor...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/tech/tech-news/amazon-suppliers-linked-forced-labor-china-watchdog-group-says-rcna16452</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company’s supplier list includes firms accused of using Uyghur laborers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN PLANS TRIP TO SAUDI ARABIA</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/biden-saudi-trip-oil-b7a91070-8045-4155-9120-a35d59fd7603.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A hat-in-hand trip would illustrate the gravity of the global energy crisis driven by Russia's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gas Nears All-Time High...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-inflation-set-heat-further-173411886.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's invasion of Ukraine has dashed any hope U.S. consumers might have had for relief from sky-rocketing costs, with prices at the gas pump in the last week surging by the most in nearly 17 years and prices for other goods like food ready to march higher as well. Even before the invasion, the latest U.S. monthly inflation report, due on Thursday, was set to show prices rising at their fastest in 40 years. The data, which is for February, will likely show only a preliminary impact from the surge in U.S. oil prices, which hit $130 a barrel on Monday, but the spike is seen driving overall inflation higher in the months to come.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETS: Oil $200 a Barrel This Month...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/oil-traders-betting-prices-may-051731959.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Traders piled into options that oil could surge even further after rising to the highest since 2008, with some even placing low-cost bets that futures surpass $200 before the end of March.Most Read from BloombergStakes Rise as Putin Says His War in Ukraine Will ContinueUkraine Update: U.S. May Go Alone on Russia Oil Ban; Crude SoarsPutin’s Ruble Workaround Still Leaves Bond Payments in DoubtUkraine Update: U.K. Premier Says More Pressure Needed on PutinOil Jumps Near $123 as Chanc</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY Silence on Florida 'Don't Say Gay'...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/diseny-dont-say-gay-bill-florida-bob-chapek-lgbtq-ron-desantis-1234972655/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facing rising outcry, Disney CEO Bob Chapek has decided to play a political and cultural version of a church mouse when it comes to Florida’s new ‘Don’t Say Gay’ bill. With the openly discrimatory …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Kyiv's Middle-Class Suburbs, People Are Trapped and Desperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/in-kyiv-e2-80-99s-middle-class-suburbs-desperate-people-are-trapped/ar-AAUJlKf?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny radio station broadcasting propaganda in DC...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-tiny-radio-station-broadcasting-russian-propaganda-in-d-c/ar-AAUJktB?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlad Has Already Lost the Digital War....</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2022/03/putin-lost-cyber-and-information-war-abroad-will-he-lose-home/362794/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its diplomatic efforts in tatters, its agencies beset by cyber vigilantes, the Russian government is still choking off the information that fuels its homegrown protest movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Can Shrink Brain as Much as Decade of Aging, Study Finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2644036?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even a mild case of COVID-19 can damage the brain and addle thinking, scientists found in a study that highlights the illness’s alarming impact on mental function.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists identify new gene differences in severe patients...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/scientists-identify-gene-differences-severe-160624182.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have pinpointed 16 new genetic variants in people who developed severe COVID-19 in a large study published on Monday that could help researchers develop treatments for very sick patients. The results suggest that people with severe COVID have genes that predispose them to one of two problems: failure to limit the ability of the virus to make copies of itself, or excessive inflammation and blood clotting. "It is potentially possible in future that we will be able to make predictions about patients based on their genome at the point of presenting (for) critical care," said Kenneth Baillie, consultant in critical care medicine at the University of Edinburgh and one of the study authors, told reporters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may act alone to ban Russian oil imports...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-prepared-move-alone-banning-155638109.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration is willing to move ahead with a ban on Russian oil imports into the United States without the participation of allies in Europe, two people familiar with the matter told Reuters, after Russia's invasion of Ukraine. President Joe Biden is expected to hold a video conference call with the leaders of France, Germany and the United Kingdom on Monday as his administration continues to seek their support for a ban on the imports. Germany is accelerating its plans to expand its use of alternative energy sources but cannot halt imports of Russian energy overnight, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz said on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Maps shows Putin's secret mansion worth $1 BILLION...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putins-alleged-secret-palace-26404333</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President of Russia Vladimir Putin is alleged to have a £1 billion mansion on the Black Sea. He denies the claims and the Kremlin insists it is merely a business venture by wealthy Russians</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns of 'global collapse' over West sending weapons to Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-russia-chilling-warning-sending-26405640</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Earlier today Vladimir Putin demanded Ukraine must distance itself from NATO, lay down its arms and recognise Russia's claims to Crimea, and to acknowledge that Donetsk and Lugansk are independent states before war can end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gold crosses $2,000; Nears Historic Highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/07/gold-markets-palladium-russia-ukraine-crisis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gold prices briefly scale the $2,000 level for the first time in 1-1/2 years as investors rushed to safety in the wake of an escalating Russia-Ukraine crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron keeps an open line to Putin...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-vladimir-putin-business-europe-moscow-912c39b11b42be00c88aff8740c9aae8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NICE, France (AP) — While most of the world is shunning President Vladimir Putin over Russia's invasion of Ukraine , one of the few leaders keeping an open line of communication is French President Emmanuel Macron.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll surpasses 6 million for pandemic now in 3rd year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-science-business-health-lifestyle-9cd511bc84955131ba00846716e02647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BANGKOK (AP) — The official global death toll from COVID-19 eclipsed 6 million on Monday — underscoring that the pandemic, now entering its third year, is far from over. The milestone, recorded by Johns Hopkins University, is the latest tragic reminder of the unrelenting nature of the pandemic even as people are shedding masks, travel is resuming and businesses are reopening around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ackman says WWIII already started...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/07/russia-ukraine-bill-ackman-says-world-war-iii-likely-already-started.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire hedge fund managerÂ BillÂ Ackman has warned that World War III has "likely started already" amid Russia's ongoing attack on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX man could become first Capitol rioter convicted by jury as trial ends...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/mar/07/first-capitol-rioter-faces-possible-convictions-from-jury</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department of Justice lawyers make closing arguments against Guy Reffitt, first of 750 people charged with joining riot to face trial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How far-right militia groups found foothold in deep-blue California...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/How-far-right-militia-groups-found-a-foothold-in-16983102.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;REDDING, Calif. - The far right is rising in the ranchland of Northern California, using...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Russia Hacks U.S. Satellite, Then What?</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/emerging-tech/2022/03/if-russia-hacks-us-satellite-then-what/362761/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Russian official warned that impacting their satellites would be considered a declaration of war, but the U.S. stance is more circumspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany Signals Opposition to Cutting 'Essential' Russian Energy...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/germany-signals-opposition-to-cutting-essential-russian-energy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNING: Sending weapons to Ukraine will lead to 'global collapse'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/sending-weapons-ukraine-will-lead-global-collapse-ifx-cites-russian-foreign-2022-03-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sending foreign weapons to Ukraine will lead to a "global collapse," Interfax news agency cited the Russian foreign ministry as saying on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Show us mercy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10585541/Ukraine-war-Russian-POW-begs-mercy-invading-forces.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prisoner, who said he is a lieutenant-colonel in the Russian national guard, begged the rest of Moscow's forces to call off the invasion and turn back 'before it is too late', adding 'we cannot win'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life after death: How Notorious B.I.G. lives on 25 years after murder...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/07/how-the-notorious-b-i-g-lives-on-25-years-after-his-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“It was all a dream/I used to read Word Up! magazine,” famously rapped the Notorious B.I.G. on his 1994 breakout hit “Juicy.” And three years later, he was living the dream …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captured officer apologizes for 'genocide'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/03/07/captured-russian-officer-apologizes-to-ukraine-for-genocide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National Guard Lt. Col. Astakhov Dmitry Mikhailovich said that he had been told they were being sent to help Ukraine because it was “dominated by a fascist regime.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rural Idaho town part of trend: Conservatives seeking space...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-lifestyle-idaho-sandpoint-ade4fb13d865eb9f9b4dce6c4d944309</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SANDPOINT, Idaho (AP) — Linda Navarre moved to Sandpoint, Idaho, from Cleveland in 1978, when the town consisted of people in the timber industry and hippies “and they all got along.” Now she barely recognizes the small resort community near the Canadian border that is quickly growing as people disenchanted with big city life move there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyiv decries 'immoral' stunt after Moscow says will allow evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/markets/asia/top-wrap-1-ukrainians-trapped-besieged-city-fighting-blocks-evacuation-efforts-2022-03-07/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia announced new "humanitarian corridors" on Monday to transport Ukrainians trapped under its bombardment - to Russia itself and its ally Belarus, a move immediately denounced by Kyiv as an immoral stunt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian rouble hits new record low...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/russia-markets/russian-rouble-hits-new-record-low-in-thin-offshore-trade-idUSKBN2L40OG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia's rouble tumbled to a fresh record low in thin offshore trade on Monday, with local markets closed for trading until at least Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Prince's $500 Billion 'Neom' Megaproject Woos Wall St...</title>
      <link>https://financialpost.com/pmn/business-pmn/saudi-princes-500-billion-neom-megaproject-woos-wall-street</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;financialpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panicked Crackdown at Home Shows He's on Way Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/vladimir-putins-panicked-panicked-crackdown-in-russia-shows-hes-on-the-way-out?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If history is any indication, Vladimir Putin already has one foot in his political grave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Warns USA Against Forming Pacific NATO and Backing Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/china-affirms-russia-ties-accuses-u-s-of-building-pacific-nato/ar-AAUIAGa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine 'decimating' Russian forces...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/ukraine-decimating-russian-forces-putins-26402315</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin's invasion of Ukraine "is not going well" with Russian troops "suffering" and not guaranteed to be victorious, one of the UK's top admirals has claimed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rents Roaring Back in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/07/rents-are-roaring-back-in-new-york-city/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gabbie Fried, an actor and comedy writer, had lived in New York City for 10 years and had never been</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New iron curtain descending across Russia internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Key-U-S-provider-of-internet-to-Russia-is-16977605.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advocates of an open, globally connected internet long have worried that a major country...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$7 in LA?</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/los-angeles-gas-prices-mid-city-olympic-boulevard/11625538/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The average price of a gallon of self-serve regular gasoline in L.A. County rose to $5.247 on Saturday, but some gas stations in the area have even higher prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo rips 'cancel culture,' hints at political comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/06/cuomo-rips-cancel-culture-hints-at-a-political-comeback.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just six months after he resigned in disgrace over sex harassment allegations, former New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo appeared to be hinting at a political comeback.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL BOUNCE FOR JOE:  47% APPROVAL...</title>
      <link>https://maristpoll.marist.edu/polls/npr-pbs-newshour-marist-national-poll-bounce-for-biden-following-state-of-the-union-march-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;maristpoll.marist.edu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  AMAZON worker trapped in warehouse by robots...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/tech/4836302/amazon-warehouse-worker-trapped-robot-shelves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN Amazon employee apparently became trapped by robot shelves when he was working on the warehouse floor. The employee shared the experience on TikTok under the username Robotman77 and the video ha…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man kills self after getting addicted to energy drinks...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4836140/energy-drinks-addiction-crippling/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHEN his marriage broke down after just three months, Justin Bartholomew turned to energy drinks. Battling depression, the 25-year-old relied on the caffeine hit they gave him to get through the da…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Navy is training for a possible fight with China. Does Russias war make that more likely?</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/branches/navy/2022-03-06/navy-training-for-possible-fight-with-china-does-russia-war-make-that-more-likely-5247470.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;National security experts cautioned against drawing too broad an association based on Cold War comparisons and the “unlimited” partnership that China and Russia announced upon the start of the Beijing Winter Olympics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia hits Ukraine from air, land and sea as civilians try to flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/breaking-news/putin-threatens-ukraine-statehood-as-moscow-sanctions-tighten/news-story/d6cd97a69bc7597a9fbaa2632459da52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian forces pummelled Ukrainian cities from the air, land and sea on Monday, with warnings they were preparing for an assault on the capital Kyiv, as terrified civilians failed for a second day to escape besieged Mariupol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANTIWAR PROTESTS JOLT MOSCOW</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/more-than-4500-anti-war-protesters-arrested-in-one-day-in-russia-group-says/ar-AAUHIgu?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TIKTOK's sickening rise in animal abuse videos...</title>
      <link> https://www.the-sun.com/news/4836438/tiktok-animal-abuse-videos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WITHIN seconds, a clip of a woman stroking a cat to the beat of Queen classic Bohemian Rhapsody went from a touching moment to apparent abuse. The individual, who The Sun has chosen not to name, ag…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working with Poland to send jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/03/05/white-house-deal-fighter-jets-ukraine-00014424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Poland wants to donate its old MiGs to Ukraine. But there’s a catch — it needs U.S. jets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel steps up...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/international/article-700429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel now is a serious world player, with that, however, comes serious responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OIL WARS 2022...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/06/us-crude-oil-jumps-to-125-a-barrel-a-13-year-high-on-possible-western-ban-of-russian-oil.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. oil surged on Sunday evening as the market continued to weigh supply disruptions from Russia in its ongoing war with Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVACUEES BOMBED...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2022/mar/06/russia-ukraine-war-biden-and-zelenskiy-discuss-more-support-for-ukraine-as-visa-mastercard-pull-out-of-russia-live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hopes of establishing a humanitarian corridor out of besieged city of Mariupol dashed for second day running</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUTIN LOSES 1,000 TROOPS IN DAY</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/russia-lost-1000-troops-day-26400197</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Official numbers released by the Ukrainian government show that Russia has lost 11,000 soldiers so far in the war as Putin's forces struggle against motivated opponents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLAD SICK?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/vladimir-putin-dying-agony-terminal-26395464</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Russia's President Putin is reportedly suffering from 'terminal bowel cancer', a Pentagon source claims, it comes after he was seen with a 'puffy face' following the invasion of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radical Christians see 'sign of Jesus's return' and 'end times'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/radical-christians-reckon-ukraine-war-26400245</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pastor Greg Laurie from the Harvest Christian Fellowship in California claims that the Russia-Ukraine war and coronavirus have 'prophetic significance' for the return of Jesus</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
