<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Tax preparers warn refund may be smaller than usual this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.postbulletin.com/news/business/tax-preparers-warn-your-refund-may-be-smaller-than-usual/article_2019b754-4d83-503e-ac96-17e0ffcde602.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.postbulletin.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doing your taxes isn’t just about placing the correct numbers in the boxes of a form and then, as many hope, collecting a refund. There’s also how you feel about</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Traffic Controllers Resign...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/01/24/texas-air-traffic-controllers-resign-government-shutdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fort Worth chapter of the National Air Traffic Controllers Association warns flights will be grounded as early as next week if they are forced to continuing to work without pay.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Therapy llamas' at STANFORD UNIVERSITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecollegefix.com/therapy-llamas-make-an-appearance-at-stanford-university/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecollegefix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The llamas came from a farm that 'specializes in llama-based therapy programs.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Israeli Filmmaker Bringing Shia LaBeouf's Pseudo-Memoir to Screen...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/meet-israeli-filmmaker-bringing-shia-labeoufs-pseudo-memoir-screen-1178394</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on an original screenplay by the embattled actor, former TV host-turned-commercial director Alma Har'el's narrative debut, 'Honey Boy,' examines the troubled relationship between an abusive father and a child actor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Trans axe attacker split man's face in HALF after bad TINDER date...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/755694/transgender-axe-attack-australia-evie-amati-ben-rimmer-petition-7-eleven-tinder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro pigs abandoned by owners who don't realize grow so large...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/25/micro-pigs-abandoned-rescue-centres-every-day-owners-still-fail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;ldquo;Micro pigs&amp;rdquo; are being abandoned at rescue centres nearly every day as owners are continuing to fail to realise that they grow so large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dig to unearth ancient road unsettles Palestinian neighborhood...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Dig-to-unearth-ancient-road-unsettles-Palestinian-13560907.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST JERUSALEM - The main road winding through the densely built Arab neighborhood of Wadi Hilweh is like many others in Jerusalem, lined with convenience stores and often crammed with traffic. There's little clue to what is happening just yards below the pavement and under the floors of surrounding houses and apartment blocks. For five years, Israeli archaeologists, supported by a nationalist Jewish organization, have been digging a tunnel here. Their aim is to uncover what they say was once an important thoroughfare used by worshipers some 2,000 years ago to reach the Jewish holy temple.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger screams 'Allahu Akbar' and 'tries to STORM cockpit' of flight in France...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/755659/transavia-flight-paris-tunis-diverted-passenger-shouted-allahu-akbar</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming to Jesus, armed: Virginia Senate OKs guns in churches...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/virginia/article_1113da8a-209d-11e9-847b-c34ec08bfea9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While Virginia has a strong gun culture and some of the nation's most lax firearms laws, churches have been gun-free zones - although the "good and sufficient reason" language offers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis users' syndrome made woman vomit 30 times in one day...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/life-style/health/ny-news-cannabinoid-hyperemesis-syndrome-marijuana-pot-smoking-vomit-20190124-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As recreational marijuana use gets legalized, an intolerance known as cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome is coming to the fore. It makes the sufferer vomit uncontrollably, symptoms that can only be alleviated by hot shower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort due in court to face allegations of lying to prosecutors...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-pol-manafort-mueller-hearing-20190125-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Manafort, President Trump's former campaign chairman, is scheduled to appear in federal court on Friday to face allegations that he lied to special counsel Robert S. Mueller III. Manafort could face a stiffer sentence if a judge agrees he lied after striking a plea deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola death toll surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190125-ebola-death-toll-surges-dr-congo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ebola death toll surges in DR Congo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How World's Worst Snakebite Became Viral Hit for 200-Year-Old Medical Journal...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/how-the-world-s-worst-snakebite-became-a-viral-hit-for-a-200-year-old-medical-journal</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the World's Worst Snakebite Became a Viral Hit for a 200-Year-Old Medical Journal</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIP to Super Bowl halftime show; No longer cultural institution...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/music/2019/01/24/super-bowl-halftime-show-no-longer-cultural-institution/2668939002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once one of music's so-called biggest nights, the halftime show has been a source of controversy this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ad Prices Stall After Years of Relentless Increases...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-24/super-bowl-ad-prices-stall-after-years-of-relentless-increases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Russians flock to Florida to deliver American babies...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190125-rich-russians-flock-florida-deliver-american-babies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Russians flock to Florida to deliver American babies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moroccan man fears for safety after arrested wearing dress...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190125-moroccan-man-fears-safety-after-arrested-wearing-dress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moroccan man fears for safety after arrested wearing a dress</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen to comply with Senate subpoena...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/ap/article-6629531/Ex-Trump-lawyer-Michael-Cohen-comply-Senate-subpoena.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen has agreed to appear in front of the House Committee on Oversight and Reform on February 12 in Washington, DC, his attorney confirmed Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Cloned monkeys' genes deliberately edited to make mentally ill...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/24/cloned-monkeys-gene-edited-mental-illness-prompts-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese geneticists have been criticised after cloning five monkeys that were deliberately &amp;ldquo;edited&amp;rdquo; to be mentally ill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prostate cancer can BOOST longevity...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/01/24/prostate-cancer-survivors-now-live-longer-average-man-long/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prostate cancer survivors live longer than men without the disease - if symptoms are caught early, new figures show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vows to protect diplomats...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-diplomats-in-Venezuela-come-under-pressure-as-13559245.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela - For years, the hulking reinforced-concrete U.S. Embassy here has been a target of Venezuela's socialist leaders, who have expelled numerous senior American envoys. But the tension has perhaps never been higher than now, with authorities ordering diplomats out of the country by this weekend. President Nicolás Maduro severed relations with Washington after the Trump administration on Wednesday recognized opposition leader Juan Guaidó as interim president. The U.S. government has defied Maduro's order to vacate the embassy, saying it has Guaidó's permission to stay. The standoff raised the possibility that Maduro could use force to expel the remaining diplomats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain researchers warn lack of sleep public health crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/Brain-researchers-warn-that-lack-of-sleep-is-a-13559608.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the screen-lit bustle of modern life, sleep is expendable. There are television shows to binge-watch, work emails to answer, homework to finish, social media posts to scroll through. We'll catch up on shut-eye later, so the thinking goes - right after we click down one last digital rabbit hole. Brain research, which has pushed back hard against this nonchalant attitude, is now expanding rapidly, reaching beyond the laboratory and delving into exactly how sleep works in disease and in normal cognitive functions such as memory. The growing consensus is that casual disregard for sleep is wrongheaded - even downright dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'DREAMERS' FOR $25 BILLION IN BORDER SECURITY...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article225034930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top White House adviser Jared Kushner told members of the Latino community that President Donald Trump was willing to give 1.8 million Dreamers permanent protections from deportation to reopen the government in exchange for $25 billion in border security, including some wall funding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koch network tells donors it will again decline to support Trump in 2020... </title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Koch-network-tells-donors-it-will-again-decline-13559863.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The conservative Koch political network has told donors that it plans to once again stay out of the presidential race and will not work to help reelect President Donald Trump in 2020, a move that sidelines a major player that has been pivotal in mobilizing voters on the right for more than a decade. The decision reflects a narrow path that the influential network led by billionaire industrialist Charles Koch has sought to walk in the Trump era: aligning with the president on some policy issues while withholding its electoral firepower on his behalf. The network's plan to stay out of the 2020 race was quietly relayed to major donors in recent months, according to people familiar with the conversations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Labrador returns home -- with another dog -- and a goat...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6617187/Hilarious-moment-man-reunited-lost-dog-returns-pooch-goat.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyle Krier's wife let out their black Labrador who disappeared. Kyle, from Kansas, went searching for 'Bo.' But when he found him, he wasn't alone. The pet made friends with another lab and a goat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUTERTE: Communism 'Rotten Ideology' Leading to 'Mass Insanity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2019/01/22/duterte-communism-rotten-ideology-leading-mass-insanity/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte condemned the Communist Party of the Philippines (CPP) as violent, hopeless, and insane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRETA VAN FLEET saviors of rock?</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/1c25ef288a4e4bf59cdbf4ad56724345</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — When the members of the rock band Greta Van Fleet put their last touches on their first full-length album, they didn't celebrate with a round of beers or a fancy dinner. They immediately started working on new songs. "Once we finished 'Anthem of the Peaceful Army' — the very day that we'd OK'd all the mixing — we started writing the next album," said Jake Kiszka, the band's guitarist. "If we're stagnant, it becomes boring." The young Michigan rockers whose sound and classic rock look is reminiscent of Led Zeppelin have done the opposite of stagnate in the last 18 months. It's been more like an explosion, capped by four Grammy Award nominations, including best new artist and best rock album.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryan Singer  blasts new sex abuse allegations...</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/bohemian-rhapsody-director-responds-sex-abuse-allegations-235053744--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Bohemian Rhapsody" director Bryan Singer on Thursday dismissed a bombshell article detailing fresh sexual misconduct allegations -- some involving teenage boys -- as a "homophobic smear piece."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asylum seekers to wait in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cefdf25f53594a02ae3eb04fc343b2cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO (AP) — The Trump administration on Friday will start forcing some asylum seekers to wait in Mexico while their cases wind through U.S. courts, an official said, launching what could become one of the more significant changes to the immigration system in years. The changes will be introduced at San Diego's San Ysidro border crossing, according to a U.S. official familiar with the plan who spoke on condition of anonymity Thursday because it was not yet publicly announced. San Ysidro is the nation's busiest crossing and the choice of asylum seekers who arrived to Tijuana, Mexico, in November in a caravan of more than 6,000 mostly Central American migrants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faces tough choices as it weighs next moves on Maduro...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d0e690d28904adcb63b85e0e87467b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump says "all options are on the table" as the U.S. seeks to push Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro to give up power. But the reality is much more complicated. The U.S. still has tools to apply pressure on Maduro, even after years of tough rhetoric and increasing sanctions. But further targeted measures may do little to hurt the already-reeling South American country, and a major step like halting Venezuelan oil imports could damage the American economy. The most extreme step, direct military action, appears not to be under consideration, at least for now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before Venezuela, USA has long involvement in Latin America...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8c99384884df4e1293690c797682f0ad</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro accuses the United States of trying to orchestrate a coup against him. While the U.S. says it's trying to rescue Venezuela's democracy, Washington has a long history of interventions — military and otherwise — in Latin American politics. Since the advent of the Monroe Doctrine in the early 19th century, the United States has involved itself in the daily affairs of nations across the hemisphere, often on behalf of North American commercial interests or to support right-leaning forces against leftist leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARACAS RAUCOUS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/52bb7f774bc94f439df0606eb96bab4e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — All eyes were on Juan Guaido's next step after the popular Venezuelan opposition leader declared he was temporarily assuming presidential powers in a high-stakes bid to unseat Nicolas Maduro, whose powerful loyalists went on the offensive Thursday in support of the embattled leader. Guaido has disappeared from view since swearing before tens of thousands of cheering supporters to uphold the constitution and rid Venezuela of Maduro's dictatorship, and his whereabouts remained shrouded in mystery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Get a loan,' Commerce chief tells unpaid fed workers...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190125000559-mc43d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ROSS (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-'Get a loan,' U.S. Commerce chief tells unpaid federal workers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gay congressman flees Brazil, citing death threats...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190124223112-150go</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRAZIL-LGBT/CONGRESS:Gay congressman flees Brazil, citing death threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC PENTHOUSE SHATTERS RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/billionaire-ken-griffin-buys-americas-most-expensive-home-for-238-million-11548271301</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The record-breaking purchase of a New York City penthouse is the latest in a string of multimillion-dollar real-estate deals by the hedge-fund manager.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soros Warns China Uses Algorithms to Find Threats to One-Party Rule...</title>
      <link>https://www.swissinfo.ch/eng/soros-warns-china-seeks-algos-to-find-threats-to-one-party-rule/44706996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.swissinfo.ch&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Billionaire George Soros warned of the “mortal danger” of China’s use of artificial intelligence to repress its citizens under the ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50% FACEBOOK ACCOUNTS FAKE?</title>
      <link>https://www.plainsite.org/realitycheck/facebook.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.plainsite.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN AIRLINES kicks family off plane, citing body odor...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/01/24/michigan-family-american-airlines-body-odor-southfield/2666303002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yossi and Jennie Adler and their 19-month-old daughter were boarding a plane at the Miami International Airport when they were escorted off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xi 'most dangerous' foe of free societies...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190124-soros-calls-chinas-xi-most-dangerous-foe-free-societies</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soros calls China's Xi 'most dangerous' foe of free societies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZUCKERBERG: Need your data for 'operation, security'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-facts-about-facebook-11548374613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We need your information for operation and security, but you control whether we use it for advertising.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP senators read Pence riot act...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/426896-gop-senators-read-pence-riot-act-before-shutdown-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrated GOP senators read Vice President Pence the riot act at a closed-door meeting Thursday, telling him the partial government shutdown needs to end soon, according to lawmakers in the room.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sundance Under Siege As Michael Jackson Movie Gets Threats, Big Police Presence...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/michael-jackson-leaving-neverland-sundance-film-festival-police-concerns-protests-threats-1202538783/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The world premiere of a controversial Michael Jackson documentary this week at the Sundance Film Festival has organizers and local police preparing for turmoil from fans of the deceased …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will ideas 'radical' for DC seem reasonable to voters?</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/01/how-the-media-can-prevent-2020-from-becoming-2016</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ultimate bias in journalism is not political. It’s toward controversy, gaffes, and scandal—shiny new things that get ratings and shares and downloads. There’s a rather obvious lesson here for Democrats seeking the White House—and for media elites who are tragically out of touch with how Americans actually consume the news.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth's oldest rock was found by astronauts -- on the Moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/24/world/earth-oldest-rock-moon/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Apollo 14 astronauts returned samples from the moon's surface, they probably didn't realize that they were reuniting Earth with a bit of its early history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamie Dimon, GOLDMAN CEO private meets with Maxine Waters...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/jamie-dimon-and-david-solomon-met-with-wall-street-critic-maxine-waters.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dimon and Solomon gave Waters their perspectives on a wide range of topics, including where they stand on the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'The Resistance' Within West Wing...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/24/exclusive-excerpts-from-team-of-vipers-john-kelly-overheard-undermining-president-trump-on-syria/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Kelly was overheard deliberately undermining Trump's strategy on Syria, an excerpt from a forthcoming book alleges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eat what want and stay slim? Being thin in DNA...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2019-01-24/eat-what-you-want-and-still-stay-slim-thank-your-genes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boxes of used tissues sell for $80: 'Schedule own illness'...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Odd_News/2019/01/24/Company-selling-boxes-of-used-tissues-for-80/8151548348856/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Los Angeles start-up is offering to let people choose their own illness schedules by buying a box of used tissues for $80.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Bomb Threat Hoax To Avoid Seeing Parents Diverts Flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/travel/news-and-advice/easyjet-bomb-threat-hoax-flight-diverted-lyon-rennes-student-parents-avoid-a8743021.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Country sent back to 'dark ages' after underwater Internet cable severed...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/tonga-sent-back-to-dark-ages-after-underwater-internet-cable-severed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of the South Pacific nation of Tonga are experiencing a total Internet shutdown after an underwater cable which connects the island to the rest of the world was severed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAIDERS QB Challenges Critical ESPN Host to Fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.times-standard.com/2019/01/23/derek-carr-challenges-max-kellerman-to-a-fight-on-twitter/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.times-standard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After the First Take personality criticized Carr on Wednesday, the quarterback barked right back on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope 'closely watching' Venezuela chaos, but takes no side...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-venezuela-vatican/vatican-calls-for-end-to-suffering-in-venezuela-but-takes-no-sides-idUSKCN1PI2QM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis is following the situation in Venezuela closely and the Holy See su...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maxine Waters planning to grill big banks on Hill...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/24/maxine-waters-scrutiny-nations-big-banks-1113148</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;quot;It's probably not going to be a real syrupy sweet committee hearing,&amp;quot; said Rep. Emanuel Cleaver, a senior member of the panel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of War: Combat artists capture soul of Marines...</title>
      <link>https://www.marinecorpstimes.com/news/your-marine-corps/2019/01/24/the-art-of-war-how-combat-artists-are-capturing-the-soul-of-the-marine-corps/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marinecorpstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Go to war, do art” is now the battle cry of the Marine combat artists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WALL 'DOWN PAYMENT' DEMANDED TO RE-OPEN...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/white-house-demands-large-down-payment-on-the-wall-as-schumer-and-mcconnell-try-to-reach-shutdown-deal.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The statement followed the failure of two Senate bills to end the partial government shutdown now in its 34th day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>16-month undercover sting to catch man illegally selling $90 worth of fish...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/saskatchewans-government-staged-a-16-month-undercover-sting-to-catch-a-first-nations-man-illegally-selling-90-worth-of-fish</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seriously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Starts Sending Some Asylum Seekers Back to Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-start-sending-some-asylum-seekers-back-to-mexico-11548362672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration will soon return some asylum-seeking migrants to Mexico to wait until their U.S. immigration court hearing, the first step in implementing a new border policy announced last month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuke chief: Bought spares for equipment we agreed to destroy...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/irans-nuclear-chief-we-bought-spares-for-nuke-equipment-we-agreed-to-destroy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ali Akbar Salehi says supreme leader was convinced West would renege on 2015 pact, so replacement tubes for nuclear reactor were secretly purchased</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL SecState resigns after blackface photos emerge...</title>
      <link>https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2019/01/24/new-secretary-state-ertel-dressed-blackface-halloween-2005/2649161002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tallahassee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Ertel was captured in a photo wearing blackface at a private party 14 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both Senate Bills Blocked...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/24/senate-rejects-trump-plan-to-fund-border-wall-and-end-shutdown-1124728</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite the failure, lawmakers expressed optimism that there's a way out of the impasse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILITARY BEHIND MADURO</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/venezuelas-military-backs-maduro-11548347862</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Venezuela’s military threw its support behind embattled President Nicolás Maduro, a day after the head of the country’s national assembly declared himself legitimate leader and was recognized by the U.S. and most Latin American nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH MERGING WITH BIG BROTHER? </title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/is-big-tech-merging-with-big-brother-kinda-looks-like-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The all-seeing Amazon, Google, and Facebook have every incentive to help the national security state undermine privacy, free speech, and democracy. We’ve read this book before.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California city sets fee on disposable cups...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article224951810.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berkeley, California, has approved a 25-cent fee on disposable cups city officials say is part of an effort to eliminate restaurant waste.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Dem counteroffer on border security!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/426810-pelosi-no-dem-counter-offer-on-border-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) said Thursday that House Democrats are not working behind the scenes to craft a counteroffer to President Trump’s border wall demands as a strategy for ending the history-making partial shutdown. &amp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran to Launch 'Massive' War Drills...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-to-launch-massive-war-drills/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian military leaders announced on Thursday that the Islamic Republic would be launching a "massive" set of war drills later this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who owns your face? Social media mobs raise new privacy concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/23/who-owns-your-face-social-media-mobs-raise-new-pri/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You might own your car, your house, your pet and your 401(k). But you don’t own your own photographic image.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren proposes new 'wealth tax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/24/elizabeth-warren-to-propose-new-wealth-tax-economic-advisor.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Warren's proposal comes alongside other Democrats' plans to raise taxes on the wealthiest Americans to pay for ambitious policy goals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLANNED PARENTHOOD launches teen sex chatbot...</title>
      <link>https://adage.com/article/agency-news/planned-parenthood-launches-roo-a-sexual-health-chatbot-teens/316365/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;adage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risky phone soars, killing Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/cars/2019/01/24/distracted-driving-iihs/2655556002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans are using theirÂ phones in riskier ways while driving, worsening the nation'sÂ crash crisis, according to a new report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos hits turbulence over CEOs' private jets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190124-davos-forum-hits-turbulence-over-ceos-private-jets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Davos forum hits turbulence over CEOs' private jets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN:  Time for journalists to sign off TWITTER?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/24/media/reliable-sources-01-23-19/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A version of this article first appeared in the "Reliable Sources" newsletter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL's first male cheerleaders to make Super Bowl debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/lifestyles/nfl-first-male-cheerleaders-make-super-bowl-debut-atlanta/9s5XwRRoBoaN4jRkkg3rNM/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Quinton Peron and Napoleon Jinnies made history last year when they joined the LA Rams squad, and will do so again at Super Bowl 53 in Mercedes-Benz Stadium on February 3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional support alligator helps depression...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6cf8234a7a5a492eabfa4b0e319f2ec3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YORK HAVEN, Pa. (AP) — A Pennsylvania man says his emotional support alligator helps him deal with his depression. Joie Henney, 65, said his registered emotional support animal named Wally likes to snuggle and give hugs, despite being a 5-foot-long alligator. The York Haven man said he received approval from his doctor to use Wally as his emotional support animal after not wanting to go on medication for depression, he told Philly.com .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McAuliffe Gets Ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/mcauliffe-hints-im-going-to-announce-says-trump-has-no-moral-core</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe, who is inching toward a 2020 Democratic presidential bid, launched a full frontal attack on President Trump’s leadership, blaming him for expanding racial division in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'No. 1 leaker'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2019/01/trump-aide-recalls-conways-leaking-tactics-in-the-west-wing-vipers-nest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive excerpt from “Team of Vipers,” Cliff Sims recalls how Kellyanne Conway played Trump, saying one thing on Fox News while bad-­mouthing his administration in private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffers brain freezes during address...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/applause-line-nancy-pelosi-repeatedly-tells-mayors-to-clap-for-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi was like a mother hen to America’s mayors on Wednesday, telling them when to clap for her. After thanking a member of her audience, she said, “That’s an applause line! I’ll let you know.” She followed through on her promise. ﻿ After claiming Democrats support “strong border security initiatives,” she said, …</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
