<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Bankrupt Illinois Cities Cut Services To Fund Pensions...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/political/bankrupt-illinois-cities-forced-cut-services-fund-pensions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors build new tongue out of woman's arm...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/doctors-build-new-tongue-out-20135144</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rebecca Patterson, from Rushcliffe, had just gotten engaged when she was diagnosed with tongue cancer in April 2018</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAREER OVER?</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/27662788/brown-pats-cut-wr-amid-field-allegations</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown's brief stint with the Patriots is over, as the team released him Friday. "We feel that it is best to move in a different direction at this time," the Patriots said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Perfectly real' deepfakes in 6 months?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/hao-li-perfectly-real-deepfakes-will-arrive-in-6-months-to-a-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Soon, it's going to get to the point where there is no way that we can actually detect [deepfakes] anymore, so we have to look at other types of solutions," says Hao Li.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KRAFT WAS ENRAGED...</title>
      <link>https://theathletic.com/1228966/2019/09/20/how-robert-kraft-and-bill-belichick-arrived-at-decision-to-cut-antonio-brown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theathletic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kraft, who was on a business trip, and Belichick spoke and decided Friday to officially release Brown just 11 days after the Patriots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranoia Written All Over Stocks in Struggle Back to Record...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/paranoia-written-over-p-500-110001512.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The relentless drive into defensive stocks is a logical way to cope for investors beset all year by signs a recession is at hand. It’s also a tough way to set a fresh stock record.Buoyed by a supportive Federal Reserve and strong economic data, the S&amp;P 500 climbed within points of an all-time</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland Best Place To Settle?</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/iceland-yes-iceland-best-place-153104626.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hello, northern lights.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PATRIOTS CUT BROWN...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/09/20/patriots-release-antonio-brown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antonio Brown's Patriots career is over after one game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT: Killer robots 'unstoppable'...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/2019/09/21/microsoft-chief-brad-smith-says-rise-killer-robots-unstoppable/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The rise of killer robots is now unstoppable and a new digital Geneva Convention is essential to protect the world from the growing threat they pose, according to the President of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest technology company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swing States Lose Most Factory Jobs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/two-u-swing-states-lost-161444923.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- As the U.S. presidential campaign heats up, Democratic candidates may want to look at two Rust Belt states that narrowly helped deliver Donald Trump’s victory in 2016: Pennsylvania and Wisconsin.The two swing states lost the most manufacturing jobs in the past 12 months, bucking the national</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran issues 'battlefield' warning...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-issues-battlefield-warning-us-deploys-troops-110024302.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Any country that attacks Iran will become the "main battlefield", the Revolutionary Guards warned Saturday after Washington ordered reinforcements to the Gulf following attacks on Saudi oil installations it blames on Tehran. Tensions escalated between arch-foes Iran and the United States after</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freeze on Ukraine aid draws new scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trumps-freeze-on-ukraine-aid-draws-new-scrutiny-amid-push-for-biden-investigation/ar-AAHBu9f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFI:  KELLYANNE GOES WITHOUT GEORGE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/462427-clarence-thomas-joe-manchin-rudy-giuliani-among-guests-at</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various political and government figures turned out at the White House on Friday as President Trump hosted Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison for an elaborate state dinner, only the second formal state visit so far during Tr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegetarian ravioli served with lemon-cheese emlusion...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fox-marvel-executives-among-guests-232207438.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Fox Corp. Chief Executive Officer Lachlan Murdoch and Marvel Entertainment Chairman Isaac Perlmutter were among those attending President Donald Trump’s second State Dinner on Friday, in honor of Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison.The guest list included a number of conservatives</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giuliani helped pressure Kiev to investigate Biden's son...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Giuliani-helped-pressure-Kiev-to-investigate-14456971.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - When President Donald Trump spoke on the telephone with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky in late July, the Ukrainians had a lot at stake. They were waiting on millions in stalled military aid from the United States, and Zelensky was seeking a high-priority White House meeting with Trump.  Trump told his Ukrainian counterpart that his country could improve its image if it completed corruption cases that have "inhibited the interaction between Ukraine and the USA," according to a readout of the call released by Kiev.  What neither government said publicly at the time was that Trump went even further - specifically pressing Ukraine's president to reopen a corruption investigation involving former vice president Joe Biden's son, according to two people familiar with the call, which is now the subject of an explosive whistleblower complaint.  Days after the two presidents spoke, Trump's personal lawyer, Rudy Giuliani, met with an aide to the Ukrainian president in Madrid and spelled out two specific cases he believed Ukraine should pursue. One was a probe of a Ukrainian gas tycoon who had Biden's son Hunter on his board. Another was an allegation that Democrats colluded with Ukraine to release information on former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort during the 2016 election.  "Your country owes it to us and to your country to find out what really happened," Giuliani said he told the Ukrainian president's aide, Andriy Yermak, during the Madrid meeting. Yermak, according to Giuliani, indicated that the Ukrainians were open to pursuing the investigations. The aide reiterated the Ukrainians' plea for a meeting with Trump, a summit that would be an important signal to Russia of Washington's support for Ukraine.  "I talked to him about the whole package," said Giuliani, who has been lobbying Ukrainian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP HOLDS STATE DINNER...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7487789/Donald-Trump-dubs-Prime-Minister-Scott-Morrison-man-titanium.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Australian Prime Minister Scott Morrison and wife Jenny have arrived at the White House for an official state dinner, where they were greeted by U.S. President Donald Trump and First Lady Melania.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WATCH ARRIVALS...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/video/?464038-1/white-house-hosts-state-dinner-honoring-australian-prime-minister</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;C-SPAN is joined by former White House social secretary and former chief of protocol Capricia Marshall to take an in-depth look at President Trump's second State Dinner, which honors Australian Prime…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>41 Climate Doomsday Predictions That Haven't Come True...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/environment/2019/09/20/nolte-climate-experts-are-0-41-with-their-doomsday-predictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For more than 50 years Climate Alarmists in the scientific community and environmental movement have not gotten one prediction correct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cubans wait hours in gas lines as fuel crisis bites...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c93abacdc9b944d2b13fbc6f4f0781f4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Bronx man chases intruder down, beats him to death...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/20/bronx-homeowner-chases-would-be-intruder-down-beats-him-to-death-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Bronx homeowner chased down a man he claimed was trying to break into his house – and bashed him to death with a metal pipe in the street, police said Friday. Troy George, 54, was hit with a murd…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau's star has lost its shine over blackface...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/justin-trudeaus-star-lost-shine-over-blackface-205456374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Images published one week into Canada's general election showing Justin Trudeau in blackface mark a low point in his political career, but it's not clear if they've caused grievous harm to his re-election bid, experts say. "Both in Canada and abroad, this affair has tarnished Justin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starving seniors: How America fails to feed its aging...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/starving-seniors-how-america-fails-to-feed-its-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One out of every 13 older Americans struggles to find enough food to eat while the federal program intended to help hasn’t kept pace with the graying population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren's momentum spurs new attacks from 2020 rivals...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/898bffd7fa87406b8e9a2cb09042f6e0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — What makes Impossible burgers possible? An engineered ingredient that makes the veggie patty look bloody — and one of many new concoctions food regulators expect to see more of in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston area sees relief, rescues after Imelda leaves 4 dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5a1271ab361a4bf3864340739662ae89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON (AP) — Emergency workers used boats Friday to rescue about 60 residents of a Houston-area community still trapped in their homes by floodwaters following one of the wettest tropical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expedites delivery of military equipment...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920230811-gljdq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAUDI-ARAMCO/USA-PENTAGON (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-United States sending troops to bolster Saudi defenses after attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopes for trade breakthrough fade as China cancels Montana farm visit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920183219-pyolx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRADE/CHINA (UPDATE 2, PIX):UPDATE 2-Hopes for trade breakthrough fade as China cancels U.S. farm visits</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete guest list...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/complete-guest-list-for-the-state-dinner-in-honor-australian-prime-minister-scott-morrison/2019/09/20/31f553a4-dbf6-11e9-a688-303693fb4b0b_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When a hurricane hits, what happens to sharks, dolphins and marine life?</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/weather/hurricane/os-ne-hurricane-what-happens-underwater-sharks-dolphins-marine-life-20190920-omf5agiktzdkhlddkyjgcsd43y-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When a hurricane passes over the ocean it can cause a lot of destruction and death to the marine inhabitants under the sea, but it can do a surprising amount of good, as well.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13 Camp Pendleton Marines charged in human smuggling operation...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/09/20/politics/13-marines-charged-human-smuggling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen Marines have been formally charged with involvement in human smuggling operations, the US Marine Corps announced Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese trade negotiators cancel US farm visit, cut trip short...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/09/20/chinese-trade-negotiators-cancels-us-farm-visit-cuts-trip-short.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese trade negotiators suddenly canceled a visit to meet U.S. farmers after they wrapped up trade talks in Washington this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMANDS FOR TRANSCRIPT</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/joe-biden-demands-trump-release-transcript-of-ukraine-call-ba1a57c4-7e66-427b-a19b-1152e3bf309f.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three House committees are investigating Trump and Giuliani over reports on Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barron Hilton dead at 91...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2019/09/20/barron-hilton-who-expanded-hilton-hotels-empire-dies-91/2388047001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hotelier and philanthropist Barron Hilton died on Thursday of natural causes at his home in Los Angeles. He was 91.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, dozens injured in Utah tour bus crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/09/20/tour-bus-crashes-near</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robert Driedonks’ voice broke as he described what he saw Friday along State Road 12, after a tour bus carrying Chinese-speaking tourists crashed next to his business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car plows into mall near Chicago...</title>
      <link>https://wgntv.com/2019/09/20/police-on-the-scene-after-reports-of-car-driving-through-woodfield-mall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wgntv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCHAUMBURG, Ill. — A driver was taken into custody after a car drove through Woodfield Mall Friday afternoon. Police were on the scene at the Schaumburg mall around 2:30 p.m. after witnesses said a black SUV drove through Sears, striking kiosks. The incident took place on the lower level of the mall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver 'Dazed And Confused'; No Injuries...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/09/20/stores-at-woodfield-mall-placed-on-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An SUV smashed into Woodfield Mall and drove down the main hallway, slamming into a kiosk and stores, sending panicked shoppers scrambling for safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic first? Israel's Arabs could lead parliamentary opposition...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920142751-zacrj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ARABS (PIX, GRAPHIC):A historic first? Israel's Arabs could lead parliamentary opposition</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Rose Faces New Allegations From Makeup Artist...</title>
      <link>https://www.thecut.com/2019/09/charlie-rose-hit-with-new-harassment-allegation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thecut.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His longtime makeup artist says Rose was verbally abusive, and that he used his Bloomberg TV studio as “a sexual hunting ground.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dwarf porn star jailed in Vegas, accused of stabbing boyfriend...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/crime/stabbings/dwarf-porn-star-jailed-in-las-vegas-accused-of-stabbing-boyfriend-1852654/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actress known as “Bridget the Midget,” was booked Wednesday under her legal name, Cheryl Marie Murphy, in connection with a domestic disturbance early that morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Calls For New Laws So Sitting Presidents Can Be Indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/09/20/762594886/pelosi-says-congress-should-pass-new-laws-so-sitting-presidents-can-be-indicted</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I do think that we will have to pass some laws that will have clarity for future presidents. [A] president should be indicted, if he's committed a wrongdoing," House Speaker Nancy Pelosi told NPR.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Felons could regain voting rights in Georgia...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/nonviolent-felons-could-regain-voting-rights-georgia/xZOpRkDHfml2GhtHjigvUK/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia senators on Friday began considering whether to restore the voting rights of many of th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: Trump must give deposition in protesters' lawsuit...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cf76347381d4470bcb9eed36947654b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — A New York judge has ordered President Donald Trump to give a videotaped deposition in a lawsuit filed by protesters who claim they were roughed up outside Trump Tower. State...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead, dozens injured in Uath tour bus crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2019/09/20/tour-bus-crashes-near/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tour bus carrying Chinese-speaking tourists crashed Friday morning near Bryce Canyon National Park, killing at least four people and critically injuring at least a dozen others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHL goaltenders getting concussions at alarming rate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dca05dd0915f43dcb8ef40f24fd99e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stanley Cup-winning experience isn't worth what it used to be. Neither is experience of any kind. As NHL teams move toward paying their stars more money and relying on young players to fill...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley moves back to SC, fuels political speculation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/nation-world/national/article235301277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM lays off thousands as plants lie idle in labor strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/autos/gm-lays-thousands-workers-plants-lie-idle-labor-union-strike-n1056946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Despite feeling the effects of the U.S. strike, GM workers in Canada are “”very supportive” of the action, said the head of Canada’s autoworkers trade union. “People are furious with General Motors. People feel betrayed.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declines to say whether he discussed Biden in call with Ukrainian president...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-declines-to-say-whether-he-discussed-joe-biden-in-call-with-ukrainian-president/ar-AAHAwF0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breakthrough device generates electricity from night sky...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/tech/breakthrough-device-can-generate-electricity-from-the-night-sky</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An innovative new device is able to generate electricity from the night sky, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says going into Iran would be 'very easy decision'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/trump-holds-press-conference-with-australian-prime-minister-scott-morrison-today-2019-09-20-live-stream/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president's remarks came at a news conference after the U.S. announced intensified sanctions on Iran</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Corporate America Profits Off Being Green...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/big-business-turns-profit-environmentalism-100018045.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s time to stop crediting corporate sustainability efforts as acts of altruism. For big business, protecting the environment often means padding the bottom line.Nike Inc. has come up with a way to weave more efficiently, reducing the raw material and labor time needed to make each shoe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau pivots from blackface scandal, pledges assault rifle ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-canada-election/canadas-trudeau-pledges-assault-rifle-ban-pivots-campaign-amid-blackface-scandal-idUSKBN1W51KJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, embroiled in a blackface picture scandal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious magnetic pulses discovered on Mars...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/09/mars-insight-feels-mysterious-magnetic-pulsations-at-midnight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nighttime events are among initial results from the InSight lander, which also found hints that the red planet may host a global reservoir of liquid water deep below the surface.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattress salesman rescues 120 people...</title>
      <link>https://www.theeagle.com/news/trending/i-can-t-let-my-people-drown-houston-mattress-salesman/article_060bfa3b-188a-5069-b249-38de35fa1af1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theeagle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Mattress Mack" knew what he had to do now: He opened his showroom as a shelter and sent out the furniture trucks to rescue Imelda's stranded victims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK DECLARES IT'S A 'PUBLISHER,' CAN CENSOR WHOMEVER IT WANTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/facebook-declares-its-a-publisher-can-censor-whomever-it-wants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tech giant walking into legal trap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba's 'sonic weapon' may have been mosquito gas...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-latin-america-49770369</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mystery illness that has blighted diplomats in Havana may have been due to fumigation, a study says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu clings to power as coalition talks loom...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190920112523-rab0m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ (PIX, GRAPHICS):Israel's Netanyahu clings to power as coalition talks loom</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKRAINE CALL 'PROMISE'</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/whistleblower-complaint-about-president-trump-involves-ukraine-according-to-two-people-familiar-with-the-matter/ar-AAHyi0V</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unethical to upgrade iPhone?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/865944/unethical-upgrade-iphone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How our addiction to new and shiny devices is doing more harm than good</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BULLARD: Manufacturing in recession...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/09/20/feds-james-bullard-says-us-manufacturing-appears-in-recession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US manufacturing sector “already appears in recession” and overall economic growth is expected to slow “in the near horizon,” St. Louis Federal Reserve Bank president James Bullard said on Frid…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth making big comeback in America...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/meth-us-big-comeback-145207167.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meth producers in Mexico are cranking up the speed of production, and the drug is making a big comeback in the U.S., drug experts warn. And “it’s really out of control.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUCKED:  Officials detail shocking case against political donor...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4f2f1f7bb4f24663ad2fbd3e5f14f29f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Gemmel Moore had moved back home with his mother in Texas two years ago and was missing Los Angeles when he texted a photo of syringe in an arm to a wealthy gay man he knew in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends himself against whistleblower complaint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/034de586020942c8a6c1367cb8dfd39c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops: Girl left alone in car while mother danced at strip club...</title>
      <link>http://thesmokinggun.com/buster/child-neglect/stripper-busted-for-child-neglect-384692</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While her mother worked the pole inside, a three-year-old girl was roaming around the parking lot of a Florida strip club early yesterday morning, police report. Responding to a 911 call about the un</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saga Threatens to Blow Up 2020 Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trump-whistleblower-saga-threatens-to-blow-up-2020-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two reports on Thursday night say the conversation in the complaint involved Ukraine, the country that the president’s close lawyer has turned to in looking for dirt on Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Military to present Trump with several options on Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/4d4ce92397ba44a68bedd60edb2aee36</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mattress salesman rescues 120 people...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/462301-houston-mattress-salesman-rescues-about-120-people-from-imelda-flooding</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Houston furniture salesman reportedly rescued more than 100 people from flooding caused by Tropical Storm Imelda.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
