<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>March honors Warsaw's Jews, activist who warned of genocide...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/march-honors-warsaws-jews-activist-warned-genocide-175505329.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — Israel's ambassador to Poland has joined Warsaw residents in recalling the first mass deportations of Jews from the Warsaw Ghetto and in honoring a Jewish activist who took his own life while despairing the world's indifference to the Holocaust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostalgic for Brazil's dictatorship, Bolsonaro looks to presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/nostalgic-brazils-dictatorship-bolsonaro-looks-presidency-135624300.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry Brazilians long for a return to order, and former army officer Jair Bolsonaro, a fan of the dictatorship that stretched from the 1960s to the 1980s, hopes to ride that wave into the presidency. Often labeled a Brazilian Donald Trump, Bolsonaro, 63, actually seems to enjoy offending his critics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High risk of 'losing control' of AIDS epidemic: experts...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/high-risk-losing-control-aids-epidemic-experts-164118164.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The AIDS epidemic risks resurging and spiralling out of control unless billions of extra dollars are pumped into prevention and treatment, experts warned Sunday on the eve of a major world conference. An alarming rate of new infections, coupled with an exploding population of young people in hard-hit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The French village that is so rich the local will pay no taxes...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/french-village-rich-local-pay-145451094.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;State auditors have told a French village near the Spanish border that it is “too rich” to continue taxing residents and should cancel council and property taxes this year. Le Perthus, a community of 586 people, earns more than £700,000 a year from parking fees alone, equivalent to nearly £1,200 per</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censors jump into action as China's latest vaccine scandal ignites...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/censors-jump-action-chinas-latest-vaccine-scandal-ignites-130244024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese censors on Sunday deleted articles and postings about the vaccine industry as an online outcry over the country's latest vaccine scandal intensified. Regulators said last week that they had halted production of a rabies vaccine at a large pharmaceutical company in the northeast after finding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  STANDOFF AT LOS ANGELES TRADER JOE'S...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/21/kcal9-employee-tells-harrowing-story-of-being-held-hostage-inside-trader-joes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lynne Westafer spoke for about 20 minutes and related the fear and fright many inside were feeling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist Dems begin arguing against far-left agenda... </title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/article215241865.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centrist Democrats met this week seeking to convince potential presidential candidates they don’t have to embrace key policies of the party’s liberal base</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOXOFFICE:  'MAMMA MIA!' Flops, Hits All The Wrong Notes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2018/07/mamma-mia-here-we-go-again-equalizer-2-summer-weekend-box-office-1202430132/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;6th Update, Sunday AM: With chart In a box office defeat that no one anticipated, Denzel Washington’s first sequel ever, Equalizer 2, stole most of the No. 1 money away from Universal’s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is he handing off key cases?</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/why-is-mueller-handing-off-key-cases</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something has been going on with Robert Mueller's investigation of people thought to have played significant roles in the Trump-Russia affair. The special counsel, assigned to investigate "any links and/or coordination between the Russian government and individuals associated with the campaign of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILLARY IN A HOUSECOAT</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/07/what-is-she-wearing-hillary-clinton-looks-like-hell-at-ozyfest-in-new-york-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Central Park raccoons die from viral 'zombie' outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2018/07/21/dozens-of-raccoons-die-from-viral-zombie-outbreak-in-central-park/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen Central Park raccoons have died in an ongoing viral outbreak that causes “zombie” behavior in the critters, authorities determined. Of 26 raccoons found dead inside the park sin…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dust Storm Invades Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/dust-storm-invades-las-vegas-heat-wave-coming/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Light sprinkles and intermittent showers are possible Saturday evening after gusts kicked up dusts in the morning, according to the National Weather Service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US fighter jet intercepts plane near Trump resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/latest-news/article215313405.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A U.S. Air Force F-16 fighter jet on Saturday intercepted a small plane near Donald Trump's private golf resort in New Jersey, where the president is currently staying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR fumbles imperil mega-merger...</title>
      <link>http://thehill.com/policy/technology/398149-sinclairs-fumbles-imperil-mega-merger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FCC's rejection of the deal is a striking reversal of fortune for the company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINA TARGETS APPLE...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/china-targets-apple-with-push-into-advanced-smartphone-screens-1532260804</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOE Technology Group, a supplier of screens for iPads and MacBooks, now wants to provide Apple with advanced organic light-emitting diode, or OLED, smartphone screens.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense bill to end Cabinet's direct control of nuclear agency...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/jul/22/trump-administration-control-national-nuclear-secu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bill being negotiated in Congress would essentially end the Trump administration’s direct supervision of an agency that oversees the nation’s nuclear weapons stockpile. The Senate-approved bill would remove the National Nuclear Security Administration from direct control of the Energy Department, where it’s been since its creation in 2000, and empower it to act nearly on its own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How long will Mueller investigation go on?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/22/politics/robert-mueller-russia-investigation-length/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week's indictments could be the high point for his team. Or it could be simply the crest of one of several coming waves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractor rampages through downtown Denver in police pursuit...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2018/07/22/tractor-pursuit-through-downtown-denver/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several Denver Police squad cars pursued a tractor through downtown Denver on Friday night before finally stopping it at 15th and Market streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused Russian agent met with Obama Treasury, Fed officials...</title>
      <link>https://uk.reuters.com/article/uk-usa-russia-butina-exclusive/exclusive-accused-russian-agent-butina-met-with-u-s-treasury-fed-officials-idUKKBN1KC0DE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused Russian agent Maria Butina had wider high-level contacts in Washington than previously known, taking part in 2015 meetings between a visiting Russian official and two senior officials at the U.S. Federal Reserve and Treasury Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: MLB pitcher punished for tweets gets standing ovation...</title>
      <link>https://www.si.com/mlb/2018/07/21/josh-hader-standing-ovation-tweet-scandal-milwaukee-brewers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.si.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several of Hader's years-old racist and homophobic tweets surfaced during the All-Star Game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super rich boost political giving...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2018/07/21/super-rich-step-up-their-giving-ahead-midterm-election-fight/813088002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group committed to helping Republicans retain the House has raised more money than any other super PAC ahead of the Nov. 6 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran warns Trump about 'mother of all wars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-nuclear-usa-rouhani/irans-rouhani-warns-trump-about-mother-of-all-wars-idUSKBN1KC07Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranian President Hassan Rouhani on Sunday cautioned U.S. President Donald Trump about pursuing hostile policies against Tehran, saying "America should know ... war with Iran is the mother of all wars," but he did not rule out peace between the two countries, either.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh scandal erupts over vaccines in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/fresh-scandal-erupts-over-vaccine-safety-china-095141360--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scandal over faulty vaccines in China has sparked anger on social media, underscoring the difficulties regulators face in rebuilding trust after years of food and drug safety controversies. The incident is a major blow for Beijing, which has been trying to push domestically made vaccines and for China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK SHOCK: Toddler injured in acid attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/6837529/three-year-old-seriously-injured-in-acid-attack-as-police-released-image-of-three-men-they-are-hunting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A THREE year old boy has been seriously injured in a suspected acid attack, West Mercia Police have said. Cops released images of three men after the tot was injured in a suspected acid attack in H…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver puts videos of hundreds of passengers online. Most have no idea...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/metro/st-louis-uber-driver-has-put-video-of-hundreds-of/article_9060fd2f-f683-5321-8c67-ebba5559c753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you taken an Uber or Lyft ride in St. Louis this year? You may have been streamed to an online audience without ever knowing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. launches campaign to erode support for Iran's leaders...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20180721211735-3xasc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-IRAN/:U.S. launches campaign to erode support for Iran's leaders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAVILY REDACTED:  Carter Page FISA Court Docs released...</title>
      <link>https://www.judicialwatch.org/press-room/press-releases/judicial-watch-obtains-carter-page-fisa-court-documents/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.judicialwatch.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Washington, DC) – Judicial Watch President Tom Fitton made the following statement regarding today’s release of 412 pages of documents about FISA (Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act) warrants targeting Carter Page, who had been a Trump campaign adviser: These documents are heavily redacted but seem to confirm the FBI and DOJ misled the courts in withholding the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico man who fed wildlife at his home bitten by bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/mexico-man-fed-wildlife-home-bitten-bear-194851590.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALAMOGORDO, N.M. (AP) — Officials say a 70-year-old southern New Mexico man who regularly fed wildlife at his home suffered multiple injuries when he was bitten by a bear as he stepped outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020:  Hillary Clinton appears at Central Park summer festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/hillary-clinton-appear-central-park-summer-festival-025859714.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Hillary Clinton was part of a star-studded lineup at a summer festival in New York's Central Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Gaza and Israel, war fears mount despite truce...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/gaza-israel-war-fears-mount-despite-truce-162401826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After seven chaotic and violent hours, quiet returned to the Gaza Strip overnight. The fatal shooting by a Palestinian of an Israeli soldier during protests along the border Friday sparked a widespread wave of Israeli bombing, with three fighters from Gaza's Islamist rulers Hamas killed and dozens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Who Lost 9 Relatives in Boating Accident Struggles With Why She Survived...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/woman-who-lost-nine-relatives-in-boating-accident-struggles-with-why-she-survived-1532214034</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tia Coleman said she can’t understand how she and a teenage nephew survived the sinking of an amphibious tour boat in a sudden violent storm on Thursday while nine other members of her family died.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hollywood, 'Anything Goes' Becomes 'You're Fired'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/in-hollywood-anything-goes-becomes-youre-fired-1532181601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood’s longstanding say-anything, do-anything culture is rapidly turning into one where the wrong words can kill careers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuba aims to build socialism, not communism, in draft constitution...</title>
      <link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/cubas-president-names-cabinet-resembling-castros-161410089.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By Sarah Marsh HAVANA (Reuters) - A draft of Cuba's new constitution keeps the Communist Party as its leading political force but states as its aim the construction of socialism rather than communism, reflecting changing times, top officials told lawmakers this weekend. Cuba is replacing its Soviet-era</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST PAGE ONE SUNDAY:  In private, Trump vents his frustration over lack of progress on NKorea... </title>
      <link>http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/ct-trump-north-korea-negotiations-20180721-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the weeks since the two leaders met, U.S. negotiators have faced stiff resistance from a North Korean team practiced in the art of delay and obfuscation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostages...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Pursuit-Ends-With-gunshots-at-Trader-Joe-in-Silverlake-488810971.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A police pursuit in the Hollywood area ended in the Silver Lake area at a Trader Joe's with a suspect inside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manafort faces federal trial with hint of presidential pardon...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/manafort-faces-federal-trial-with-a-hint-of-a-presidential-pardon/ar-BBKTJKH?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA authorities recorded privileged attorney-client conversations, district attorney says...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2104485?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES -- After Los Angeles County's public defender expressed concerns about possibly illegal recordings of privileged attorney-client meetings at a downtown courthouse, a spokeswoman for the district attorney has acknowledged that such recordings had "inadvertently...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Suspect Barricaded Inside Los Angeles TRADER JOE'S...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/07/21/reports-of-possible-active-shooter-at-silver-lake-trader-joes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police were responding to a report of shooting at the Trader Joe's near Hyperion Avenue and Silver Lake Boulevard in Silver Lake Saturday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LA TIMES FRONT PAGE SUNDAY:  European govts rethinking their reliance on USA as ally...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-pol-trump-europe-20180718-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Deeply alarmed at President Trump’s attacks on NATO and the transatlantic relationship, European governments are rethinking their reliance on the United States as an ally, a potentially momentous shift that could eventually lead to new security arrangements independent of Washington, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>http://abc7.com/live/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watch live streaming video on ABC7.com and stay up-to-date with the latest KABC news broadcasts as well as live breaking news whenever it happens.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
