<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>25 years after Black Hawk Down, US troops still fighting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/americas-other-endless-war-somalia-11547738433</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The death of Staff Sgt. Alex Conrad puts into sharp relief the cost of America’s long fight against the militant group. It is just one of a series of under-the-radar conflicts, in Africa, South Asia and the Middle East, which have simmered since 9/11.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facing populist assault, global elites regroup in Davos...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/facing-populist-assault-global-elites-regroup-in-davos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVOS, Switzerland (AP) — As the world's financial and political elites convene here in the Swiss Alps for the World Economic Forum, their vision of ever-closer commercial and political ties is under attack — and the economic outlook is darkening....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does corporate debt mountain pose avalanche risk?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190120-does-corporate-debt-mountain-pose-avalanche-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Does the corporate debt mountain pose an avalanche risk?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle over Virgin Mary painting at trailer park goes to higher authority...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/local/article224745285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 85-year-old Bradenton woman is refusing to take down a painting of the Virgin Mary as lawyers get involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Vatican knew bishop close to Pope took naked selfies...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5a2904f21a664229a006f3b9ead429b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ORAN, Argentina (AP) — The Vatican received information in 2015 and 2017 that an Argentine bishop close to Pope Francis had taken naked selfies, exhibited "obscene" behavior and had been accused of misconduct with seminarians, his former vicar general told The Associated Press, undermining Vatican claims that allegations of sexual abuse were only made a few months ago. Francis accepted Bishop Gustavo Zanchetta's resignation in August 2017, after priests in the remote northern Argentine diocese of Oran complained about his authoritarian rule and a former vicar, seminary rector and another prelate provided reports to the Vatican alleging abuses of power, inappropriate behavior and sexual harassment of adult seminarians, said the former vicar, the Rev. Juan Jose Manzano.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected car bomb explodes in Northern Ireland...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190120-suspected-car-bomb-explodes-northern-ireland</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspected car bomb exploded in the Northern Irish city of Derry/Londonderry on Saturday, police said, with leading politicians alleging the blast was terror-related.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tough times for Amsterdam sex business...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46919294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Dutch worry that part of central Amsterdam is now just a sleazy tourist trap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4,141 Latvians Just Outed as K.G.B. Informants...</title>
      <link>https://indianexpress.com/article/world/as-many-as-4141-latvians-were-just-outed-as-kgb-informants-5545765/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;indianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For many the appearance of their names, code names and dates of recruitment in the recently released KGB documents has come as a traumatic surprise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's oldest man dead at 113...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/314fd201b66e40c9a6129ad8f1bc453a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The world's oldest man has died at his home — a hot springs inn — in northern Japan at the age of 113. Masazo Nonaka died in the early hours of Sunday while sleeping at home in Ashoro on Japan's northern main island of Hokkaido, his family said. He died peacefully from natural causes, according to his granddaughter Yuko Nonaka. The supercentenarian, whose family has run a hot springs inn for four generations, was certified by Guinness World Records in April 2018 as the world's oldest living man at 112 years and 259 days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK police speak to Prince Philip about not wearing seatbelt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/230ebe98e327468aa97c714b0dda09bf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — British police have spoken with Prince Philip after the husband of Queen Elizabeth II was photographed apparently driving without wearing a seatbelt — just two days after he was involved in a serious car crash. Norfolk Police said late Saturday "suitable words of advice have been given to the driver". The police spoke to Philip after British media on Saturday published a photograph showing Philip, 97, driving a new Land Rover near the royal residence at Sandringham. Police said the advice given to Philip was "in line with our standard response when being made aware of such images showing this type of offence."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ebola in Congo moving toward major city...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/science-and-health/2019/1/18/18188199/drc-ebola-outbreak</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With at least 680 cases, it’s already the second-largest Ebola outbreak in history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's March Protesters Call For Trump to 'Drop Dead,' His Children Caged...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/01/19/photos-womens-march-protesters-call-for-trump-to-drop-dead-his-children-to-be-caged/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Women's March protesters in Washington, D.C. called for free abortions for all, President Trump's children to be caged, and for Trump to "drop dead."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SIGNAL WILL REJECT</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-19/trump-promises-announcement-on-border-as-talks-remain-stalled</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's Cutest Dog' dies of 'broken heart'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/boo-pomeranian-dead-worlds-cutest-13877935</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boo the Pomeranian's death was announced to his millions of Facebook and Instagram followers this morning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shouting, near fisticuffs, emotions high: Today's DC could get worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Shouting-near-fisticuffs-emotions-high-Today-s-13546818.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - One political rule of life is never ask a question unless you really want to know the answer. Example: It cannot possibly get worse in Washington, can it? By early Thursday afternoon, President Donald Trump and House Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., had traded insults several times. Pelosi called for a delay of Trump's planned Jan. 29 State of the Union address as long as portions of the government were shut down. The president then revoked military support for her weekend trip to visit troops in Afghanistan. A couple days earlier, the House rebuked Rep. Steve King, R-Iowa, for a history of racially and ethnically charged remarks, the latest his questioning of how "white supremacy" had become offensive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dowdy no more: Men in suits storm back into style...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190119-dowdy-no-more-men-suits-storm-back-style</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dowdy no more: Men in suits storm back into style</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans to download souls onto microchips so can 'live forever'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/754342/science-news-microchips-live-forever-ai-immortality-richard-skellett</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Satellite Network to Watch 'Any Process on Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201901191071631216-russian-sovereign-eye-satellite-constellation/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia launched over two dozen satellites into space last year, and had some 146 civilian and military satellites orbiting the planet as of mid-2018, according to UN figures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuels doubts about press...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/government/politics/nation/article_fb1f8062-1c0f-11e9-b129-57d17605e533.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The fact that the normally buttoned-up special counsel's office felt compelled to issue a statement suggests that the story's conclusions were too baldly stated and too consequential to stay unchallenged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety in Alaska as endless aftershocks rattle residents...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/anxiety-alaska-endless-aftershocks-rattle-residents-60491372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Seven weeks after a massive earthquake rocked Alaska, aftershocks are still shattering 7-year-old Connor Cartwright's sense of safety. They shake the earth far less than the 7.0 magnitude quake that sent a mirror, TV and dishes crashing to the ground in the Anchorage home where Connor lives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>777X: Gigantic plane that could change flying forever...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/777x-gigantic-plane-could-change-080000250.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the world’s most prestigious airlines are on tenterhooks as the first flight of an aircraft that could change long-haul travel for decades looms ever closer. Executives at Singapore Airlines, Emirates and Qatar Airways, among others, will have their eyes cast to the skies this spring when Boeing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standup comedy doomed?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/culture/2019/jan/19/is-standup-comedy-doomed-future-of-funny-kevin-hart-louis-ck-nanette</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether it’s censorship, problematic tweets or #MeToo, comics are being scrutinised like never before. Is there a ‘new sense of panic’ in the industry?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human family tree gains new member as scientists confirm 'missing link' ...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2019/01/18/human-family-tree-just-gained-new-member-scientists-confirm/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new &amp;lsquo;missing link&amp;rsquo; between our ape-like ancestors and early humans has been identified, showing that we were still swinging from the trees less than two million years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How real is Clint Eastwood's 'THE MULE'? Prosecutor speaks...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/movies/2019/01/18/mule-prosecutor-leo-sharp-clint-eastwood-detroit/2620800002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood's "The Mule" is loosely based on a true story. Here's what the real prosecutor of the drug case says about the film.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families, Celebs Want New Probe of JFK, RFK, MLK, Malcolm X Assassinations...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/19/jfk-rfk-mlk-malcolm-x-murders-assassinations-conspiracies-reopen-trc/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King, Kennedy Family Calls for New Investigation into JFK, RFK, MLK and Malcolm X assassinations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Ed Buck? Erratic life of Dem donor in whose home two dead men found...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-ed-buck-west-hollywood-20190110-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Who is Ed Buck? The longtime Democratic donor's West Hollywood home has been the site of two men's deaths since 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIRACLE: Rudolph the puppy 'euthanized but lived'...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/2019/01/17/euthanized-dog-woke-up-animal-shelter-davenport-kings-harvest-pet-rescue-save-puppy-no-kill-adopt-ia/2602695002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rudolph was designated to be killed because of a full shelter. When he woke up, another Iowa rescue saved him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem nominee might be someone never heard of!</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/13708fb844264d2fbaf4a2181418ac4d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SOUTH BEND, Ind. (AP) — At 36, Pete Buttigieg is just over the minimum age required to be president of the United States. Outside South Bend, Indiana, the Rust Belt community where he's been mayor since age 29, few people know his name. Those who know it struggle to pronounce it. (It's BOO'-tah-juhj.) None of that has deterred Buttigieg — a Democrat, Rhodes scholar and Navy veteran known to most people as "Mayor Pete" — from contemplating a 2020 presidential bid against a crowd of much better-known lawmakers with more experience and more money.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicious deposits made to account of Brazil president's son: report...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190119-suspicious-deposits-made-account-brazil-presidents-son-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suspicious deposits made to account of Brazil president's son: report</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animal shelters becoming inundated with 'mini pigs'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/mini-pigs-growing-to-be-a-big-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animal shelters across the country are facing an influx of fully-grown pigs from owners who claimed they were duped. As it turns out, there really is no such thing as a true mini pig.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Products made of threatened African wildlife sold at U.S. expo...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/3bc8d6756c424f25bc777af84e3a0643</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RENO, Nev. (AP) — Photos and video taken by animal welfare activists at a recent trophy hunting convention show an array of products crafted from the body parts of threatened big-game animals, including boots, chaps, belts and furniture labeled as elephant leather. Vendors at the Safari Club International event held last week in Reno, Nevada, also were recorded hawking African vacations to shoot captive-bred lions raised in pens. The club has previously said it wouldn't allow the sale of so-called canned hunts at its events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists ID another possible threat to orcas: pink salmon...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/scientists-id-another-possible-threat-to-orcas-pink-salmon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOMO 4 TV provides news, sports, weather and local event coverage in the Seattle, Washington area including Bellevue, Redmond, Renton, Kent, Tacoma, Bremerton, SeaTac, Auburn, Mercer Island, Bothell, Shoreline, Lynnwood, Mill Creek and Everett.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's Marches Aim to Rev Momentum Ahead of 2020...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/womens-marches-aim-to-rev-momentum-ahead-of-2020-11547899201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third annual wave of women’s marches are scheduled in hundreds of cities Saturday, with organizers saying this year’s goal is to build momentum for the 2020 elections. Marches are planned in cities across the U.S., including New York, Boston, Washington, D.C., Houston, Los Angeles and Denver.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hot New Channel for Reaching Real People: Email...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-hot-new-channel-for-reaching-real-people-email-11547874005</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Frustrated and fatigued by social-media challenges, businesses and others looking for an audience turn to an old standby.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Railways Chug Toward Automation...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/american-railways-chug-toward-automation-11547902810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rio Tinto calls it the world’s largest robot: mile-long driverless trains traversing the sparsely populated Australian Outback. American railroad companies call it the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen kill two Buddhist monks in Thailand's troubled south...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-thailand-south/gunmen-kill-two-buddhist-monks-in-thailands-troubled-south-idUSKCN1PC26B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unknown gunmen shot dead two Buddhist monks and injured two others in an attack ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA threatens to pull e-cigs off market, citing possible 'existential threat'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/426140-fda-threatens-to-pull-e-cigarettes-off-the-market-citing-possible</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Food and Drug Administration says that e-cigarettes face an uncertain future in U.S. markets unless youth smoking rates drop over the next year.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
