<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Professor Who Wrote Book on Drug Crime Accused of Money Laundering...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-11-18/professor-wrote-laundering-book-then-washed-millions-u-s-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell 'can't imagine a scenario' in which Senate removes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/470957-mcconnell-cant-imagine-a-scenario-in-which-senate-removes-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) said Monday that he can't envision any scenario in which the GOP-controlled Senate would vote to remove President Trump from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MYSTERY: Massive Fire Destroys Multi-Million Dollar FL 'Mega' Yachts...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/11/18/fire-destroys-2-yachts-worth-24-million-in-fort-lauderdale/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators are working to figure out what may have sparked a major fire that destroyed two multi-million dollar yachts in Fort Lauderdale over the weekend.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS whistleblower case advances...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/IRS-whistleblower-case-advances-as-Senate-staff-14843718.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Two Senators are probing a whistleblower's allegations that at least one political appointee at the Treasury Department may have tried to interfere with the audit of President Donald Trump or Vice President Mike Pence, according to two people with knowledge of the matter, a sign that lawmakers are moving to investigate the complaint lodged by a senior staffer at the Internal Revenue Service.  Staff for Sens. Chuck Grassley, R-Iowa, and Ron Wyden, D-Ore., the chair and ranking Democrat on the Senate finance committee, met with the IRS whistleblower earlier this month, those people said. Follow-up interviews are being scheduled to further explore the whistleblower's allegations.  It could not be learned to what extent the senators view the whistleblower as a credible source. Trump administration officials have previously downplayed the complaint's significance and suggested it is politically motivated.  The whistleblower, a career IRS official, initially filed a complaint in July, reporting that he was told at least one Treasury political appointee attempted to improperly interfere with the annual audit of the president's or vice president's tax returns. In recent weeks, the whistleblower filed additional documentation related to the original complaint, which was given to congressional officials in July, the two people said. These people spoke on the condition of anonymity due to the sensitivity of the complaint, which pertains to a confidential IRS audit that cannot be disclosed under federal law.  The contents of the additional information provided by the whistleblower were not known.  The IRS whistleblower complaint was first disclosed in an August court filing by Rep. Richard Neal, D-Mass., the chair of the House Ways and Means Committee. It raises the prospect that Trump administration officials at...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraqi spy chief warns ISIS is rebuilding...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/18/middleeast/iraq-spy-chief-isis-rebuilding/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISIS financiers have escaped and are planning mass jailbreaks and a resurgence after the death of leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, Iraq's intelligence chief tells CNN in a rare interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supremes block House subpoena of Trump financial records...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/470927-supreme-court-temporarily-blocks-house-subpoena-of-trump-financial</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court has issued a temporary stay of an appeals court ruling that granted House Democrats access to President Trump's financial records, Chief Justice John Roberts announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Discussed 
'Negative Rates' In Unscheduled Meet With Fed Chair...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/fed-says-powell-unexpectedly-met-trump-mnuchin-monday-morning</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATLANTA JOURNAL-CONSTITUTION Editor Questions Accuracy of Clint Eastwood's 'RICHARD JEWELL' Ahead of Premiere...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/atlanta-journal-constitution-editor-questions-accuracy-of-clint-eastwoods-richard-jewell-ahead-of-premiere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's also ironic that a film purporting to hold the media to account disregards such crucial facts," newspaper's editor-in-chief Kevin G. Riley says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming of Los Angeles?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/tom-brady-focused-only-on-the-present-but-expect-him-to-eye-los-angeles-if-he-leaves-patriots/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brady hasn't made any indications he's thinking about the future, but here's why some think L.A. is in play</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Empty Seats Stun Amid Playoff Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/11/17/weak-11-empty-seats-abound-nfl-heads-down-final-stretch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Week 11 came to a close, it was clear that many fans are still avoiding stadiums all across the country even as the league looks to expand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICK-FIL-A Stops Donations To Charities With Anti-LGBT Views...</title>
      <link>https://www.bisnow.com/national/news/retail/exclusive-amid-global-expansion-and-lgbt-pushback-chick-fil-a-changes-charitable-giving-structure-101818</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bisnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chick-fil-A plans to change its charity structure after LGBT protests blocked the company from expanding in several U.S. airports and at locations abroad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESSURE BUILDS ON TRUMP TO TESTIFY</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6d5d4cb9e198475584b993fa950f2de4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Democratic House Speaker Nancy Pelosi invited President Donald Trump to testify in front of investigators in the House impeachment inquiry ahead of a week that will see several...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA softens position on Israel settlements in West Bank...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3da4fb3671004679a91a7d4ae9ab4e57</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Secretary of State Mike Pompeo is expected to announce on Monday that the U.S. is softening its position on Israeli settlements in the occupied West Bank, the latest in a series...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Quality Of Friendships, Not Quantity, Linked To Well-Being...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/for-older-adults-its-the-quality-of-friendships-not-quantity-that-improves-well-being/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study finds that well-being is more closely related to how people feel about their friends than their overall number of friendships.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DEPORTATIONS FEWER THAN OBAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/immigration-jails-in-trump-era-are-packed-but-deportations-are-fewer-than-in-obamas/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has been nearly 700 days since Bakhodir Madjitov was taken to prison in the United States. He has never been charged with a crime. Madjitov, a 38-year-old Uzbek national and father of three U.S. citizens, received a final deportation...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling Brady frustrated following PATRIOTS win...</title>
      <link>https://www.providencejournal.com/sports/20191117/tom-brady-frustrated-following-patriots-17-10-win-in-philadelphia</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.providencejournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHILADELPHIA — Tom Brady walked up to the podium deep inside Lincoln Financial Field and looked angry. Wearing a big camouflage winter jacket and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is GDP 1.9% growth 'the greatest' or 'deep trouble'?</title>
      <link>https://www.palmbeachpost.com/opinion/20191110/bernstein-is-19-percent-growth-the-greatest-or-deep-trouble-according-to-trump-its-both</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.palmbeachpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GDP ain't everything, by a long shot. It's an aggregate measure of the dollar value of what the economy produces, and it fails to account for both</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 DEAD AT OKLAHOMA WALMART... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.kswo.com/2019/11/18/reports-shots-fired-inside-duncan-wal-mart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kswo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Duncan Police Chief Danny Ford tells us that three people were killed outside the store near a vehicle. One of the people killed is the shooter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Ex-Top Cop: He Must Be Investigated... </title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/british-ex-top-cop-prince-andrew-must-be-investigated-over-epstein-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FBI also reportedly preparing to analyze disastrous interview for ongoing probe into billionaire pedophile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLITICO reporter &amp; MSNBC contributor sued by White House official...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/white-house-official-sues-politico-targets-schiffs-role-in-impeachment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impeachment inquiry against President Trump has triggered a wave of charges, countercharges, court battles, subpoenas and legal threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS:   Possible Pay-To-Play Scheme For Ambassador Role Uncovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/doug-manchester-possible-pay-to-play-scheme-for-ambassador-role-in-trump-administration-uncovered/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Emails obtained by CBS News show Trump's nominee for ambassador to the Bahamas was asked by the RNC to donate half a million dollars as his confirmation in the Senate hung in the balance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camel, Cow, Donkey Found Roaming Together Along Kansas Road...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/best-states/kansas/articles/2019-11-18/camel-cow-donkey-found-roaming-together-along-kansas-road</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  Tom Hanks Playing Mr. Rogers May Save Us All...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/a-beautiful-day-in-the-neighborhood-finally-something-nice-tom-hanks-playing-mr-rogers-may-save-us-all</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hollywood’s living saint playing America’s one true hero: What we can learn from the Hanks-Rogers niceness summit in the new film “A Beautiful Day in the Neighborhood.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With safe injection sites, 'Somebody has to go first.' It could be Philadelphia...</title>
      <link>https://www.penncapital-star.com/health-care/with-safe-injection-sites-somebody-has-to-go-first-it-could-be-philadelphia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.penncapital-star.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of jail and facing uncertain future, Brazil's Lula trying to stage improbable comeback...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Out-of-jail-and-facing-an-uncertain-future-14843261.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RECIFE, Brazil - The spectacle known as Lula is on the move. Thousands of people in red are massing in the streets. There are demands to remember the poor. And Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the leftist former president of Brazil, is overlooking the throngs, booming into a microphone.  Fresh out of prison, Lula, as he is widely known, is a gifted orator who for decades has been one of Latin America's most influential figures. After serving 580 days for corruption and money laundering, he was released this month on grounds that he had been denied due process.  For now, he is free to give speeches like one at this seaside city on Sunday - or at least until he exhausts all of his appeals.  The uncertainty of his legal situation underscores his political limitations and the obstacles that lie before him in his apparent quest to reassert himself as Brazil's dominant political leader.  He is out of prison, but he is not innocent. He is back in public, but is making appearances only where he is assured to receive a warm welcome. He has spent much of his adult life either running for or being president, but is now barred from doing so because of his criminal record. Even some on the left aren't rejoicing at his return. "Snake charmer," one prominent center-left politician here called him last week.  It is clear that Lula - who has been tweeting, giving speeches and holding rallies since the moment of his release - wants Brazil back. But is the feeling mutual? Or has Lula, who left office with an 80 percent approval rating, become too polarizing, too associated with scandal and corruption, to ever again command widespread support?  In recent polls, 58 percent of Brazilians said they had a negative impression of him while 34 percent had a positive one. By that measure, he is less popular than Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil unrest haunts those who remember juntas...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/sns-tns-bc-latinamerica-military-20191118-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY Unrest in Latin America is putting the region's soldiers back into the public eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIREFOX fight for future of the web...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/17/firefox-mozilla-fights-back-against-google-chrome-dominance-privacy-fears</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Google’s Chrome dominating the market, not-for-profit rival Mozilla is staking a comeback on its dedication to privacy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Soledad O'Brien Became Mainstream Media's Most Outspoken Critic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/how-soledad-obrien-became-cnn-and-the-mainstream-medias-most-outspoken-critic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former CNN host turned CEO and film producer sounds off to Lloyd Grove about why the cable news media’s been such an embarrassment during the Trump era.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo draws president's ire...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/trump-s-impeachment-ire-turns-pompeo-amid-diplomats-starring-roles-n1082716</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Impeachment hearings have created a rift between the president and one of his staunchest allies in the administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's fastest car' hits 628mph in warm-up for 1,000mph record attempt...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/worlds-fastest-car-hits-speeds-20905594</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the test run, which took place in the Hakskeenpan desert, the Bloodhound LSR car went supersonic, leading to the paint being stripped from the vehicle</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malkin fired over support...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/michelle-malkin-fired-from-conservative-group-and-condemned-for-backing-alt-right-holocaust-denier/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conservative commentator Michelle Malkin has been fired by the Young America's Foundation (YAF) for defending a Holocaust-denying, far-right activist who has been trying to ingrain the alt-right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESLA Supercharger catches fire at WAWA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/18/tesla-supercharger-fire-at-wawa-store-in-new-jersey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wawa says Tesla is investigating the cause of the fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Trump-Nixon comparison, Pelosi raises specter of resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-impeachment/in-trump-nixon-impeachment-comparison-pelosi-raises-specter-of-resignation-idUSKBN1XR0N1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is amplifying her unfavorable comparison of Pres...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT OPEN TO TESTIFYING</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/trump/trump-says-he-will-strongly-consider-testifying-in-impeachment-probe-i-like-the-idea/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Monday to lash out at House Speaker Nancy Pelosi. But the president also signaled he is open to her demand he testify in the impeachment inquiry. "Our Cr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaepernick NFL tryout chaos leads to pissed off Jay-Z...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/17/kaepernicks-nfl-tryout-chaos-leads-to-a-pissed-off-jay-z/?_ga=2.107316930.1324931475.1574076632-161878978.1574076632</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kaepernick used the workout as an ad of sorts when the former NFL star debuted a pair of Nike Air Force 1s on the field, which he's created for the brand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snooze cruise: Study sees future for hibernating astronauts...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/201ad6dfcbb04eff845d95456805ba90</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — The European Space Agency says putting astronauts into a state of suspended animation could make it easier to reach other planets. The agency said Monday that its researchers...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaskans experience record high temp, record snowfall -- in same day...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1f8011a791be48049033be0ebd25d3f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANCHORAGE, Alaska (AP) — Alaskans have experienced both a record high temperature and a record amount of snowfall in the same day. The Anchorage Daily News reports the Municipality of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unequal and Irate, Latin America Coming Apart at Seams...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/unequal-and-irate-latin-america-is-coming-apart-at-the-seams</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unequal and Irate, Latin America Is Coming Apart at the Seams</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye Takes Osteen to Church...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/11/17/kanye-west-talks-about-serving-god-during-visit-with-joel-osteen/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rapper Kanye West declared he no longer cares for fame and money but is “in service to God” while performing at a Houston megachurch on Sunday. West, who claims to be in the middle of a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China defends Xinjiang crackdown after massive document leak...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-defends-xinjiang-crackdown-massive-document-leak-100102456.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China on Monday vowed it would "never be soft" in its crackdown in Xinjiang, after a massive leak of government documents shed new light on the mass detention of Muslims in the far-west region. Over 400 pages of internal papers obtained by the New York Times showed that President Xi Jinping</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probe Turns to Ally at Heart of Storm...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/impeachment-probe-turns-trump-ally-090000654.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- After weeks of Republican complaints that the Democrats’ impeachment inquiry relied on secondhand information, the centerpiece of this week’s public hearings is testimony from a man with a direct line to President Donald Trump.The political peril for Trump, who was dealt a series of setbacks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORD May Make New Electric MUSTANG in China...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ford-unveils-electric-mustang-suv-023000014.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Ford Motor Co. is reinventing one of its marquee models -- the Mustang muscle car -- as a battery-powered crossover to become a player in the electric-vehicle market that is expected to take off in the coming decade.In a splashy ceremony Sunday ahead of the Los Angeles Auto Show, the carmaker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: 70% of Americans say Trump actions tied to Ukraine were wrong...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/70-americans-trumps-actions-tied-ukraine-wrong-poll/story?id=67088534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A slim majority of Americans, 51%, believe Trump’s actions were wrong and he should be impeached and removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says no more talks with USA just so Trump can brag...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191118094157-b9g1f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NORTHKOREA-ENVOY/RUSSIA (UPDATE 2, TV):UPDATE 2-N.Korea says no more talks with U.S. just so Trump can brag</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT Editor: Trump Trolling Has Put My Reporters' Lives at Risk...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2019/nov/18/new-york-times-editor-says-trump-has-put-his-reporters-lives-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dean Baquet decries abuse of journalists and defends not calling president racist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Absolutely No Mercy': Leaked Files Expose How Beijing Organized Mass Detentions of Muslims...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/5-takeaways-from-the-leaked-files-on-chinas-mass-detention-of-muslims/ar-BBWRcNT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China building up 'shadow reserves' to counter reliance on US dollar...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/11/18/china-diversifying-fx-reserves-assets-to-counter-us-dollar-exposure.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is heavily exposed to the U.S. dollar, but now, with the risk of "decoupling," Beijing is silently diversifying its reserves to reduce its dependence on the world's largest reserve currency, analysts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Rome's lesson for Washington as impeachment inquiry progresses...</title>
      <link>https://www.baltimoresun.com/opinion/op-ed/bs-ed-op-1118-rome-burning-20191118-ox6vhpnunzfc5olrx3avjv3evi-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.baltimoresun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rome’s fateful slide from republic to empire increasingly appears to augur Washington’s crumbling ethicality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BATTLE RAGES ON HONG KONG CAMPUS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1575c7c2ce5c4cc3a572741b1e806320</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONG KONG (AP) — As night fell in Hong Kong, police tightened a siege Monday at a university campus as hundreds of anti-government protesters trapped inside sought to escape. Protesters...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday football party turns bloody...</title>
      <link>https://www.yourcentralvalley.com/news/crime/multiple-people-shot-in-southeast-fresno/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yourcentralvalley.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRESNO, California (KSEE/KGPE) – Ten people were shot at a gathering in southeast Fresno, and police are calling it a “mass casualty” shooting after four people died. Reports of a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine shot, multiple killed at family gathering in Fresno... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://abc30.com/at-least-9-shot-some-killed-as-gunman-opens-fire-on-family-watching-football-in-fresno-backyard-suspect-still-at-large/5704122/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc30.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Multiple people were shot, and some are dead after police say a suspect opened fire at east central Fresno home during a family gathering Sunday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUND:  Bloomberg Panders on Frisk... </title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2019/11/bloomberg-once-a-tough-talker-becomes-a-pander-bear/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His recent apology for stop-and-frisk probably won’t win him the nomination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will now face frontrunner scrutiny... </title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/pete-buttigieg-iowa-poll-scrutiny-republicans-87d1ec00-8958-411d-9207-c46e6a0ec388.html?</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Top Republicans are taking Buttigieg seriously as a potential general election candidate after his breakout poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SNL' Gay-Themed Sketch Sends SARA LEE Scrambling...</title>
      <link>https://tvline.com/2019/11/17/harry-styles-gay-sara-lee-sketch-snl-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;tvline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saturday Night Live cast member Bowen Yang is calling out the Sara Lee corporation for allegedly censoring Instagram comments spawned by a sketch that aired as part of the Nov. 16 episode. The sexu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy Sends Letter To ABC Demanding Information On Spiked Epstein Story...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/11/17/kevin-mccarthy-letter-abc-jeffrey-epstein/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kevin McCarthy sent a letter to ABC demanding answers surrounding allegations that the network killed a story about alleged sex trafficker Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He dropped f-bombs in nasty letter to judge and got jailed for it. What about his free speech rights?</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/local/palm-beach/fl-ne-judge-criticism-free-speech-case-20191115-znsx2sng2faw5gouhid6woi5se-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man wrote an insulting letter to the South Florida judge handling his civil case, and wound up locked in jail for 30 days. What happened to freedom of speech?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist has been counting butterflies for 47 years and has no plans to stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/this-scientist-has-been-counting-butterflies-for-47-years-and-has-no-plans-to-stop/ar-BBWTXX5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She once called herself 'political conservative'... </title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/politics/nation/a/elizabeth-warren-2020-election-rutgers-penn-20191112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before Elizabeth Warren became a Democrat, the young mother entered a liberal cauldron at Rutgers Law School, where students strived for big, systemic change. How Rutgers and later Penn Law shaped the presidential contender.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Radio Host Fired Midshow After Criticizing Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2019/11/16/craig-silverman-radio-show-donald-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Craig Silverman, a former chief deputy district attorney in Denver and talk-show host on the conservative 710 KNUS radio station, said he was fired mid-show Saturday after criticizing President Don…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SLAM...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/finance/470846-democrats-seize-on-report-of-fedexs-0-tax-bill-to-slam-trumps-tax-plan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats are seizing on a report published by The New York Times on Sunday that found FedEx didn’t owe anything in taxes in fiscal year 2018, a year af</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
