<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Russia calls USA adversary, warns warships to avoid Crimea...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210413103817-sjzzo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-CRISIS/RUSSIA (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Russia calls US an adversary, warns its warships to avoid Crimea</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan to release Fukushima treated radioactive water into sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/japan-says-release-fukushima-treated-radioactive-water-sea-n1263893</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan Fisheries Cooperatives chairman said the decision was “absolutely unacceptable," and protesters demanded the plan be retracted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO urges halt to sale of live wild mammals in food markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210413-who-urges-halt-to-sale-of-live-wild-mammals-in-food-markets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHO urges halt to sale of live wild mammals in food markets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Times Square crowds show NYC returning to life...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/12/times-square-crowds-show-nyc-returning-to-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s something we never expected to cheer: The Mickey Mice are back in Times Square, along with the Batmen and other buskers, including the accept-no-substitutes Naked Cowboy. It’s a …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 not sole cause of excess U.S. deaths in 2020...</title>
      <link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2021-04-covid-sole-excess-deaths.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;medicalxpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By the year 2017, the United States was already suffering more excess deaths and more life years lost each year than those associated with the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020, according to research from demographers Samuel Preston of the University of Pennsylvania and Yana Vierboom of the Max Planck Institute for Demographic Research.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India reels amid surge, affecting world vaccine supply...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-pune-united-kingdom-india-coronavirus-pandemic-55b7313c688b9a4c05a68a9c13e499da</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — The Indian city of Pune is running out of ventilators as gasping coronavirus patients crowd its hospitals. Social media is full of people searching for beds, while relatives...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Kremlin Mouthpiece Warns of 'Inevitable' War With USA Over Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/top-kremlin-mouthpiece-warns-inevitable-105301739.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John MacDougall/AFP via Getty ImagesAll-out cyber-warfare, nation-wide forced black-outs, and the targeted disruption of internet services—for one of the Kremlin’s top propagandists, all of those tactics are fair-game in what she describes as a fated war-to-come against the U.S.“War [with the U.S.] is inevitable,” declared Margarita Simonyan, editor-in-chief of the state-funded media outlets, RT and Sputnik, who believes the conflict will break out when, not if, Putin moves to seize more territory from Ukraine.As Russia’s military buildup on Ukraine’s doorstep mounts, Kremlin loyalists have been urging for even more overt aggression and bloodshed in the campaign to annex Ukraine’s Donbas region. The only thing standing in the way, they say, is U.S. support for their beleaguered neighbor.The club of G7 nations, which includes the U.S., issued a joint statement on Monday demanding an end to Russia’s troop build up on the border with the disputed territory of Donbas in eastern Ukraine, reminiscent of the build-up prior to Russia’s annexation of Crimea in 2014. The U.S. underlined those words by deploying two warships to the Black Sea.On Tuesday, Russia’s deputy foreign minister Sergei Ryabkov threatened retaliation. “We warn the United States that it will be better for them to stay far away from Crimea and our Black Sea coast. It will be for their own good,” he said.The escalation was foreshadowed on state television’s Sunday Evening with Vladimir Soloviev over the weekend. Simonyan explained that it was time for Russia to gear up for a showdown against the U.S., and prophesized a kind of war driven by hacking, the forced disruption of internet access, the shutting down of power supplies, and an all-out offensive on U.S. infrastructure.“I do not believe that this will be a large-scale hot war, like World War II, and I do not believe that there will be a long Cold War. It will be a war of the third type: the cyber war,” said Simonyan.She warned that—in this theoretical battle—the U.S. would plot to cut off the electricity of entire Russian cities. In turn, she speculated, Moscow would be able to force a black-out in Florida or Harlem at the flip of a switch.“In conventional war, we could defeat Ukraine in two days,” Simonyan said, “but it will be another kind of war. We’ll do it, and then [the U.S.] will respond by turning off power to [the Russian city] Voronezh,” she said.The top RT editor asserted that “[Russia] needs to be ready for this war, which is unavoidable, and of course it will start in Ukraine,” arguing that the Kremlin is “invincible where conventional war is concerned, but forget about conventional war... it will be a war of infrastructures, and here we have many vulnerabilities.”Her solution consists of Stalin-type measures to eliminate “vulnerabilities” in the run-up to another escalation, emphasizing the need for a hack-proof, government-controlled internet. “We still don’t have a sovereign internet, but god-willing, we will,” she said.She wholeheartedly endorsed a suggestion from Vladimir Zhirinovsky, the leader of one of Russia’s Liberal Democratic Party, who argued that all of Russia’s opposition must be eliminated by May 1, 2021. With imprisoned opposition leader Alexei Navalny on a hunger strike—and suffering from severe health ailments after being denied appropriate medical treatment—the Kremlin seems to be firmly set on that course.Simonyan argued that once Russia minimizes its vulnerabilities and renders Putin’s opposition powerless—which she argued could happen in a matter of months—the Kremlin will finally be ready to annex Ukraine’s eastern region.“I’ve been agitating and even demanding that we take Donbas. We need to patch up our vulnerabilities as fast as we can, and then we can do whatever we want,” she boldly proclaimed. The host, Vladimir Soloviev, wholeheartedly agreed: “We only lose if we do nothing.” He argued that by absorbing parts of Ukraine—or the entire country—Russia would be able to remove the zone of American influence further away from its borders.As one of the Kremlin’s most valued propagandists, Margarita Simonyan is notoriously close to the Russian president and has received multiple awards directly from Vladimir Putin. After accepting one such award in 2019, Simonyan thanked Putin “for the most important reward in life… this honor to serve one’s Motherland.”Her “service” has involved RT and Sputnik-driven disinformation operations aimed at influencing the 2016 U.S. presidential election, which she often boasts about by pointing to the inclusion of her name in various U.S. intelligence reports.Russia’s recent cyberspace activities seem to serve as good practice for the “inevitable war” foreshadowed by Simonyan.Last year, six Russian intelligence officers were criminally charged by the U.S. for using the world’s most destructive malware to force blackouts in Ukraine and damage the critical infrastructure of multiple countries, which caused nearly $1 billion in losses. On Monday, hackers operating from Russia targeted France's homeschooling platform.The Kremlin is prepared to intensify its offensive against the West, but fears of the retaliation that would follow. The idea of a bullet-proof “sovereign internet”—completely under government control within Russian borders—is already on the books, with Moscow having introduced the idea as a preventative measure against retaliatory hacking attempts from other nations.Simonyan argued that Russia will surely be able to exploit the U.S.’s “catastrophic” educational standards, and referred to American military analysts and specialists as incompetent and stupid. She heartily laughed about news that more than 200,000 U.S. service members experienced hearing loss due to defective earplugs.“We can never come to any agreements with [Americans],” Simonyan said, arguing that instead, Russia can just as easily defeat the U.S. in a cyberspace war.She added, mockingly: “We don’t even need the nukes.”Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Cuomo's White-Knuckle Ride...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/13/andrew-cuomos-white-knuckle-ride/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Andrew Cuomo lives, still, in a 40-room Victorian mansion on Eagle Street in downtown Albany, despite the television correspondents descending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop who 'mistakenly' used gun 25-year vet...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2690090/senior-female-cop-identified-daunte-wright-death-2/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE senior female cop who allegedly shot and killed Daunte Wright by accident was named, as a state of emergency was declared in Minneapolis. Kimberly Potter, a 25-year veteran of the force, allege…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to anger, and stakes, as Chauvin trial nears end...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/minnesota-killing-adds-to-the-anger-and-the-stakes-as-chauvin-trial-nears-its-end/ar-BB1fA1Ef</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting death by police of Daunte Wright added to fears of unrest after the verdict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN reporter confronted in heated on-air interview...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cnn-reporter-confronted-during-minnesota-protests-in-heated-on-air-interview-get-away-from-here/ar-BB1fB3tF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A demonstrator confronted CNN’s Sara Sidner in a live interview during protests over Daunte Wright's fatal police shooting, demanding that CNN leave the scene.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: More clashes in Minnesota after Black motorist shot dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/13/us/daunte-wright-minnesota-shooting-tuesday/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furious over the fatal shooting of a Black man by a police officer during a traffic stop, demonstrators gathered Monday night to protest outside the police department of a Minneapolis suburb for a second night in a row.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italian priest hangs up cassock for love...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/italian-priest-hangs-up-cassock-for-love-01618308317</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Churchgoers in a small town in central Italy assembled for mass as usual were hardly expecting a confession from their own parish priest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan's spike highlights fatigue over restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/547815-michigans-spike-highlights-fatigue-over-restrictions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes are on Michigan as the state endures a surge of COVID-19 cases, underscoring how fatigue with coronavirus restrictions, and political divisions, have disrupted the response to the pandemic across the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers urged to re-think police calls for low-level crimes...</title>
      <link>https://www.startribune.com/retailers-urged-to-re-think-police-calls-for-low-level-crimes-after-george-floyd-s-death/600044887/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.startribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the trial over George Floyd's death unfolds, many are hoping the case will prompt retailers to reassess how they treat Black and other minority customers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii allows nurses perform abortions...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/hawaii-to-allow-nurses-to-perform-abortions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hawaii law previously said only physicians could perform early, in-clinic abortions. But because of a doctor shortage, several smaller islands lack abortion providers which forces residents of those islands to fly to Honolulu if they need the procedure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battleground: Concrete barriers erected...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9463537/Twins-Wolves-Wild-postpone-games-following-police-shooting.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz announced a curfew from 7 p.m. Monday until 6 a.m. Tuesday for three counties following the death of Daunte Wright.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boehner says 'unemployed' Trump has nothing else to do but 'cause trouble'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/news/547712-boehner-says-unemployed-trump-has-nothing-else-to-do-but-cause-trouble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio) on Monday said the "unemployed" former President Trump has nothing better to do than stir up trouble following his departure from Washington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: PANDEMIC AT 'CRITICAL POINT'</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pandemic-hits-critical-point-europe-202237675.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Europe passed the grim milestone of one million coronavirus deaths on Monday, as the World Health Organization warned that infections are rising exponentially despite widespread efforts aimed at stopping them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Minneapolis under curfew after officer shoots Black motorist dead...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/judge-refuses-sequester-floyd-trial-170813221.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Minneapolis curfew was set to begin Monday after a police officer fatally shot a young Black man when she confused her handgun with her taser, fueling tensions in a US city already on edge because of the George Floyd murder trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE END:   Iconic Hollywood Cinemas Shutter Due To Economic Woes...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/arclight-cinemas-and-pacific-theatres-wont-be-reopening-1234732936/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: The last thing we needed to hear as the box office and exhibition are rebounding from the pandemic was a piece of bad news, but word spread like wildfire in distribution and exhibition c…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOMINO'S using robots to deliver pizza...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/dominos-pizza-announces-autonomous-delivery-nuro-r-2-self-driving-car/10510677/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gone are the days of having your pizza delivered by someone. Now, Domino's is launching its on-road robot in this part of Houston. Here's how it works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airborne plastic pollution 'spiralling around the globe'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2021/apr/12/airborne-plastic-pollution-spiralling-around-the-globe-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rising levels of microplastic pollution raise questions about the impact on human health, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasal spray 'kills off 99.99% of virus'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2689351/nasal-spray-kills-off-covid/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A COVID-busting nasal spray has been proven to kill 99.99 per cent of the virus, research shows. It could prevent the transmission of coronavirus. For those infected it could shorten the duration o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Students at North Texas school disciplined for 'slave trade' held over socials...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/education/article250615554.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Aledo school district confirmed students cyberbullied and harassed other students based on their race, but did not provide further specifics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen to meet with prosecutors FOR NINTH TIME in Trump probe; Have given 300 hours of testimony...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/manhattan/ny-michael-cohen-meeting-manhattan-prosecutors-ninth-time-300-hours-cooperation-20210412-pr34536bkzbtpmlxpalg4rcvby-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cohen's latest rendezvous with Manhattan District Attorney Cyrus Vance’s team of investigators — headed by veteran white-collar prosecutor Mark Pomerantz — will add to more than 300 hours Cohen’s already spent cooperating against his former boss in various investigations, the source said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds to anger, and stakes, as Chauvin trial nears end...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/minnesota-killing-adds-to-the-anger-and-the-stakes-as-chauvin-trial-nears-its-end/ar-BB1fA1Ef?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooting death by police of Daunte Wright added to fears of unrest after the verdict.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bicyclist killed in crash tweeted just hours earlier about danger of riding in DC!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bicyclist-killed-in-crash-tweeted-just-hours-earlier-about-the-danger-of-riding-in-dc/ar-BB1fA1aX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jim Pagels, an economics PhD student, was passionate about biking and advocated for road safety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jewish population at lowest percentage since founding of Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/jews-make-up-smallest-percentage-of-population-since-founding-of-israel-664899</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Close to the establishment of the state, the Jewish percentage of the population stood at 82.1%, while today it stands at only 73.9%.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lachlan Murdoch Rejects ADL Calls To Fire Tucker Carlson...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/tucker-carlson-lachlan-murdoch-fox-news-anti-defamation-league-1234732832/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox Corp. CEO Lachlan Murdoch responded to the Anti Defamation League’s call for the ouster of Tucker Carlson, concluding that the Fox News host was not advocating for “white replacemen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Indicted on 11 Sex Assault Charges in LA...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/harvey-weinstein-new-indictment-rape-charges-los-angeles-extradition-hearing-1234732596/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With a new indictment coming down from a Los Angeles grand jury, Harvey Weinstein’s long delayed extradition hearing in upstate New York to face West Coast justice just hit the pause button anew. D…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Ellison bought $80 million Palm Beach tear down...</title>
      <link>https://www.vox.com/recode/2021/4/12/22380192/larry-ellison-lanai-hawaii-palm-beach-mansion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vox.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Oracle founder moved to Hawaii late last year. He’s not coming back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontario hospitals may have to withhold care as hospitals fill...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-canada-hospitals-idUSKBN2BZ205</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doctors in the Canadian province of Ontario may soon have to decide who can and cannot receive treatment in intensive care as the number of coronavirus infections sets records and patients are packed into hospitals still stretched from a December wave.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA suspended...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210412-nba-suspends-minnesota-game-over-fatal-police-shooting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBA suspends Minnesota game over fatal police shooting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pain At The Pump: Gas Prices Soar To Nation-Leading $4 In San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/04/12/gas-pump-sticker-shock-bay-area-approaching-nation-leading-4-a-gallon/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just in time for California's reopening from all COVID-19 restrictions and the first unencumbered summer travel season since 2019, prices at the gas pump have again soared to a nation's high of $3.99 a gallon in San Francisco.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 P.M. Curfew...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/12/7-p-m-curfews-go-into-effect-for-twin-cities-metro-area-after-daunte-wright-shooting-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Tim Walz is calling for a curfew Monday evening following Sunday's officer-involved fatal shooting of Daunte Wright in Brooklyn Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Deshaun Watson every play for TEXANS again?</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2021/04/12/texans-remove-deshaun-watson-from-intro-to-in-house-tv-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s the latest tangible sign that quarterback Deshaun Watson won’t be part of the Houston Texans’ future. Via Rivers McCown, the Texans have removed Watson from the introduction to the teams’ online TV show, Texans 360. The development comes during an offseason that has seen Watson request a trade and that, more recently, has seen [more]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jumps to record $1.7 trillion -- this year!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-72cfb190291ce19c33938e6183391453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The U.S. government's budget deficit surged to an all-time high of $1.7 trillion for the first six months of this budget year, nearly double the previous record, as another round...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weinstein Indicted on 11 Sex Assault Charges in LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/harvey-weinstein-los-angeles-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Harvey Weinstein was indicted on 11 sexual assault charges in Los Angeles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women Stressed Out Before Pregnancy Twice As Likely To Have Girl...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/women-stressed-out-before-pregnancy-twice-likely-have-girl/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Several studies have shown fetuses are vulnerable to the effect of stress, since it plays a key role in their development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman caught Covid, got vaccinated, then became infected again...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/12/alaska-woman-caught-covid-got-vaccinated-then-got-it-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Alaska woman says she tested positive for COVID-19 after she was fully vaccinated — and after she had already contracted the virus before she got the jab. Kim Akers, of Palmer, said she wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Personalized' Cancer Vaccines Show Promise In Early Trials...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/personalized-cancer-vaccine/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an average of 880 days, four of those patients showed no signs of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB game postponed...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/04/12/twins-game-against-red-sox-postponed-after-daunte-wright-shooting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Minnesota Twins are postponing Monday’s game against the Red Sox after the fatal shooting of Daunte Wright, which has caused widespread protests throughout the city. Wright was killed dur…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Skilled predator' FBI boss harassed 8 women, watchdog finds...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fbi-james-hendricks-sexually-harassed-8-women-b2b7653303d5d56c5bee61c137ec4b22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — One woman carried a ruler at FBI headquarters so she could smack James Hendricks’ hands when he reached for her legs and breasts. Another went home shaken after he tugged on her...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time, spacecraft caught active satellite to extend its life...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/northrop-grumman-mev-2-spacecraft-services-intelsat-1002-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Northrop Grumman and Intelsat accomplished a space industry first on Monday, with a small spacecraft docking with an active satellite in orbit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservationists spreading pathogens to threatened species?</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210412-are-conservationists-spreading-pathogens-to-threatened-species</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Are conservationists spreading pathogens to threatened species?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER -- but for cannabis delivery...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/uber-ceo-says-company-could-get-into-cannabis-delivery.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uber could start delivering cannabis once federal regulation allows the company to do so, CEO Dara Khosrowshahi told CNBC on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistook Handgun For Taser?</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/04/12/holy-st-i-just-shot-him-brooklyn-center-releases-body-camera-footage-of-police-killing-of-daunte-wright/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During a press conference Monday afternoon, officials in Brooklyn Center released body camera footage of the fatal police shooting of 20-year-old Daunte Wright.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine President heads to trenches as Russia masses troops...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/12/europe/ukraine-zelensky-front-lines/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tens of thousands of Russian troops gathered across the Ukrainian border are raising fears of an invasion. Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky visited troops on the front line and told CNN he wants more support from the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC:  MICHIGAN NEEDS TO CLOSE</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-michigan-cdc-director-vaccine-3a387859-a6d9-4e17-81d2-56ff6d747d89.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rochelle Walensky said the state can't vaccinate its way out of the surge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moby on fame and regret: 'I was out-of-control, utterly entitled drug addict'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2021/apr/12/moby-on-fame-and-regret-i-was-an-out-of-control-utterly-entitled-drink-and-drug-addict</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He declared his intention to go away for a while after pointed criticism of his second memoir. But now the musician is back with a new album - and a visceral documentary</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bogus reporter grilled Jen Psaki for weeks!</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/04/09/lego-gamer-infiltrated-white-house-press-480673</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Kacey Montagu" posed as a reporter for the fictitious WHN and managed to fool real correspondents — and even the new Biden administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>States growing fewer trees. Forest owners say that's a problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2021/04/05/states-are-growing-fewer-trees-forest-owners-say-thats-a-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Half of America’s forestland is privately owned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ROCK Says He'll Run For President If It's 'What The People Want'...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/dwayne-johnson-says-hell-run-for-president-if-its-what-the-people-want-163810</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor recently reacted to a poll that found that at least 46 percent of Americans would support his run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's priciest painting may be a Leonardo after all!</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worlds-priciest-painting-may-leonardo-143932092.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world's most expensive painting, the "Salvator Mundi", may be the work of Leonardo da Vinci after all, with several media reports contradicting doubts raised in a French documentary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN:  Prison threatens to force-feed Navalny...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russian-prison-threatens-force-feed-134718237.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian prison officials are threatening to start force-feeding jailed Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny, his team said Monday, after he lost eight kilograms (18 pounds) since starting a hunger strike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran accuses Israel of sabotage at nuclear site, vows revenge...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/iran-blames-israel-attack-natanz-090343038.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran charged Monday that its arch-enemy Israel was behind an attack on its Natanz uranium enrichment plant and vowed it would take "revenge" and ramp up its nuclear activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers developing blood test to gauge depression...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/researchers-develop-blood-test-that-could-help-gauge-depression-bipolar-disorder</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say they found a way to tell from a person’s blood how severe their depression is, the risk of developing severe depression in the future and the risk of future bipolar disorder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TX Gov. says state 'very close' to herd immunity. Data tells different story...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/houston-texas/article/abbott-herd-immunity-texas-16093952.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Texas Gov. Greg Abbott said</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rallies fizzle...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/unlawful-assembly-declared-white-supremacist-rally-9536047a-f3ab-4faf-b299-580a40164d19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poor showings demonstrate how the white supremacist movement has been driven underground since the U.S. Capitol riots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>536:  Historians pinpoint very worst year EVER to be alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/severe-weather/historians-pinpoint-the-very-worst-year-to-ever-be-alive/927803</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Next time you think we have it hard today, remember what life was like during this truly terrible year. Even after it ended, a decade of pain and suffering followed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives fight for leverage amid ever-slimming majority...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/547454-progressives-fight-for-leverage-amid-ever-slimming-majority</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressives are ascendant in the Democratic-controlled Congress, but they may not have the political leverage to dramatically shape legislative priorities like President Biden’s infrastructure and jobs package as they return to Washington this week with an even slimmer majority.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER ONE:  Navy destroyer captures mysterious flashing UFOs...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2683726/us-navy-filmed-ufo-sky-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE Pentagon has admitted the US Navy filmed “pyramid” and “spherical” shaped UFOs buzzing two warships. Startling footage captured by a US Navy destroyer using night vision…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'White Lives Matter' rally ends early as outnumbered marchers chased by counter-protesters...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2681680/white-lives-matter-rally-huntington-beach-counter-protesters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A “WHITE Lives Matter” rally in Orange County was cut short after the marchers were outnumbered and chased down by a hundreds-strong swarm of “anti-fascist” counter-proteste…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman high on bath salts claiming to be Harry Potter kills federal judge in hit-and-run...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/new-york-judge-killed-by-erratic-hit-and-run-driver-in-possession-of-bath-salts-police/2992432/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida woman who claimed she is Harry Potter struck and killed a federal judge visiting from New York and seriously injured a 6-year-old boy after swerving her car onto a sidewalk, officials said. The crash occurred Friday morning in Boca Raton, Florida. According to multiple reports, U.S. District Judge Sandra Feuerstein was walking on a sidewalk when a car…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA NOT:  Gaetz denied audience with Trump...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/04/11/politics/matt-gaetz-donald-trump-denied-meeting/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz, who's facing a federal investigation into sex trafficking allegations, was recently denied a meeting with Donald Trump at his Mar-a-Lago estate as the ex-President and his allies continue to distance themselves from the Florida congressman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS RAMPAGES THROUGH INDIA...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/coronavirus-india-becomes-second-worst-hit-country-as-covid-cases-surge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The South Asian nation reported more than 168,000 new cases over a 24-hour period on Monday, according to health ministry data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eyes Potential Threat From China's Digital Yuan Plans...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-team-eyes-potential-threat-220001877.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Biden administration is stepping up scrutiny of China’s plans for a digital yuan, with some officials concerned the move could kick off a long-term bid to topple the dollar as the world’s dominant reserve currency, according to people familiar with the matter.Now that China’s digital-currency efforts are gathering momentum, officials at the Treasury, State Department, Pentagon and National Security Council are bolstering their efforts to understand the potential implications, the people said.American officials are less worried about an immediate challenge to the current structure of the global financial system, but are eager to understand how the digital yuan will be distributed, and whether it could also be used to work around U.S. sanctions, the people said on the condition of anonymity.A Treasury spokeswoman declined to comment. A National Security Council spokeswoman did not reply to a request for comment.The People’s Bank of China has rolled out trial issuance of a digital yuan in cities across the country, putting it on track to be the first major central bank to issue a virtual currency. A broader roll-out is expected for the Winter Olympics in Beijing next February, giving the effort international exposure.Many key details of the digital yuan are still in flux, including specifics on how it would be distributed. China’s recent establishment of a joint venture with SWIFT, the messaging nexus through which most cross-border settlements pass through today, suggests it is possible a digital yuan could work within the current financial architecture rather than outside of it.U.S. officials are reassured that China’s intentions aren’t to use the digital yuan to evade American sanctions, according to people familiar with the matter. The dollar’s current dominance in cross-border transactions gives the U.S. Treasury the power to cut off much of a business or even a country’s access to the global financial system.China’s officials have said the main intentions of the digital yuan are to replace banknotes and coins, to reduce the incentive to use cryptocurrencies and to complement the current private-sector run electronic payments system -- dominated by Ant Group Co.’s Alipay and Tencent Holdings Ltd.’s WeChat Pay. The PBOC has been working for years on the digital yuan, also called the e-CNY, having set up a specialist research team in 2014.Here’s How a Central Bank Digital Currency Could Work: Chart​​“To provide a backup or redundancy for the retail payment system, the central bank has to step up” and provide digital-currency services, Mu Changchun, the director of the PBOC’s digital-currency research institute, said at an event last month.Beyond seeking a backup to privately run e-payments, Chinese regulators have more broadly been expanding their oversight of the country’s digital champions. Ant Group was told by Beijing to become a financial holding company, which will be regulated more like a bank. China also imposed a $2.8 billion antitrust fine on Ant’s affiliate Alibaba Group Holding Ltd.Read More: Ant to Be Financial Holding Firm in Overhaul Forced by ChinaThe PBOC is also examining the potential for using the digital yuan in cross-border payments, launching a project studying the issue with a unit of the Bank for International Settlements along with the United Arab Emirates, Thailand and Hong Kong’s monetary authority.The Biden administration isn’t currently planning to take any action to counter longer-term threats from China’s digital currency, the people familiar with the discussions said. However, China’s plans have given renewed impetus to efforts to consider the creation of a digital dollar, they said.Members of Congress have also been increasingly interested in a digital dollar, aware of China’s moves, and asked Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell and Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen about the issue in hearings earlier this year.Powell: Need for Digital Dollar Is an Issue for Congress, PublicPowell said in February the Fed was looking “very carefully” at a digital dollar. “We don’t need to be the first. We need to get it right.”Yellen has signaled interest in research into the viability of a digital dollar, a shift from a lack of enthusiasm under her predecessor, Steven Mnuchin.“It makes sense for central banks to be looking at” issuing sovereign digital currencies, she said at a virtual conference in February. Yellen said a digital version of the dollar could help address hurdles to financial inclusion in the U.S. among low-income households.A recent report from the U.S. Director of National Intelligence said the extent of the threat of any foreign digital currency to the dollar’s centrality in the global financial system “will depend on the regulatory rules that are established.”China’s currency makes up little more than 2% of global foreign exchange reserves compared with nearly 60% for the U.S. dollar. Policy decisions, rather than technical developments, will also be necessary to push forward yuan internationalization, as China maintains a strict regime of capital controls.China’s financial system is too “fragile and weak” to pose a real threat to the dollar’s status as the world’s reserve currency, according to Mark Sobel, U.S. chairman for the Official Monetary and Financial Institutions Forum.“At the end of the the day the markets have more confidence in the Fed” than China’s central bank, said Sobel, a former senior U.S. Treasury official for international matters.(Adds reference to China’s regulatory measures in 10th paragraph.)For more articles like this, please visit us at bloomberg.comSubscribe now to stay ahead with the most trusted business news source.©2021 Bloomberg L.P.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLORADO NEW HOTSPOT</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/04/09/colorado-covid-fourth-wave-young-people/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just as Colorado was given its first dose of hope at COVID-19 restrictions being fully lifted, Governor Jared Polis said a fourth wave of COVID-19 cases has arrived in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith 'EMANCIPATION' Pulls Production From Georgia Over New Voting Restrictions...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/04/apple-will-smith-antoine-fuqua-runaway-slave-movie-emancipation-georgia-exit-election-law-1234732247/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED, 6:01 AM: The Georgia exit for Emancipation is now official. Said star Will Smith and director Antoine Fuqua: “At this moment in time, the Nation is coming to terms with its history a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds shroud ID of hacker who forfeited stolen Bitcoin now worth $4 billion!</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/doj-bitcoin-forfeiture-412750</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;APRIL 12--Thanks to the ballooning value of Bitcoin, the U.S. government could liquidate more than $4 billion in cryptocurrency confiscated from a hacker whose identity--despite an array of felonio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Smith 'EMANCIPATION' Pulls Production From Georgia Over Voting Laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/will-smith-antoine-fuquas-emancipation-pulls-production-georgia-voting-restrictions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antoine Fuqua and Will Smith's pre-Civil War drama "Emancipation" will move production from Georgia due to the state's new voting restriction laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO: Pandemic at 'critical point' as cases rise exponentially...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/12/who-says-covid-pandemic-is-growing-exponentially-at-more-than-4point4-million-new-cases-a-week.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vax Requirements Spread in USA, Sowing Concern on Overreach...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/vaccine-requirements-spread-in-us-sowing-concern-on-overreach/ar-BB1fvESh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Covid-19 vaccination requirements are fast becoming facts of life in the U.S., spreading business by business even as politicians and privacy advocates rail against them. Brown, Notre Dame and Rutgers are among universities warning students and staff they’ll need shots in order to return to campus this fall. Some sports teams are demanding proof of vaccination or a negative test from fans as arenas reopen. Want to see your...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: Bay of Pigs has lessons for our time...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/547637-bay-of-pigs-has-lessons-for-our-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It forced JFK to take stock, re-evaluate ... and act accordingly — in essence, to learn from his mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brits Get Morning Drunk in the Snow to Celebrate Grand Reopening...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brits-morning-drunk-snow-celebrate-134918774.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ITV NewsIt’s been a long, cold, lonely winter in England.So, as four months of a nationwide lockdown finally came to an end, nothing was going to stop people from enjoying a refreshing pint of beer at the crack of dawn on a Monday morning—not even driving rain, freezing temperatures, and some pretty unseasonal snowfall.Pubs started serving outdoors again as part of a reopening plan that also covers indoor gym sessions, swimming pools, non-essential shops, beauty salons, and, for those who have been gagging to see some sad animals, zoos. Prime Minister Boris Johnson had urged people to “behave responsibly” with their new freedoms, but didn’t explicitly say they shouldn’t get drunk in the snow before having breakfast.One pub in the town of Huddersfield was swamped when it opened at the stroke of midnight. “We didn’t even know if anyone was going to come,” said the pub landlord fittingly named Ian Snowball. “It’s in Huddersfield, it’s midnight, it’s freezing cold—but look, everyone has come.”If you thought you were starting early today… 🍻These drinkers in Huddersfield braved the snow to enjoy a beer garden pint at midnight ❄️https://t.co/UASiR7bXEv pic.twitter.com/i2O79eocSR— BBC Breakfast (@BBCBreakfast) April 12, 2021 One drinker commented matter-of-factly: “It was snowing earlier but I was still going to come out, I just put my coat on.” Another, sitting in a thick jacket next to an icy-looking gin and tonic, made the fair point: “After 14 months of not going anywhere, except funerals, it’s a great place.”Sky News reported that 50 pub-goers headed to the Fox On The Hill pub in south London this morning. The most emotional was perhaps Tony Blake, 59, who gushed to the news network: “I am so happy that it’s open again, it’s unbelievable, I’m so happy.” Student Sasha Carrington, 19, said she planned to stay there for the entire freezing cold day, explaining: “We’ve got our layers on, thermals, we’re going to stay outside.”Pippa Ingram, 51, and Sue Bell, 55, celebrated a chilly seaside pint in Kent, with Ingram describing her first sip in detail. “Absolutely delicious,” she said. “It’s not gonna last long at all! That is banging.” Back in Huddersfield, in footage timestamped at 8.17 a.m., a woman identified only as Sandy was seen having pints with her friends, and she told Good Morning Britain: “It’s not that cold after a while when you’re sat in the sun.”As pub gardens reopen from today, @NickDixonITV talks to some people who have enjoyed a pint since 8am this morning.They discuss how happy they are to be back in pub gardens following the lockdown.Watch GMB 👉 https://t.co/6iQ6ebeOEQ pic.twitter.com/W0yAai1tGD— Good Morning Britain (@GMB) April 12, 2021 One pub in Coventry appears to have taken things slightly too far. Videos posted online showed more than 100 people lining the street outside the Oak Inn after it had publized its grand plans to open a massive outdoor space with heaters, marquees and blankets. The pub is now under investigation for its “unmanageable amounts of visitors.”But, largely, the grand reopening has been welcomed as a major landmark—particularly following the success of the Britain’s vaccine rollout, which has many hoping that there won’t be another lockdown. Nicholas Hair, landlord of the Kentish Belle in south-east London, told BBC News that there was a “sense of celebration” in the country, adding: “I’m hoping this is a sort of rebirth, and that we’re reopen for the foreseeable.”As for Boris himself, government sources confirmed that the prime minister received a long-awaited haircut on Monday—but his planned trip to the pub has been cancelled out of respect for the late Prince Philip.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pints, shopping sprees, hair cuts...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210412073825-mnd81</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN (REPEAT, UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):RPT-UPDATE 2-'I'm so excited' - England reopens with pints pulled, shopping sprees and hair cuts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rippling through markets...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/nation-and-world/cars-anyone-how-the-computer-chip-shortage-is-rattling-the-economy-2326719/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the U.S. economy rebounds from its pandemic slump, a vital cog is in short supply: the computer chips that power a wide range of products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House to zero in on chip shortage in meeting with company officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-biden-chips-idUSKBN2BZ118</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Senior White House officials will meet on Monday with top executives from nearly 20 major companies to discuss a global semiconductor shortage that has roiled the automotive industry and technology firms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAWKER Set for Relaunch -- Again...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/gawker-is-set-for-relaunch-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Gawker writer Leah Finnegan is helming Bustle Digital Group's latest effort to resurrect the website</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kanye sneakers headed for millionaire status in SOTHEBY'S sale...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210412115502-l79ew</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUCTION-YEEZY/ (PIX):Kanye's Yeezy sneakers headed for millionaire status in Sotheby's sale</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Huge' explosion rocks Caribbean island as volcano keeps erupting...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-coronavirus-pandemic-explosions-evacuations-2c26166fa05e0ec6840669972ea1aaf0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KINGSTOWN, St. Vincent (AP) — La Soufriere volcano fired an enormous amount of ash and hot gas early Monday in the biggest explosive eruption yet since volcanic activity began on the eastern...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
