<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bookmakers see Macron easily winning...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2022-04-20/bookmakers-see-frances-macron-easily-winning-sundays-runoff</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega dance company bred culture of sex, silence, dancers say...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/britney-spears-entertainment-business-arts-and-music-190b7a81d2aeccde252bae59b4509f03</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Every year, one of the world’s leading dance competition companies sells the dream of Hollywood fame to hundreds of thousands of ambitious young dancers hoping to launch careers on television, in movies and on stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fearful Elite Worries About Way Out...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2022-04-20/russia-s-fearful-elite-worries-about-a-way-out</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK CRASHES</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-shares-set-lose-40-090208434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Netflix Inc. shares are on course to lose about $42 billion in value Wednesday after the streaming giant reported its first subscriber decline in more than a decade as the company pledges to make a slew of changes to its business to arrest a customer exodus. Most Read from BloombergNetflix Breaks Its Own Rules After Subscriber Losses Batter SharesKremlin Insiders Alarmed Over Growing Toll of Putin’s War in UkraineIn Defense of Elon Musk's Managerial ExcellenceTwitter Has a Poison</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Security Deal in Pacific Could Ripple Through World...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/20/why-a-chinese-security-deal-in-the-pacific-could-ripple-through-the-world/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SYDNEY, Australia — When the Solomon Islands’ prime minister stood before Parliament on Wednesday to announce that his government had</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicolas Cage Is in on the Nicolas Cage Jokes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/20/nicolas-cage-is-in-on-the-nicolas-cage-jokes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirty-two years ago, Nicolas Cage swaggered onto the set of a British talk show to promote his movie “Wild at</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK Court Issues Order To Extradite Assange To USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/julian-assange-to-be-extradited-to-us-uk-court-formally-issues-order-news-agency-afp-2903729</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A UK court on Wednesday issued a formal order to extradite WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange to the United States to face trial over the publication of secret files relating to the Iraq and Afghanistan wars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk talks of TWITTER takeover mask TESLA troubles in China...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/elon-musk-e2-80-99s-talks-of-a-twitter-takeover-mask-tesla-e2-80-99s-troubles-in-china/ar-AAWoTLN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macron, Le Pen square off for decisive debate as vote looms...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-france-elections-campaigns-presidential-24d8ca9828ab7855b4d27d3bb3cf8bfe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARIS (AP) — In the climax of France’s presidential campaign, centrist President Emmanuel Macron and far-right contender Marine Le Pen will meet Wednesday evening in a one-on-one television debate that could prove decisive before Sunday's runoff vote.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARNS TWITTER WILL BE HELD 'ACCOUNTABLE' AGAINST MUSK...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/desantis-hold-twitter-board-accountable-musk-buyout-bid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Ron DeSantis said Tuesday that Florida will seek ways to hold Twitter's board of directors “accountable” over their response to billionaire Elon Musk's bid to take the company private.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Sordid Culture of Celeb Enablers...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/johnny-depp-amber-heard-trial-will-smith-movie-stardom-dark-side-1235235378/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The latest act in the very public unraveling of Johnny Depp began last week in a courtroom in northern Virginia, pulling back the curtain on the secretive world of celebrity enablers and hangers-on…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRETS OF WORLD'S OLDEST DOG...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/19/owner-of-worlds-oldest-dog-shares-secrets-to-his-long-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Toby Keith, a 21-year-old Chihuahua in Florida, has officially been crowned by the Guinness World Records.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Testimony a disaster class in acting'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/19/johnny-depps-testimony-a-disaster-class-in-acting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Depp depicted himself — brilliantly — as a confused, sad, gentle soul who somehow stumbled into global fame and ungodly wealth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk doesn't make life on Mars sound very fun...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/19/elon-musk-warns-life-on-mars-will-be-dangerous-cramped-difficult-hard-work/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first settlers to arrive on Mars shouldn’t expect a glamorous lifestyle or even safe conditions during their stay, according to the leading proponent of human exploration of the red planet, Elo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARRY:  AMERICA NOW MY HOME....</title>
      <link>https://www.today.com/news/news/prince-harry-queen-protected-today-show-rcna25037</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.today.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a TODAY exclusive, the prince tells Hoda Kotb he's also happy living in California "for the time being."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spies 'have infiltrated US intelligence' warn ex-officials...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5159703/russian-spies-us-intelligence-anticipate-putins-next-move/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIAN moles have “almost certainly” infiltrated US intelligence services, former spooks have warned in an explosive new book. Active spies working for Russian president Vladimir Putin are likely …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SECRETS OF WORLD'S OLDEST DOG...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5158174/florida-chihuahua-worlds-oldest-dog-guinness-world-records/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 21-YEAR-old Chihuahua out of Florida has been recognized as the world’s oldest dog, and his secret to longevity is being shared. The website for the Guinness Book of World Records revealed …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden Weighs Appeal That May Be Fruitless, or Worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-weighs-mask-mandate-appeal-that-may-be-fruitless-or-worse/ar-AAWnznJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with inhumane killing of free-roaming donkey...</title>
      <link>https://www.kwtx.com/2022/04/19/livestock-contractor-charged-with-inhumane-slaughter-animal-deputies-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kwtx.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities in Florida have arrested a man in the death of an animal after they say he was initially called to help them with a roaming donkey.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sudden end sparks confusion, mixed messages ...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/3273527-mask-mandates-sudden-end-sparks-confusion-mixed-messages/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sudden end to the mask mandate for planes, trains and buses has sparked confusion for travelers and uncertainty over how to approach travel, especially as the Biden administration recommends th…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Worse to be gay than corrupt' in Venezuela's military...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/worse-gay-corrupt-venezuelas-military-014123933.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jose, an army captain, deserted after years of pressure. Rafael, a lieutenant, was prosecuted and expelled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil readies first carnival since Covid...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazil-readies-first-carnival-since-014012377.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After two bleak years of lock-downs and loss, Rio de Janeiro will hold its famed carnival this weekend for the first time since Covid-19 hit Brazil, promising a giant, glittering spectacle of pandemic catharsis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICIOUS PURGE: DESPERATE ATTEMPT TO STAVE OFF KREMLIN COUP?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5155722/vladimir-putin-overthrown-coup-russia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANY former close allies of Vladimir Putin have either died, been jailed, or disappeared from the public eye, as Russia’s increasingly-paranoid president looks to fight off a potential coup. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road rage increasing. How to deal with an angry driver  --  even if it's you...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/road-rage-is-up-how-to-deal-with-an-angry-driver-e2-80-94-even-if-it-e2-80-99s-you/ar-AAWnyZ7?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFTER 700 DAYS:  Some city transit systems drop mask mandate, and unease follows...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/metro-drops-mask-mandate-after-700-days-and-unease-follows/ar-AAWnTY5?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  DeSantis proposes dissolving special tax status for DISNEY...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desantis-proposes-dissolving-special-tax-status-for-disney-world/ar-AAWnv33?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May be fruitless, or worse...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/biden%20weighs%20mask%20mandate%20appeal%20that%20may%20be%20fruitless,%20or%20worse/ar-AAWnznJ?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX LOSES SUBS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/19/netflix-nflx-earnings-q1-2022.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's the first time the streamer has reported a subscriber loss in more than a decade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  In Shanghai, TESLA Workers Forced to Sleep on Factory Floors...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2022/04/tesla-shanghai-gigafactory-resume-production-amid-covid-lockdown/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla Shanghai factory resumed production after a three-week pause. Workers are required to live on site and work six days a week, but Tesla owners don’t seem troubled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STOCK CRASHES 25%</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/netflix-subscribers-fall-first-time-200457023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix Inc said inflation, the war in Ukraine and fierce competition contributed to a loss of subscribers for the first time in more than a decade and predicted deeper losses ahead, marking an abrupt shift in fortune for a streaming company that thrived during the pandemic. The company said it lost 200,000 subscribers in its first quarter, falling well short of its forecast of adding 2.5 million subscribers. Wall Street sent Netflix's stock tumbling 26% after the bell on Tuesday and erased about $40 billion of its stock market value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Depp takes stand in defamation trial...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/johnny-depp-testimony-trial-amber-heard-abuse-defamation-1235005588/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;2ND UPDATE, 1:23 PM: “I tend to be quite expressive in my writing,” a halting Johnny Depp said Tuesday on the stand of his $50 million defamation trial against ex-wife Amber Heard. After previous t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea hacks growing threat...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2022/04/19/crypto-hacks-cyber-FBI-Treasury-CISA-advisory/1811650351713/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A trio of U.S. agencies have issued a joint advisory to warn of escalating North Korean cyberattacks on cryptocurrency and blockchain platforms in the wake of a $620 million heist by the secretive regime's Lazarus Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside new military race to dominate metaverse...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/5149367/metaverse-military-race-war-us-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TECH race to build the most sophisticated and expansive metaverse could establish the next world power and change the future of war. The metaverse is still in its infancy, but its limitless poten…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Earthquakes keep coming.' Another one shakes SoCal...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/california/article260563137.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The region has seen nearly a dozen earthquakes with a magnitude of 2.5 or bigger in the past week, according to the USGS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How video games sucked in millions of seniors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/19/how-video-games-have-sucked-in-millions-of-seniors-citizens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Old people don’t just want to sit on the porch and watch leaves fall, they want to have fun,” FandomSpot’s Alyssa Celatti said in a statement provided to The Post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oath Keepers, Proud Boys in touch before US Capitol attack, texts reveal...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/apr/19/oath-keepers-proud-boys-capitol-attack-texts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The messages could strengthen a theory being explored by the House committee that January 6 included a coordinated assault</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG:  The End of Alcohol...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/the-end-of-alcohol/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Glamorous influencers are blending science and superstition to help people “change their relationship to drinking.” Did I miss out by getting sober the old-fashioned way?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major Covid rule to finally be scrapped in Australia...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/national/huge-change-to-covid-isolation-rules-in-victoria-and-nsw/news-story/bbe232cda8e75c90ed96495cd3417ea6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Victoria and NSW are expected to scrap isolation requirements for household contacts of people with Covid within days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warden at Epstein jail quietly retires amid federal probe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/prisons-new-jersey-jeffrey-epstein-04a7c866c49d15a32ddc6f57fe18dca1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The warden who ran the federal jail where disgraced financier Jeffrey Epstein killed himself was allowed to quietly retire from the Bureau of Prisons in February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmates Study at 1st College Based Behind Bars...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/us/articles/2022-04-19/california-inmates-study-at-1st-college-based-behind-bars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Behind a fortress wall and razor wire and a few feet away from California’s death row, students at one of the country’s most unique colleges discuss the 9/11 attacks and issues of morality, identity and nationalism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House faces choice...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/3273300-white-house-faces-tough-choice-on-appealing-mask-mandate-for-travel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House is facing a politically charged decision on whether to appeal a Trump-appointed judge’s decision to block a federal requirement to wear masks on public transportation. Officials hav…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will rally with Nebraska candidate accused of groping...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/19/2022-elections-trump-to-rally-with-nebraska-candidate-charles-herbster-following-accusations-of-groping.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Herbster has denied the accusations, compared himself to Trump and Supreme Court Justice Kavanaugh and suggested current Gov. Pete Ricketts pushed the report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretly recorded call adds to controversy swirling around Cawthorn...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/3272947-secretly-recorded-call-adds-to-controversy-swirling-around-cawthorn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former district staff member for Rep. Madison Cawthorn (R-N.C.) is accusing him of improperly firing her after denying her family and medical leave, allegations the lawmaker and his office have v…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA urged to probe URANUS...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-10732511/NASA-urged-probe-URANUS-study-gaseous-atmosphere.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known as the Committee on the Planetary Science and Astrobiology Decadal Survey, it designates a Uranus Orbiter and Probe as the highest-priority flagship mission.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'Reilly threatens JETBLUE worker over delayed flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10731909/Youre-gonna-lose-job-Bill-OReilly-threatened-airline-worker-delayed-flight.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Fox News host Bill O'Reilly was caught on tape threatening a JetBlue worker while his flight was delayed. 'You're gonna lose your job,' the one-time TV host told him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psilocybin, active ingredient in 'magic mushrooms,' makes scientific gains...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/3272317-psilocybin-the-active-ingredient-in-magic-mushrooms-makes-scientific-gains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Story at a glance Studies over the past several years have shown promise in using psilocybin-assisted therapy to treat psychiatric disorders like depression. A recent follow-up study by Johns Hopki…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE INSIDE MAN...</title>
      <link>https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/joe-kahn-new-york-times-profile.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nymag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meet Joe Kahn, the enigma who will now run the Times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Headlines Hollywood DNC Fundraiser...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/04/kamala-harris-doug-emhoff-dana-walden-fundraiser-1235004932/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATE, 8:27 PM PT: About $1 million was raised at a Democratic National Committee fundraiser headlined by Vice President Kamala Harris and held at the Brentwood home of Dana and Matt Walden. About…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Kremlin official found dead 'with gun in hand'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10731251/Ex-Kremlin-official-Gazprombank-vice-president-dead-gun-hand.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alongside the body of Vladislav Avayev, 51, was his 'pregnant' wife Yelena, 47, and younger daughter Maria, 13. They were found in their Moscow apartment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian tracks Russian troops' movements via looted APPLE AirPods...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/ukrainian-tracks-russian-troops-movements-26744208</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vitaliy Semenets’ Bluetooth headphones were looted from his home in Hostomel, near Kyiv, and he has since tracked them to Belarus and Russia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wing activists plan Jerusalem flag march...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/article-704562</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The groups stressed that they intend to march in any case on Wednesday at 5 p.m., telling police "you've forgotten your role. We'll march, you secure [it]."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service seizes $102 million in crypto...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/19/secret-service-seizes-more-than-102-million-in-crypto-assets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Secret Service, known for protecting the president, is taking aim at illicit digital currencies, seizing over $102 million in the past seven years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN+ looks doomed...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/discovery-cnn-plus-marketing-layoffs-jobs-b088c03c-b202-4756-8f5f-e64ee77b5095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN execs think the launch has been successful. Discovery executives disagree.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAMA:  Boris jeered by angry MPs as he issues grovelling apology over covid parties...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/04/19/boris-johnson-makes-first-commons-statement-since-partygate-fine-16494690/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The prime minister is being questioned by MPs after the Met fined him for going to a party during lockdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA:  DON'T FORGET TO TAKE YOUR BOOSTER$...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-science-business-health-82d673c5cfd213e089c24e2e2eb90d20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna hopes to offer updated COVID-19 boosters in the fall that combine its original vaccine with protection against the omicron variant. On Tuesday, it reported a preliminary hint that such an approach might work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J&amp;J suspends vax sales forecast...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-united-states-6af42ab530eb052417333d66f4a12649</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson is suspending sales forecasts for its COVID-19 vaccine only a few months after saying the shot could bring in as much as $3.5 billion this year. A global supply surplus and uncertainty about future demand — fueled in part by vaccine hesitancy in some developing markets — prompted the change, J&amp;amp;J said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER gets rid of masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/uber-scraps-mask-requirement-riders-111028095.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lyft, which also ended requirements for the vehicle windows to be kept open and for the front seat to empty, said health safety reasons will no longer appear under cancellation options on its app. Uber, which introduced mask mandates for its drivers, riders and delivery workers around the world in May 2020, said that riders will have the option to cancel their trip if they feel uncomfortable with revocation of the mask mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Studies: Multivitamins Have NO Health Benefits?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/multivitamins-no-health-benefits-studies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent years, more research calls to question whether or not multivitamin supplements, which can be very costly, are truly necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Christian nationalism behind Putin's war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-christian-nationalism-behind-putin-s-war/ar-AAWlQGp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Florida judge voids mask mandate for planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/end-of-federal-transportation-mask-mandate-greeted-with-confusion-relief/ar-AAWmuHp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bosses Don't Follow Own Advice in Returning to Office!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/bosses-dont-follow-their-own-advice-in-returning-to-the-office/ar-AAWmslF</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman dies after getting stuck on U.S. border wall...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox19.com/2022/04/14/police-woman-dies-after-getting-stuck-upside-down-while-climbing-us-mexico-border-wall/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox19.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Arizona said a Mexican woman died after illegally attempting to cross into the U.S. earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opposition mounts against Newsom's plan for court-ordered treatment of homeless...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/opposition-mounts-against-newsoms-plan-120045056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 14-page opposition letter to Newsom's big proposal raises questions over whether the governor can get CARE Courts signed into law by this summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dollar hits 20-year peak vs yen!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nothing-stops-yen-slide-falls-014559989.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dollar rose on Tuesday to a fresh 20-year high against the Japanese yen, supported by the divergence in monetary policy between a Federal Reserve determined to keep a lid on soaring inflation and a Bank of Japan that has kept interest rates ultra-low. The greenback hit 128.765 yen, the highest since May 2002. It was last up 1.4% at 128.74 yen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jen Psaki Breaks Down in Tears Condemning 'Harsh and Cruel' Anti-LGBTQ Bills...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/jen-psaki-breaks-down-in-tears-condemning-harsh-and-cruel-anti-lgbtq-bills-in-florida-and-elsewhere/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House Press Secretary Jen Psaki broke down during a podcast interview while condemning a series of anti-LGTBQ bills moving through statehouses as "harsh and cruel."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has told Obama HE IS running again...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/news/administration/3272281-biden-has-told-obama-hes-running-again/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden has told former President Obama that he is planning to run for reelection in 2024, two sources tell The Hill.   The admission to Obama is the latest indication t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers cheer and whip off coverings...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/04/19/judges-decision-to-void-mask-mandate-prompts-mid-flight-cheers-among-fliers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Judge Kathryn Kimball Mizelle ruled Monday that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention failed to properly explain its decision to impose the mandate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA:  BARE-FACE NOW LEGAL IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/judge-strikes-down-mask-mandates-1fccaa750b6d42b6b609ef75d3c14c26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ST. PETERSBURG, Fla. (AP) — A federal judge's decision to strike down a national mask mandate was met with cheers on some airplanes but also concern about whether it's really time to end one of the most visible vestiges of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis says lawmakers will consider stripping DISNEY of self-govt power...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/desantis-stripping-disney-self-government-power/39761559#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeSantis issued a proclamation calling for the special session to be expanded to include consideration of terminating all special districts enacted in Florida prior to 1968.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry will discuss meeting with Queen in interview with 'TODAY' show...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/5154329/prince-harry-bombshell-interview-meghan-markle/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Harry will give ANOTHER bombshell interview on his private meeting with the Queen tomorrow. The Duke of Sussex will sit down with US news anchor Hoda Kotb in The Hague, where the Invictus Ga…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former MSNBC analyst joins resistance...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/former-msnbc-analyst-joins-ukrainian-112206930.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A former MSNBC foreign affairs analyst has joined Ukrainian forces fighting back Russian President Vladimir Putin’s troops. Malcolm Nance, a longtime analyst for the network on national security, intelligence and military matters, joined Ukrainian fighters earlier this month, motivated, he said, by the atrocities committed by the Russian military against civilians over the last several…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial sperm donor reveals he will soon be father to 55 children after 'donation tour'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-10731151/American-serial-sperm-donor-travels-UK-impregnate-women-possible.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kyle Gordy, 30, from LA, California, has already made six donations to women in the UK and Europe on what he's dubbed his 'donation tours'.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three sailors from aircraft carrier found dead in week...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/18/politics/uss-george-washington-sailors/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three sailors from the USS George Washington aircraft carrier were found dead in less than one week, the Navy said, as the Naval Criminal Investigative Service and local authorities investigate the deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS Jesse Watters says he let air out of colleague's tires so he could drive her home...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/snyde/ny-jesse-water-fox-news-emma-air-out-of-tires-20220418-47n33bqzwnaoxfauz3olbuzbbu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watter's frequently complains about inflation on his show</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH POST reporter claimed 'severe PTSD' from Internet criticism -- then doxxed anonymous TWITTER user...</title>
      <link>https://hotair.com/ed-morrissey/2022/04/19/unreal-wapo-reporter-claimed-severe-ptsd-from-internet-criticism-and-then-doxxed-an-anonymous-twitter-user-n463195</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;hotair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's horrifying."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kahn Named Next Executive Editor of NYT...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/19/joe-kahn-is-named-next-executive-editor-of-the-new-york-times/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joseph F. Kahn, a Pulitzer Prize-winning China correspondent who rose to lead the international desk of The New York Times,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Militants prepare tunnels as next conflict looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220419-gaza-militants-prepare-tunnels-as-next-conflict-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a "tunnel city" under the sandy soils of southern Gaza, Palestinian militants are preparing for the next conflict with Israel, as tensions in Jerusalem threaten to escalate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST: World's Most Affordable and Least Affordable Cities to Buy Home...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/pittsburgh-most-affordable-for-housing-hong-kong-most-expensive</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;These Are the Worldâ€™s Most Affordable and Least Affordable CitiesÂ</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King of the 'Lunatics' Becomes Bitcoin's Most-Watched Whale...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/king-lunatics-becomes-bitcoin-most-040002343.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Back in 2016, when Do Kwon was just a little-known startup founder with grand ambitions of bringing free internet to all, he noticed his research on distributed networks kept bringing up stuff on Bitcoin and Ethereum.Most Read from BloombergU.S. Stops Mask Requirement on Planes After Judge’s RulingUkraine Update: Russia Assault in Donbas, EU Mulls Postwar CostsGlobal Investors Flee China Fearing That Risks Eclipse RewardsTesla Autopilot Stirs U.S. Alarm as ‘Disaster Waiting to Hap</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRIs Finding Connections Between Brain Activity, Psychology...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/04/19/m-r-i-s-are-finding-connections-between-our-brain-activity-and-psychology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In March, neuroscientists and psychiatrists from the School of Medicine at Washington University, St. Louis, along with colleagues elsewhere, published</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
