<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>From Rotten Teeth to Advanced Cancer, Patients Feel Effects of Treatment Delays...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/from-rotten-teeth-to-advanced-cancer-patients-feel-the-effects-of-treatment-delays/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Health providers are seeing the consequences of pandemic-delayed preventive and emergency care, from longer hospital stays to more root canals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Office of future outdoors?</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90628880/the-office-of-the-future-is-outdoors</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Landlords and designers are adding more outdoor space to office buildings, so employees can actually work outside.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: SOS messages, panic as virus breaks India's health system...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-india-coronavirus-1bda2318594d65be400074da41fa13c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW DELHI (AP) — Dr. Gautam Singh dreads the daily advent of the ventilator beeps, signaling that oxygen levels are critically low, and hearing his critically ill patients start gasping for air in the New Delhi emergency ward where he works. Like other doctors across the country, which on Monday set another record for new coronavirus infections for a fifth day in a row at more than 350,000, the cardiologist has taken to begging and borrowing cylinders of oxygen just to keep his most critical patients alive for one more day. On Sunday evening, when the oxygen supplies of other nearby hospitals were also near empty, the desperate 43-year-old took to social media, posting an impassioned video plea on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Let the bodies pile high'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510133/Boris-Johnson-said-bodies-pile-high-order-lockdown-sources-claim.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downing Street last night strongly denied the Prime Minister made the comment, insisting it was 'just another lie'. But those who say they heard it stand by their claim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOO BORING TO BEAT?</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/979486/biden-boring-republicans-beat</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Biden hits the traditionally symbolic first-100-days mark of his presidency this week, and 'it has dawned on Republicans that the man their standard-bearer once mocked as 'Sleepy Joe' is a formidable adversary,' Jonathan Chait writes in New York on Monday. 'And the quality that has made him so effective up to this point is, well, his sleepiness.' Before Biden's immediate predecessor, the last handful of presidents were 'nice,' but Biden is 'also tedious,' Chait argues: He is relentlessly enacting an ambitious domestic agenda — signing legislation that could cut child poverty by more than half, expanding ObamaCare, and injecting the economy with a stimulus more than twice the size of what [President Barack] Obama's Congress passed in 2009 — while arousing hardly any controversy. There's nothing in Biden's vanilla-ice-cream bromides for his critics to hook on to. Republicans can't stop Biden because he is boring them to death. [Jonathan Chait, New York] All signs point to this being a deliberate strategy, borne of wisdom or expediency, and it's 'a fascinating counterpoint to a career spent trying desperately to be interesting,' Chait adds. 'Biden used to overshare, with frequently disastrous results that led him to accurately self-diagnose as a 'gaffe machine,'' but now 'the tedium is the message.' Biden's new persona has been very effective at promoting progressive ideas in a way that strikes centrist voters as pretty anodyne, Democratic strategist Cornell Belcher tells the Los Angeles Times. 'You cannot underestimate how comfortable Uncle Joe is for a lot of people. They give an old, white guy the benefit of the doubt.' Certainly, 'lowering the temperature of Washington's political debates' has helped Biden's agenda, David Lauter writes at the Times. 'But it could create a problem down the road, depriving Biden of the fervent support that can sustain a president in bad times.' If his sleepiness does end up leaving Democratic allies cold, Biden will still have hot Oval Office chocolate chip cookies for potential allies in Congress. Peter Weber</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death of cities greatly exaggerated...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/articles/978456/death-cities-greatly-exaggerated</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why the pandemic predictions about urban flight were wrong</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space junk map shows '200 ticking time bombs' in orbit around Earth...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mind-blowing-space-junk-map-23983994</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have created the space junk map, AstriaGraph, which shows where thousands of human-made objects are located. The technology can track and predict its behaviour</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Kanye sneakers snag world record $1.8 million in private sale...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/kanyes-yeezy-sneakers-snag-world-130528028.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Kanye West sneakers that sent athletic shoes strutting down fashion runways sold for $1.8 million, a new world record price for a pair of sneakers, Sotheby's announced on Monday. The American rapper's 2008 'Grammy Worn' Nike Air Yeezy samples were prototypes for a line developed by West and Mark Smith for Nike.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Pink Supermoon' To Brighten Skies...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/04/26/april-pink-supermoon-full-moon-monday-night/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;April's full moon is the "pink" moon, and it's a supermoon, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I have given up fight': 'Italy's Robinson Crusoe' to leave island...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/26/mauro-morandi-budelli-island-italy-robinson-crusoe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mauro Morandi has lived alone on Budelli since 1989 but will relocate after several eviction threats</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Actor Backlash...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9511165/Academy-Awards-ends-fizzle-Best-Actor-Anthony-Hopkins-skips-night.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Film fans have blasted the Oscars as the 'wokest ever' after an evening of virtue-signalling speeches by celebs and controversy over Anthony Hopkins winning best actor instead of Chadwick Boseman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE will spend $1 billion to open 3,000-employee campus in NC...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/04/26/apple-announces-1-billion-north-carolina-campus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The campus is a sign of Apple's continued expansion beyond its home in Cupertino, California, where most of its engineering has been based.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscars unlike any other...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/strangest-oscars-ever-snubbing-chadwick-055209751.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Todd Wawrychuk/Getty ImagesFor the first time in my lifetime, the Academy Awards weren’t a spectacle, but an awards show. I’ve never been so moved by it.I’ve also never been so frustrated by it. That was inevitable, given the circumstances circling the now-infamous pandemic Oscars, but also owed to a handful of chaotic producing decisions. (Where was the comedy? Could that whiplash-inducing In Memoriam segment have been more disrespectful? And Best Picture before Best Actor and Actress?!? Absolute nonsense.)An intimate gathering at a train station with satellite cameras in locations like London and Sydney, this year’s ceremonies felt nothing like the Oscars we know. That seems correct, as having an awards show at all in these times can feel completely inappropriate. The traditional glitz, bombast, and Hollywood narcissism needed Sunday night’s humbling. At the same time, it is a television show, one that needed more spark.There will be complaints that the night was a bit of a bore, and the show, while finishing closer to three hours than most ceremonies, seemed endless.Not saving Best Picture for the night’s climax may rank among the worst creative misfires in the show’s history. Presumably, producers assumed Chadwick Boseman would win for Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom, not Anthony Hopkins for The Father, and were then building up to an emotional close to the telecast.Hopkins’ surprise win, his not being in attendance, and the show just ending after that was nothing short of disorienting. You should feel guided through an award show, not wondering what the hell just happened. The blunder is a slight to movie fans, to Hopkins, and to Nomadland, one of the refreshing cases of the right film at the right moment winning Best Picture. Because of that production choice, the very Academy that selected the film to win seemed to have dismissed it.What makes the whole thing more egregious is that the producers didn’t need to manipulate the traditional show order to manufacture an emotional night. Until it veered off the rails near the end, it was already an incredibly heartfelt, powerful, meaningful telecast. I’m an easy target, but I found myself crying...constantly?There are few better choices for launching any major event than by having Regina King strut in a long tracking shot to a stage and deliver a sermon about the complexity of our times, the impulse to fete movies, and why the art matters: "Now, I know that a lot of you people at home wanna reach for your remote when you feel like Hollywood is preaching to you, but as a mother of a Black son, I know the fear that so many live with, and no amount of fame or fortune changes that, OK?"Starting with her, the tenor of the telecast was a celebration of inclusivity, dictated by the memorable speeches given by the winners. It was a gratitude for opportunity, and a demand for a platform. After months of screaming “who cares?” about the idea of the Oscars taking place, and anecdotal evidence about how few people watched the nominees—even though they were all available to watch from home—the show seemed to make a point of emphasizing why the show matters and why the movies matter. Reuters Chloé Zhao made history, becoming the second woman to ever win Best Director for her work in Nomadland. The love was spread around this year. While Nomadland took home three of the biggest prizes—Best Picture, Director, and Actress for Frances McDormand, now the second woman to win the category three times—Promising Young Woman, The Father, Sound of Metal, Judas and the Black Messiah, and Minari all won major awards.Early speeches by Emerald Fennell (Best Original Screenplay, Promising Young Woman) and Florian Zeller (Best Adapted Screenplay, The Father) were babbling and overwhelmed and earnest. Thomas Vinterberg (Best International Feature, Another Round) and Mia Neal (Best Makeup and Hairstyling, Ma Rainey’s Black Bottom) made poignant dedications in their thank yous that had the in-person audience in tears, and me at home practically inconsolable.Yuh-jung Youn and Daniel Kaluuya, winning Best Supporting Actress and Actor, respectively for Minari and Judas and the Black Messiah, were magnetic and charismatic as they accepted their trophies. That the set and the ceremony was so intimate made those winning moments feel even more electric.Throwing to the Zoom locations abroad felt seamless—so much so that all the hand wringing from producers ahead of time over whether they could or should allow satellite feeds seems ridiculous. And the presenters, the “ensemble cast” as the producers kept advertising them, were on their game.I remember years in which a new Hollywood It Girl would walk to the microphone and giggle about how they forgot their glasses and couldn’t read the teleprompter. This year, the actors presenting, which included King, Angela Bassett, Reese Witherspoon, Harrison Ford, and Riz Ahmed, were serving as actual emcees. It may have been a little buttoned-up, but it was impressive.Hours later, after the whole ceremony has unfolded and I’m thinking back on it, I keep returning to King’s striking introduction.She had a thankless task, making the argument for why an award show is taking place in such serious times, even admitting that if the jury in the Derek Chauvin trial had ruled differently, “I’d have traded in my heels for marching boots.”She also had to defend the optics of Hollywood’s rich and famous gathering maskless when most of us still safely can’t get together with friends and family. When Regina King shows up, she’s gonna do her job. And damn if she didn’t sell the lunacy of the excuse that this was “an Oscars movie with a cast of over 200 nominees” and the show was a “film production” and they were all at work.I still don’t understand all the “it’s an award show and it’s a movie” nonsense that the show’s producers kept repeating in interviews leading up to the telecast. Nothing about it felt like a “movie,” at least not any more or less than any other year’s awards. Actors came out, presented awards, and people gave speeches. Nothing seemed more cinematic than usual. It actually felt more like an award show than an entertainment event than in any year I can remember.Some of that didn’t work. Viewers who hadn’t seen all the nominees were starved of clips of the nominees that only played for a few categories.Two and a half hours of the ceremony passed without a comedy bit. By that time, it was not entirely welcome—at that point, you just want the whole thing to be done with—though Glenn Close dancing to “Da Butt” may be the greatest Oscars moment of all time. Still, after a long night that seemed disinterested in creating anything resembling a viral moment, it felt out of place, funny as it was.And Frances McDormand, begging for there to be karaoke while on stage accepting Best Actress, articulated what we were all thinking: The show was missing music.For the first time, the stage had an accessible ramp. The ramp was also poorly placed, with winners who walked from stage left having to awkwardly jump over it, a rare case in which the production design made no sense neither aesthetically and logistically; I get that the ceremony was filmed at a train station to make COVID safety easier, but did the stage they built have to look so cheap?The show looked and felt, at times, like a perfunctory luncheon. And while that often was refreshing—it actually seemed like it was produced by people who like movies and the artists who make them, not ratings-hungry egotists—it shined a harsher spotlight than usual on the fact that it is a slog to present 24 award categories. When there are no sketches, montages, or musical performances distracting from the task at hand, the task does seem more like a chore.That said, past efforts to minimize the act of handing out awards never made sense to me. Why not lean into the purpose of the whole thing? Yes, presenting 24 awards is a tedious exercise, but Sunday night’s show was the most emotional exercise of tedium I’ve ever partaken in.There were moments that felt surreal, like every time the show returned from commercial break and panned across the in-person audience and you’d see flashes of Amanda Seyfriend and Carey Mulligan’s gorgeous gowns and oversized skirts. It’s still jarring to see celebrities in red-carpet fashion when everyday life is still in pandemic disarray.And, while there were plenty of powerful speeches that spoke to our volatile cultural moment, that still can seem like an awkward fit in this venue. Case in point, the wild transition from Best Short Film winner Travon Free speaking movingly about police killings of Black people to his collaborator, Martin Desmond Roe, saying, “We’d like to thank Netflix…”But for all the faults, from the small ones (that stage design) to the major ones (not saving Best Picture for last was egregious and nearly show-ruining), it was just plain poignant to watch the Academy Awards and celebrate movies.I think the producers made the right choice when it came to the scale of the ceremony, allowing that celebration to seem invigorating instead of ostentatious. It does feel like the country is starting to heal, even if slowly and only a little bit, and it’s exciting to embrace possibility again.Maybe the most meaningful part of the night to me was when the In the Heights trailer played, and I actually felt the thrill and anticipation of getting to see it in theaters. There’s a way of looking at this year’s Oscars show as a failure, if the most memorable part of the night didn’t involve any of the nominated films or the telecast itself. But I actually think of it as a triumph.The last year has made me so cynical. My expectations for the Oscars were so low you’d have to dig for them. So what a surprise it was, and even a rejuvenation, to come away from the ceremony hopeful about film and the community that surrounds it once again.Read more at The Daily Beast.Get our top stories in your inbox every day. Sign up now!Daily Beast Membership: Beast Inside goes deeper on the stories that matter to you. Learn more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Economic Confidence Positive First Time in Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/348959/economic-confidence-positive-first-time-pandemic.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time since the coronavirus pandemic led to widespread business closures in the U.S., Gallup's Economic Confidence Index has registered a net positive reading.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington state passes carbon pricing measure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-government-and-politics-washington-legislature-1da0a978342ad9787552f8e7926cee0a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OLYMPIA, Wash. (AP) — Washington is on track to become the second state in the nation to have a comprehensive carbon pricing policy under a measure passed by the state Legislature Saturday. The Seattle Times reported that the Senate gave the final 27-22 vote on the measure. It now heads to Gov. Jay Inslee, who had requested the legislation. “We are genuinely, authentically on the march toward Paris accord levels of emissions reductions,” said Democratic Sen. Reuven Carlyle, the bill's sponsor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Examines Heart Inflammation After PFIZER Shot...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/israel-examines-heart-inflammation-cases-after-pfizer-covid-shot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel Examines Heart Inflammation Cases After Pfizer Covid Shot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We're Coming for You': For Public Health Officials, Year of Threats and Menace...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/article/public-health-officials-year-of-threats-menace-santa-cruz-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local health officials have become the face of government authority as they work to stem the pandemic. That has made them targets for chilling threats from some of the same militia groups that stor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked recording of Iran's top diplomat offers blunt talk...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/iran-iran-nuclear-middle-east-europe-0068e6e181a4cc9aaa8433d8257ce04e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A recording of Iran's foreign minister offering a blunt appraisal of diplomacy and the limits of power within the Islamic Republic has been leaked, providing a rare look inside the country's theocracy. The release of the comments by Mohammad Javad Zarif set off a firestorm within Iran, where officials carefully mind their words amid a cut-throat political environment that includes the powerful paramilitary Revolutionary Guard, ultimately overseen by the country's supreme leader. Zarif has been suggested as a possible candidate for Iran's June 18 presidential election as well. Outside of Iran, Zarif's comments could also affect talks in Vienna aimed at finding a way for Tehran and the U.S. to both come into compliance with Iran's 2015 nuclear deal with world powers. Already, sabotage targeted Iran's nuclear facility at Natanz  during the talks as Tehran has begun enriching a small amount of uranium up to 60% purity , which edges the country closer to weapons-grade levels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1970s-Era Taxes on Rich Collide With GOP, SALT Rebels...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-e2-80-99s-1970s-era-taxes-on-rich-collide-with-gop-and-salt-rebels/ar-BB1g3kSO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Joe Biden is poised to unveil a plan that would raise taxes on the income, investments and estates of the wealthiest Americans to levels not seen in more than four decades, a move that will trigger intense debate in Congress about whether and how to address income inequality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business class opens to masses as affordable refuge from virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2021/04/26/business/business-class-travel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.japantimes.co.jp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flush with cash and a record number of air miles after a year on the ground, leisure travelers are splurging on premium seats for their first trips back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking barrier, women become Marines after surviving the 'crucible'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426085347-p9nzn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-MARINES/WOMEN (PIX):Breaking a barrier, women become U.S. Marines after surviving the 'crucible'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preachers 'n' Sneakers Trend Alive and Well and Spawning Merch...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/the-preachers-n-sneakers-trend-is-alive-and-well-and-spawning-merch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ben Kirby started the Instagram account @preachersnsneakers as a gag in 2019. Mr. Kirby, then a 29-year-old MBA student and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Point: How Zuckerberg, Cook Became Foes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/breaking-point-how-mark-zuckerberg-and-tim-cook-became-foes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO — At a confab for tech and media moguls in Sun Valley, Idaho, in July 2019, Timothy D.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Time Gun Buyers Push Record Fireman Sales...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/04/26/989699122/1st-time-gun-buyers-help-push-record-u-s-gun-sales-amid-string-of-mass-shootings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data from the FBI's firearms background check database shows six days in March of this year made up the top 10 highest days of firearms background checks since 1998.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India patients dying in streets; Hunt for black market oxygen...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/india-covid-crisis-victims-dying-23981902</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India is struggling with a devastating second wave of coronavirus with cases and deaths now at record highs and experts fearing they could actually be up to five times worse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Farm Droid Kills 100,000 Weeds per Hour...</title>
      <link>https://www.freethink.com/articles/farming-robot</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freethink.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Carbon Robotics’ Autonomous Weeder is a smart farming robot that identifies weeds and then kills them using high-power lasers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBD Superbug Slayer?</title>
      <link>https://www.freethink.com/articles/cbd-and-antibiotics</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freethink.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the search for new weapons against superbugs, CBD and antibiotics in combination, as well as CBD alone, may prove to be promising candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC cop cars totaled after officers drag race...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox29.com/news/dc-cop-cars-totaled-after-officers-drag-race-in-ne-says-commander</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox29.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two D.C. police cars were totaled after officers decided to drag race each other, according to an internal email obtained exclusively by FOX 5’s Lindsay Watts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bali hunts tourist who made porn video on sacred volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/police-hunt-russian-tourist-model-23983312</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The footage, taken on Mount Batur in Bali, was afterwards uploaded to Pornhub and received millions of views. Police are now trying to work out if the pair are still on the island</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's most elite sex club reopens...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/love-sex/worlds-most-elite-sex-club-23982542</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Snctm – AKA the world's most elite sex club – has returned with a very saucy event. The exclusive members club has a new penthouse venue where wild orgies are set to take place</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bodies fall from overloaded ambulances...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9511529/India-Morgues-run-stretchers-deaths-hit-2-800-day.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India recorded 2,812 Covid deaths overnight and infections in the last 24 hours rose to 352,991 on Monday - a record peak for a fifth day running - as vital life-saving oxygen is in short supply in hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans worry fiscal conservatism losing rallying cry...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/550074-gop-worries-fiscal-conservatism-losing-its-rallying-cry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans say fiscal conservatism simply isn’t the GOP rallying cry it used to be, and that’s making it much harder to counter President Biden’s push for trillions of dollars in new government spending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia Using Deepfakes to Imitate Political Rivals...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/russia-accused-using-deepfakes-imitate-political-rivals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities suspect that Kremlin operatives have used the deepfakes in order to gain information against Alexei Navalny's opposition movement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed Groups Step Into Venezuela as Lawlessness Grows...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/04/26/armed-groups-step-into-venezuela-as-lawlessness-grows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GUARERO, Venezuela — They bring drinking water to residents in the arid scrublands, teach farming workshops and offer medical checkups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Americans CAN visit Europe this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510375/Vaccinated-American-tourists-allowed-visit-Europe-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American tourists who are fully vaccinated will be allowed to visit Europe this summer while the European Union hailed progress the U.S. has made in its COVID vaccine drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worker  'mugged' after ceremony switches venue to homeless hotspot Union Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9510299/Homeless-ordered-LAs-Union-Station-ahead-tonights-Academy-Awards.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The glitzy awards show will be held Sunday at Union Station, close to encampments set up by vagrants in the city's downtown area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playboy businessman arrested for posing with nude models in Dubai...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2769768/playboy-businessman-photoshoot-nude-dubai-speaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE American playboy behind the Dubai balcony naked photoshoot has spoken for the first time. Vitaliy Grechin, 41, remains detained in the Gulf city where he has tested positive for Covid but has i…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheerleader's SNAP rant leads to 'momentous' Supreme Court case on speech ...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Cheerleader-s-Snapchat-rant-leads-to-momentous-16128064.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The high school cheerleader relegated to the JV squad for another year...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spielberg Releases 'WEST SIDE STORY' trailer...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/steven-spielbergs-west-side-story-unveils-first-trailer-during-oscars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90-year-old accused of gunning down neighbor...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/man-90-accused-of-shooting-neighbor-in-trenton</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities say a 90-year-old man has been arrested in the shooting death of his neighbor on a side street across from police headquarters in New Jersey’s capital city.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot dog security force roams Air Force base...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/air-force-base-deploys-pack-of-robot-dogs-to-enhance-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tyndall AFB is using robodogs as an added layer of security on base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Americans CAN visit Europe this summer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dw.com/en/coronavirus-eu-set-to-allow-vaccinated-us-tourists-this-summer-report/a-57331605</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dw.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen said in a newspaper interview that the vaccines used in the US should enable "free movement and travel" to the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhao makes history as director...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210426001021-xhcj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWARDS-OSCARS/ (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV):UPDATE 4-Chloe Zhao nabs historic best director win for 'Nomadland'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red carpet makes comeback...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210425221246-sj4vc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWARDS-OSCARS/RED CARPET (UPDATE 1, REPEAT, PIX, TV):RPT-UPDATE 1-Red carpet makes a comeback at history-making Oscars</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No 10 rules out inquiry into mistakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/apr/25/uk-governments-claim-it-is-too-busy-for-covid-inquiry-prompts-anger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: bereaved families are told that ‘people who would need to give evidence’ are ‘working round clock’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccinated Americans CAN visit Europe this summer... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/04/25/world/europe/american-travel-to-europe.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The head of the European Commission said the bloc would switch policy, under certain conditions, after more than a year of mostly banning nonessential travel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Modern science' says there are six sexes, state legislator insists...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/apr/24/texas-democratic-lawmaker-modern-science-says-ther/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Harvard-educated Texas Democratic lawmaker drew double-takes for declaring at a hearing that there are six sexes, prompting a rebuke from skeptics who said his count was off by four.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roller coaster breaks down 200 feet up!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9509647/Visitors-forced-CLIMB-200ft-high-Blackpool-Pleasure-Beach-rollercoaster.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adrenaline junkies were left stranded at the highest point of The Big One rollercoaster at Blackpool Pleasure Beach this afternoon after it broke down mid-ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops troll LeBron on TIKTOK...</title>
      <link>https://notthebee.com/article/cops-are-trolling-lebron-on-tiktok-and-i-am-100-here-for-it</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;notthebee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hey LeBron...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACEX 'NEAR MISS' WITH UFO</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2770635/spacex-starship-near-miss-ufo-astronauts-prepare-crash/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE SPACEX starstip is reported to have had a near miss with a UFO – with astronauts on board told to buckle up and prepare for a crash, Nasa has revealed. While en route to the International…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  80% SEE NATION STILL DIVIDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/meet-the-press/poll-100-days-biden-s-approval-remains-strong-can-honeymoon-n1265199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Majorities approve of the president's handling of the pandemic and the economy in a new NBC News poll, but strong divisions remain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming becomes promised land for crypto firms...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/how-wyoming-became-the-promised-land-for-bitcoin-investors-11619201182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wyoming’s economy is powered by some of the oldest industries in human history, including mining, agriculture and tourism. But in recent years the state has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Businesswoman image key to Marjorie Taylor Greene's rise...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/politics/national-politics/businesswoman-image-key-to-greenes-rise/5RX3LQEGUJFI5P6N6EQWZCA5T4/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Georgia Congresswoman Marjorie Taylor Greene stressed her businesswoman image in her campaign, but an AJC review found that thereâ€™s little evidence of her involvement in her family's construction company operations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allies of Russia's Navalny defiant in face of possible extremism charges...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210425162536-0r2cj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-POLITICS/NAVALNY-ALLIES:Allies of Russia's Navalny defiant in face of possible extremism charges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More action, less talk, distinguish Biden's 100-day sprint...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-immigration-health-joe-biden-election-2020-0bf5f72ba4194ba4247dcf7130af70b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The card tucked in President Joe Biden’s right jacket pocket must weigh a ton. You can see the weight of it on his face when he digs it out, squints and ever-so-slowly reads aloud the latest tally of COVID-19 dead. Sometimes he’ll stumble on a digit — after all, flubs come with the man. But the message is always clear: The toll of the virus weighs on him constantly, a millstone that helps explain why the typically garrulous politician with the megawatt smile has often seemed downright dour. For any new leader, a lingering pandemic that has killed more than a half-million citizens would be plenty for a first 100 days. But it has been far from the sole preoccupation for the now 78-year-old Biden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young adults' relocations reshaping political geography...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-census-2020-business-government-and-politics-immigration-cbc10b35e47a331515cce18abc9dcddc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Garima Vyas always wanted to live in a big city. She thought about New York, long the destination for 20-something strivers, but was wary of the cost and complicated subway lines. So Vyas picked another metropolis that's increasingly become young people's next-best option — Houston. Now 34, Vyas, a tech worker, has lived in Houston since 2013. "I knew I didn’t like New York, so this was the next best thing,” Vyas said. “There are a lot of things you want to try when you are younger -- you want to try new things. Houston gives you that, whether it’s food, people or dating. And it’s cheap to live in.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Aide to Blame Boris for Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/dominic-cummings-to-blame-boris-johnson-for-covid-death-toll-kwr6zn3xv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dominic Cummings is preparing a dossier of evidence that will attempt to blame Boris Johnson personally for the tens of thousands of deaths during the second wave of the pandemic.The prime minister’s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  More Violence at London anti-lockdown protest...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2021/apr/25/anger-met-police-anti-lockdown-protest-violence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metropolitan Police Federation chair to urgently raise matter with hierarchy after eight officers injured</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talking to yourself: Good antidote to loneliness -- or sign of real problem?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2021/apr/25/talking-to-yourself-a-good-antidote-to-loneliness-or-the-sign-of-a-real-problem</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;During the pandemic, I have gone from uttering a few words of encouragement to myself to full-blown arguments. I’m not the only one. I asked psychologists what purpose this serves</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The internet has turned us all into amateur detectives...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/apr/25/internet-amateur-detectives-social-media-true-crime</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On social media, hunting for clues about other peoples’ lives is increasingly popular – and risky, says tech writer Amelia Tait</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broken record or new tune? Cuba's leaders preached continuity but some saw slivers of reform...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/broken-record-or-new-tune-cuba-s-leaders-preached-continuity-but-some-saw-slivers-of-reform/ar-BB1fY2o8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Miguel Díaz-Canel took the stage for the first time as Cuba’s Communist Party chief, a position that makes him the most powerful political leader in the country, he launched into a speech with a similar refrain to the words of his rebel elders. The state sector of the island’s moribund economy should be strengthened. Detractors to Cuba’s socialist system were “mercenary lumpen.” Vocal ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switzerland Says Third of Population Has Had Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/switzerland-says-a-third-of-population-has-had-covid-19-nzz/ar-BB1g1SL9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Swiss government estimates that about one-third of the population has been infected with Covid-19 since the start of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TURKEY TEAMS WITH IRAN?</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/turkeys-genocide-blackmail-threats-to-work-closer-with-iran-and-russia-666263</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has called Turkey’s bluff: that it might leave NATO because it is angry to hear the word “genocide” – and that Ankara should never be offended, but can do what it wants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  An Oscars unlike any other...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oscars-2021-guide-67f5600e59179e1161d2db3ba48ad31d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oscars unlike any before will get underway Sunday night, with history on the line in major categories and a telecast retooled for the pandemic. The 93rd Academy Awards will begin at 8 p.m. EDT on ABC. There will be no host, no audience, nor face masks for nominees attending the ceremony at Los Angeles' Union Station — this year's hub for a show usually broadcast from the Dolby Theatre. In contrast with the largely virtual Golden Globes , Zoom boxes have been closed out — though numerous international hubs and satellite feeds will connect nominees unable to travel. Show producers are hoping to return some of the traditional glamor to the Oscars, even in a pandemic year. The red carpet is back, though not the throngs; only a handful of media outlets will be allowed on site. (E! red carpet coverage starts at 3 p.m.) Casual wear is a no-no. The pre-show on ABC begins at 6:30 p.m. EDT and will include pre-taped performances of the five Oscar-nominated songs. The ceremony is available to stream on Hulu Live TV, YouTubeTV, AT&amp;amp;T TV, FuboTV and on ABC.com with provider authentication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TONIGHT:  Art or activism? Oscars identity crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/apr/23/art-v-activism-can-the-oscars-survive-its-identity-crisis</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s awards will be a battle between political propriety and cinematic excellence. But will medium or message finally triumph?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals filling up again with Covid patients...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/fl-ne-south-florida-covid-hospitalizations-continue-20210424-jxuqa5zerfc2lfaturmabsbke4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For a few weeks in March, South Florida hospital workers took a breath and thought the state was on the right track with coronavirus cases. But in April, the situation shifted again and COVID hospitalizations are increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Family may spend life in prison after 'church' sold bleach as cure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/bradenton-family-may-spend-life-in-prison-after-church-sold-bleach-as-covid-19-cure/ar-BB1fZob4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apr. 23—A federal grand jury brought charges against members of a Bradenton family nearly a year after they were arrested for selling bleach that they claimed to be a cure for the COVID-19 virus. Mark Grenon and his three sons — Jonathan, Jordan and Joseph — face several charges for peddling their "Miracle Mineral Solution" to customers even after the Food and Drug Administration refuted those ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police depts struggling with shortage of recruits, surge in retirements...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/philadelphia-police-recruitment-pennsylvania-nj-jobs-20210423.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“People don’t want to be police anymore," one local police chief said. "It’s a good job, and good-paying job, but when you look at national news every day, people just don’t want to be officers."</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
