<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WARNING TAMPA</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2021-07-07-tropical-storm-elsa-florida-landfall-forecast-east-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest, complete forecast briefing on the fifth named storm of the hurricane season. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haiti President assassinated at home...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/caribbean-haiti-government-and-politics-b56a0f8fec0832028bdc51e8d59c6af2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORT-AU-PRINCE, Hatii (AP) — Haitian President Jovenel Moïse was assassinated after a group of unidentified people attacked his private residence, the country’s interim prime minister said in a statement Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundy seizes on housing shortage in new bid to take public lands in Idaho...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ammon-bundy-seizes-housing-shortage-120044791.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ammon Bundy built his name on confronting government. Now he wants to be Idaho's governor, pledging to protect conservative values by turning federal land into private development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RADAR</title>
      <link>http://radar.weather.gov/ridge/lite/KTBW_loop.gif?ecf1310032b5d6a716c761e7d77c9d39</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;radar.weather.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to ban boiling lobsters alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/ban-on-boiling-lobsters-alive-under-plans-to-boost-welfare-rights-of-crustaceans-and-molluscs-jpx2whf0v</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boiling lobsters alive will be banned under plans being drawn up by ministers to strengthen the welfare rights of crustaceans and molluscs.The government is preparing to recognise that lobsters, crabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAS DODGED DIRECT HIT FOR CENTURY</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/supernatural-forces-at-play-tampa-bay-dodges-hurricanes/770503</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tampa Bay hasn't been struck by a hurricane in 100 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flying is mess this summer. Travelers share horror stories...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/flying-is-a-mess-this-summer-6-travelers-share-their-cancellation-horror-stories-and-tips/ar-AALQvtE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tales of “milk runs,” fights over gummy bears, $12 vouchers and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's claims to being 'king of the tax code' could come back to haunt him...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-Trump-s-claims-to-being-the-king-of-the-tax-16296223.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When former president Donald Trump weighed in on the criminal tax case against his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOTHER Oath Keeper charged with conspiracy in MAGA riot...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/oath-keeper-charged-conspiracy-u-205128796.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Oath Keeper on Tuesday became the latest member of the right-wing group charged with conspiracy for his alleged role in the attack on the U.S. Capitol, as more than 535 people have now been arrested for joining in that deadly violence. The FBI said about 40 people, including members of the Oath Keepers, Proud Boys and Three Percenters, face conspiracy charges related to the Jan. 6 riot, when hundreds of supporters of then-President Donald Trump stormed the Capitol in an unsuccessful attempt to stop Congress from certifying his election defeat. Tuesday marked six months since the assault, which the FBI said has also led to more than 165 arrests of people on charges of assaulting, resisting or impeding police officers and other employees of the Capitol, including 50 charged with using a deadly weapon or seriously injuring a police officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adams wins Dem primary in NYC mayor race...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/ny-state-wire-government-and-politics-9c564828a29831747f9c2e6f52daf55e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Brooklyn Borough President Eric Adams has won the Democratic primary for mayor of New York City after appealing to the political center and promising to strike the right balance between fighting crime and ending racial injustice in policing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iraq base hosting US troops under attack with drones and rockets... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3232307/iraq-base-hosting-us-troops-attacked-rockets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN airport in Iraq that is hosting US troops has reportedly come under attack with “at least three drones and 20 rockets.” Militia affiliated channels say that at least 20 rockets hit t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Hits Wealth Record of $211 Billion on Pentagon Move...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/jeff-bezos-hits-wealth-record-of-211-billion-on-pentagon-move/ar-AALQIfR?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff Bezos is leaving the rest of the world behind when it comes to wealth accumulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMW Takes Lead in Luxury Market With Better Access to Chips...</title>
      <link>https://www.explica.co/bmw-leads-us-luxury-market-with-better-access-to-chips.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.explica.co&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sydney lockdown extended ANOTHER week...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/sydney-covid-19-lockdown-extended-223338961.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A two-week COVID-19 lockdown in Australia's largest city of Sydney will be extended for another week in a bid to contain an outbreak of the highly infectious Delta virus variant, local media reported on Wednesday. The city, home to a fifth of Australia's 25 million people, is fighting its worst outbreak of the year so far, with total cases reaching more than 330 since the first case was detected three weeks ago. New South Wales (NSW) state authorities imposed a hard lockdown on June 26 to get on top of the Delta strain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPENING NIGHT MOVIE FALLS FLAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/07/06/cannes-early-reviews-for-opening-film-starring-adam-driver-marion-cotillard-cite-oral-sex-scene-bizarre-joyless</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;And so it begins. Cannes 2021 opened with Leos Carax’s movie with music, by the cult group Sparks, called “Annette.” Early reviews describe “Annette” as “bizarre…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranians protest over power outage crisis, chant 'Death to Khamenei'...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/iranians-protest-over-power-outage-crisis-chant-death-to-khamenei-673049</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Protests turned political in some areas, with people chanting "Death to the dictator" and "Death to Khamenei," according to videos posted on social media.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Loneliness Lowers Life Expectancy...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/loneliness-years-off-older-adults/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say seniors also "pay a penalty for their shorter life by forfeiting potential years of good health."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheeran gets govt call LIVE on-air to check if he's following quarantine rules...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/entertainment/3224610/ed-sheeran-call-covid-rules/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ED SHEERAN had a shock call from government Covid officials checking he was complying with quarantine rules after he came back from the US. The singer was doing a remote interview with Harry Potter…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debit Card Apps for Kids Collecting Shocking Personal Data...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/4avqx3/debit-card-apps-for-kids-are-collecting-a-shocking-amount-of-personal-data</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greenlight says it isn't currently selling data on kids' spending habits to advertisers, but its privacy policy suggests it could start anytime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch crime reporter shot on Amsterdam street...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/dutch-crime-reporter-shot-amsterdam-street-parool-2021-07-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Celebrity crime reporter Peter R. de Vries, known for his work in exposing the Dutch underworld, was shot and seriously wounded on a street in Amsterdam, police said on Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can virus cause lasting erectile dysfunction?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/covid-19-and-lasting-erectile-dysfunction-heres-what-we-know/ar-AALQ7Tz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are several possible reasons why COVID-19 can impair male sexual health, health experts say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disputes over mask mandates comprise 75% of unruly passenger complaints on planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/07/06/disputes-over-mask-mandates-comprise-75percent-of-faas-unruly-passenger-complaints-on-planes-.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHINESE DIPLOMAT MOCKS TRAGEDY...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/a-chinese-diplomat-mocks-the-surfside-tragedy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Li Yang’s tweets tell you everything you already knew about the Chinese Communist Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol Police opening up new offices in FL, CA...</title>
      <link>http://www.drudgereport.comfoxnews.com/politics/capitol-police-new-offices-florida-california-threats-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.drudgereport.comfoxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WARNING TAMPA</title>
      <link>https://weather.com/storms/hurricane/news/2021-07-06-tropical-storm-elsa-forecast-hurricane-florida-southeast-united</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's the latest, complete forecast briefing on the fifth named storm of the hurricane season. - Articles from The Weather Channel | weather.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman Sues Tenn. for Revoking Her '69' Vanity Plate...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2021/07/06/tennessee-woman-sues-state-officials-for-revoking-her-69-vanity-plate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nashville’s Leah Gilliam says her vanity plate is protected by the First Amendment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Village's peace shattered by 'screaming and moaning' from swingers festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3228299/locals-furious-about-swingers-festival/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FURIOUS locals complained that their village’s peace and quiet was shattered by “screaming and moaning” from a swingers festival at the weekend. Four-hundred swingers took part in a four-day sex-fe…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Aryeh Bourkoff Became Media's Hottest Dealmaker...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/business-news/aryeh-bourkoff-media-dealmaker-1234975489/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fresh from the blockbuster deal that puts him in charge of one the world’s most important media companies, David Zaslav, the CEO of Discovery, is waxing poetic about an investment banker, of …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Arthritis drugs reduce deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210706-arthritis-drugs-tocilizumab-and-sarilumab-reduce-covid-deaths-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arthritis drugs tocilizumab and sarilumab reduce Covid deaths: study</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuhan virologist claims Covid originated in USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3229625/wuhan-virologist-covid-originated-america-white-supremacists-bullying-scientists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA has sensationally claimed that Covid originated in America in a bid to shift the blame from Wuhan and said that “white supremacists” are bullying anti-lab leak scientists. The nat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC fights to keep cruise rules in place, warns of increased spread...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/tourism-cruises/article252593583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is fighting to keep its COVID-19 cruise regulations in place and warned a federal judge that without them, there is increased risk of COVID-19 spread in the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65% believe in aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/aliens-exist-poll-8749c450-1e70-4e8e-a2ed-130c6e46c35e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new poll surveyed 10,417 U.S. adults in June ahead of the release of a UFO report mandated by Congress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI seized 'fully constructed Capitol LEGO set' from alleged rioter's home...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/crime/lego-evidence-seized-745916</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JULY 6--Along with a notebook containing step-by-step instructions on how to create a “hometown militia,” FBI agents seized a “fully constructed U.S. Capitol Lego set” from the Pennsylvania man indi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVEY: MALE FRIENDSHIP IN CRISIS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/2021/07/american-men-suffer-a-friendship-recession/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American men have fewer friends than in decades past. We should dedicate time to fostering friendships. They provide an immediate and enduring reward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19-year-old TIKTOK star dies from gunshot wound...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/19-year-old-tiktok-star-swavy-known-for-dances-and-memes-dies-from-gunshot-wound-police/ar-AALQ6Xy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TikTok star Swavy, whose real name is Matima Miller, died from a gunshot wound on Monday, the Wilmington Police Department said. He was 19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French prosecutors probe 'slavery' claims against Saudi prince...</title>
      <link>https://www.dawn.com/news/1633371</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dawn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some maids were required to sleep on the floor and barely had time to eat while serving the prince's four children, claims paper.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oxford trials first HIV vaccines...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/first-hiv-vaccines-given-volunteers-24473264</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In what scientists hope could be a critical blow against the disease, volunteers have received the first HIV vaccinations as part of an Oxford University trial as 'an effective HIV vaccine has been elusive for 40 years'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSK XL:  SPACEX Launching Rocket the Size of Statue of Liberty...</title>
      <link>https://observer.com/2021/07/spacex-starship-super-heavy-booster-orbit-test-preview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;observer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Super Heavy booster will have more than 30 Raptor engines at the bottom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nordic Region, Arctic Circle Feel the Heat as Brutal Summer Hits...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/theaters/americas/2021-07-06/weather-northern-hemisphere-arctic-circle-heat-2066360.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record-high temperatures from Canada to Scandinavia and intense wildfires flaring up from California to Russia’s Far East are adding to extreme weather events recorded at the start of the summer in the Northern Hemisphere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The end of California's groundwater free-for-all... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/drought-the-end-of-california-s-groundwater-free-for-all/ar-AALO4Oq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Long opposed, now meters are measuring farmers' water use and changing cultivation in the Golden State's thirsty fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUBWAY Grasps for Lifeline With Americans Shunning Aging Brand...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagobusiness.com/restaurants/subway-grasps-lifeline-americans-shun-aging-brand</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagobusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World run by gangsters': Spike Lee sets political tone...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/world-run-gangsters-spike-lee-150924908.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cannes film festival kicked off with a heavy political tone on Tuesday, with jury president Spike Lee denouncing authoritarians and the fact that black people are still "hunted down like animals" in the US.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Looters ransack San Francisco NEIMAN MARCUS in broad daylight...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/san-francisco-looters-neiman-marcus-california</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looters were captured on video Monday ransacking a Neiman Marcus in San Francisco as thefts continue to plague businesses in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>125 test positive at Texas church camp...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/coronavirus/article252591403.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“This is a reminder that COVID-19 is still here and we have to take precautions,” the health director said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANDATES AT WORK?</title>
      <link>https://www.protocol.com/workplace/interest-in-vaccine-mandates-rising</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.protocol.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Facebook, Google and Amazon won’t make employees get vaccinated before returning to the office. But some other big tech companies are starting to show interest in vax mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital nomads embraced work-life flexibility. Now their offices want them back...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/business/business-news/office-life-beckons-again-pandemic-s-digital-nomads-weigh-benefits-n1273000</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid-19 opened up the possibility of a nomadic lifestyle to entirely new groups of people. Now, many of them don't want to go back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buyers shun older buildings...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/condo-buyers-shun-older-buildings-after-surfside-collapse/ar-AALPV5D?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. – The collapse of the Champlain condo building in Surfside could reverberate through the real estate market in South Florida for months to come, real estate experts say. The red-hot condo market could cool as buyers might hesitate to buy in older buildings, worried that the buildings have put off maintenance and that mammoth repair bills could be coming, brokers say. ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STORM ELSA FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/live-news/live-follow-tropical-storm-elsa-updates/975544</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Southeast puts together its final preparations and as Tropical Storm Elsa closes in on the Florida peninsula, follow along here for the latest updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Monroe, dead 59 years, still counterfeiter's best friend...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/marilyn-monroe-dead-59-years-is-a-counterfeiter-s-best-friend/article_4b4abcaa-84ac-5f3c-8fe7-d960386712ef.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly six decades after her death, Marilyn Monroe is still a popular choice for mugs, T-shirts, jewelry and other products using her name — even illegally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Sydney lockdown EXTENDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9761217/Coronavirus-Australia-Sydney-lockdown-extended-July-16-schools-closed-masks-stay.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Millions of Sydneysiders will endure another week of lockdown, with restrictions extended until at least July 16.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparks fly as musical film 'ANNETTE' geeks out festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210706-sparks-fly-as-musical-film-annette-geeks-out-cannes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sparks fly as musical film 'Annette' geeks out Cannes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Rash of Unexplained Deaths at Fort Hood...</title>
      <link>https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2021/06/inside-the-rash-of-unexplained-deaths-at-fort-hood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vanityfair.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of people were killed, died by suicide, or went missing from the Texas military base last year alone. What is behind the violence and tragedy at Fort Hood?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 79, McConnell contemplating legacy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2021/07/mitch-mcconnell-power-senate/619350/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At age 79, Mitch McConnell is contemplating his legacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin war dogs parachute into battle from 13,000ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3227010/putin-war-dogs-parachute-battle-13000ft-russian/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BONKERS footage has emerged showing Russian army pooches parachuting into battle zones from heights of 13,000ft. Vladimir Putin’s crack team of canine warriors can be seen being hurled out of plane…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI reveals 'exact location aliens hiding'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/3222902/ai-location-aliens-hiding-civilisations-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SCIENTISTS have identified the place where aliens are most likely lurking in the Milky Way. Using computer simulations, the US team determined that the mysterious centre of our galaxy represents ou…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moguls Ready for Deals and Corporate Drama at Sun Valley Conference...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/sun-valley-allen-co-conference-discovery-warnermedia-1235012189/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If ever there was a year for the Allen &amp; Co. conference to be a fertile ground for dealmaking among the titans of tech and media, it’s this one. The entertainment industry is in an everyone’s-t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Soil. No Growing Seasons. Just Add Water and Technology...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/no-soil-no-growing-seasons-just-add-water-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOREHEAD, Ky. — In this pretty town on the edge of coal country, a high-tech greenhouse so large it could</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megyn Kelly To Host Daily Talk Show For SIRIUSXM...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/07/megyn-kelly-siriusxm-talk-show-1234786686/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Megyn Kelly has signed with SiriusXM to host a daily talk show, taking her podcast to the satellite network’s Triumph channel starting on Sept. 7. The former Fox News host will headline The M…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan troops filmed surrendering...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9760119/20-000-Tajikistan-troops-ordered-border-stop-Afghanistan-soldiers-fleeing-Taliban.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;General Austin Scott Miller, commander of US and Nato troops in Afghanistan, said he was shocked by how quickly the Afghan National Army had surrendered to the resurgent jihadists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lambda: 'World's most transmissible strain' spreading in 31 countries...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9759677/Coronavirus-Australia-Covid-19-strain-Lambda-infectious-Delta-variant.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lambda variant was detected in a traveller undergoing hotel quarantine in New South Wales, Australia, in April, according to the national genomics database AusTrakka.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black bears, with disease that makes fearless, swim alongside beachgoers in Tahoe...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9758035/Black-bears-play-water-sun-Lake-Tahoe-surrounded-stunned-beachgoers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A large adult black bear and her three cubs visited a South Lake Tahoe beach last weekend to escape the heat while beachgoers watched in shock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man went on racist rant, gave out address and said come 'see me.' 100 protesters did...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-man-who-went-on-a-racist-rant-gave-out-his-address-and-said-come-see-me-more-than-100-protesters-did/ar-AALPc5r</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The New Jersey man was later arrested as protesters gathered outside of his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horn-wearing 'shaman.' Cowboy evangelist. For some, Capitol riot was Christian revolt...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/A-horn-wearing-shaman-A-cowboy-evangelist-For-16295334.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Late last month, one of the accused Jan. 6 Capitol insurrectionists told a D.C. judge...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel blocks law that keeps out Palestinian spouses...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-israel-religion-business-government-and-politics-f99c3aff0368bde00eef634ef42fde7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s parliament early on Tuesday failed to renew a law that bars Arab citizens from extending citizenship or residency rights to spouses from the occupied West Bank and Gaza, in a tight vote that raised doubts about the viability of the country’s new coalition government.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER restricts account of academic who mocked China leader...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/china-business-technology-3741dcfb1c2eb11f17280c9ed8c06fc4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WELLINGTON, New Zealand (AP) — A New Zealand academic says Twitter temporarily restricted her account after she mocked Chinese President Xi Jinping. University of Canterbury Professor Anne-Marie Brady is an expert on China's attempts to exert political influence around the world and has been an outspoken critic of its ruling Communist Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Streets Erupt Into '12 Hours Of Non-Stop Chaos'; Homicides, Shootings...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2021/07/05/oakland-july-4-sideshow-violence/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Fourth of July reeled into "12 hours of non-stop chaos" Sunday night with several victims wounded by celebratory gunfire, a homicide and a massive sideshow marred by gunfire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Tokyo Olympics approach, covid worries rise in Japan...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/africa-japan-tokyo-2020-tokyo-olympics-olympic-games-9fbd360e4524dca0b25140e60ebda389</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The pressure of hosting an Olympics during a still-active pandemic is beginning to show in Japan. The games begin July 23, with organizers determined they will go on, even with a reduced number of spectators or possibly none at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Will China Rule World? Maybe Never...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/china-rule-world-maybe-never-210013340.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- When will China overtake the U.S. to become the world’s biggest economy?Few questions are more consequential, whether it’s for executives wondering where long-term profits will come from, investors weighing the dollar’s status as global reserve currency, or generals strategizing over geopolitical flashpoints.In Beijing, where they’ve just been celebrating the 100th anniversary of the Chinese Communist Party, leaders are doing their best to present the baton-change as imminent and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taliban advance accelerating...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-taliban-advance-is-accelerating/ar-AALOBkg </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inmate firefighter takes engine on joyride, crashes and injures self...</title>
      <link>https://www.gazettextra.com/news/nation_world/inmate-firefighter-takes-engine-on-joyride-in-california-crashes-and-injures-himself/article_0dc150be-3418-5bf2-bec8-eaec4077b220.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.gazettextra.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate firefighter stole a fire truck while fighting a vegetation fire in Gold Country outside Sacramento, California, and took it on a joyride before crashing and injuring himself, a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Soil. No Growing Seasons. Just Add Water and Technology....</title>
      <link>https://www.365newslive.com/2021/07/06/no-soil-no-growing-seasons-just-add-water-and-technology/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.365newslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOREHEAD, Ky. — On this fairly city on the sting of coal nation, a high-tech greenhouse so massive it might cowl 50 soccer fields glows with the pinks and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They Resurrected MGM. AMAZON Bought Studio. Now What?</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/07/06/they-resurrected-mgm-amazon-bought-the-studio-now-what/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul Thomas Anderson and Michael De Luca are film geeks with a shared history. As a studio executive, Mr. De</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah's Great Salt Lake Near 170-Year Low...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/great-salt-lake-air-quality-lakes-wildlife-lifestyle-1adae582035c7f1b03f2a5cb57c0dda8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — The silvery blue waters of the Great Salt Lake sprawl across the Utah desert, having covered an area nearly the size of Delaware for much of history. For years, though, the largest natural lake west of the Mississippi River has been shrinking.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
