<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NY Port Hustles to Cut Logjam Amid Labor Woes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bnnbloomberg.ca/new-york-port-hustles-to-cut-rare-logjam-amid-covid-labor-woes-1.1704736</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bnnbloomberg.ca&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Port of New York and New Jersey is working to clear a small but rare bottleneck of container ships anchored off the coast of Long Island as Covid-19 cases among dockworkers collide with a pandemic-fueled surge in cargo volumes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watershed moment: New law allows noncitizens to vote...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-new-york-new-york-city-voting-united-states-64edb2ed4de261156f5e717b61101247</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — More than 800,000 noncitizens and “Dreamers” in New York City will have access to the ballot box — and could vote in municipal elections as early as next year — after Mayor Eric Adams allowed legislation to automatically become law Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why was there less lightning during lockdowns?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/lightning-covid-lockdowns/story?id=82143368</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have determined that COVID-19 lockdowns resulted in less lightning because aerosol emissions also declined.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENN trans swimmer loses to YALE trans swimmer in women's Ivy League race...</title>
      <link>https://www.outkick.com/penn-transgender-swimmer-lia-thomas-beaten-by-yale-transgender-swimmer-iszac-henig/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.outkick.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Penn transgender swimmer Lia Thomas, who had been crushing her competition since joining the women's swim team after three years swimming as a biological</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Colombian with non-terminal illness dies legally by euthanasia...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/man-dies-euthanasia-colombia-first-non-terminal-illness-rcna11506</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombian Victor Escobar became the first person in the Andean country with a non-terminal illness to die by legally regulated euthanasia late on Friday, his lawyer confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder suspects allegedly had sex in victim's bed while she died in next room...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/08/murder-suspects-allegedly-had-sex-in-victims-bed-as-she-died/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Two people accused in the murder of an Oklahoma woman allegedly had sex in the victim’s bed while they heard her “struggling to live” in the next room, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cows given VR headsets to reduce anxiety, increase milk...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2022/01/07/farmer-gives-cooped-up-cows-vr-headsets-to-increase-milk-production-15880604/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They're cooped up in a cow shed but think they're outside in the pasture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside landmark push for reparations for Black Californians...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/09/california-reparations-slavery-african-americans</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taskforce including civil rights leaders and attorneys scrutinizes legacy of centuries of injustice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escapees pay bribes, cross rivers, risk lives -- to return to NKorea...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/escapees-pay-bribes-cross-rivers-110039277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While tens of thousands risk everything to flee North Korea, a few, having failed to adjust to the capitalist South, make a desperate journey back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man makes bomb threat to jump line for DOJA CAT concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.indystar.com/story/news/local/2022/01/08/doja-cat-indianapolis-2022-free-concert-bomb-threat-monument-circle/9145396002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.indystar.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Doja Cat is performing in Indianapolis at Monument Circle for the College Football Playoff national championship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China's Tianjin testing all residents after omicron found...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-winter-olympics-sports-health-beijing-84d7be3e7dfb2da4cce5b6e87d321a46</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Tianjin, a major Chinese port city near the capital Beijing, began mass testing of its 14 million residents on Sunday after a cluster of 20 children and adults tested positive for COVID-19, including at least two with the omicron variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Backer of 'Anti-Smoking' Vape Group? Big Tobacco...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/secret-backer-anti-smoking-vape-020030856.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Elizabeth Brockway/The Daily Beast/GettyA pro-vaping group says it wants to save your life. Cigarettes, they remind us, can kill you. But smokers may be surprised who’s behind that message.“The World Vapers’ Alliance amplifies the voice of passionate vapers around the world and empowers them to make a difference for their communities,” reads the homepage for the WVA, whose logo is revolutionary pastiche—a left fist clenching a vape pen. “Back vaping. Beat smoking,” the page</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic pictured smiling with kids day AFTER testing Covid positive...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/17258987/novak-djokovic-anti-vaxxer-tennis-charity-kids-test-positive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANTI-VAX tennis star Novak Djokovic was snapped smiling while handing out awards to a group of young tennis fans AFTER testing positive for Covid. The World No 1 tested positive on December 16, but…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA really heading for second civil war?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/09/is-the-us-really-heading-for-a-second-civil-war</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the country polarised and Republicans embracing authoritarianism, some experts fear a Northern Ireland-style insurgency but others say armed conflict remains improbable</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL cases, hospitalizations surging, but has 2nd-lowest death rate. What's going on?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/florida-e2-80-99s-covid-cases-and-hospitalizations-are-surging-but-the-state-has-the-second-lowest-death-rate-in-the-nation-what-e2-80-99s-going-on/ar-AASyQKx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 MILLION OUT SICK NEXT WEEK?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10381669/Five-million-people-call-sick-week-hits-second-highest-daily-case-count.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States has posted its second-highest daily total for new COVID-19 cases, as one expert predicts some 5 million Americans could call in sick in the coming week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals struggle to match WALMART pay as staff flees omicron...</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/currentnews/newsheadlines/s-2617292-p2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. hospitals are struggling to get the workers they need to treat patients through the winter’s COVID-19 surge as the virus collides with a historically tight labor market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant Telescope Grows in Space...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/08/a-giant-telescope-grows-in-space/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astronomers are starting to breathe again. Two weeks ago, the most powerful space observatory ever built roared into the sky,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duchess of Cambridge, the reliable royal, turns 40...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-arts-and-entertainment-prince-philip-london-europe-a1668accc67638478e993b10e7824840</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — At least there’s Kate. The Duchess of Cambridge, who turns 40 on Sunday, has emerged as Britain’s reliable royal. After Prince Harry and Meghan’s stormy departure to California in 2020, the death of Prince Philip last year, and now sex abuse allegations against Prince Andrew, the former Kate Middleton remains in the public eye as the smiling mother of three who can comfort grieving parents at a children's hospice or wow the nation by playing piano during a televised Christmas concert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital turns to heated tent to ease crush...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-michigan-muskegon-0c3cda9fa32c62bf05c062e056be65ac</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUSKEGON, Mich. (AP) — A hospital in western Michigan is using a heated tent as extra emergency space due to a surge in COVID-19 cases. The tent at Mercy Health Muskegon was set up a few weeks ago but put into service Thursday, WOOD-TV reported.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkmenistan leader wants 'Gates of Hell' fire put out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-fires-environment-and-nature-turkmenistan-ashgabat-5aa743375a84ecd181a8f3886e322047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ASHGABAT, Turkmenistan (AP) — The president of Turkmenistan is calling for an end to one of the country’s most notable but infernal sights — the blazing natural gas crater widely referred to as the “Gates of Hell.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vax protesters tell Macron: 'We'll piss you off'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20220108154503-gu785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/FRANCE-PROTEST (TV, PIX):Anti-vax protesters tell France's Macron: 'We'll piss you off'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC: Conflict Quickly Emerges Between Top Prosecutor, Police Commissioner...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/08/conflict-quickly-emerges-between-top-prosecutor-and-police-commissioner/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York City’s new police commissioner has expressed severe dissatisfaction with the policies of the new Manhattan district attorney, sending</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: 28,000 canceled flights later, airlines still looking for upper hand against virus, weather...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/28000-canceled-flights-later-airlines-still-looking-for-upper-hand-against-omicron-weather/ar-AASyQlG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions between USA, Russia rise over military involvement in Kazakhstan...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/588860-tensions-between-us-russia-rise-over-military-involvement-in-kazakhstan</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Diehards About to Find Out If Really Bubble...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-diehards-really-bubble-154108904.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- To cryptocurrency true believers, Bitcoin is the ultimate store of value, the most solid hedge against the rampant inflation manufactured by reckless central banks and their money-printing. To skeptics, the crypto world as a whole is a mirage whose massive run-up past $2 trillion was simply the speculative byproduct of the extraordinary amount of easy cash that’s been sloshing around in the global economy — in effect, a big bubble.Most Read from BloombergOmicron Study in South Afr</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron explosion spurs nationwide breakdown of services...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-health-business-education-pandemics-76830eee3a8c2a5688df4fc77488195a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambulances in Kansas speed toward hospitals then suddenly change direction because hospitals are full. Employee shortages in New York City cause delays in trash and subway services and diminish the ranks of firefighters and emergency workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Gravitational Forces Of Sun, Moon Impact Behavior Of All Organisms...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/sun-and-moon-impact-behavior/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"All matter on Earth, both live and inert, experiences the effects of the gravitational forces of the Sun and Moon expressed in the form of tides," researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat, egg shortages?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4420761/meat-egg-shortages-fears-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEVERAL American supermarkets are reporting incidents of “bare shelves” as fears grow over an imminent meat and egg shortage amid a surge in Omicron cases. Food chains have been one of the first to…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK 'most Covid-immune country'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/health/4421359/uk-most-immune-country-omicron-covid/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN could be the world’s most immune country in the fight against Covid-19, according to an expert. The hugely positive claim comes as data revealed around 98 per cent of over 15s in the …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing global potato shortage affecting french fries from Japan to Kenya...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/a-growing-global-potato-shortage-is-affecting-french-fries-from-japan-to-kenya/ar-AASzhF2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bare rooms, rotten fruit, boredom: Isolation on cruises...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bare-rooms-rotten-fruit-and-boredom-quarantine-life-on-infected-cruises/ar-AASz79q</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitol attack panel investigates Trump over potential criminal conspiracy...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2022/jan/08/capitol-attack-committee-donald-trump-white-house-stop-biden-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Messages between Mark Meadows and others suggest the Trump White House coordinated efforts to stop Joe Biden’s certification</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRING A TRAILER Sold $829 Million in Cars in '21, Walloping Auction Houses...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/business/bring-a-trailer-sold-829m-in-cars-in-2021-walloping-auction-houses/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2021, the online car auction site Bring a Trailer sold $828.7 million worth of cars, a 108% gain over the $398 million it sold in 2020 — and a full quarter billion dollars ahead of its closest live-auction-house competitor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Historic step forward or cover-up plot? Pentagon UFO office splits ufologists...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/national-security/disclosure-or-deception-new-ufo-pentagon-office-divides-believers-n1287199</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. government hasn't comprehensively studied UFOs in decades — but not all ufologists are excited about a new Pentagon investigative office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans adopted millions of dogs during the pandemic. Now what do we do with them?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/americans-adopted-millions-of-dogs-during-the-pandemic-now-what-do-we-do-with-them/ar-AASwPtf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse clothing, travel, plastic surgery: Life in 2030...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/08/experts-predict-living-in-the-metaverse-by-2030/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In its fully realized form, the metaverse promises to offer true-to-life sights, sounds and even smells, where a tour of ancient Greece or a visit to a Seoul café can happen from your home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENOUGH: FED UP LEARN TO LIVE WITH VIRUS</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fed-pandemic-angelenos-time-learn-130018175.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Omicron variant infects record numbers of people, many in Southern California say they are no longer willing to hide from a virus that has already killed 800,000 Americans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHOLE FOODS Claims Constitutional Right to Disallow 'Black Lives Matter' Masks...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/whole-foods-cites-constitution-disallowing-204631789.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- U.S. labor board prosecutors are trying to violate Whole Foods Market’s copyright and constitutional rights by forcing it to let employees wear “Black Lives Matter” masks at work, the Amazon.com Inc. subsidiary claims.Most Read from BloombergOmicron Study in South Africa Points to End of Acute Pandemic PhaseU.S. Is Open as Canada Shuts Down. The Difference? Their Health Care SystemsCiti Confronts Vaccine Holdouts in No Jab, No Job MandateDjokovic Used December Covid Case for Exemp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinead O'Connor Says Teen Son Dead After Disappearing...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/sinead-oconnor-says-her-teen-son-shane-is-dead-after-disappearing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer tweeted that the 17-year-old “decided to end his earthly struggle today.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC updates straining health depts...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/cdc-updates-are-straining-already-pressed-public-health-departments-rcna11275</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Michael Kilkenny did not expect the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention news release he received on Dec. 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poitier changed Blackness in eyes of generation of Black people...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/sidney-poitier-changed-blackness-eyes-generation-black-people-rcna11375</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The power of Sidney Poitier’s career resounded around the country Friday as it mourned his death. For many Black people, his films went beyond entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic granted vax exemption after testing positive for Covid, court docs show...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/08/tennis/novak-djokovic-covid-australia-intl-spt/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Novak Djokovic was granted a medical exemption to compete in the Australian Open as he had recently recovered from Covid-19, court documents published on Saturday by Australia's Federal Circuit show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-driving race cars zip into history at CES...</title>
      <link>https://techxplore.com/news/2022-01-self-driving-cars-history-ces.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;techxplore.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A racecar with nobody at the wheel snaked around another to snatch the lead on an oval track at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas Friday in an unprecedented high-speed match between self-driving vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kazakhstan Arrests Ex-Intelligence Chief on Suspicion of Treason...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/08/kazakhstan-arrests-ex-intelligence-chief-on-suspicion-of-treason/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BISHKEK, Kyrgyzstan — Kazakhstan’s powerful intelligence agency said on Saturday that it had arrested Karim Masimov, who only days before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy expands boot camp to sharpen focus on character issues...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/politics-navy-767b230cd898b3e43e0866d3992fc331</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Navy is adding two weeks to boot camp this year in a major overhaul aimed at improving recruits' war fighting and emergency skills while also focusing on suicide prevention and character issues such as sexual assault, hazing and extremism in the ranks.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
