<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON to run daily temp checks on workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/608338/amazon-temperature-checks-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMAZON has said it will start taking daily temperatures of its employees after reports that at least 17 company locations have had employees test positive for the coronavirus. The retail giant will…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Yorkers who break distancing rules face fines of $500...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/albany/story/2020/03/29/new-yorkers-who-break-social-distancing-rules-will-now-face-fines-up-to-500-1269545</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fines will be a last resort, but de Blasio has authorized police officers to give them out to people who are ordered to disperse but fail to do so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megachurches Still Packing In Crowds...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/some-megachurches-are-still-packing-in-crowds/ar-BB11SBxU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Social Distancing Looked Like in 1666...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/what-social-distancing-looked-like-in-1666/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A lot of English people believed 1666 would be the year of the apocalypse. You can’t really blame them. In</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man hosts party, gets arrested...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/coronavirus/article241605346.html  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugs, Kisses, Dining Out During Virus Raise Fear in Mexico...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/hugs-kisses-dining-out-during-virus-raise-fear-in-mexico/ar-BB11SinY</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO CITY WILL BE SPARED</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/media/dr-deborah-birx-issues-coronavirus-warning-we-dont-think-any-city-will-be-spared</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump sought to keep the public safe Saturday when he said he was considering a mandatory quarantine for the New York City metro area, a key member of his Coronavirus Task Force said Saturday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Armed 'vigilantes' in Maine cut down tree to quarantine men from New Jersey...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165415/Armed-vigilantes-cut-tree-use-roadblock-quarantine-workers-New-Jersey.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said they were called on Friday afternoon to the island of Vinalhaven to reports of  several people with guns threatening a man who had left his home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LONDON LOCKDOWN COULD GO MONTHS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8165169/Coronavirus-lockdown-SIX-MONTHS-says-Dr-Jenny-Harries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Jenny Harries told a Downing Street press conference that people should not be viewing the coronavirus crisis as something that will blow over soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vaunts his TV ratings amid pandemic..</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-vaunts-tv-ratings-amid-virus-pandemic-201026555.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump took to Twitter on Sunday to vaunt the television ratings of his daily briefings on the coronavirus pandemic gripping the United States. "Because the 'Ratings' of my News Conferences etc. are so high... the Lamestream Media is going CRAZY," the president tweeted</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow Orders All Residents to Stay Home...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/moscow-mayor-orders-residents-stay-home-192601827.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moscow's mayor announced strict isolation rules for the city from Monday, the latest in a series of measures introduced in Russia to fight the spread of the coronavirus. The new restrictions would apply to all the city's residents, regardless of age, mayor Sergei Sobyanin said in a statement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field hospital set up in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/field-hospital-set-yorks-central-park-202813283.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York's Central Park on Sunday, a field hospital was going up. Samaritan's Purse, a US-based Christian global relief agency, is setting up the hospital on the park's East Meadow lawn, where workers in face masks unloaded a white tarp and other equipment on the grass. The site is right</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing, testing, testing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7d851c87c07a7e0f67c245abe0d86e56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As President Donald Trump looks for ways to restore normalcy in parts of the U.S., his foremost infection disease expert says the country could experience more than 100,000...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASHBACK:  Why Second Wave of 1918 Spanish Flu Was So Deadly...</title>
      <link>https://www.history.com/news/spanish-flu-second-wave-resurgence</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.history.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first strain of the Spanish flu wasn’t particularly deadly. Then it came back in the fall with a vengeance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Tried to Build New Fleet of Ventilators. Mission Failed...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/03/29/the-u-s-tried-to-build-a-new-fleet-of-ventilators-the-mission-failed/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thirteen years ago, a group of U.S. public health officials came up with a plan to address what they regarded</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 MORE MONTHS? Lockdown could last to June...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11279739/coronavirus-lockdown-june-death-toll-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN must stay in full coronavirus lockdown until June to beat coronavirus, a health chief has warned. It comes after the UK’s death toll for the deadly bug surged to 1,019 last night R…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ER doctor fired after criticizing his hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/coronavirus/2020/03/er-doctor-fired-after-criticizing-coronavirus-response-at-his-hospital.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The physician complained on Facebook that the hospital was slow to screen visitors, negligent in not testing staff, wrong to rely on a company that was taking 10 days to process COVID-19 test results, and derelict in obtaining protective equipment for staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Tried to Build New Fleet of Ventilators. Mission Failed...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/29/business/coronavirus-us-ventilator-shortage.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the coronavirus spreads, the collapse of the project helps explain America’s acute shortage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate states encounter beleaguered national stockpile...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/desperate-for-medical-equipment-states-encounter-a-beleaguered-national-stockpile/ar-BB11QGh3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First federal inmate dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/coronavirus-disease-covid-19-latest-news-2020-03-29/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The total number of cases in the U.S. increased to more than 124,000, with more than 2,100 deaths, including an infant in Illinois.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why antibody testing in one town could provide way forward...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/antibody-testing-colorado-town-provide-forward/story?id=69856623&amp;</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Testing going on in the Colorado ski town could allow lifting of restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida state border checkpoints begin...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/news/2020/03/28/florida-coronavirus-cases-pass-4000-border-checkpoints-vacation-rentals-suspended/2934407001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis tells travelers, "Don't come here" as cases pass 4,000. The state is also checking Louisianians crossing the border by car.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Spreaders Poised to Unleash Second Wave of Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/coronavirus-silent-spreaders-poised-to-unleash-second-wave-of-disaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Trump repeatedly suggesting restrictions might ease in a matter of days or weeks, the prospect of silent spreaders wreaking epidemiological havoc looms large.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost Month: How Failure to Test Blinded USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/the-lost-month-how-a-failure-to-test-blinded-the-us-to-covid-19/ar-BB11Qo84</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment, Shutdowns Raise Risks...</title>
      <link>https://reason.com/2020/03/27/pandemic-related-unemployment-and-shutdowns-are-a-recipe-for-social-unrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;reason.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple run Dubai balcony marathon...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/couple-run-dubai-balcony-marathon-beat-coronavirus-blues-095259686.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A South African couple who ran a marathon on the balcony of their Dubai apartment, streaming it online, plan to take the project global to help people shake off the coronavirus blues. Collin Allin, 41, and wife Hilda covered the 42.2-kilometre (26-mile) distance by running more than 2,100 laps of their</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEARS OF CIVIL UNREST...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/069d01bafbb1f15b1f6c4a4479ab1456</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST BLOOMFIELD, Mich. (AP) — More than a fifth of Detroit's police force is quarantined; two officers have died from coronavirus and at least 39 have tested positive, including the chief of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Religious exemptions could keep pews full in some states...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/states-crack-gatherings-due-coronavirus-exemptions-religious-groups/story?id=69847021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some states have not barred churches from gathering despite COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog-walking ban sparks outrage in Serbia...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/mar/29/dog-walking-ban-sparks-outrage-serbia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pet owners in Serbia are furious over the populist government’s decision to ban even a brief walk for people with dogs during an evening curfew to contain the spread of the new coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPAIN SURGE: Death Toll Rises 838 in Worst Day Yet...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/11280320/coronavirus-deaths-in-spain-rise-by-838-in-countrys-worst-day-yet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SPAIN has registered another national record for coronavirus deaths in a single day at 838. It surpasses the figure for the previous 24 hours, announced yesterday morning by six. ⚠️ Read our corona…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOUNGEST VICTIM: Baby under age of 1 dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/605000/baby-youngest-coronavirus-victim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN INFANT under the age of one has died after testing positive for the coronavirus. The death of the Illinois baby was announced by Governor Pritzker on Saturday, local news reported. The baby is b…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How virus mutated and 8 strains raced around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8164235/US-coronavirus-Map-shows-eight-strains-raced-world.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers say the virus appears to mutate very slowly, with only tiny differences between the different strains, and that none of the strains of the virus is more deadly than another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers already planning more $timulus...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/489946-lawmakers-already-planning-more-coronavirus-stimulus-after-2t-package</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers are already planning another round of legislation aimed at keeping companies flush with capital and millions of workers on payrolls amid the coronavirus pandemic, even after passing a $2 trillion relief bill this past week, the largest s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locked up: No masks, sanitizer as virus spreads behind bars...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e1e4ffaeb6bf9a9fabcc566fe5b110d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something was wrong. The chow hall line at New York’s Rikers Island jail had halted. For three hours, the men stood and waited, without food, until a correctional officer quietly delivered the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado tears through northeast Arkansas...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/03/29/tornado-tears-through-arkansas-injuring-least-6-people/2935258001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A tornado ripped through northeast Arkansas on Saturday, leaving six people hurt after hitting a college town of Jonesboro.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban centers nationwide gird for catastrophe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/its-no-different-from-new-york-urban-centers-nationwide-gird-for-catastrophic-virus-outbreak/ar-BB11QzZ6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC Mayor to synagogues: Close or be shut down permanently...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Diaspora/NYC-Mayor-to-synagogues-Close-for-coronavirus-or-be-shut-down-permanently-622767</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I understand how important people’s faiths are to them, and we need our faith in this time of crisis. But we do not need gatherings that will endanger people."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industrial alcohol 'cure' kills hundreds of Iranians...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/coronavirus/ny-coronavirus-iran-alcohol-20200328-nzjbp6lspjaafnfbhmsoa7lie4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iranians are dying by drinking industrial alcohol in an attempt to cure coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media nightmare of cures, claims, snake-oil sales...</title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/why-novel-coronavirus-became-social-media-nightmare-014917035.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biggest reputational risk Facebook and other social media companies had expected in 2020 was fake news surrounding the US presidential election. Be it foreign or domestic in origin, the misinformation threat seemed familiar, perhaps even manageable. The novel coronavirus, however, has opened up</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospitals turn to snorkel masks... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/hospitals-turn-snorkel-masks-ease-respirator-overload-020738689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As hospitals face an overload of COVID-19 patients struggling to breathe, innovative medical staff are turning to snorkelling masks from sports stores to stop their lungs collapsing. The idea started in Italy, the European country worst-hit by the coronavirus pandemic, with hospitals in other nations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-virus measures spark Mideast fears of setback in liberties... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/anti-virus-measures-spark-mideast-fears-setback-liberties-022504291.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armoured vehicles in the streets, hundreds arrested, smartphone surveillance -- sweeping measures to fight the coronavirus have raised concerns in the Middle East over the erosion of already threatened human rights. As the world battles the COVID-19 pandemic, more than three billion people are now living</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
