<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Squirrels Have Personalities...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/squirrels-personalities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Animal personality is a hard science, but if it makes you relate to animals more, maybe people will be more interested in conserving them,” researchers say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands released from prison because of Covid. Will they have to return?</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/thousands-released-prison-covid-will-return-rcna1977</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 4,500 people released to home confinement from prison are facing the possibility of being returned to prison once the Covid-19 pandemic recedes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden readies campaign stop...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-heads-west-to-assess-wildfires-campaign-for-newsom/ar-AAOmhd3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden departed on a three-state western swing Monday. In California, he'll assess wildfire damage and campaign for Newsom ahead of the recall election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer refused mask in WELLS FARGO. Waited to ambush manager after his shift...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/a-customer-who-refused-to-wear-a-mask-in-a-wells-fargo-bank-waited-in-the-parking-lot-to-violently-ambush-the-manager-at-the-end-of-his-shift-report-says/ar-AAOmgn3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The bank manager was reportedly called a racist slur by a client and then attacked in the parking lot when his shift ended.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honolulu moves to destroy 'Stairway to Heaven'...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/11/honolulu-city-council-moves-to-destroy-stairway-to-heaven/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Honolulu City Council moved to remove the city’s famous Haiku Stairs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Al Qaeda chief in new video despite rumors he was dead...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/middle-east-syria-afghanistan-taliban-islamic-state-group-79fc96bd028a31718e3c69fc6aba2a96</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIRUT (AP) — Al-Qaida leader Ayman al-Zawahri appeared in a new video marking the 20th anniversary of the Sept. 11, attacks, months after rumors spread that he was dead. The SITE Intelligence Group that monitors jihadist websites said the video was released Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press freedoms crumble as authoritarianism spreads...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/press-freedoms-crumble-hong-kong-afghanistan-b0c8799c-84bb-4340-91f3-976e9a8484fa.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The press is being pulverized in places where democracy is deteriorating.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildfire forces closure of California freeway...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-environment-and-nature-california-weather-wildfires-f7c21368ec324ca393f60965a9f73c4c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CASTIAC, Calif. (AP) — A wildfire near Castaic Saturday has led to the closure of a part of a major freeway in Southern California, officials told local media. The fire, known as the Route Fire, reached 392 acres, or a little more than half a square mile, as of 6:28 p.m.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newsom fights for survival as historic crises fuel extraordinary race...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2021/sep/12/california-recall-election-gavin-newsom</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic governor says Covid and western fires illuminate the stark choice voters must make</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why America's So Bad at Keeping People Alive...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/why-is-america-so-bad-at-keeping-people-alive/ar-AAOmdgN</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. life spans, which have fallen behind those in Europe, are telling us something important about American society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3.5 trillion spending goal slipping away...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/571780-democrats-see-35t-spending-goal-is-slipping-away</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a growing realization among Democrats that their plans for a $3.5 trillion spending package to reshape the nation’s social safety net and to tackle climate change will have to be slimmed down because of anxious centrists worried about the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phony Diagnoses Hide High Rates of Drugging at Nursing Homes...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/09/11/phony-diagnoses-hide-high-rates-of-drugging-at-nursing-homes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The handwritten doctor’s order was just eight words long, but it solved a problem for Dundee Manor, a nursing home</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh China outbreak...</title>
      <link>https://www.scmp.com/news/china/science/article/3148449/fresh-covid-19-outbreak-china-prompts-focus-vaccines-teens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.scmp.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta variant imported by an adult patient who came back from Singapore on August 4 believed to be the source of outbreak in Fujian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socialist Paris mayor enters race for French presidency...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-france-election-hidalgo-idUSKBN2G804N</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris Mayor Anne Hidalgo said on Sunday she would run for president in 2022 on a Socialist ticket, though polls indicate she has little chance of mounting a serious challenge unless she can unite the fragmented left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holyfield, 58, dropped in 1st round TKO in farcical comeback fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/sport/boxing/breaking-evander-holyfield-dropped-stopped-24964585</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Holyfield returned to the ring at the age of 58, 10 years after his last professional fight, as he took on UFC legend Belfort over eight rounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY hospital stops baby deliveries after staffers quit over jab mandate...</title>
      <link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/trending/ny-hospital-pause-baby-deliveries-after-staffers-quit-over-vaccine-mandate/NNMBMQ6VTFFT5DDAMXV46DQ5TQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kiro7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An upstate New York hospital said it will pause the delivery of babies in two weeks because of a spate of resignations by maternity unit workers who are objecting to COVID-19 vaccination mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope meets Orban in worldview clash...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210912-pope-francis-meets-viktor-orban-in-worldview-clash</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis meets Viktor Orban in worldview clash</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's doors slamming shut for Americans...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/what-americans-need-to-know-about-eu-restrictions/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a summer of wide-open possibilities for Americans seeking a European vacation, the rules are changing fast. Here's what US travelers need to know about which destinations are still open to them on the continent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans fighter wins MMA debut after rear-naked choke...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/11/transgender-fighter-alana-mclaughlin-wins-mma-debut/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alana McLaughlin won her debut Friday night via submission at the Combate Global prelims in Miami, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rulings in antitrust cases show tough to define monopoly in age of Big Tech...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/rulings-in-facebook-apple-antitrust-cases-show-how-tough-it-is-to-define-a-monopoly-in-the-age-of-big-tech/ar-AAOjwUK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Obama-appointed judges on opposite ends of the country have refused to rein in Big Tech.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami fans save falling cat with American flag...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/09/11/fans-at-miami-app-state-game-save-falling-cat-with-american-flag/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;College football fans came to the rescue when a stray cat was spotted angling by its claws from the upper bowl of Hard Rock Stadium — making a soft landing thanks to an American flag.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Roe v. Wade in jeopardy, abortion advocates change strategy...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/with-roe-v-wade-in-jeopardy-abortion-rights-advocates-plan-a-change-in-strategy-090003962.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For half a century, the pro-abortion-rights movement in America has been confident that abortion would remain legal nationwide due to the Supreme Court’s 1973 ruling in Roe v. Wade. But now that confidence is shaken.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI'S SECRET 9/11 FILE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9982081/FBI-release-secret-9-11-files-Anonymous-Saudi-embassy-staffer-helped-two-hijackers-LA.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The document was published Saturday evening, a week after President Biden signed an executive order directing the agency to make the secret files available to the public for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more lockdowns, UK health minister suggests...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210912090529-5m6aq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-LOCKDOWN (URGENT):No more COVID-19 lockdowns, UK health minister suggests</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leather lovers' mass at Berlin church...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210912-leather-lovers-mass-at-a-berlin-church</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leather lovers' mass at a Berlin church</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
