<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'I just wonder what's next'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation-now/2018/11/09/ventura-hill-woolsey-fire-california-thousand-oaks-shooting/1949030002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As people struggled to make sense of the brutal spraying of bullets in a Thousand Oaks bar, 95,000 of them were pushed from their homes by fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lady Gaga shares mental health struggle, thoughts of suicide: 'My inner voice shut down'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/people/2018/11/09/lady-gaga-mental-health-patron-awards-sag/1940329002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"A Star Is Born" leading lady Lady Gaga accepted a SAG-AFTRA Patron Award and used her time at the podium to advocate for mental health support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPERMOM HAS 21ST CHILD!</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/7705758/radford-britains-biggest-family-21st-baby-last-one/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SUPERMUM Sue Radford is celebrating the birth of her 21st baby. Sue, 43, welcomed Bonnie Raye into her king-sized clan after a 12-minute labour. She said: “I thought I’d need more than gas and air …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida deja vu as state election hit by chaos, fraud accusations...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/florida-headed-recounts-republican-challenger-sues-062348994.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida has made a troubling return to the election spotlight 18 years after the drama that launched George W Bush's presidency, as the state braces for race recounts amid tit-for-tat accusations of fraud. Two major contests in the southeastern state, for governor and US Senate, hung in the balance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taunts reporters, claims Acosta video wasn't altered...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e38b5c9615a94567ade42da1400e3883</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Before hopping on a plane to Paris on Friday, President Trump insulted some more reporters, threatened that others may have their White House credentials pulled like CNN's Jim Acosta and disputed reports that his press secretary spread a doctored video of Acosta's encounter with a White House intern. During a brief media availability outside the White House, the president gave more fodder to fans who enjoy watching him scrap with journalists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infernos Choke California, Piling On the Grief...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20181109201733-it7lv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRES/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-Five dead in California wildfire as second blaze forces Malibu evacuation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER bans drivers from broadcasting recordings of riders, months after livestreamer was exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/metro/uber-bans-drivers-from-broadcasting-recordings-of-riders-months-after/article_febb3b4f-cedd-59ca-813a-8a34ba617275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The company changed its guidelines for drivers in response to a Post-Dispatch report about a St. Louis driver's secret videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residents accuse Los Angeles of abetting illegal mega-mansion construction...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/residents-accuse-los-angeles-of-abetting-illegal-mega-mansion-construction/article_9a631eb0-4f1d-545e-9544-f833eb3565f9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — Residents living downhill from a massive, unfinished Los Angeles mansion that spurred criminal charges have already lodged a lawsuit against the real estate developer behind the project,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prepares for bitter legal fight over votes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/416020-florida-prepares-for-legal-fight-over-votes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats and Republicans are bracing for a bitter legal fight over vote tallies in Florida that have thrown the state’s hotly contested Senate race into chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORDERS IMMEDIATE INSPECTIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.local10.com/news/elections/emergency-hearing-to-be-held-after-rick-scott-files-lawsuit-against-broward-elections-supervisor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.local10.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A judge ordered Broward County Supervisor of Elections Dr. Brenda Snipes to allow immediate inspection of voter records during an emergency hearing Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARS FLEE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6373429/Caitlyn-Jenners-Malibu-house-burns-California-wildfires-rage-control.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Caitlyn Jenner's home in the Malibu hills has been destroyed by wildfires raging in Southern California, after she and girlfriend Sophia Hutchins evacuated the mansion that she bought in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS ON TRACK TO WIN MOST HOUSE SEATS SINCE WATERGATE; +40...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/democrats-2018-midterm-elections-house-congress-20ad294d-c608-4f70-af89-97d683757ed0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They haven't won this many seats since Watergate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Rules Broward Violated Constitution...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/judge-rules-in-gov-scotts-favor-in-broward-elections-records-request/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Broward judge has ruled in favor of Gov. Rick Scott and says Broward Supervisor of Elections Brenda Snipes must "allow immediate" viewing and copying of records that have been requested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SETTLEMENT REACHED; NOV 14 DEADLINE...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/state/settlement-reached-in-tight-arizona-senate-vote-count</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arizona Republicans and Democrats agreed Friday to give rural voters an extra chance to fix problems with their ballots in the count of the state's tight Senate race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders AMAZON to give 'ECHO' recordings in homicide case...</title>
      <link>https://www.wmur.com/article/nh-judge-orders-amazon-to-give-echo-recordings-in-double-homicide-case/24893714</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wmur.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Amazon Echo device could play a role in a double homicide case in Farmington.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typical wildfire season may now be year-round...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/there-s-no-more-typical-wildfire-season-california-it-may-n934521</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"You're getting longer periods of the year when you get these fires. We're literally burning the candle at both ends," said a UCLA climatologist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALIBU in danger...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/2018/11/09/several-homes-burned-thousands-more-threatened-as-woolsey-fire-threatens-to-jump-101-freeway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All residents are being told to evacuate immediately as an out-of-control fire headed toward populated areas of Malibu early Friday afternoon, the city said. The Woolsey Fire had already destroyed an unknown number of structures, and thousands of homes remain threatened or under a mandatory evacuation order.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AT LEAST 5 DEAD AS CARS CONSUMED DURING ESCAPE...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/fires/article221407060.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five people are confirmed dead in Paradise, California, Friday by the Butte County Sheriff’s Office. Flames from the 70,000-acre Camp Fire consumed their cars as they tried to flee, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Eyes Private Mission to Hunt for Aliens...</title>
      <link>https://www.space.com/42384-breakthrough-initiatives-alien-life-search-mission.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.space.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Breakthrough Initiatives, which already scans the heavens for possible signals from faraway alien civilizations, is considering looking for E.T. closer to home — in our own solar system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Multimillion-Dollar Bounty Program Just for Drug Lords...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2018-11-09/america-s-multimillion-dollar-dea-bounties-just-for-drug-lords </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life on Saturn moon?</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/report-nasa-and-yuri-milner-working-together-on-life-h-1830309201</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It looks like NASA will offer billionaire entrepreneur and physicist Yuri Milner help on the first private deep-space mission: a journey designed to detect life, if it exists, on Saturn’s moon Enceladus, according to documents acquired by New Scientist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Lopez battery charge over 'MAGA' confrontation in HOOTERS...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2018/nov/9/george-lopez-slapped-with-battery-charge-over-maga/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Comedian George Lopez is headed to court on battery charges over an October “MAGA” confrontation that turned physical and was caught on camera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Women nearly as 'distressed' as men over compulsive sexual urges...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/health/women-nearly-as-distressed-as-men-over-compulsive-sexual-urges-and-behaviour-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first study of its kind, 10 per cent of men and seven per cent of women, met criteria for ‘compulsive sexual behaviour disorder’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Begins Paris Visit By Bashing Macron...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-11-09/trump-attacks-macron-for-military-proposal-as-he-lands-in-paris</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House tells Wall St. to end China 'shuttle diplomacy'... </title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/09/white-house-china-trade-957218</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Navarro said Wall Street should butt out of the U.S.-China discussions and instead focus on investing in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines To Charge Reporter Critical of Duterte...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2018/11/09/business/duterte-critic-rappler-charges-in-philippines.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her news site, Rappler, called the charges “intimidation and harassment” and accused President Rodrigo Duterte’s government of trying to silence critical coverage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAITLYN JENNER HOME CHARRED...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/biz/news/kardashian-rainn-wilson-alyssa-milano-malibu-fire-1203024558/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UPDATED 1 p.m.: Celebrities including Kim Kardashian West, Rainn Wilson and Melissa Etheridge are among the thousands forced to flee their homes as fires continue to threaten Malibu, Calabasas, and…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER: TWITTER 'gave Saudi info about journalist who ended up dead'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/09/twitter-gave-saudi-arabia-information-about-journalist-who-ended-up-dead-8123873/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The hashtag #TwitterKilledTurkiAlJasser has been used online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rising between Mueller, Manafort...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/tensions-rising-mueller-manafort-level-cooperation-sources/story?id=59086047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talks between Special Counsel Robert Mueller and former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort have grown increasingly tense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrote about mental state...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5133931a9d734dfcb38d44feec1ec9b6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THOUSAND OAKS, Calif. (AP) — The gunman who killed 12 people at a country music bar in Southern California went on social media during the attack and posted about his mental state and whether people would believe he was sane, a law enforcement official said Friday. Also, one of the possibilities investigators are looking into is whether gunman Ian David Long believed his former girlfriend would be at the bar, the official said. Authorities have not determined a motive for Wednesday's night rampage at the Borderline Bar &amp;amp; Grill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swastika sent to phones of students at Chicago school...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/oprf-high-school-swastika-airdrop-500151501.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Someone air-dropped a photo of a swastika to Oak Park River Forest High School students' cell phones at an assembly Friday morning, a spokeswoman for the school said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Uncalled Races...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/elections/here-are-all-uncalled-house-senate-governor-races-n934541</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three days after Election Day, almost a dozen House races, two Senate races and at least one governor's race remain unsettled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40 More SEARSKMART Stores to Close...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcchicago.com/news/local/chicago-kmart-sears-illinois-closing-list-500149341.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcchicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sears Holdings released a new list of 40 more stores slated to shut down in February, and two Illinois locations are on it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WESTWORLD' SET BURNS DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/film/news/westworld-paramount-ranch-western-town-woolsey-fire-1203024785/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The historic Western town area at Paramount Ranch in Agoura Hills, Calif., where productions including “Westworld” have shot, has burned down in the Woolsey fire, according to the Santa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>91-Year-Old Body Slammed in WALMART Lot Fights Off Attacker...</title>
      <link>http://www.nbc-2.com/story/39454746/91yearold-robbed-in-walmart-parking-lot-fights-off-attacker</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbc-2.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mary Kennedy is battered, bruised but not broken after being attacked and robbed in a Walmart parking lot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems Plan Most Aggressive Gun-Control Legislation in Decades...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/democrats-plan-to-pursue-most-aggressive-gun-control-legislation-in-decades-1541791440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats say they will pass the most aggressive gun-control legislation in decades when they become the House majority in January, plans they renewed this week in the aftermath of a mass killing in a California bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA, ICE hiding surveillance cameras in streetlights...</title>
      <link>https://qz.com/1458475/the-dea-and-ice-are-hiding-surveillance-cameras-in-streetlights/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;qz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I can tell you this—things are always being watched."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan leaves Mexico City for border...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/migrants-decide-depart-mexico-city-without-buses-054119018.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — About 500 Central American migrants headed out of Mexico City on Friday to embark on the longest and most dangerous leg of their journey to the U.S. border, while thousands more were waiting one more day at a massive improvised shelter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thai businessman buys FORTUNE...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/fortune-magazine-sold-thai-businessman-6f26d8f1-b3ea-48dd-99bc-71c1d01d8386.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortune's CEO tells Axios that the deal came together in just a few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China scolds USA over presence in South China Sea...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d53570a43f97408b99b72c76322f9c08</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on U.S.-China talks involving top diplomats and defense chiefs (all times local): 1:50 p.m. China is telling the U.S. to stop sending American ships and military aircraft close to islands that Beijing claims in the South China Sea. Top Chinese diplomat Yang Jiechi (YAHNG jee-uh-CHERR) is making his government's position clear after the latest round of U.S.-China security talks in Washington. The Trump administration has criticized China's militarization of the South China Sea, which is a vital waterway for world trade.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military to help evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a8a3574ac33b4280851dc6740268eb50</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARADISE, Calif. (AP) — The Latest on California's wildfires (all times local): 10:20 a.m. A California National Guard official says 100 military police are headed to Northern California to help evacuate people from a wildfire. Maj. Gen. David Baldwin says other military personnel are studying satellite imagery to assess the scope of the damage and map the fire. The ferocious fire near the Northern California town of Paradise has grown to nearly 110 square miles (285 square kilometers). Paradise is 180 miles (289 kilometers) northeast of San Francisco. Smoke from the fire has made the air unhealthy in the San Francisco Bay Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYTIMES Suspends Luxury Tours To Iran...</title>
      <link>https://www.algemeiner.com/2018/11/09/new-york-times-under-pressure-suspends-luxury-tours-to-iran/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.algemeiner.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area Air Quality Reaches Beijing Levels! </title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/camp-fire-drapes-bay-area-smokey-air-beijing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It was a strange scene on an Autumn afternoon in Wine Country. People walking up and down Yountville's main street wearing surgical masks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Wild Rabbits Trapped Against Wall...</title>
      <link>http://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/watch-bunnies-trapped-by-woolsey-fire-in-thousand-oaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With their habitat ablaze, wildlife have been also forced out of their homes by the Woolsey Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSJ:  Trump Played Central Role in Hush Payoffs to Stormy, McDougal...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/donald-trump-played-central-role-in-hush-payoffs-to-stormy-daniels-and-karen-mcdougal-1541786601</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors have gathered evidence of the president’s participation in deals to buy the silence of a former adult-film actress and an ex-Playboy model. The deals have led Trump’s former lawyer to plead guilty to violating campaign-finance laws.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 dead, 2 hurt in Melbourne 'terror' attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/one-dead-two-hurt-in-melbourne-terror-attack/ar-BBPvKsZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch doctor faces first euthanasia prosecution...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/dutch-launch-first-euthanasia-prosecution-145309235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dutch authorities are prosecuting a doctor for euthanising an elderly woman with dementia in the first case of its kind since the practice was legalised in 2002, officials said Friday. The Netherlands and neighbouring Belgium became the first countries in the world to legalise so-called mercy killing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Trump telling people he wants to replace Commerce Secretary...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/09/trump-could-replace-commerce-secretary-wilbur-ross-by-end-of-the-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Linda McMahon is favored by President Donald Trump to replace Ross in the role, said sources said. He is also considering Ray Washburne, president and CEO of Overseas Private Investment Corporation, according to one of the sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ruth Bader Ginsburg released from hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/supreme-court-justice-ginsburg-working-fall-101653457.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ginsburg, one of four liberals on the Supreme Court and at 85 its oldest justice, was hospitalized on Thursday after falling in her office at the court on Wednesday evening. Republican President Donald Trump, whose second conservative nominee to the country's highest court, Brett Kavanaugh, took</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greece arrests 5,633 at airports with fake ID...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/latest-macedonia-extends-state-emergency-borders-143842662.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SARAJEVO, Bosnia-Herzegovina (AP) — The Latest on the flow of migrants to Europe (all times local):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60 MPH WINDS</title>
      <link>https://www.dailynews.com/2018/11/09/woolsey-fire-jumps-101-freeway-in-agoura-hills-see-maps-of-the-evacuation-areas-in-la-city-and-county/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A brush fire driven by 50 to 60 mph wind gusts that broke out in Ventura County west of Chatsworth and is zero percent contained jumped the 101 Freeway near Chesebro Road in Agoura Hills Friday mor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECOUNT 2018...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6372595/Trump-blasts-Florida-Democratic-officials-finding-votes-nowhere.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump slammed Brenda Snipes on Friday, suggesting that 'dishonesty'  could play a role in changing the result of the state's Senate election, which Republican Rick Scott won narrowly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Threatens to Revoke More Press Passes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/415900-trump-calls-april-ryan-a-loser-threatens-to-revoke-more-press</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday suggested he could pull press credentials from other reporters who don't show him "respect."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrities evacuate...</title>
      <link>https://people.com/human-interest/celebrities-evacuate-their-homes-as-wildfires-spread-in-southern-california/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;people.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two wildfires currently burning through Southern California have forced thousands of people in the area to flee their homes for safety, including many high-profile celebrities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man punches bear in nose...</title>
      <link>https://myfox8.com/2018/11/09/nc-man-punches-bear-in-nose-during-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;myfox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HAYWOOD COUNTY, N.C. — A Haywood County man says he battled a bear outside his home and he has the scrapes and bruises to prove it, WLOS reported. Sonny Pumphrey was in his driveway Tuesday afternoon when he says a mother bear and her two cubs showed up. He says the cubs ran off but the mother bear reared up and attacked him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire breaks out in Griffith Park behind LA Zoo... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-griffith-park-fire-20181109-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New fire breaks down in Griffith Park behind L.A. Zoo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient who died during robot surgery had 99% chance of living...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/patient-who-died-during-robot-13560373</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stephen Pettitt, 69, died following a "catalogue of errors" and lead surgeon Sukumaran Nair had not been trained enough to use the robot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALIBU Evacuated...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/fast-moving-wildfires-paradise-south-california-1159833</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials have ordered the evacuation of the California beachside community of Malibu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LADY GAGA OPENS UP ABOUT 'MENTAL HEALTH CRISIS'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2018/scene/news/lady-gaga-mental-health-struggles-1203023093/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lady Gaga has no problem living — and revealing — her truth. While accepting a patron award at the SAG-AFTRA Foundation’s third annual Patron of the Artists Awards on Thursday night in …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corsi in Mueller Crosshairs...</title>
      <link> https://dailycaller.com/2018/11/09/mueller-grand-jury-jerome-corsi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOUSTON CHRONICLE Retracts 8 Stories After Fraud Investigation...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/houston-chronicle-retracts-8-stories-after-fraud-investigation-we-apologize-to-our-readers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This investigation points to an egregious breach of that trust that is an offense to readers and journalists alike," says Executive Editor Nancy Barnes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Social media increases depression, loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2018/11/181108164316.htm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencedaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi Readies Amnesty Push...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2018/11/09/pelosi-now-we-can-talk-about-comprehensive-amnesty-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) said on Thursday that “now” is the time to talk about comprehensive amnesty legislation because Democrats have regained control of the House. | Politics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans Freak as New Ballots Threaten Florida Senate Win...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/republicans-freak-out-as-new-ballots-threaten-florida-senate-win</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New ballots in Broward County have conspiracy theorists—including the state’s top elected officials—calling for an investigation of Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/florida/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Florida election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/election-results/2018/arizona/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get real-time 2018 Arizona election results &amp; live maps by county. POLITICO's coverage of the 2018 midterm races for Senate, House, Governors &amp; Key Ballot Measures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRES RAGE SOUTHERN CAL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbclosangeles.com/news/local/Woosley-Fire-Voluntary-Evacuations-Underway-500096741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbclosangeles.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Firefighters worked through the night to protect homes in the path of a fast-moving wildfire that tore through hillside brush in Ventura and Los Angeles counties, riding strong wind gusts through neighborhoods...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>114,637,000 Americans in Households Getting Govt Assistance...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/commentary/terence-p-jeffrey/welfare-generation-kids-households-getting-government-assistance-drop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau has released new data that strengthens the case for calling the current generation of American children “The Welfare Generation.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some called him Cujo, others knew him as The Dog. But in this Utah town, all knew him as killer...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/some-called-him-cujo-others-knew-him-as-the-dog/article_d84ade8c-0481-57a5-a3e7-633eee2f3c7b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WEST VALLEY CITY, Utah — Some took to calling him Cujo. Others dubbed him Zorro. At least one named him Jack. For most around these parts, however, he was simply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller's New Boss Has Broad Powers to Throttle Trump Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/mueller-s-new-boss-has-broad-powers-to-throttle-trump-probe#gs.6xUmzD8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mueller's New Boss Has Broad Powers to Throttle Trump Probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT HITS BACK</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/trump-fires-back-after-michelle-obama-says-she-wont-forgive-his-birtherism-i-wont-forgive-barack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN ACOSTA WAITS FOR TRUMP IN PARIS...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/Acosta/status/1060909506559987712</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Greetings from Paris where we are on the ground for Trump’s trip to France. #1A”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APOCALYPSE CALIFORNIA...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/woolsey-fire-75k-homes-evacuated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of homes have been damaged or destroyed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temps far below normal across 30 states...</title>
      <link>https://www.iceagenow.info/temps-far-below-normal-across-30-states/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.iceagenow.info&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Central states running 10 to 20 degrees below normal as far south as Texas. See map http://www.intellicast.com/National/Temperature/Departure.aspx Thanks to Jake Spicer for this link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posted on INSTAGRAM during killings...</title>
      <link>http://www.tmz.com/2018/11/09/thousand-oaks-bar-shooter-ian-long-post-instagram-killing-revenge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shooter who killed 12 in Borderline Bar &amp; Grill posted on social media as he killed patrons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants evolving to lose tusks?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2018/11/wildlife-watch-news-tuskless-elephants-behavior-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Mozambique, researchers are racing to understand the genetics of elephants born without tusks—and the consequences of the trait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside disturbing world of illegal wildlife trade...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/2018/11/poaching-tigers-bears-bile-farming-book-talk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;To expose criminals who traffic animals, Rachel Nuwer went undercover—even posing as a prostitute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As RVs regain popularity, younger fans seek out ways to rent joyride...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-rv-rentals-20181109-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RV sales are setting fresh records driven by retiring baby boomers and Instragram-postng Millennials and Gen Xers, who increasingly are looking to rent. That benefits companies like Escape Campervans of Inglewood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President signs order to restrict asylum access...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us-immigration-officials-move-restrict-asylum-border-055150535--politics.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump on Friday invoked extraordinary national security powers to deny asylum to migrants who enter the country illegally, tightening the border as caravans of Central Americans slowly approach the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM: Number of million-dollar homes surges...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/personalfinance/real-estate/2018/11/09/million-dollar-homes-number-increased-400-000-year/1936628002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US homes over $1 million increased by 400,000 the past year, the largest jump since 2012. Long Island, Seattle, California among pricey spots</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of buildings destroyed...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8cc9527b1d904dedbe9b39d10df99c58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PARADISE, Calif. (AP) — A fast-moving wildfire that ravaged a Northern California town Thursday sent residents racing to escape on roads that turned into tunnels of fire as thick smoke darkened the daytime sky. Several thousand buildings were destroyed by flames, a California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection official said. "We were surrounded by fire, we were driving through fire on each side of the road," said police officer Mark Bass, who lives in the hard-hit town of Paradise, where harrowing tales of escape and heroic rescues emerged after the entire community of 27,000 was ordered to evacuate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VICTIMS...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2018/11/08/the-victims-of-the-thousand-oaks-massacre/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are a list of the victims that have been identified so far in the mass shooting at the Borderline Bar &amp; Grill Wednesday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chilling final FACEBOOK post...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6370709/Chilling-final-Facebook-post-ex-Marine-PTSD-shot-California-bar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ian David Long, 28, stormed into the Borderline Bar and Grill in Thousand Oaks, California on Wednesday night, firing into the crowd before turning the gun on himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman in Minnesota Receives Broward Ballot in Mail...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2018/11/woman-in-minnesota-receives-broward-county-ballot-in-the-mail/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: WORLD'S FIRST AI NEWS ANCHOR GOES LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/09/the-worlds-first-ai-news-anchor-has-gone-live-in-china.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"English AI Anchor" debuted at the World Internet Conference in the country's eastern Zhejiang Province. Modeled on the agency's Zhang Zhao presenter, the new anchor learns from live videos and is able to work 24 hours a day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relics of 'lost continents' hidden under Antarctica revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-6371355/Relics-lost-continents-hidden-Antarctica-revealed-satellite-images.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New satellite images from the European Space Agency reveal a timeline of the ancient landmasses buried a mile (1.6 km) beneath Antarctica.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'NEVER FORGIVE'</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/415868-michelle-obama-id-never-forgive-trump-for-birther-conspiracy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former first lady Michelle Obama reportedly rips President Trump's spreading of the "birther" conspiracy theory against her husband in her upcoming book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil below $60...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/11/09/oil-markets-crude-supply-global-economy-in-focus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both Brent and U.S. West Texas Intermediate crude oil futures have declined by about 20 percent from four-year highs seen in early October.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant caravan to leave Mexico City for US border...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/latino/415875-migrant-caravan-to-leave-mexico-city-for-us-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A group of thousands of Central American migrants on Friday will leave Mexico City and continue their journey toward the U.S. as the Trump administration takes steps to limit their ability to request asylum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor James Woods Aids In Search For Missing...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/09/actor-james-woods-aids-search-camp-fire-missing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Families across California and the country got help from actor James Woods as they searched desperately for relatives missing in the devastating Camp Fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARADISE LOST...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2018/11/08/thousands-flee-paradise-camp-wildfire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-moving wildfire has driven thousands of residents of the Butte County town of Paradise from their homes, forcing some to abandon their cars during their flight to safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia unleashes 'unstoppable' hypersonic super-nuke...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2018/11/09/russia-prepares-to-unleash-terrifying-unstoppable-hypersonic-super-nuke-capable-of-destroying-a-city-8121885/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vladimir Putin says his new weapon can dodge missile defences and wreak destruction on a terrifying scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President moves to restrict asylum access at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2018/11/08/trump-moves-to-restrict-asylum-access-at-the-border-978233</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move is almost certain to trigger legal challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 1,000 structures destroyed...</title>
      <link>http://www.latimes.com/local/la-me-camp-fire-20181108-story.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of people in a rural part of Northern California were ordered to evacuate their homes Thursday as a fast-moving wildfire exploded from 10 acres to more than 10,000 acres in a matter of hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Semitic acts up 69% in France so far this year...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181109-france-anti-semitic-edouard-philippe-mireille-knoll-nazi-kristallnacht</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anti-Semitic acts in France rose by 69 percent in the first nine months of 2018, Prime Minister Édouard Philippe said Friday, on the 80th anniversary of the infamous "Kristallnacht" attacks on Jews in Nazi Germany.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows terrifying drive to escape...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/video-shows-the-terrifying-drive-to-escape-massive-fire-1830331814</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The so-called Camp Fire has already consumed over 20,000 acres in Northern California, forcing about 50,000 people to evacuate. But the fire has moved so quickly that some people have barely escaped—like Brynn Parrott Chatfield from the town of Paradise, who posted this video to social media showing her family’s terrifying drive through the flames yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letter shows a fearful Einstein long before Nazis' rise...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/letter-shows-fearful-einstein-long-nazis-rise-59076888</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than a decade before the Nazis seized power in Germany, Albert Einstein was on the run and already fearful for his country's future, according to a newly revealed handwritten letter. His longtime friend and fellow Jew, German Foreign Minister Walther Rathenau, had just been...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Bader Ginsburg 'up and working' after breaking ribs, nephew says...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-film-ruth-bader-ginsburg/justice-ginsburg-up-and-working-after-breaking-ribs-nephew-says-idUSKCN1NE0XO</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg is "up and working" and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internet Splitting in Two Amid U.S. Dispute With China...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/technology/the-internet-is-splitting-in-two-amid-u-s-dispute-with-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Western bigwigs were a no-show at Chinaâ€™s biggest web conference.Â</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7-ELEVEN at War With Own Franchisees Over ICE Raids...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/businessweek/7-eleven-is-at-war-with-its-own-franchisees-over-ice-raids#gs.O3WkjlU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The War Inside 7-Eleven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain Struggles With Rise in Knife Attacks...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/britain-struggles-with-rise-in-knife-attacks-1541759400</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Knife crimes are rising in Britain and knives have become the weapon of choice for London gang members, leaving the U.K. struggling with a crime trend that the city’s mayor says will take a generation to solve.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trio of wildfires gain strength in California...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/11/09/california-wildfires-wall-fire-ravages-golden-state/1939919002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the Camp Fire raged in the northern part of the state, about 90 miles north of Sacramento in Butte County, the Hill and Woolsey fires triggered widespread evacuations to cap a hellacious day in Ventura County that began with news of a mass shooting that left 13 people dead at a neighborhood bar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires/northern-california-wildfire-leaves-town-in-ruins-thousands-flee-idUSKCN1NE0WQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-moving wildfire advanced to the outskirts of the Northern California city...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California wildfire leaves town in ruins, thousands flee...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-california-wildfires/northern-california-wildfire-leaves-town-in-ruins-thousands-flee-idUSKCN1NE0WQ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fast-moving wildfire advanced to the outskirts of the Northern California city...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
