<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>NFL STAR KUECHLY SHOCKS WITH RETIREMENT; HISTORY OF CONCUSSIONS...</title>
      <link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/sports/nfl/carolina-panthers/article239299573.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.charlotteobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10491032/results</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>**DRUDGE POLL** WHO WON?</title>
      <link>https://poll.fm/10491032</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;poll.fm&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST:  Jim Rogers warns economic system not sound...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/insanity-jim-rogers-warns-horrible-time-ahead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Feet Entering China May Presage New Trading Era!</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/us-chicken-feet-entering-china-may-presage-new-trading-era/ar-BBYXNFy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL DEBATE BEFORE VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/politics/live-news/january-democratic-debate-live/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CNN/Des Moines Register Democratic presidential debate features six qualifying candidates in January. Watch livestream and follow live coverage here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tempers rise... </title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tempers-rise-democrats-hold-final-debate-iowa-vote-010312565.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Democrats braced for fireworks at Tuesday's presidential debate, with liberal Bernie Sanders signalling he could clash with rivals in the final showdown before voters in Iowa kick off the nomination process. While former vice president Joe Biden, the 77-year-old establishment candidate, is leading</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Census Bureau kicks off 2020 ad campaign amid fears about privacy and hacking...</title>
      <link>http://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Census-Bureau-kicks-off-2020-ad-campaign-amid-14975521.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Census Bureau on Tuesday unveiled an ad campaign to persuade every household in America to fill out the once-a-decade survey, which begins next week in remote parts of Alaska.  The decennial count of everyone living in the United States is used to determine a decade's worth of congressional apportionment, redistricting, and hundreds of billions of dollars in federal funding. But a rising distrust of government, combined with the battle over whether to add a citizenship question and fears that the newly digital survey could be hacked, may make counting every person more difficult than ever.  Many of the 1,000-plus print, television, radio and Internet ads target immigrant and minority communities, which are traditionally among the hardest to count, and emphasize that data collected by the Census Bureau is confidential and cannot be shared, even with other government agencies.  Bureau Director Steven Dillingham, who will fly this week to Toksook Bay, Alaska, population about 660, to count the first person in the census, introduced the campaign in the District of Columbia, where placards displayed print and television ads, along with a coloring book about the census that will go to more than 117,000 schools across the nation.  In one Spanish-language television spot featuring young Hispanic men, one says he is worried it could be dangerous to fill out the form. Not at all, his friend assures him, saying he filled out the census 10 years ago and it was fine.  The campaign targets audiences in 13 languages, along with African Americans, Native Americans and children, who also are typically undercounted.  But some immigrant advocates said they were distressed that there was no mention in the ads of the citizenship question the Supreme Court blocked from the survey last...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917': Film's Single, Continuous Shot Challenges a Short-Attention Span...</title>
      <link>https://www.moviemaker.com/archives/news/watching-1917-in-2020-when-our-lives-are-more-edited-than-ever/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.moviemaker.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Watching 1917 in 2020 was a jarring experience for me: My broken attention span isn't used to watching continuous, unbroken scenes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Loaf sues Dallas hotel, convention after fall from stage...</title>
      <link>https://www.dallasnews.com/news/courts/2020/01/14/meat-loaf-sues-dallas-hotel-convention-after-fall-from-stage-that-hes-still-recovering-from/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dallasnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The singer Meat Loaf is suing a Dallas hotel and a horror convention after a fall from a stage last year that he said left him seriously injured and unable...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEDERAL SPENDING SETS RECORD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/article/washington/terence-p-jeffrey/1163090000000-federal-spending-sets-record-through-december</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The federal government spent a record $1,163,090,000,000 in the first three months of fiscal 2020 (October through December), according to the Monthly Treasury Statement released Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://go.cnn.com/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;go.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNNgo is a revolutionary news-watching experience that offers the live CNN broadcast with unprecedented features. You can catch-up on the stories you‘ve missed, go deeper and learn more about the stories that interest you with related coverage, and enjoy the most popular On Demand Shows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Enhances Privacy and Perhaps Itself at the Same Time...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/google-enhances-privacy-perhaps-itself-211227826.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- If you lived west of the Mississippi at the dawn of the 20th century, there must have been a moment when it became clear that the Wild West of old was no more. Perhaps it was the arrival of the railroad, or the last stagecoach robbery or the introduction of a federal income tax.For</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSU's Big Win Scores Over 25M Viewers, Biggest Cable Audience In Two Years...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/lsu-win-ncaa-national-championship-football-clemson-espn-viewership-up-donald-trump-vince-vaughn-1202830464/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a lot of social media spittle flying over Vince Vaughn shaking hands with Donald Trump at Monday’s 2020 College Football Playoff National Championship in New Orleans, but the real action wa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRACKDOWN WILL LIMIT PRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/impeachment-trial-security-crackdown-will-limit-capitol-press-access</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An unprecedented crackdown on the Capitol press corps will be unleashed for the Senate impeachment trial of President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate War Powers Resolution Has 51 Votes...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/senate-war-powers-resolution-has-51-votes-democrat-kaine-says/ar-BBYXlDE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff sends evidence from Rudy associate...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/schiff-lev-parnas-ukraine-impeachment-5562caa2-dd94-4ecf-a05d-1bdce494c67c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new evidence includes communications between Parnas and Ukrainian officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: 17 Students, 9 Adults Exposed After Aircraft Dumps Fuel On Elementary School Near LAX...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/jet-fuel-aircraft-dump-cudahy-lax-students-school/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than two dozen elementary school kids in Cudahy were being evaluated Tuesday after an aircraft dumped fuel on its final approach to LAX, authorities said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Indiana man sparked Secret Service investigation shouting outside Mar-a-Lago...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article239243583.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daredevil Wallenda to make 1,800-foot wirewalk over active volcano on live TV...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldtribune.com/news/20200114/sarasotarsquos-nik-wallenda-to-wirewalk-over-active-volcano</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daredevil will perform the feat live on television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aircraft near LAX 'dumps jet fuel on elementary school playground'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7887443/Aircraft-final-approach-LAX-dumps-jet-fuel-elementary-school-playground.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paramedics are on the scene in Cudahy, according to local fire crews. Around 30 children at Park Avenue Elementary School reported a reaction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Woman Caught Trying To Build Bomb Inside WALMART...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/01/14/supplies-needed-mass-destruction-florida-woman-build-bomb-walmart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A woman is accused of trying to build and detonate an explosive device inside a Tampa Walmart store.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA drinking more now than just before Prohibition...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1f81ade0748410aaeb6eeab7a772bf7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Americans are drinking more now than when Prohibition was enacted. What’s more, it’s been rising for two decades, and it’s not clear when it will fall again. That’s the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars struggle to breathe at Australian Open...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/player-quits-australian-open-after-coughing-fit-smoke-filled-air-n1115046</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The air quality in Melbourne was “the worst in the world” overnight, according to Victoria state’s chief health officer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Seniors Getting Roommates To Help Save Money...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/senior-citizens-getting-roommates-to-help-save-money/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More senior citizens are moving in together to make ends meet financially. In New York, one senior who picked up a roommate said the financial relief is "like a step into heaven."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tragic kingdom: Dad in custody after family found slain in DISNEY community...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/14/dad-in-custody-after-family-found-slain-inside-disney-world-community/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fairytale Florida community built by Disney World has turned into a horror scene after cops discovered four bodies in the home of a missing former Connecticut family. A man identified by neighbor…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUZ: LET'S HEAR FROM MORE WITNESSES</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2020/01/14/ted-cruz-senate-call-witnesses-whistleblower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ted Cruz said in a new interview that he is &amp;quot;open&amp;quot; to the Senate calling witnesses in an impeachment trial, specifically naming the Trump-Ukraine whistleblower.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite Security Fears, Caucuses Will Use New Smartphone App...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/01/14/795906732/despite-election-security-fears-iowa-caucuses-will-use-new-smartphone-app</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Iowa Democratic Party confirmed to Iowa Public Radio and NPR that it plans to use an Internet-based app to transmit results, but it declined to provide any more specifics or security details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man requests 'trial by combat' with Japanese swords to settle dispute with ex-wife...</title>
      <link>https://www.desmoinesregister.com/story/news/crime-and-courts/2020/01/13/iowa-courts-david-ostrom-requests-trial-combat-swords-settle-dispute/4456079002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.desmoinesregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Ostrom asked an Iowa court to give him 12 weeks notice to "source or forge" a katana and wakizashi for the duel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59 year-old Afghanistan vet re-enlists in US Army...</title>
      <link>https://www.armytimes.com/news/your-army/2020/01/14/59-year-old-afghanistan-veteran-will-report-to-army-basic-training-this-summer/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.armytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood Fights Plans To Install 5G Cell Service Over Health Worries...</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/hinsdale-neighbors-fight-plans-to-install-5g-cell-service-citing-health-worries/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;5G internet means more cellphone towers – which will appear every 12 homes in some neighborhoods. Some Hinsdale neighbors are worried about health risks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUGHER SHOVING EXPECTED...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ec4da97dd1619a43474fab2c819a22a6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Rougher shoving and sharper jabs are expected as a tighter field of Democrats takes the stage for Tuesday night's final debate before Iowa's leadoff presidential...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terrified residents flee homes as crazed gang of 400 monkeys raid village...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/crazed-gang-400-monkeys-raid-21279520</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Monkeys from the Indian village of Narasapuram have been terrorising residents, raiding homes and stealing food, leading to many being forced to flee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFLATION TAME...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/economy/2020/01/14/consumer-price-index-shows-very-low-inflation-persists/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Inflation has been slowing down for the last two months, suggesting that the Fed will not hike rates this year. | Economy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARK BITE NORTH CAROLINA IN JANUARY... </title>
      <link>https://wpde.com/news/local/surfer-bitten-by-shark-nc-coast</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wpde.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RODANTHE, Dare County &amp;mdash; A North Carolina man taking advantage of unseasonably warm weather was bitten by a shark while surfing off the coast Monday afternoon, according to a chief beach ranger. A 26-year-old was taken to the Outer Banks Hospital about 2:30 p. m. with injuries that weren&amp;rsquo;t considered life-threatening, Boone Vandzura, chief ranger with Cape Hatteras National Seashore, said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Brady Moves to Greenwich, Stadium Suite Cleaned Out...</title>
      <link>https://weei.radio.com/blogs/weei/tom-brady-rumors-qb-has-moved-to-greenwich-connecticut</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;weei.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Greg Hill, Tom Brady's Gillette Stadium suite has been cleaned out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'HOMELAND' star accuses Trump of trying to have it both ways on intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/in-the-know/in-the-know/478145-homeland-star-accuses-trump-of-trying-to-have-it-both-ways-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Homeland" star Mandy Patinkin is accusing President Trump of wanting to have it "both ways" with the U.S. intelligence community and selectively picking which conclusions to support.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Video Stages Assassinations...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-video-stages-assassination-of-trump-pompeo-netanyahu/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Iranian propaganda video dramatizes the assassination of President Donald Trump, Secretary Mike Pompeo, and Israeli prime minister Benjamin Netanyahu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Colorado Scaling Back Drone Investigation; 'Unaware Of Any Crime Being Committed'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2020/01/13/state-scaling-back-drone-investigation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Colorado Department of Public Safety said Monday it will be scaling back operations of its investigations into suspicious drone activity in northeastern Colorado.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Questions of racism linger as Harry, Meghan step back... </title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1420bd1ff04ac8f330bdd9cf9d061e52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — When accomplished, glamorous American actress Meghan Markle married Prince Harry in 2018, she was hailed as a breath of fresh air for Britain’s fusty royal family. That honeymoon...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germans 'obsessed' with refugee porn...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10736004/germany-obsessed-refugee-porn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GERMANS have become ‘obsessed’ with refugee porn after the country took in more than one million migrants. Interest in the fetish has rocketed since Angela Merkel opened the countryR…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STD map reveals worst cities for sexually transmitted diseases; Baltimore tops list...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/250900/std-map-us-cities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AN STD map ranks Baltimore as the worst US city for sexually transmitted diseases as they run rampant in the South and California. Testing experts at Innerbody analyzed CDC data to reveal the Top 1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Parrots Naturally Exhibit Kindness, Selfless Behavior; Intelligence Comparable To Apes, Dolphins...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/parrots-naturally-exhibit-kindness-selfless-behavior-in-extraordinary-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new set of research focusing on African gray parrots finds that besides just being smart these fascinating animals are also very kind to one another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON CLIFFHANGER</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Will-John-Bolton-testify-at-Trump-impeachment-14974182.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGON - The House is about to send President Donald Trump's impeachment over to the Senate, setting the stage for a high-profile showdown over just what kind of trial we'll see. And perhaps the biggest looming question is: Will John Bolton testify?  That question is starting to come into focus. The idea that Senate will quickly dismiss the impeachment articles and move on, as Trump has suggested, apparently isn't going to happen - which that means we can now turn to other matters like Bolton.  Sen. Mitt Romney, R-Utah, this week became the first to directly indicate he supports Trump's former national security adviser testifying and would likely vote in favor of it. And despite declining to insist on Bolton's testimony as part of the trial's initial rules, two others appear amenable to voting for witnesses like Bolton during the trial. But that would still leave the vote deadlocked at 50-50, with one more GOP senator needed to put Bolton - and other witnesses Democrats desire, like acting White House chief of staff Mick Mulvaney - on the stand.  In other words: It's on a knife's edge.  Romney has previously indicated he wants to hear from Bolton, who resisted testifying to the House but says he would in a Senate trial. But now Romney has further clarified (with some wiggle room) that he would likely vote in favor of it.  "I presume I'll be voting in favor of hearing from John Bolton, perhaps among others," Romney said. "That could change depending on what happens in the ensuing days and during those arguments."  The two other most likely crossover votes - Sens. Susan Collins, R-Maine, and Lisa Murkowski, R-Alaska, - have been even more coy. But they have been working behind the scenes to make sure there will be votes on witnesses.  Murkowski also says in a new interview...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL DEBATE BEFORE VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/14/politics/democratic-debate-guide/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The final Democratic debate before the Iowa caucuses brings new challenges for the Democratic presidential field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau appears to blame Trump, USA for downing...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/01/14/canadian-pm-justin-trudeau-blames-downing-of-ukraine-jet-on-us-escalation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau took a swipe at President Trump, saying the victims of the Iran-downed Ukrainian airliner would still be alive if tensions had not risen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: Don't count Warren out...</title>
      <link>https://newrepublic.com/article/156204/dont-count-elizabeth-warren</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newrepublic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The press seems to have written her off, but she still has a good shot at winning the Iowa caucuses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOM:  For First Time in 26 Years, All U.S. Metros Enjoyed Income Gains...</title>
      <link>https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/first-time-26-years-u-150735277.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ca.finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Americans in every U.S. metropolitan area experienced economic prosperity in 2018, according to a recent report from the Bureau of Economic Analysis.For the first time in 26 years, no metro area saw per-capita incomes fall that year -- the latest available data -- and it was only the fourth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PELOSI MOVES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8276d7dc28f15fc46d1b6c546dd66382</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — After weeks of delay and strategizing, the U.S. House is planning to vote Wednesday to send the articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump to the Senate to start the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Russian spy satellite 'explodes in space'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10735117/secret-russian-spy-satellite-explode-space/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TOP-SECRET spy satellite operated by Russia is feared to have “disintegrated” in space. The mysterious probe had lurked in Earth’s orbit for more than half a decade and was repo…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TINDER, GRINDR accused of illegally sharing user data...</title>
      <link>https://www.channelnewsasia.com/news/world/tinder-grindr-accused-illegally-sharing-user-data-12262912</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.channelnewsasia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OSLO: Popular dating apps like Tinder and Grindr are sharing the personal data of their users to third parties in breach of EU regulations, a ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O'KEEFE: Sanders Field Organizer Suggests Gulags to Help 'Nazified' Voters...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2020/01/14/project-veritas-bernie-sanders-field-organizer-suggests-gulags-to-help-nazified-trump-voters/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An undercover video shows a Bernie Sanders field organizer saying Soviet gulags were actually a positive phenomenon, suggesting that some similar program could re-educate Trump supporters and billionaires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catholic Church criticises 'NEW POPE' for scene of nuns in nighties dancing beneath crucifix...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/catholic-church-criticises-pope-scene-150034499.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A scene in The New Pope, a mini-series starring Jude Law and John Malkovich, in which sexy young nuns dance in their nighties beneath a giant fluorescent crucifix, has incurred the wrath of the Catholic Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEDNESDAY: VOTE TO TRANSMIT IMPEACHMENT ARTICLES</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/14/house-vote-wednesday-to-transmit-trump-impeachment-articles-to-senate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The House of Representatives is preparing a likely Wednesday vote to transmit articles of impeachment against President Donald Trump to the Senate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARREN: I'll Bypass Congress to Cancel Federal Student Debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/14/elizabeth-warren-says-she-can-forgive-student-loan-debt-without-congress.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The plan, which comes weeks before voting begins in the first primary and caucus states, adds urgency to legislation she introduced over the summer to cancel the bulk of the nation's outstanding student debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to headline Davos summit as Iran drops out...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-headline-davos-summit-iran-drops-143858980.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump will be the star attraction at this year's Davos forum, which will also focus on the fallout of climate change and a more inclusive model of capitalism, organisers said Tuesday. The annual gathering of global movers and shakers in the village of Davos in the Swiss Alps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airline employee took woman's number from her bag tag, then followed her on flight...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Airline-employee-took-woman-s-number-from-her-bag-14972771.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ashley Barno was in a boarding area at San Diego International Airport, awaiting a Chicago-bound flight, when a message from an unfamiliar number flashed across her phone, saying hello and asking how she was doing.  The person then added, "Btw I must tell you that you are gorgeous!"  Barno thanked the sender for the flattery and asked again for his name. How had he gotten her number, she asked, and why was he texting her?  "You guess!!" he told her, adding that he worked for American Airlines, which was operating the flight Barno was waiting to board.  "I just saw you at the airport again!" he wrote, telling her in a later message: "you are looking very gorgeous in grey top today!!"  Barno, clad in a gray shirt, looked around the gate area, glancing over her shoulder. She was scared.  The disturbing encounter, which occurred in April and unfolded over more than 100 text messages that were later shared with The Washington Post, spurred a lawsuit against the airline and its employee over allegations of negligent hiring, sexual harassment and stalking. The interaction has left Barno reeling more than eight months later, nervous when she travels and sometimes fearful she's being watched, her attorney, Joseph Samo, said in an interview.  American Airlines did not answer specific questions about the allegations or the case, but company spokesman Joshua Freed said in a statement that, "The employee involved in the complaint is no longer employed at American Airlines."  "American Airlines takes the privacy and safety of our customers seriously. We investigated the allegations and took appropriate action," Freed said.  The person was not on duty at the time, he said.  The messages continued even after Barno got on the plane.  "This is weird," she wrote to him.  Then she learned he was on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-secret UFO files could 'gravely damage' national security, Navy says...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/science/top-secret-ufo-files-gravely-damage-us-national-security</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Defense has top-secret classified briefings and a classified video about a UFO incident.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWO POPES: Dispute over former pontiff's role in controversial book...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/dispute-over-former-popes-role-controversial-book-112936166.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican was gripped Tuesday by a dispute over whether elderly ex-pope Benedict XVI was being used by the Catholic Church's ultra-conservative wing to undermine his successor Pope Francis. At least three Vatican correspondents cited a source close to Benedict saying the former pontiff had not</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL DEBATE BEFORE VOTE...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/democrats-clash-final-debate-iowa-votes-020822527.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Democrats braced for Tuesday's final presidential debate before Iowa kicks off the nomination process February 3, and with no candidate yet gaining the upper hand, they were ready to rumble. Former vice president Joe Biden is leading nationally, but no clear frontrunner has emerged in Iowa,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Philippine volcano trembles more, spews lava half-mile high...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b3f5c5efe6cba83e0790745a8d5f2ed7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAGAYTAY, Philippines (AP) — A volcano near the Philippine capital spewed lava into the sky and trembled constantly Tuesday, possibly portending a bigger and more dangerous eruption, as tens of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Arabia executes record number of prisoners...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/International/saudi-arabia-executed-record-number-prisoners-2019-report/story?id=68250502</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Arabia executed record number of prisoners in 2019, a year which saw the kingdom come under scrutiny for its human rights record.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER REMOVES VIDEO OF PRINCE HARRY PITCHING MEGHAN MARKLE TO DISNEY CEO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/twitter-removes-cringey-video-of-prince-harry-pitching-meghan-markle-to-disney-ceo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Showcases worst of cronyism: a brazen display of influence-peddling, among elites of government, big business, and Hollywood...'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vince Vaughn faces backlash after shaking Trump's hand at football game...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/films/news/vince-vaughn-trump-handshake-lsu-clemson-tigers-republican-melania-a9282706.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queen agrees 'period of transition'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7882589/Prince-Harry-Prince-William-Prince-Charles-leave-Sandringham-separate-cars.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The unprecedented statement came after a summit at Sandringham between the Queen and Princes Charles, William and Harry, with Meghan believed to have dialled in from Canada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to live longer? Art museums may be key...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/lifestyles/health/want-live-longer-art-museums-may-the-key-study-suggests/p7MFFirkuR2t9y1jeqMAUP/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Living longer may be a matter of attending more art museums, theaters and galleries, according to a study published in the BMJ journal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speakeasies back in vogue -- in echo of Prohibition era...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-speakeasies-back-vogue-echo-prohibition-era-021241525.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A century after the United States clamped down on alcohol and ushered in the Prohibition era, speakeasies are once again popping up behind hidden doors and luring in revelers seeking fancy cocktails with an illicit 1920s vibe. Just a few blocks from the White House in downtown Washington, a steady stream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike Lee to be first black head of Cannes film festival jury...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/spike-lee-first-black-head-cannes-film-festival-105950497.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;American director Spike Lee was named president of this year's Cannes film festival jury on Tuesday, becoming the first black head of the panel. The maker of "Malcolm X" and "Do the Right Thing" is the first person of black African descent to preside at the world's biggest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed up Venezuelans find solace on beach...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/fed-venezuelans-solace-beach-013646156.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido called for street protests at the weekend in a bid to rekindle popular outrage against President Nicolas Maduro, only a few hundred people turned up. It's a far cry from the tens of thousands he mobilized a year ago after declaring himself interim president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EILISH TO RECORD BOND THEME?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/01/hans-zimmer-confirmed-james-bond-pic-no-time-to-die-billie-eilish-record-theme-1202829945/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oscar-winning composer Hans Zimmer has officially taken over the reins on the next James Bond pic, No Time To Die, replacing Dan Romer. The James Bond twitter account tweeted the following message …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO says new China virus could spread, warns hospitals worldwide...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200114111930-u8ea4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHINA-HEALTH/PNEUMONIA-WHO (UPDATE 1, TV):UPDATE 1-WHO says new China coronavirus could spread, warns hospitals worldwide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran makes arrests over plane disaster as protests rage on...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200114111028-rpkhe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-CRASH/ (WRAPUP 2, PIX, TV):WRAPUP 2-Iran makes arrests over plane disaster as protests rage on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'LIVING ROBOT' DEVELOPED BY SCIENTISTS USING FROG EMBRYOS...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/jan/13/scientists-use-stem-cells-from-frogs-to-build-first-living-robots</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers foresee myriad benefits for humanity, but also acknowledge ethical issues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BURNOUT' LINKED WITH IRREGULAR HEARTBEAT...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2020-01-14/burnout-linked-with-irregular-heartbeat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do the Machines Driving Markets Remember 2000?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2020-01-14/u-s-stocks-rally-starts-to-resemble-2000-tech-euphoria-k5derskz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian gas company at center of impeachment 'hacked by Russian agents'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-51103556</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian energy company Burisma is at the centre of President Donald Trump's impeachment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up to 10 Republican senators consider bucking Trump on war powers...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478093-up-to-10-gop-senators-consider-bucking-trump-on-war-powers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 10 Republican senators are considering bucking President Trump on a resolution that would limit his ability to take military action against Iran.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
