<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bats may have started coronavirus. Could they be key to ending it?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/bats-may-have-started-the-coronavirus-pandemic-could-they-be-the-key-to-ending-it/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists explain the mechanisms underlying bat virus tolerance and how bat immune systems may provide clues to treating viruses like coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8510917/Mississippis-five-largest-hospitals-run-ICU-beds-infections-soar-state.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mississippi's five largest hospitals reached ICU capacity midweek, four other hospitals have 5 percent or less ICU beds available and an additional three have less than 10 percent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER censors anti-Chinese content...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2020/07/10/twitter-flags-video-of-chinese-cultural-revolution-as-sensitive-content/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC said contributor had coronavirus -- he didn't...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/nbc-contributor-reveals-he-never-had-coronavirus-after-network-documented-his-recovery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An NBC medical expert who detailed a terrible struggle with Covid-19 never had the virus, he revealed this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta to reactivate makeshift hospital...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/blog/politics/georgia-reactive-makeshift-hospital-atlanta-convention-center/0mQrnN9qhxmOEfIwVK0CzO/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Georgia is planning to reactivate a makeshift hospital for coronavirus patients built in the Georgia...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix nearly out of morgue space...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc15.com/news/coronavirus/phoenix-mayor-abrazo-nearly-out-of-morgue-space-may-be-requesting-refrigerated-trucks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc15.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phoenix Mayor Kate Gallego says Abrazo is requesting refrigerated trucks after hitting capacity in their morgue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberts steers the Supremes to surprising term...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/chief-justice-roberts-full-control-182344617.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chief Justice Roberts sends a message that the Supreme Court is independent and not an ally of one party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON Homeless Shelter Faces Crisis, Criticism...</title>
      <link>https://ktiv.com/2020/07/10/amazons-homeless-shelter-faces-seattle-crisis-criticism/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktiv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — A homeless shelter built on Amazon’s perfectly manicured urban Seattle campus is a major civic contribution that pushes the company to face the crisis and criticism in the hometown it has rapidly transformed. Believed to be the first homeless shelter built inside a corporate office building, Amazon’s partnership housing a local nonprofit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUSTICE DEPT PUSHED JAIL</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/roger-stone-should-go-to-prison-during-pandemic-us-says-in-reversal/ar-BB16xK3O</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon AI center now focusing on war-fighting operations...</title>
      <link>https://www.c4isrnet.com/artificial-intelligence/2020/07/08/pentagon-ai-center-shifts-focus-to-joint-warfighting-operations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c4isrnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Joint Artificial Intelligence Center is focusing its efforts on building AI for the Department of Defense's Joint All-Domain Command and Control concept.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama in trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.al.com/news/2020/07/public-health-experts-weigh-in-on-herd-immunity-in-alabama-and-are-not-optimistic.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.al.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reaching herd immunity may be difficult under any circumstances but would cost tens of thousands of lives in Alabama without a vaccine, experts say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to hell: 'Sex slave' priest found dead at NJ home...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/10/sex-slave-priest-peter-miqueli-found-dead-at-new-jersey-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disgraced “sex slave” priest Peter Miqueli —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Hollywood Icons Topple Like Confederates?</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/07/peter-bart-hollywood-icons-cancel-culture-walt-disney-john-wayne-gone-with-the-wind-1202982037/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could Walt Disney be next? Really? Let me explain: Most industry people I know were drawn to Hollywood by the prospect of creating things, not cancelling things. Now the dialogue has shifted, wheth…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk to reveal AI brain chips?</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/1118388/elon-musk-neuralink-brain-chip-statement/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ELON Musk has announced he’ll be making a statement about his human brain implants next month. The billionaire has previously said his Neuralink firm will have a device ready “in less t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 Covid Cases Linked to Oakland MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/bayarea/article/Oakland-Mcdonalds-Linked-To-25-Covid-Cases-Is-15398555.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OAKLAND (BCN)  A McDonald's restaurant in Oakland's Temescal District that has been linked to 25 cases of the novel coronavirus may reopen Sunday but must show it is keeping employees and the public safe from the virus, following a court order on Thursday.  A 10-month-old baby who experienced severe symptoms of COVID-19 was among the employees of this McDonald's and an affiliated restaurant in Berkeley and their family members who have contracted the virus, according to a complaint filed in the case last month.  So far, those diagnosed with COVID-19 include a manager for both stores, 11 workers at the Oakland restaurant, six of their family members and seven workers at the Berkeley store, for a total of 25 linked cases, according to the complaint.  Workers allegedly were discouraged from taking sick leave when they experienced virus symptoms and were not told when their co-workers tested positive. An emergency ordinance in Oakland mandates paid sick leave for many workers affected by the COVID-19 pandemic.  Owners of the McDonald's at 4514 Telegraph Ave., which closed in May after its employees went on strike to protest their working conditions, according to the complaint, face contempt charges if the store backslides, said Michael Rubin of Altshuler Berzon, an attorney for the employees and their families. The Berkeley restaurant is at 1998 Shattuck Ave.  The stores are franchises owned by a Michael Smith, who appears to live in Hayward, and members of his family. The owners must file a brief with the court by July 27 indicating how the Oakland restaurant has complied with the requirements of the restraining order.  Attempts to reach Smith on Thursday were unsuccessful. A spokesperson for McDonald's Corp., which is not a defendant in the case, said the company does not comment on hearings or...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VEGAS BARS ORDERED TO CLOSE AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/news/politics-and-government/sisolak-says-restrictions-on-some-bars-will-return-friday-2071154/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Steve Sisolak says that bars in certain counties in Nevada will return to Phase One (in which bars that didn’t serve food were closed) starting at 11:59 p.m. Friday. A list of counties a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen behind bars again after dispute over gag order...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-cohen/former-trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-taken-into-custody-idUSKBN24A2WQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, U.S. President Donald Trump's former personal attorney, was taken to a federal jail on Thursday after refusing to agree to a gag order as a condition of serving his criminal sentence under home confinement, Cohen's lawyer said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pathogen Behind Mass Elephant Deaths?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/elephant-die-off-may-be-due-to-e2-80-98novel-disease-e2-80-99-botswana-says/ar-BB16zytj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Begs her to slash him with knife!</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/3am/celebrity-news/bone-chilling-moment-johnny-depp-22336320 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient on ventilator gives birth...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/brooklyn-center-man-is-fighting-for-his-wifes-life-after-she-gives-birth-on-ventilator-battling-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Juan Duran’s wife, Aurora, has been on a ventilator at North Memorial Hospital since June 19. Since then, her baby was delivered via emergency C-section. Now Juan is fighting to get her a treatment she needs that could be the last resort to save her life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu Admits Reopening Too Fast...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2020/07/10/netanyahu-admits-reopening-economy-too-fast-amid-coronavirus-surge/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu admitted his government was too hasty in reopening Israel's economy and as a result...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UC Berkeley Surge Blamed Frat Parties...</title>
      <link>https://sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com/2020/07/08/uc-berkeley-covid-19-cases-jump-following-fraternity-sorority-parties/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sanfrancisco.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The University of California, Berkeley reported Wednesday a spike in students testing positive for the COVID-19 and is attributing the increase in cases to a series of fraternity and sorority parties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC WORRIED ABOUT MIAMI...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/miami-is-a-new-coronavirus-hotspot-internal-cdc-document-says-162804209.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Miami, Florida's second-largest city, is set to host the Republican National Convention next month. But some have questioned the wisdom of holding a large gathering in a state where the pandemic has been raging out of control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFE IN THE BUBBLE:  NBA players complain about quarantine food...</title>
      <link>https://ftw.usatoday.com/2020/07/nba-bubble-food-disney-world-hotel-embiid-photos-videos</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ftw.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But good food is on the way!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Feds worried jailed Epstein confidante Maxwell might 'kill herself'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/80e1d24b3111582256de4fb788fc4fc2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LITTLE ROCK, Ark. (AP) — Federal officials were so worried Jeffrey Epstein’s longtime confidant Ghislaine Maxwell might take her own life after her arrest that they took away her clothes and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  67%  disapprove of his handling...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/broad-disapproval-trumps-handling-coronavirus-race-relations-poll/story?id=71704889</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is facing broad disapproval for his management of the two major crises gripping the nation according to a new ABC News/Ipsos poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depp accuses Amber of Elon Musk affair in blockbuster rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1116876/johnny-depp-text-rant-elon-musk-amber-heard-affair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHNNY Depp wrote of karma hopefully “taking the gift of breath” from Amber Heard in an astonishing text accusing her of having an affair with Elon Musk, a court heard. In the shocking …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amlo thanks him for not mentioning border wall at summit...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-usa/mexican-president-thanks-trump-for-not-mentioning-border-wall-at-summit-idUSKBN24B1TT?il=0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador on Friday expressed gratitude to Donald Trump for avoiding in public the thorny subject of the U.S. president's promised border wall during a summit in Washington earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/101449.shtml</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACK MAP...</title>
      <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT06/refresh/AL062020_3day_cone_no_line_and_wind+png/145240_3day_cone_no_line_and_wind.png</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nhc.noaa.gov&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND DRAMA...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-says-he-is-looking-at-clemency-for-roger-stone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Friday said he was “looking at” a pardon for longtime GOP operative Roger Stone, who is slated to report to prison for more than three years on Monday, saying he was treated “unfairly.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STILL PEAKING; USA  VIRUS RECORD, 63,247 CASES IN DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/10/us-reports-record-single-day-spike-of-63200-new-coronavirus-cases.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;White House health advisor Dr. Anthony Fauci has urged officials in states where the outbreak is worsening to reconsider reopening plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROPICAL STORM DRENCH NY...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/hurricane/tropical-storm-fay-swirls-northward-threatens-landfall-in-new-jersey/773849</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan reopens Hagia Sophia for Muslim worship, angering Christian leaders...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/erdogan-says-hagia-sophia-reopened-muslim-worship-143446037.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan announced Friday that the Hagia Sophia, one of the architectural wonders of the world, would be reopened for Muslim worship, sparking fury in the Christian community and neighbouring Greece. The UNESCO World Heritage site in historic Istanbul, a magnet for tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATHOLIC CHURCH LOBBIED FOR TAXPAYER FUNDS, GOT $1.4 BILLION</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/dab8261c68c93f24c0bfc1876518b3f6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The U.S. Roman Catholic Church used a special and unprecedented exemption from federal rules to amass at least $1.4 billion in taxpayer-backed coronavirus aid, with many millions...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Slays Anti-Maskers, 'Dirty' Cops on New Track...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/eminem-slays-anti-maskers-dirty-cops-in-new-single-with-kid-cudi-plus-f-drew-brees-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marshall Mathers also sends "prayers to George Floyd and Ahmaud Arbery" in "The Adventures Of Moon Man &amp; Slim Shady"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCarolina besieged...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/south-carolinas-coronavirus-outbreak-is-worse-than-most-countries</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;South Carolina is besieged by the coronavirus, reporting more cases per capita than most countries. “We’ve completely lost control of the situation,” one doctor told the Beast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's president's endorsement worth? Texas, Alabama runoffs will tell...</title>
      <link>https://www.rollcall.com/2020/07/09/whats-trump-endorsement-worth-texas-house-and-alabama-senate-runoffs-will-tell/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three Trump-backed candidates lost last month, but Trump support for Texas' Ronny Jackson and opposition to Alabama's Jeff Sessions is personal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago summer already sizzling...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/weather/ct-chicago-summer-weather-1995-heat-wave-20200709-hrvkdrwpknfh5g22tnrxfwv3p4-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heading into July 12 of this year — the 25th anniversary of the 1995 heat wave — temperatures in Chicago are already warmer than average.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steve Cohen Takes On A-Rod in Push to Buy METS...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/markets/steve-cohen-takes-on-a-rod-in-push-to-buy-new-york-mets</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Steve Cohen Takes On A-Rod in Push to Buy New York Mets</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fauci says he hasn't briefed president in 2 months...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/924772/fauci-says-hasnt-briefed-trump-covid19-2-months</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has apparently not been briefed by the country's top infectious disease expert for months, even amid a surge in COVID-19 cases. Dr. Anthony Fauci, director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, spoke to the Financial Times in an interview published Friday, in which he revealed that it's been more than a month since he actually saw the president in person at the White House; that last happened on June 2, he said. Additionally, Fauci said that it's been at least two months since he briefed Trump, though he's 'sure' his messages are being relayed to the president. If that's the case, 'Trump is evidently not listening,' the Financial Times writes. After all, Fauci in the interview had to offer a fact-check of Trump's recent false claim that 99 percent of COVID-19 cases are harmless. 'I'm trying to figure out where the president got that number,' Fauci said. 'What I think happened is that someone told him that the general mortality is about 1 percent. And he interpreted, therefore, that 99 percent is not a problem, when that's obviously not the case.' Fauci noted that despite Trump's assertion, since COVID-19 has such a 'broad range of manifestations,' 'even if it doesn't kill you, even if it doesn't put you in the hospital, it can make you seriously ill.' It's not just Trump who's been seeing less of Fauci lately, as he's also been making fewer TV appearances in recent weeks as CNN reports the White House has blocked some interview requests with him. Fauci himself seems to have a theory as to why. 'I have a reputation, as you probably have figured out, of speaking the truth at all times and not sugar-coating things,' Fauci told the Financial Times. 'And that may be one of the reasons why I havenâ€™t been on television very much lately.' Brendan Morrow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Film Exposing Hollywood's Child-Abuse Epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/showbiz-kids-exposes-hollywoods-pedophilia-epidemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Pretty much all of the young men were abused in some way, sexually,” says Evan Rachel Wood in “Showbiz Kids,” a disturbing new HBO documentary premiering July 14.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida county reports 33.5% positivity rate...</title>
      <link>https://www.sun-sentinel.com/coronavirus/fl-ne-florida-coronavirus-cases-deaths-thursday-july-9-20200709-6w6t7xksvjgz7msqzpwtyzfymu-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sun-sentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida on Thursday recorded the most deaths in a 24-hour period: 120. It also has been the state’s deadliest week so far, with more than 300 new deaths reported since Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York diners being attacked by rats while eating on sidewalk...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8510109/Diners-forced-sidewalks-restaurants-attacked-RATS.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Yorkers have been flocking in their droves to enjoy outdoor dining ever since the city entered phase two of its coronavirus reopening plan on June 22.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eminem Unloads on Drew Brees, Police on New Track...</title>
      <link>https://www.complex.com/music/2020/07/eminem-disses-drew-brees-raps-about-covid-19-police-brutality-on-new-kid-cudi-collab-the-adventures-of-moon-man-and-slim-shady</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.complex.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kid Cudi came through with a new track featuring Eminem on Thursday night and the Detroit rapper touched on multiple topics, including police brutality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cryonics, brain preservation and weird science of cheating death...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/features/cryonics-brain-preservation-and-the-weird-science-of-cheating-death-alcor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would you suspend your body in liquid nitrogen for a second chance at life?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>250,000 By Year's End?</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/zeke-emanuel-covid-deaths-250000-americans/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On "The Takeout" this week, Dr. Zeke Emanuel of the University of Pennsylvania slammed the Trump administration's response to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah gov declares state of emergency...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/506714-utah-governor-declares-state-of-emergency-due-to-civil-unrest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Utah Gov. Gary Herbert (R) late Thursday declared a state of emergency in Salt Lake City following tense demonstrations that saw protesters square off against Salt Lake City police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROP STORM FAY TO DUMP ON TRI-STATE...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2020/07/10/tropical-storm-fay-tri-state-area/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some models predict up to 4 inches of rainfall accompanied by 45 mile-an-hour winds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEATHS BEGIN TO CLIMB AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/coronavirus-live-updates-us-covid-19-deaths-begin/story?id=71706388</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus death toll continues to climb and the seven-day average is increasing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Threatened to cut off Elon Musk's penis'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8510087/Johnny-Depp-threatened-cut-Elon-Musks-penis.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actor has accused Ms Heard of having an 'extra-marital affair' with the SpaceX billionaire - which Musk vehemently denies and insists their relationship began only after she filed for divorce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK bug crashes IOS apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/popular-ios-apps-including-spotify-pinterest-crashing-2020-7 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran explosion: Panic erupts as third blast rocks capital...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1307578/iran-explosion-tehran-power-cut-Israel-world-war-three-garmdareh-quds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXPLOSIONS have rocked the Iranian capital of Tehran, according to online reports. This marks the third blast in three weeks for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Pathogen Behind Mass Elephant Deaths?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/elephant-die-off-may-be-due-to-novel-disease-botswana-says</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elephant Die-Off May be Due to â€˜Novel Disease,â€™ Botswana Says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trio of Mars missions in starting blocks...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2020-07-trio-mars-missions-blocks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We have lift-off, we have lift-off!"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Epic failure': Election officials warn of November chaos...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200710091357-1udrv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/BUDGETS (INSIGHT, PIX, GRAPHIC):INSIGHT-'Epic failure': U.S. election officials warn of November chaos due to budget crunch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Homeland Security' Turns to Defending Statues Amid Questions Over Priorities...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/10/homeland-security-turns-to-defending-statues-amid-questions-over-priorities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — When he first took office, President Trump repurposed the Department of Homeland Security to focus on illegal immigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Unexpected Struggle for Trump: Defining an Elusive Biden...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/10/an-unexpected-struggle-for-trump-defining-an-elusive-biden/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump won the White House in no small part by seizing on Hillary Clinton’s missteps and using them to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feces in bed was last straw in marriage...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/63f99fb7ecc1b7c5449414a323406fec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Johnny Depp said in a London court on Friday that ex-wife Amber Heard's claims he abused her turned him from “Cinderella to Quasimodo” in the public eye. He also said the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No longer dream, UFC 'Fight Island' real...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5bcfb72dd8da9cec1f65a27ee84608d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The imagery evoked by Dana White's crazy idea was undeniably intoxicating: An octagon perched amid swaying palm trees on a white sand beach, waves lapping at the canvas while mixed martial arts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious pneumonia 'more deadly' than covid sweeps across Asia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/mysterious-pneumonia-more-deadly-coronavirus-22332846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kazakhstan’s Health Ministry said it had recorded more than 32,000 cases and 451 deaths from pneumonia in June – a fatality rate four times higher than 12 months before</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starting at $500,000: Swiss Mountain Vault for Storing Riches...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/starting-500-000-swiss-mountain-070032802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Long known as a bastion of discrete, secure banking, Switzerland will soon offer the world’s wealthy another choice for storing their prized possessions: rock vaults carved into foothills of the Alps.The idea comes from entrepreneurs in central Switzerland, home of the Bruenig massif,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing chorus pushes for renewed shutdown orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Growing-chorus-pushes-for-renewed-shutdown-orders-15398322.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;They raced to shut down their economies in March, and many opened them just as quickly in May.  Now, governors across the country are facing growing pressure from public health experts and local leaders to reimpose stay-at-home orders as the only way to regain control of coronavirus outbreaks that threaten to overwhelm hospitals and send the death count spiraling.  The push appeared to receive a boost from Anthony Fauci, the nation's top infectious-disease official, who suggested in comments released late Wednesday that struggling states "should seriously look at shutting down."  He took a more measured approach on Thursday, emphasizing that stay-at-home orders should remain a last resort and suggesting a pause in reopening plans instead.  So far, that has been the preferred method for governors seeking to arrest climbing caseloads while not alienating a virus-weary public. Yet, with scant evidence of progress in states across the Sun Belt - and beyond - experts are increasingly concluding that more drastic measures are necessary.  "Stay-at-home is a blunt instrument," said Farshad Fani Marvasti, director of public health at Arizona State University. "But when you're leading the world in new cases and things don't seem to be getting better, you may have to use that blunt instrument."  Studies have found that orders that closed nonessential businesses and forbid nonessential travel or gatherings prevented millions of coronavirus cases nationwide when they were imposed this spring. Researchers have also found such orders could have saved tens of thousands of lives had they been implemented earlier.  But with the economy reeling from a prolonged shutdown, and President Donald Trump agitating for a quick reopening, governors across the country lifted restrictions in May. That...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 1,000 TSA employees have tested positive... </title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/more-than-1000-tsa-employees-have-tested-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TSA officers who worked at 43 different airports within the last two weeks have tested positive. They include airports in states across the South, Southwest and Midwest where cases have been climbing among the population as a whole.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says much of eastern Oklahoma remains Indian land, including much of Tulsa...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2020/07/09/889562040/supreme-court-rules-that-about-half-of-oklahoma-is-indian-land</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Today we are asked whether the land these treaties promised remains an Indian reservation. ... Because Congress has not said otherwise, we hold the government to its word," wrote Justice Gorsuch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sidelines public health advisers in growing rift over response...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/cdc-feels-pressure-from-trump-as-rift-grows-over-coronavirus-response/ar-BB16ycOj?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC cancels all large events until October...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nyc-cancels-all-large-events-through-september-30</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Bill de Blasio has announced that any large events that require a permit from the city have been canceled through September 30 as the city works to prioritize open space for public use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA sending robot to asteroid worth 'more than global economy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/nasa-sending-space-robot-asteroid-22332229</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Space agency NASA is to preparing to launch its groundbreaking "Psyche" spacecraft that will explore a huge asteroid claimed to be worth more than the economy on planet Earth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA NEW VIRUS RECORD:  65,551 cases in day...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/us-posts-new-record-daily-virus-caseload-of-more-than-65-000-johns-hopkins-01594341905</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The US on Thursday posted 65,551 new coronavirus cases, a record for a 24-hour period, according to a tally by Johns Hopkins University.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Senate majority in reach, Dem candidates rake in massive donations...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/senate-majority-reach-democratic-candidates-175417558.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democratic Senate candidates in several key races announce huge fundraising totals that raise the party's hopes of retaking the chamber in November.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus clobbers Marshall Island communities...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/coronavirus-clobbers-marshall-island-communities-120045272.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COVID-19 is disproportionately killing Marshallese immigrants in states such as Arkansas, Washington and Oregon, even as their homeland remains free of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resignations, clashes leave Pentagon with gaping holes in upper ranks...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/8/mark-esper-defense-secretary-battles-pentagon-vaca/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A rash of resignations has left U.S. military leaders scrambling to fill vacancies in key positions throughout the Pentagon and has sparked a standoff with lawmakers who are convinced that President Trump’s personal politics drive hirings, firings and promotions inside the Defense Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De Blasio jeered trolls president with huge 'Black Lives Matter' mural outside Trump Tower...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1110265/nyc-de-blasio-black-lives-matter-trump-tower/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NYC Mayor Bill De Blasio was jeered as he helped to paint the Black Lives Matter mural on Fifth Avenue outside Trump Tower.  De Blasio was heckled at Millionaire’s Row on Thursday, the site o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Confederate names on bases, top general says...</title>
      <link>https://www.newsobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article244124662.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newsobserver.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old Friends Expect USA to Become Even More Erratic...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/old-friends-expect-trump-e2-80-99s-us-to-become-even-more-erratic/ar-BB16vMXP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Swamp Sun Belt Hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/patients-swamp-sun-belt-hospitals-with-covid-19-on-a-rampage/ar-BB16yquJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK to Use Drones to Deliver Covid Tests to Scottish Islands...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/u-k-to-use-drones-to-deliver-covid-19-tests-to-scottish-islands/ar-BB16yfk5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL RECORDS FACE SUBPOENA</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/supreme-court-rules-trump-cannot-block-release-of-financial-records/ar-BB16xq1B?li=BBnb7Kz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mary Trump memoir publisher says 600,000 copies already shipped...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/mary-trump-memoir-publisher-says-600000-copies-already-shipped/ar-BB16xWwm</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP RAGES AT COURT!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/07/09/trump-rages-at-supreme-court-over-tax-records-case-claims-political-prosecution.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The decisions handed a win to the Manhattan district attorney but rejected parallel efforts by Democrats in the House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  HIGH HEAT BLAST SET FOR MOST OF USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.accuweather.com/en/weather-forecasts/scorching-heat-wave-to-intensify-across-southwestern-us/773793</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.accuweather.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky new hotspot...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/506655-kentucky-to-mandate-masks-in-public-amid-an-explosion-of-covid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear (D) says the state will require all residents to wear masks in public for 30 days, beginning Friday, citing an "explosion" of cases of COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUPREMES:  PRESIDENT NOT ABOVE LAW</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200709141051-kuteo</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TRUMP (UPDATE 3, PIX):UPDATE 3-U.S. Supreme Court allows prosecutor but not Congress to get Trump's financial records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GORSUCH, KAVANAUGH JOIN MAJORITY</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/supreme-court-puts-trump-place-171930742.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg Opinion) -- If you’re the president of the United States, you don’t stand above the law. But if you’re a member of Congress seeking the president’s personal records in order to exercise oversight of the executive branch, you better not overreach.That, essentially, is how the Supreme Court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONGRESS DENIED FOR NOW</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a7a9e075f0ac771e95bf0fc6012d181a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Rejecting President Donald Trump’s complaints that he's being harassed, the Supreme Court ruled Thursday in favor of a New York prosecutor’s demands for the billionaire...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lack of insurance threatens supply of Hollywood films, TV shows in 2021...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-health-coronavirus-insurance-hollywoo/lack-of-insurance-threatens-supply-of-hollywood-films-tv-shows-in-2021-idUSKBN24A3A7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Insurers have largely stopped covering independent film and television productions against the risk of COVID-19 illness, a shift that threatens the supply of new entertainment in 2021, Hollywood producers, insurers and industry experts said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admits HEADBUTTING Amber Heard in face...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/uknews/12079323/johnny-depp-admits-headbutting-accidental-amber-heard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JOHNNY Depp today admitted headbutting Amber Heard in the face “accidentally” in a shocking courtroom revelation. The 57-year-old movie star had previously denied hurting his ex-wife bu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA enters the bubble...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/philadelphia/76ers/joel-embiid-shows-airport-hazmat-suit-sixers-depart-disney-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Embiid may have "hated the idea" of the NBA's Disney World bubble, but he clearly isn't letting that affect his sense of humor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chelsea Clinton considering forming venture capital firm...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chelsea-clinton-venture-capital-firm-d2a0f510-32b5-46ce-a373-2e264441fe9b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She has already committed to investing in at least two startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado town threatens year in jail for those who refuse masks...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/09/colorado-town-threatens-jail-time-for-residents-refusing-to-wear-masks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Englewood, Colorado, just south of Denver, is requiring all of its residents to wear face masks amid a spike in coronavirus cases — and violators could face up to a year behind ba…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street Loving Bank-Bailout Critic Tapped PPP Loan...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-loving-bank-bailout-180357533.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The Washington advocacy group Better Markets has spent a decade fighting big banks and railing against the government’s 2008 financial industry bailout. Now it has taken one of its own.The organization was identified by the Small Business Administration earlier this week as being the recipient</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'White Lives Matter' illegally painted on city street; police investigating...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jul/9/white-lives-matter-painted-martinez-california-str/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in a San Francisco Bay Area city are investigating who is responsible for illegally painting “White Lives Matter” on a street the same day prosecutors announced charges against two people accused of defacing a city-sanctioned “Black Lives Matter” sign.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Isolation Could RAISE Vulnerability...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/quarantine-bad-for-you-study-suggests-self-isolation-might-raise-covid-19-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mystifying new study now suggests that prolonged periods of isolation may actually increase one's vulnerability to the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more physical fitness assessments, Navy says...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2020/07/09/no-more-physical-fitness-assessments-for-2020-navy-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Navy is cutting physical fitness tests for the remainder of the year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Female soldier becomes FIRST to join Green Berets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8507523/Female-soldier-join-Green-Berets.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A female solider became the first to join the Green Berets after completing the Armed Special Forces qualification course at Fort Bragg, North Carolina, along with 400 other service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research suggests antibodies may last just months...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/research-coalescing-around-idea-coronavirus-194200542.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists still don't know how long coronavirus antibodies last or what level you need to be protected from future infection.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
