<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasonic bracelet jams microphones around you...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2020/02/15/ultrasonic-microphone-jamming-bracelet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You could thwart eavesdroppers with your wristwear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing Refusing to Hand Over Evidence...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/02/17/senator-cotton-china-refusing-to-hand-over-evidence-about-wuhan-biolab/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New report says lab was likely source of coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeegee men, scourge of '90s, back in NYC...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/02/16/squeegee-men-scourge-of-the-90s-are-back-in-new-york/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just when you thought they were washed up, the notorious squeegee men are streaking back to Big Apple streets. The panhandling window-washers, who became the face of former Mayor Rudy Giuliani’s qu…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOUTH SOAKED: With 'Mother Nature in charge,' dams unleash floodwaters...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/43543e5a265ebaed46472216ddf38e38</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JACKSON, Miss. (AP) — Days and days of heavy rain have created a dilemma for authorities managing dams along swollen rivers in Mississippi and Tennessee. The water has to be released eventually,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armed gang steals toilet rolls in panic-buying Hong Kong...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/armed-gang-steals-toilet-rolls-panic-buying-hit-021750782.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gang of knife-wielding men jumped a delivery driver in Hong Kong and stole hundreds of toilet rolls, police said Monday, in a city wracked by shortages caused by coronavirus panic-buying. Toilet rolls have become hot property in the densely packed business hub, despite government assurances that supplies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands Gather for Japan Naked Festival...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/travel/article/japan-naked-festival-intl-hnk/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands braved chilly weather Saturday to gather at Japan's largest and most famous "naked festival" in Okayama prefecture. The event, called "Hadaka Matsuri" in Japanese, is a wild and raucous festival held annually on the third Saturday of February.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facial expressions do not reflect our innermost feelings, new research suggests...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/facial-expressions-not-reflect-innermost-170000213.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It might be more accurate to say we should never trust a person's face, US scientists say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German far right arrests reveal 'shocking' mosque attack plot...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/german-far-arrests-reveal-shocking-mosque-attack-plot-115756435.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Members of a German extreme right group arrested last week were believed to have been plotting "shocking" large-scale attacks on mosques similar to the ones carried out in New Zealand last year, a government spokesman said Monday. Officials said that investigations into 12 men detained in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn Shot At Santa Monica Public Library During Business Hours Sparks Outrage...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/02/16/adult-film-shot-at-santa-monica-public-library-during-business-hours-sparks-outrage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the clip, the woman in the video walks into the library, apparently during business hours and shoots the video while talking about not getting caught.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famed Sex Therapist Murdered in Hollywood Hills...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2020/02/amie-harwick-famed-therapist-who-appeared-in-the-doc-addicted-to-sexting-murdered-in-hollywood-1202861234/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Amie Harwick, a well-known Hollywood family and sex therapist, was killed Saturday at her home in the Hollywood Hills, according to the Los Angeles Police Department. “On Saturday, Februa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Campaigns warn of chaos ahead of Nevada caucuses...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Campaigns-warn-of-chaos-ahead-of-Nevada-caucuses-15061369.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS - With the Nevada caucuses days away, campaign officials and Democratic activists are increasingly alarmed that they might prove a debacle as damaging as the vote in Iowa, further setting the party back in its urgent effort to coalesce around a nominee to take on President Donald Trump.  Campaigns said they still have not gotten the party to offer even a basic explanation of how key parts of the process will work. Volunteers are reporting problems with the technology that's been deployed at the last minute to make the vote count smoother. And experts are raising serious questions about an app the party has been feverishly assembling to replace the one scrapped after the meltdown in Iowa.  "It feels like the [state party is] making it up as they go along," said one Democratic presidential aide, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss the process. "That's not how we need to be running an election."  Adding to the challenge is the complexity of Nevada's caucuses. Unlike in Iowa, where caucuses are conducted in one evening, Nevadans have the option of voting early. At sites across the state, Democrats can rank their top presidential choices on a paper ballot.  On Saturday, caucus day, Democrats can gather at one of about 2,000 sites to vote for their preferred candidate. If their first choice doesn't get enough backing, voters can throw their support behind someone else, a second round of voting known as "final alignment." Early voting preferences will be treated the same way, as though the voter were attending in person.  The party had planned to use two specially designed apps for reporting results, developed by political technology firm Shadow, the same company that designed the vote-recording app blamed for the chaos in Iowa. A coding error in the Iowa app made it impossible to tally results,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists theorize aliens already here, but we don't recognize them...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/science/article/Scientists-theorize-that-space-aliens-may-already-15061387.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent discovery of two interstellar objects zipping through our solar system has prompted stargazing scientists to consider the likelihood that humans will eventually encounter intelligent extraterrestrials. So they are conjuring up images of what these aliens might look like and instead of reptilian people-eaters, astrobiologists think the invaders might well be microscopic and unrecognizable to humans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEADLIER REINFECTION CAUSING SUDDEN HEART ATTACKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/hubei-doctors-warn-of-even-deadlier-coronavirus-reinfection-causing-sudden-heart-attacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It can fool the test kit – there were cases they found, CT scan shows both lungs fully infected but test came back negative four times,' says scientist</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locust plague reaches China after wreaking havoc across Africa...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/locust-plague-reaches-coronavirus-hit-21513111</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chilling footage has shown thousands of insects swarming the skies at a border in China. They reportedly come from a plague that has devastated east Africa in recent weeks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fears of global contagion as 3,000 passengers return to 40 countries...</title>
      <link>https://fortune.com/2020/02/16/diamond-princess-cruise-ship-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fortune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their worldwide transit is sparking concerns that the disease will spread far beyond its epicenter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ink Rx? Welcome to World of Paramedical Tattoos...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/02/17/ink-rx-welcome-to-the-world-of-paramedical-tattoos/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HECKER, Ill. — The first fingernail tattoo started off as a joke. The client, a man who had lost part</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade one quarantine for another...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8296fc5a288587fe08a70fb72d4c433c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TRAVIS AIR FORCE BASE, Calif. (AP) — Two charter flights carrying cruise ship passengers from Japan landed at military bases in California and Texas overnight, starting the clock on a quarantine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44 Americans on cruise ship in Japan get virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Fears-mount-over-new-coronavirus-case-in-15060451.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - Hundreds of U.S. citizens who have spent nearly two weeks exposed to the coronavirus and quarantined aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship docked near Tokyo were evacuated Sunday evening and taken by bus to a nearby airport, where two chartered planes are scheduled to return them to the United States.  Forty-four Americans who were traveling on the Diamond Princess have been infected, Anthony Fauci, director of the U.S. National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, told The Washington Post on Sunday.  About 400 Americans were on the cruise ship when it docked in Japan, and the Japanese Defense Ministry said 300 of them disembarked Sunday night, the Associated Press reported. Once they land on U.S. soil, the passengers will be quarantined and monitored for an additional 14 days at military bases in Texas and California.  The number of coronavirus diagnoses has continued to rise sharply among the 3,700 passengers and crew members originally on board. Japanese Health Minister Katsunobu Kato said early Sunday that the quarantined ship floating near Tokyo has 355 confirmed cases, or about 30 percent of the 1,219 people who have been tested so far. That represents one of the highest infection rates in the world.  "The degree of transmissibility on that cruise ship is essentially akin to being in a hot spot," Fauci, who is also a member of the White House task force for coronavirus, told CBS' "Face the Nation."  The Diamond Princess has been quarantined since Feb. 5. Those who elected to forgo the chartered flight back to the United States are expected to leave the ship on Feb. 19, but officials have said that they will not be able to find a different flight home until at least March 4.  Their motivations to stay behind varied. Some passengers have sick family members being treated for coronavirus in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topless protesters storm stage as Bernie campaigns in Nevada...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/ny-bernie-sanders-topless-protest-20200216-pz2tvkclpjektiwqinclvvzw6q-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Democratic presidential hopeful had just finished introducing his wife Jane O'Meara Sanders when a woman walked up to the mic and started rambling about subsidies for the dairy industry, video posted to social media showed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL HE DEBATE IN VEGAS?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/483292-speculation-swirls-around-whether-bloomberg-will-make-las-vegas-debate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speculation is increasing over whether Democratic presidential hopeful Michael Bloomberg will participate in next week’s Las Vegas primary debate after the Democratic National Committee (DNC) opened the stage to the former New York City mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adds Top Clinton Advisor to Campaign...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/02/16/mike-bloomberg-adds-capricia-marshall-top-clinton-ally-to-2020-campaign/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marshall served as Bill Clinton’s White House social secretary from 1997 to 2001.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS:  Mao-Style Social Control Blankets China...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/to-tame-coronavirus-mao-style-social-control-blankets-china/articleshow/74161581.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities have been combining enormous manpower with mobile technology to track people in China.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked armed robbers posing as women on dating apps...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5dc.com/news/masked-men-pose-as-women-on-dating-apps-then-rob-victims-maryland-police-warn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5dc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>44 Americans on cruise ship in Japan get virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/asia_pacific/coronavirus-china-updates/2020/02/16/616e9a74-4f6d-11ea-bf44-f5043eb3918a_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Concern is growing after an 83-year-old American woman on board another cruise liner docked in Cambodia also tested positive for the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCAREDY CATS</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10947705/pets-china-makeshift-face-masks-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PETS in China are being forced to wear bizarre makeshift face masks by their owners who fear they could catch the deadly coronavirus. Several worried animal lovers have shared snaps of their pets o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Tests Positive After Hawaii Visit...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-hunt-for-clues-in-hawaii-after-a-tourist-couple-falls-ill-with-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU — Chantelle Pajarillo had settled into a resort on Hawaii’s famous Waikiki Beach, hoping for a peaceful long weekend away from work and school with her family. The peaceful part came to an end as soon as she turned...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SHE WANTS BACK IN'...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/bloomberg-campaign-downplays-report-he-is-considering-hillary-clinton-as-running-mate/ar-BB102hZA</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.instagram.com/p/B8j4oBvlTQw/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.instagram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;9.7m Likes, 56.9k Comments - BILLIE EILISH (@billieeilish) on Instagram: “stream changes”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic during evacuation as woman chants 'USA, USA' with no face mask on...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8009967/Americans-leave-quarantined-Japan-ship-virus-cases-hit-355.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans began leaving a quarantined cruise ship off Japan on Monday to board chartered flights home as the number of new coronavirus cases diagnosed on the vessel jumped to 355.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did it originate in lab? </title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8009669/Did-coronavirus-originate-Chinese-government-laboratory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new bombshell paper from the Beijing-sponsored South China University of Technology says that the Wuhan Center for Disease Control could have spawned the contagion in Hubei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein-Barr, Lyme, Exhaustion, Jesus... </title>
      <link>https://www.billboard.com/articles/columns/pop/8551138/justin-bieber-emotional-changes-interview-with-apple-music-zane-lowe-10-highlights</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.billboard.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Read the top 10 highlights from Justin Bieber's interview with Apple Music's Zane Lowe here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TELSA ordered by German court to stop cutting down trees for Gigafactory...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200216163942-v57f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers have been caught out by the strength of opposition to the Gigafactory, with hundreds of demonstrators protesting over the threat it poses to local wildlife and water supplies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government offers bounties to rat out sick neighbors...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/china-desperate-to-stop-coronavirus-turns-neighbor-against-neighbor/articleshow/73922967.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a bid to stop the virus, leaders in China have focused efforts on finding and isolating people from Hubei.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg calls for government rules on 'harmful' speech...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/policy/defense-national-security/facebooks-mark-zuckerberg-requests-government-rules-on-what-discourse-should-be-allowed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MUNICH — Facebook chief executive Mark Zuckerberg called on Western governments to provide regulatory guidance for how social media companies can identify the boundaries of “what discourse should be allowed” on their platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elton John breaks down in tears and leaves stage after suffering pneumonia...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/showbiz/elton-john-breaks-down-tears-21507944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elton John broke down in tears on stage this weekend after being forced to cancelled an Auckland gig mid show after illness left him unable to sing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Justin Bieber says he just wants to 'protect' Billie Eilish...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/justin-bieber-protect-billie-eilish-131336750.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wiped away tears as he said he doesn't want her going through what he did</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoid crowds, Japan health minister warns...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/avoid-crowds-over-virus-japan-health-minister-warns-134748040.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan's health minister on Sunday urged the public to avoid crowds and "non-essential gatherings", including notoriously packed commuter trains, to prevent the new coronavirus from spreading in the country. Katsunobu Kato warned the nation was "entering a new phase" in the outbreak</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple Tests Positive After Hawaii Visit...</title>
      <link>https://internewscast.com/a-hunt-for-clues-in-hawaii-after-a-tourist-couple-falls-ill-with-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;internewscast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU — Chantelle Pajarillo had settled into a resort on Hawaii’s famous Waikiki Beach, hoping for a peaceful long weekend away from work and school with</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orangutan granted 'personhood' turns 34, makes new friend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f5bf0834c9363563815318ca37b3de8a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WAUCHULA, Fla. (AP) — A orangutan named Sandra, who was granted legal personhood by a judge in Argentina and later found a new home in Florida, celebrated her 34th birthday on Valentine's Day with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No handshakes: Outbreak spooks places of worship...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/aa7622e62633d95966763794ea0d40f9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA, Philippines (AP) — In a popular Catholic church in the Philippines, nearly half of the pews were empty for Sunday Mass. The few hundred worshippers who showed up were asked to refrain from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home quarantine for travelers buys time as virus spreads...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24f0467ead5541ccb228ff70c698eb91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — On his return from China last week, Dr. Ian Lipkin quarantined himself in his basement. His wife now puts his food on the stairs. He’s run out of things to watch on Netflix. At odd...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel's Gantz vows to form government without Netanyahu...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/156653623a0f717e875ec0ce44816edd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israeli opposition leader Benny Gantz is vowing to form a government that will include neither the indicted Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu nor the predominantly Arab parties in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monogamous Bird Models Importance Of Loving Family, Close Friends...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/monogamous-bird-scrub-jays-found-in-florida-models-importance-of-loving-family-close-friends/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers from the Sunshine State recently studied the Florida scrub jay and made some fascinating discoveries about their unique behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was in prison for murder. Computer algorithm helped set him free...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/texas-man-close-exoneration-after-computer-algorithm-leads-new-suspect-n1124946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lydell Grant was supposed to be in prison for murder. But an emerging form of DNA technology, which has also come under scrutiny, is helping to free him in an unprecedented case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,100 ex-officials call for resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/more-than-1100-ex-justice-department-officials-call-for-barrs-resignation/ar-BB103DK5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NY judge orders 20 floors from 52-story skyscraper REMOVED...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8008913/New-York-judge-orders-20-floors-52-story-luxury-Manhattan-skyscraper-REMOVED.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York judge on Thursday sided with community activist Olive Freud (left) and ordered permits revoked for the 200 Amsterdam skyscraper on Manhattan's Upper West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should cars be banned in downtown LA?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-02-16/los-angeles-ban-cars-broadway-downtown-streetcar-pedestrian-zone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If Councilman Jose Huizar's idea is approved, Broadway would be the first major street in Los Angeles to go car free.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Athletes killing themselves and schools fear their players could be next...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/in-depth/sports/columnists/jeff-seidel/2020/02/16/student-athlete-suicide-michigan-football-zachary-winston/4654919002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everybody knows it's a problem. Can it be fixed?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bansky's Valentine's Day mural vandalized...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9395357a334dc928bf39bd50df2cb74e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — The family who owns a house in southwest England where an artwork from Banksy appeared in time for Valentine's Day has covered the mural after it was defaced. Temporary fencing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wall claim beyond 'redemption'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/850cf00b403e230809f9d07e2a0a9c7d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — On the eve of the New Hampshire primary, President Donald Trump told a rally that people who are in the United States illegally are paying for his Mexico border wall. It was the...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
