<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Unrest grips Israel, West Bank ahead of large scale demonstrations...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/unrest-grips-israel-and-west-bank-ahead-of-large-scale-demonstrations/ar-BB1gKZPy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rockets launched from Syria...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/jordanian-protestors-passed-police-barrier-on-way-to-israel-border-668187</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eleven Palestinians were killed as over 5,000 people gathered to protest in the West Bank. Over 150 people were injured in the same protests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jesus statue toppled, American flag burned in NYC church attack...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/14/jesus-statue-toppled-american-flag-burned-in-brooklyn-church-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Msgr. David Cassato noticed the crime at the Brooklyn church early on Friday. The NYPD Hate Crime Task Force is now investigating further into the case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLY LAND HELL</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210515102102-k4xoi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-Israel-Gaza conflict rages on, diplomacy yet to gain traction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo Accusers Subpoenaed as State Inquiry Enters Critical Phase...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/05/15/cuomo-accusers-are-subpoenaed-as-state-inquiry-enters-a-critical-phase/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ALBANY, N.Y. — Four women who have accused Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo of sexual harassment have received subpoenas to testify</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airstrike in Gaza destroys building with AP bureau...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/israel-west-bank-gaza-middle-east-israel-palestinian-conflict-7974cc0c03897b8b21e5fc2f8c7d8a79</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;GAZA CITY, Gaza Strip (AP) — An Israeli airstrike destroyed a high-rise building in Gaza City that housed offices of The Associated Press and other media outlets on Saturday, the latest step by the military to silence reporting from the territory amid its battle with the militant group Hamas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA warns extremists may strike as virus restrictions ease...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-government-and-politics-7788f527ec6c429be2cdf4392f473157</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A national terrorism alert issued Friday warns that violent extremists may take advantage of the easing of pandemic restrictions to conduct attacks. The alert does not cite any specific threats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIACOMCBS says ex-CEO Moonves won't get $120M severance...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-arts-and-entertainment-537b712842cd122ca6a739eb8f06a27e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — ViacomCBS said Friday that former CBS CEO Les Moonves will not get his $120 million severance package from his firing in 2018, ending a long-running dispute over the money. Moonves was ousted in 2018 after a company investigation into allegations of sexual misconduct spanning three decades found Moonves violated company policy and did not cooperate with the investigation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medina Spirit passes drug tests, cleared to run Preakness...</title>
      <link>https://abc7.com/sports/medina-spirit-passes-drug-tests-cleared-to-run-in-preakness/10634702/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Medina Spirit has passed three rounds of prerace drug testing and been cleared to run in the Preakness on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Humane Society's law enforcement investigating Cox's 1,000-lb bear...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/politics/article/John-Cox-bear-investigation-California-recall-code-16177548.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Cox may have violated a San Diego city code related to unusual animals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted leader says McCarthy 'absolutely' should testify about Jan. 6...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/liz-cheney-regrets-voting-trump-2020/story?id=77695446</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Liz Cheney said she regrets voting for Donald Trump in the 2020 election, speaking in a "This Week" interview with ABC Chief Washington Correspondent Jonathan Karl.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dialed Back On Retail Therapy; Spent More Eating Their Feelings...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/05/14/996806349/americans-are-spending-less-on-things-but-more-on-eating-out-or-getting-a-drink</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retail sales were flat in April from a month earlier as Americans spent less on things such as clothes or sporting goods but increased their spending at bars and restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Violence spreads to West Bank...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/at-least-six-palestinians-reported-killed-as-violence-spreads-to-west-bank/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Palestinians report 500 injured in clashes, including by live fire; IDF says 3,000 participate in violent riots that involve stone-throwing, Molotov cocktails</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURVIVOR star 'among honeytraps hired by ex-British spy'...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2885839/survivor-honeytraps-british-expose-enemies-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FORMER ‘Survivor’ contestant was hired for a honeytrap operation to discredit enemies of Donald Trump, it was reported. Anna Khait was reportedly recruited to go on fake dates in an effort to exp…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ex-Gaetz Confidant Pleads Guilty and Agrees to Cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/just-in-matt-gaetzs-ex-confidant-joel-greenberg-pleads-guilty-admits-to-sex-trafficking-of-a-minor/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rep. Matt Gaetz’s (R-FL) former confidant Joel Greenberg has admitted to several crimes in court papers on Friday, including sex trafficking of a minor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish health system targeted in 'serious' ransomware attack...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-coronavirus-pandemic-technology-health-f9478d95ff0f085fa382819e981f4b56</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Ireland's health service shut down its IT systems on Friday after being targeted in a ransomware attack by what it called “international criminals.” Appointments and elective surgeries were canceled at several hospitals and Deputy Prime Minister Leo Varadkar said the disruption could last for days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agent charged in cyberstalking plot against ex-lover...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-government-and-politics-bb057af1814fc24cd8dbc40928b4f25f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A deputy U.S. marshal was charged in a cyberstalking scheme that authorities said he perpetrated with his ex-wife to have a former lover thrown in jail, the Justice Department said Friday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Ex-Gaetz Confidant Pleads Guilty and Agrees to Cooperate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2021/05/14/us/politics/joel-greenberg-matt-gaetz.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joel Greenberg, a former tax collector in Florida, admitted to sex trafficking a minor and agreed to help in prosecutions of others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can new Podcast Academy break awards show curse?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2021-05-14/podcast-academy-awards-ambies-ceremony</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the biggest players in podcasting have created the Podcast Academy and an awards show for podcasts, The Ambies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private firefighters fuel tensions while saving CA vineyards and mansions...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/us/private-firefighters-fuel-tensions-while-saving-california-vineyards-mansions-2021-05-14/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last October, firefighter Ryan Bellanca and his crew battled to keep the raging Glass Fire from devastating an upmarket Napa Valley vineyard.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lowrider back: Glorious return of cruising to streets of LA...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/tripideas/the-lowrider-is-back-the-glorious-return-of-cruising-to-the-streets-of-la/ar-BB1gJRwj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have you noticed? Every weekend, caravans of lowriders and custom cars are cruising and hopping in a resurgent ritual. Van Nuys Boulevard is one of the city's oldest sites of this resilient SoCal obsession.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamikaze drones and 'skunk water'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/14958454/hamas-rockets-kamikaze-drones-skunk-water-israeli/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL and Hamas have been building up a lethal stockpile of weapons that are being unleashed in the escalating conflict.  The warring neighbours’ deadly arsenals threaten to make it the…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halston: Almost forgotten icon now getting NETFLIX series...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/media/2021/may/14/halston-almost-forgotten-icon-netflix-biopic-fashion</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Designer who dictated American glamour in 1960s and 70s is set to hit radar of younger generation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newly Discovered Letter Reveals Einstein's Views On Birds and Bees...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/einstein-birds-bees-physics/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recent discoveries pertaining to migratory birds actually appear to corroborate what Einstein wrote all those years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:   Activists and Ex-Spy Said to Have Plotted to Discredit Trump 'Enemies' in Government...</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2021/05/13/breaking-news/activists-and-ex-spy-said-to-have-plotted-to-discredit-trump-enemies-in-government/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON &gt;&gt; A network of conservative activists, aided by a British former spy, mounted a campaign during the Trump administration to discredit perceived enemies of President Donald Trump inside the government, according to documents and people involved in the operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar Storms Threaten America...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/ideas/2021/05/racing-sun-protect-america/174029/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lessons from the solar storm of May 1921.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cat survives 5-story jump from burning building...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/cat-fleeing-fire-survives-5-story-jump-walks-off</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chicago cat may now have eight lives after jumping out of a fifth-floor window Thursday afternoon to escape an apartment fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEALED: HUSTLER Larry Flynt's Absolutely Wild FBI File...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7evg4/larry-flynt-fbi-file-hustler</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 322-page file contains a litany of events from John DeLorean’s cocaine bust to an alleged effort by Flynt to blow himself up in front of the Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRIVER HOARDS, CAR CATCHES FIRE DURING POLICE CHASE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thestate.com/news/nation-world/national/article251409553.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thestate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The driver told deputies “that she was transporting several containers of fuel that she was hoarding in the trunk.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12-year-old closes in on world record for youngest chess grandmaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2021/may/14/chess-american-12-year-old-closes-in-on-world-record-for-youngest-grandmaster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Abhimanyu Mishra poised to break Sergey Karjakin’s mark of 12 years seven months mark despite going six months without playing in a tournament due to Covid-19</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our politics is no uglier or more dysfunctional than in past...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-our-politics-is-no-uglier-or-more-dysfunctional-than-in-the-past/ar-BB1gJdIH</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Remembering 20th century politics fondly is a distortion of the history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETSMART Workers Criminally Charged After Poodle Dies During Grooming...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/05/13/pittsburgh-petsmart-dog-grooming-death-kobe-aj-ross/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PetSmart says it launched an internal investigation and found “unintended failure to adhere to pet safety processes.” Four workers were fired and criminally charged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLY LAND HELL</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210514115812-k3u1w</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-PALESTINIANS/ (UPDATE 5, TV, PIX):UPDATE 5-Israel pounds Gaza to curb Palestinian militants but rockets still fly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Sentiment Declines; Inflation Fears Mount...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/markets/consumer-sentiment-in-us-declines-as-inflation-fears-mount/ar-BB1gJH4B</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. consumer sentiment slumped in early May as Americans grew increasingly concerned about rising prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picasso sells for $103 million!</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210514-picasso-painting-sells-for-103-mn-in-new-york-auction-house</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Picasso painting sells for $103 mn in New York: auction house</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising rapper, ill-fated INSTAGRAM post and killing in Hollywood Hills...</title>
      <link>https://www.bakersfield.com/ap/national/a-rising-rapper-an-ill-fated-instagram-post-and-a-killing-in-the-hollywood-hills/article_1b7617c3-a9bc-5980-924d-45a8b0c0017b.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bakersfield.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES – At 2 a.m., a black BMW rolled past a house the rapper Pop Smoke was renting in the Hollywood Hills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greene Shouted 'Get Rid of Your Diaper' Through AOC's Office Mailbox...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/marjorie-taylor-greene-shouted-get-rid-of-your-diaper-through-aoc-office-mailbox</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a 2019 livestream resurfaced by CNN’s KFile, Greene can be seen making a fool of herself outside Ocasio-Cortez’s office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGET Pulls Sports Cards From Shelves After Brawls Nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/14/following-parking-lot-brawl-in-wisconsin-target-pulling-trading-cards-from-store-shelves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Target will no longer sell Pokémon and sports trading cards in its physical locations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addiction Experts Set Clinical Guidelines For 'Shopaholism'...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/addiction-guidelines-shopaholic-compulsive-buying-shopping-disorder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The experts conclude a key feature of being a shopaholic is buying items without ever using them for their intended purpose.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans elect Stefanik to replace Cheney in leadership post...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/14/house-gop-elects-elise-stefanik-as-conference-chair-after-ousting-liz-cheney.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vote for Stefanik came days after House Republicans ousted Rep. Liz Cheney from the role over her opposition to former President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>90% DRY IN DC!</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/local/2021/05/panic-buying-continues-as-colonial-restarts-pipeline-operations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colonial has restarted its pipeline operations as gas stations across the D.C. area remain low on fuel, and in many cases are out of gas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-era peace deals fade from view...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/As-Arab-world-rallies-around-Palestinians-and-16176741.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISTANBUL - The videos from East Jerusalem showing Israeli police violently arresting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDF deception leads to massive assault on Hamas...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/idf-deception-leads-to-massive-aerial-assault-on-hamass-metro-668182</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At midnight, the IDF Spokesperson’s English department tweeted that “IDF air and ground troops are currently attacking in the Gaza Strip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I want to break cycle of pain for my children'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-57110267</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Duke of Sussex compares his life to a mixture of the film the Truman Show and being in a zoo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUST: Retail sales flat as stimulus spending wanes...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/retail-sales-health-coronavirus-pandemic-business-f1e6c9e3133fe44e50198b8b5479344e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Retail sales in the U.S. were flat in April, after soaring in March, when many Americans received $1,400 stimulus checks that boosted spending. The report Friday from the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHORTAGE FOR WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-technology-hacking-business-472c7e4f30649aec2dbf38200521b906</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gas shortages at the pumps are spreading from the South to the Mid-Atlantic states, where Virginia and the District of Columbia have become some of the hardest-hit areas following a cyberattack that forced a shutdown of the nation’s largest gasoline pipeline.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
