<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>PFIZER Begins Human Trials of New Pill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/pfizer-begins-human-trials-of-new-pill-to-treat-coronavirus/ar-BB1eSHnp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfizer Inc. said it has begun human safety testing of a new pill to treat the coronavirus that could be used at the first sign of illness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana Gov Given Warning After Trapping, Killing Of Yellowstone Wolf...</title>
      <link>https://www.boisestatepublicradio.org/post/montana-governor-given-written-warning-after-trapping-killing-yellowstone-wolf#stream/0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.boisestatepublicradio.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Montana's newly elected Republican governor violated state hunting regulations when he trapped and shot a collared wolf near Yellowstone National Park in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polish writer facing prison for calling president 'moron'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-media-poland-social-media-059e5db66925f01119c746625b9071e8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WARSAW, Poland (AP) — A popular Polish writer is facing a potential sentence of up to three years in prison for calling the nation's president a “moron” on social media. Jakub Zulczyk had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANON pushing alarming myths targeting China, Jewish people...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/qanon-now-pushes-alarming-conspiracy-120001897.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Online conspiracy theorists have pivoted their focus to a "new world order" - a cabal of global elites they say include vaccine proponents, Biden and Gov. Newsom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard Soldiers transporting vaccines held at gunpoint ...</title>
      <link>https://www.wafb.com/2021/03/22/national-guard-soldiers-transporting-vaccines-held-gunpoint-west-texas-suspect-arrested/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wafb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An Arizona man has been arrested after he cut off and held at gunpoint a caravan of National Guardsmen transporting COVID-19 vaccines to Matador, Texas around 7 a.m. this morning, according to Idalou Police.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authors fear the worst if BERTELSMANN takes over SIMON &amp; SCHUSTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/books/2021/mar/22/authors-fear-the-worst-if-bertelsmann-takes-over-simon-schuster</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analysis: if Bertelsmann, owner of Penguin Random House, buys US publisher, writers expect smaller deals and less choice for readers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MENTAL ILLNESS'</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/boulder-colorado-cops-identify-king-soopers-supermarket-massacre-suspect-as-ahmad-alissa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police also identified the 10 people who lost their lives when the 21-year-old gunman allegedly opened fire on Monday afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Eating Processed Meat Significantly Raises Risk Of Dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/eating-bacon-processed-meat-increases-dementia-risk/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the other hand, study authors reveal eating unprocessed red meat may actually lower the chances of developing the disease.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sometimes-fuzzy $400,000 threshold...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/The-sometimes-fuzzy-400-000-threshold-in-Biden-s-16046525.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Even supermarkets could close!</title>
      <link>https://www.spiegel.de/politik/deutschland/corona-angela-merkel-plant-radikalen-lockdown-inklusive-supermaerkte-a-b8744b25-8499-437a-93ab-786e8a63eef0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.spiegel.de&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nach SPIEGEL-Informationen hat sich Kanzlerin Merkel mit den Länderchefs Söder und Müller sowie Vizekanzler Scholz auf neue, schärfere Corona-Maßnahmen verständigt. Ab 1. April könnten selbst Supermärkte schließen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finland Warns Far-Right Terror Threat Growing as Plans Detected...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/finland-warns-far-right-terror-threat-growing-as-plans-detected/ar-BB1eRO3n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extreme right-wing terrorism is becoming a growing threat in Finland, the Finnish Security and Intelligence Service said, citing attack preparations it has detected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There's commune of venomous cottonmouths on NC coast, and they have FACEBOOK page...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/there-s-a-commune-of-venomous-cottonmouths-on-the-north-carolina-coast-and-they-have-a-facebook-page/ar-BB1eRRTQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. — If North Carolina has such a thing as celebrity wildlife, it would include a group of 100-plus venomous cottonmouths living in a secret spot near the coast. This bunch of pit vipers are the stars of their own Facebook page — Cottonmouth Acres. The page has nearly 1,500 followers and a bold approach to the things shared online. Nothing is held back. Posts in recent months have ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden prepares massive infrastructure bill with universal pre-K, free community college, climate measures...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/biden-team-preparing-up-to-3-trillion-in-new-spending-for-the-economy/ar-BB1eQspQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Biden’s economic advisers are pulling together a sweeping $3 trillion package to boost the economy, reduce carbon emissions and narrow economic inequality, beginning with a giant infrastructure plan that may be financed in part through tax increases on corporations and the rich. After months of internal debate, Mr. Biden’s advisers are expected to present the spending proposal to the president and congressional leaders...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two visitors allegedly drugged, raped woman. She was found dead in hotel room...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/two-spring-breakers-allegedly-drugged-raped-woman-in-miami-beach-she-was-found-dead-in-a-hotel-room/ar-BB1eRBFL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police said two men from Greensboro, N.C., drugged a 24-year-old woman visiting from Pennsylvania, sexually assaulted her and then stole her credit cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUBIO: 'There's Stuff Flying Over Military Installations' We Can't Identify...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/marco-rubio-talks-to-tmz-about-ufos-and-the-possibility-of-alien-life-theres-stuff-flying-over-military-installations-we-cant-identify/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Marco Rubio (R-FL) shared his thoughts on aliens with TMZ -- revealing he is worried about UFOs flying near United States military bases.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Huntsman, of prominent Utah family, files fraud lawsuit against Mormon church...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/James-Huntsman-of-prominent-Utah-family-files-16046024.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James Huntsman, of a prominent Mormon family from Utah, filed a federal lawsuit Tuesday...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE searches for 'hope' and 'prayer' peak...</title>
      <link>https://www.irishnews.com/magazine/technology/2021/03/23/news/google-searches-for-hope-and-prayer-peak-while-party-and-festival-slump-2264673/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.irishnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Trends search data gives an insight into the public's interests and mood over the past 12 months of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists can implant false memories -- and reverse them...</title>
      <link>https://www.inverse.com/mind-body/how-to-reverse-false-memories-study</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inverse.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;False memories can be implanted through suggestion. Now, new research suggests they can be reversed too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC's 'TONIGHT SHOW' Brings Back Live Studio Audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/nbcs-tonight-show-starring-jimmy-fallon-brings-back-live-studio-audience</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move, which also saw the host return to his longtime home of Studio 6B, makes it likely the first nightly, network late-night program to bring back a live audience since the pandemic began.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado man livestreams supermarket slaughter...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/colorado-man-livestreams-boulder-supermarket-shooting/article_cd29be28-87e1-5464-9b1a-4870c5d44ddb.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Boulder, Colorado, man who livestreamed the shooting scene at the King Soopers grocery store on Monday afternoon drew sharp criticism from some, and praise from others, for his actions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza rocket hits near city as PM campaigns there...</title>
      <link>https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/.premium-gaza-rocket-hits-near-southern-israeli-city-as-netanyahu-campaigns-there-1.9647662</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.haaretz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;***</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First news conference big test...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Biden-s-first-news-conference-is-a-test-for-him-16046313.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The first news conference of a new administration is always a high-stakes affair for the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Hike Details...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/sarahhansen/2021/03/23/new-biden-tax-hike-details-are-out-heres-what-we-know-now/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts increasingly warn against manipulating natural systems...</title>
      <link>https://www.downtoearth.org.in/blog/climate-change/why-geoengineering-is-still-a-dangerous-techno-utopian-dream-74828</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.downtoearth.org.in&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experts have increasingly warned against manipulating Earth&amp;rsquo;s natural systems&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting suspect had previously attacked classmate, court records show...</title>
      <link>https://www.denverpost.com/2021/03/23/boulder-shooting-suspect-ahmad-al-aliwi-alissa/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.denverpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 21-year-old Arvada man arrested in Monday’s mass shooting at a Boulder King Sooper’s previously attacked a classmate at Arvada West High School, according to court records and the Colorado Bure…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AHMAD AL ALIWI ALISSA CHARGED IN RAMPAGE</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9393669/Gunman-21-charged-murder-shooting-killing-10-people.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alissa, who has lived most of his life in the US, is now in custody and has been charged with 10 counts of murder. At 2.40pm, he opened fire on King Soopers grocery store in Boulder, killing ten people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pushes immediate gun control...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/us/live-news/boulder-colorado-shooting-3-23-21/h_1f11eb1535df9ebb5a3723e2b7a9d945</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ten people, including a police officer, were killed Monday after a gunman opened fire in a grocery store in Boulder, Colorado. Follow here for the latest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERKEL: We are in new pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.barrons.com/news/we-are-in-a-new-pandemic-due-to-virus-variant-merkel-01616466604 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.barrons.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist behind 'VIEW' tell-all takes aim at 'APPRENTICE'...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2021/tv/news/the-apprentice-book-donald-trump-1234936339/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Variety executive editor and New York Times bestselling author Ramin Setoodeh is writing a reported nonfiction book about “The Apprentice,” the TV show that single handedly changed the course of Am…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET Intel? Scientists Discover Clues to Emissions of Intergalactic Radio Bursts...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/202103231082426789-et-intel-scientists-discover-clues-to-emissions-of-intergalactic-fast-radio-bursts-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers have arrived at the most precise time estimates to date pertaining to the mystery of so-called "fast radio bursts" (FRBs), which are abrupt pulses from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To escape pandemic and lockdowns, Californians resettle in Taiwan...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/escape-pandemic-lockdowns-californians-resettle-100000745.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the start of the pandemic, scores of Angelenos have moved to Taiwan, where they have roots and coronavirus spread has been kept in check.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disgraceful' sex acts in parliament rock Australia's government...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/disgraceful-parliament-sex-acts-rock-020555748.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leaked videos of staff from Australia's conservative government performing sex acts in parliament, including one man masturbating over a female MP's desk, left Scott Morrison's administration facing yet another major scandal Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sao Paulo reports record 1,021 deaths in 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323130726-nvlaa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French hospitals 'violent shock'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323073328-fx3ez</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfing pet goat coolly rides waves at California beach...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210323012710-l1iqs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP:  Satisfaction with direction of country increases...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/341675/satisfaction-continues-improve-march.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Satisfaction with the direction of the U.S. improved again in March, to 32%. This is the second monthly increase Gallup has recorded after the measure fell to its lowest point in nearly a decade in January.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRING BREAK SPIRAL:  Miami Beach Business Owners Opt To Remain Closed Than Deal With 'Crime Zone'...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/03/22/miami-beach-business-owners-residents-have-had-enough-spring-break-crowds/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Everyone who lives or works in Miami Beach is hoping for a much calmer week and weekend ahead. Still, the tumultuous couple of days of spring break trouble has been more than enough for some people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry Lands Gig At Silicon Valley Startup...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/03/prince-harry-silicon-valley-startup-betterup-meghan-markle-1234719966/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Harry won’t have to rely entirely on streaming services for an income – he’s joined a Silicon Valley coaching and mental health services company called BetterUp as its chief impact officer. …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Putin's vaccination to be kept out of public eye...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/vladimir-putin-immunizations-europe-coronavirus-pandemic-russia-0ca9d03310c85097422fc28181efc831</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — Russian President Vladimir Putin will be getting his first vaccination against COVID-19 on Tuesday, but out of sight of the cameras, his spokesman said, prompting questions about...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASTRA Jab Faces Fresh Setback as Feds Question Trial Data...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/us-news-coronavirus-pandemic-a98ef616f4e861a4b7568891d06b7da8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — AstraZeneca may have included “outdated information” in touting the effectiveness of its COVID-19 vaccine in a U.S. study, federal health officials said Tuesday in an unusual...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Illinois city 1st to offer Black residents reparations...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/race-and-ethnicity-chicago-discrimination-recreational-marijuana-slavery-752a6fe83c560117523d7f8abba1bfb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EVANSTON, Ill. (AP) — Using tax money from the sale of recreational marijuana, the Chicago suburb of Evanston has become the first U.S. city to make reparations available to its Black residents...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERROR AT BOULDER  SUPERMARKET</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/colorado-supermarket-shooting-10-dead-3da92f0d3db65afdb373cc6bb534a711</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOULDER, Colo. (AP) — Police on Tuesday identified a 21-year-old man as the suspect who opened fire inside a crowded Colorado supermarket, and court documents showed that he purchased an assault...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration releases video from inside crowded detention facilities...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/biden-administration-releases-video-inside-crowded-migrant-detention/story?id=76618644</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Biden administration has now released its first official images from inside two Texas migrant detention facilities. ABC News got an exclusive first look.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOCKDOWNS RETURN IN EUROPE</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/mar/22/lockdowns-return-extended-third-wave-covid-europe</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plans to ease restrictions have been rolled back in several countries owing to new variants taking hold</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO responds to leaked report into 'inhumane' working hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/mar/22/goldman-sachs-boss-responds-to-leaked-report-into-inhumane-working-hours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;David Solomon says he takes survey in which junior analysts claimed damage to physical and mental health very seriously</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC WARNS OF 'AVOIDABLE' SURGE</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/covid-19-surge-cdc-director-mitigation-variants-2fd889a5-4244-493e-b80f-c15ea59585c1.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though daily cases are dropping in the U.S., variants are increasingly a threat, CDC director Rochelle Walensky said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARD TIME:  Ghislaine Maxwell denied bail for third time...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ghislaine-maxwell-denied-bail-third-225408056.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accused sex trafficker Ghislaine Maxwell was denied bail by a New York judge for the third time on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  SPRING BREAK SPIRAL IN SOUTH BEACH!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/miami-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-restaurants-edd4a28c41892586bddb7616ba42ef78</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH, Fla. (AP) — Florida’s famed South Beach is desperately seeking a new image. With more than 1,000 arrests and nearly 100 gun seizures already during this year's spring break...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLINT AT 90:  Next Film 'MACHO' Lands October Release...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/clint-eastwoods-next-film-cry-macho-lands-october-release/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clint Eastwood's next movie "Cry Macho," which he directs, produces and stars in, has landed a release date from Warner Bros. this fall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone films incredible flight through erupting volcano...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/lifestyle/tech/2560449/drone-footage-iceland-volcano-eruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;STUNNING footage of Iceland’s erupting volcano has been captured by a low flying drone which got terrifyingly close to the boiling lava. Iceland’s Fagradalsfjall volcano began erupting last F…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannes Film Fest May Delay AGAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2021/03/22/cannes-film-festival-may-move-again-to-october-as-covid-rises-in-france-paris-in-lockdown</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Cannes Film Festival usually starts in the second week of May. But this year, with the pandemic, the Festival took preventative measures and made the wise decision to move to July, just between…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 people running for office in Mexico this year have been killed!</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/politicians-keep-getting-killed-in-mexico</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;18 pre-candidates have been killed so far in the run-up to the June mid-term elections in Mexico.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>650+ people in India suddenly developed seizures. Cause is mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/nation-world/story/2021-03-22/something-poisoned-more-than-650-people-in-india-amid-the-pandemic-the-cause-is-a-mystery</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KOMIREPALLE, India - The men gathered on a recent evening as the sun slipped lower in the sky, turning the rice fields golden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health officials alarmed...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210322-us-health-officials-alarmed-by-rise-in-air-travel</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US health officials alarmed by rise in air travel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poop-testing startup, compared to THERANOS, charged in $60M fraud scheme...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/editorspicks/article/ubiome-richman-apte-sec-filing-charges-fraud-16042042.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A married pair of San Francisco entrepreneurs were indicted Thursday on multiple federal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos highlight secrecy...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-donald-trump-border-patrols-immigration-4462413114790eebc81ba82857c475b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Joe Biden's administration has tried for weeks to keep the public from seeing images like those that emerged Monday showing immigrant children in U.S. custody at the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious new system keeps migrants guessing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/honduras-mexico-coronavirus-pandemic-immigration-central-america-1cbd87dabb52664295e50683888eb578</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BROWNSVILLE, Texas (AP) — After hearing rumors that Central American families with younger children were being allowed into the U.S., Irma Paz left Honduras with her husband and two kids on a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critics accuse 'white shark Mafia' of blocking research...</title>
      <link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/shark-fight-pits-state-against-private-research-group/35813385#</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wcvb.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What would seem to be the collegial world of local shark research has in fact become a simmering feud between competing factions, with some saying the public is the loser because the research is not keeping up with great white's growing incursions on our local waters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Straphanger urinates on Asian woman in NYC subway car...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/22/straphanger-urinates-on-asian-woman-in-nyc-subway/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man urinated on an Asian woman aboard a Queens-bound subway train over the weekend, cops said Monday. The disgusting act unfolded around 1:30 p.m. Saturday when the creep pulled out his penis on …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBER driver allegedly tries to kidnap passenger...</title>
      <link>https://abc7chicago.com/uber-driver-allegedly-tries-to-kidnap-passenger/10440958/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7chicago.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kamal Essalak is accused of trying to kidnap an Uber passenger in Boston last week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Iger On Life After DISNEY: 'I'm Not Retiring. I Can't Possibly Do That'...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/bob-iger-on-life-after-disney-im-not-retiring-i-cant-possibly-do-that</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top FOX producer dies from corona...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/03/22/media/fox-business-network-producer-eric-spinato-death/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eric Spinato, the head booker and senior story editor for the Fox Business Network, died over the weekend, the network said Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia: Another tax-free haven?</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/opinion/commentary/ct-opinion-west-virginia-tax-cut-cal-thomas-20210322-ukxmrtq5ojgijmkne3wykxd7vm-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;West Virginia Gov. Jim Justice wants to eliminate the state's income tax. Syndicated columnist Cal Thomas explains why he thinks it's a great idea — and why other states should take note.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO says he'll try to give 100-hour-a-week workers Saturdays off...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/03/22/goldman-ceo-tells-exhausted-workers-hell-try-to-give-them-saturdays-off/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldman Sachs boss David Solomon has heard the complaints from junior bankers about their 100-hour work weeks — and he promises he’ll try to give them Saturdays off. In a voice memo lat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overstimulated? Stocks soar 75% in historic 12-month run...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/financial-markets-stock-markets-coronavirus-pandemic-economy-028b5d5d24b425788df8ee59123e0ad8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — It was one year ago that the terrifying free fall for the stock market suddenly ended, ushering in one of its greatest runs. On March 23, 2020, the S&amp;P 500 fell 2.9%. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ellen Loses 1 Million Viewers After Apologies for Toxic Workplace...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/03/22/ellen-degeneres-loses-1-million-viewers-after-apologies-for-toxic-workplace/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Ellen DeGeneres returned from a summer hiatus to open the 18th season of her daytime talk show in September,</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
