<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sanders rifts may help Trump, Dems fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Sanders-rifts-may-help-Trump-Democrats-fear-14993595.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AMES, Iowa - On Tuesday, when Democrats had hoped to focus Americans squarely on President Donald Trump's impeachment trial, many in the party were instead watching in alarm and dismay as a fresh spat erupted between Hillary Clinton and the candidate she defeated in 2016, Sen. Bernie Sanders.  In comments published early Tuesday, Clinton left open the possibility that she might not support Sanders if he is the party's nominee. The remarks unleashed fresh angst less than two weeks before the Iowa caucuses amid a flurry of other attacks dividing the presidential candidates and their allies.  Sanders, I-Vt., has been engaged in battles with rivals on various fronts over the past week - squabbling with Sen. Elizabeth Warren, D-Mass., over whether he once said a woman could not be president, attacking former vice president Joe Biden with an out-of-context video about Social Security and issuing a rare apology after a top surrogate called Biden corrupt.  The conflicts have reignited Democratic fears that, whoever becomes the nominee, the party will rupture as it did in 2016, when divisions between the Clinton and Sanders camps marred the primaries and the summer convention, and were blamed by many for contributing to her loss to Trump that November.  "Nobody wants to re-litigate 2016. I don't want Democrats focused on the last campaign; I want to focus on the next campaign," said Terry McAuliffe, the former Virginia governor and former head of the Democratic National Committee. "People have to check their attacks. We can't get in the mud pit where Donald Trump wants to be. Let's not be playing on his turf."  "If Bernie is the nominee," he added, "everyone has to rally."  Rebecca Katz, a liberal New York-based consultant, put the blame squarely on Clinton.  "This is bringing up...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DANGER:  TESLA stock rally 'extremely unusual'...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/tesla-stock-rally-extremely-unusual-analyst-says-2020-01-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tesla shares resume their rally on Tuesday with the company pushing back against “unintended acceleration” safety allegations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX changes its view on 'views,' which will boost its numbers by 35%...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/netflix-changes-its-view-on-views-which-will-boost-its-numbers-by-35-2020-01-21</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What does it mean to “watch” a show on a streaming service? For Netflix Inc., it now means viewing at least two minutes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE US troops evacuated from Iraq for medical evaluation after Iran missile attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7913983/US-United-States-Iran-Missiles-Injuries.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additional U.S. troops have been flown out of Iraq for closer evaluation of potential concussion injuries from the Iranian missile attack of January 8, U.S. defense officials said Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell in 1999: I support 'live witnesses'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/21/politics/mcconnell-1999-impeachment-kfile/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mitch McConnell said in 1999 he believed the Senate was entitled to witnesses in President Bill Clinton's impeachment trial and added that he would have voted to give House impeachment managers "whatever" they wanted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collins and Romney hold keys...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Collins-and-Romney-hold-the-keys-in-the-14993295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eyes will be glued to the Senate floor over the next two weeks as the Senate formally conducts its impeachment trial of President Donald Trump. The process got off the ground Tuesday as the two sides debated the rules.  But in actuality, much if it is window-dressing. The most significant stuff is what's happening off the Senate floor - particularly when it comes to potential GOP swing votes like Sens. Susan Collins of Maine and Mitt Romney of Utah. They hold the keys to new evidence that could actually change hardened views of Trump's actions with regard to Ukraine, and their words and actions are what matter most.  And a couple of significant things happened in that regard Tuesday.  One was a change to the rules that were initially proposed by Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell, R-Ky. The change brought the rules more in line with how they were during Bill Clinton's impeachment trial, and they were reportedly changed at the urging of Collins and others.  One rule change made it so evidence compiled by the House would automatically be included in the record, subject to objections by Trump's legal team, whereas before the Senate had to approve that. The other is that the 24 hours of opening arguments that have been allotted to each side will take place over three days each, rather than two each. Both of these are changes that Democrats wanted, and they apparently got some Republicans to side with them - enough to force McConnell to preemptively change the rules, just as the proceedings were beginning.  Democrats might be encouraged by that for a few reasons. One is that it reinforces the fact that McConnell wasn't actually going with the complete Clinton rules and erred in Trump's direction on a couple of things. It suggests that McConnell either wasn't aware of these objections or that they materialized later in the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horrific photos of starving lions at zoo prompt outcry...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/truly-horrific-photos-starving-lions-161725942.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photos of malnourished and dying lions at a zoo in Sudan have sparked global backlash and a growing online campaign to save the animals.The five African lions were found in an emaciated state by activist Osman Salih in Khartoum’s Al-Qureshi Park.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg calls for Trump removal in new ad...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f73765998174ca6e9bd93350c26557d8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Democratic presidential candidate Michael Bloomberg launched a new impeachment-focused television ad Tuesday urging the Senate to remove President Donald Trump from...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temperature checks, extra cleaning at airports...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c27ec8b555c6a4fb0d8defab61618928</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — Many countries are checking the temperatures of arriving airline passengers and adopting precautionary quarantine procedures in response to a new virus that has sickened nearly 300...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict escalates...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/29afb0d57286930a98a467a8a4523e89</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DES MOINES, Iowa (AP) — Democratic presidential candidates have spent weeks reassuring voters they can unify the party, avoid the divisions that plagued the 2016 primary and defeat President...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Standoff: U.S. troops block Russian forces from capturing Syrian oil field...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/jan/21/us-troops-block-russian-forces-capturing-syrian-oi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. troops last weekend reportedly found themselves in a standoff with Russian forces trying to gain access to key oil fields in northeastern Syria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The JFK Mistress Gunned Down in Cold Blood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-jfk-mistress-mary-pinchot-meyer-was-gunned-down-in-cold-blood-why</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Among those haunted by the memory of President Kennedy’s murdered lover, Mary Meyer, were the most powerful reporters—and spies—in America. What secrets were in her lost diary?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC COMICS' first Asian American GREEN LANTERN Lantern is boy who fights racism...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/asian-america/dc-comics-first-asian-american-green-lantern-boy-who-fights-n1119751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"To be able to write a story that centers our community — where we're not just background characters or sidekicks but the actual heroes of the story — was really meaningful," author Minh Lê said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Antonio Brown Reportedly Facing Felony Battery Charges After Incident At FL Home...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2020/01/21/hollywood-police-antonio-brown-battery-arrest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There’s a heavy police presence at Antonio Brown’s residence Tuesday evening, and multiple reports believe it's linked to a battery on his property.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: SAUDI PRINCE HACKED BEZOS' PHONE!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2020/jan/21/amazon-boss-jeff-bezoss-phone-hacked-by-saudi-crown-prince</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Exclusive: investigation suggests Washington Post owner was targeted five months before murder of Jamal Khashoggi</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lose First Battle to Subpoena White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7912653/Donald-Trumps-Senate-trial-begins-senators-war-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats lost the first round in Donald Trump's impeachment trial when the Senate voted down an attempt by Chuck Schumer to subpoena documents from the White House on the Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service warns of falling iguanas...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/21/weather/miami-freeze-falling-iguana-forecast-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday afternoon, the National Weather Service in Miami issued a rare forecast regarding cold temperatures but it was for iguanas. Yes, you read that correctly. Iguanas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: Large Police Presence, 'Active Scene' In Front Of Antonio Brown's FL Home...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2020/01/21/police-at-antonio-browns-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is reportedly a large police presence and "active scene" in front of Antonio Brown's home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House weighs travel ban expansion in coming days...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/21/donald-trump-travel-ban-expansion-101581</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is eyeing seven countries for new immigration restrictions three years after its original order, which created an uproar for targeting Muslim-majority nations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea says may seek 'new path' of weapons build-up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/north-korea-says-may-seek-new-path-of-weapons-build-up/ar-BBZbE5Y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terror spies stationed across US...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/iran-has-spies-across-u-s-officials-warn-after-tehran-posts-3m-bounty-on-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. officials and terrorism experts are warning that Iran has significantly expanded its terror capabilities in America.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senators bend by wearing APPLE Watches...</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/congress/218484-2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At least eight senators had Apple watches to their wrists at the start of the impeachment trial Tuesday, despite a ban on electronics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell softens hard-line tactics...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/01/21/mcconnell-schumer-senate-impeachment-trial-101372</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But Senate Republicans are still preparing to steamroll Democrats on the rules to govern the impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-minute, handwritten changes...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/mcconnell-makes-last-minute-changes-trump-impeachment-trial-rules-n1119511</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The sudden revision in the Senate's organizing resolution also ensures House Democrats' evidence will be admitted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Africa's richest woman under scrutiny after docs show she's exploiting country...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/africas-richest-woman-is-barred-from-her-bank-and-under-investigation/ar-BBZa7XU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Player Making Anti-Abortion Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/patriots-benjamin-watson-producing-abortion-documentary-1270926</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The movie, budgeted at less than $1 million, features former presidential candidate Ben Carson and Alveda King, the niece of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man stabs, kills pro-Trump boss...</title>
      <link>https://www.clickorlando.com/news/local/2020/01/21/man-stabs-kills-pro-trump-boss-drapes-american-flag-over-him-deputies-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.clickorlando.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A man was stabbed to death by his coworker in an apparent argument over their views on the government and President Donald Trump, officials say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100s in river 'no-man's land' after Mexico troops block way...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4d685100193f6a2c521267fe614356df</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CIUDAD HIDALGO, Mexico (AP) — Hundreds of Central American migrants were stranded in a sort of no-man’s land on the river border between Guatemala and Mexico after running up against lines of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside NYC cyber lab trying to break iPhone...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90453437/inside-the-10-million-cyber-lab-trying-to-break-apples-iphone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration wants Apple to create a backdoor into the iPhone. District Attorney Cy Vance Jr. has spent millions trying to find other ways in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.c-span.org/event/?468163/senate-impeachment-trial-day-2&amp;live</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.c-span.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry and Meghan threaten legal action over paparazzi photos...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/harry-meghan-threaten-legal-action-over-paparazzi-photos-n1119206</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Letter addressed to the media says that photographers are tracking the prince and Meghan's every move.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin to legalize taking selfies with ballot...</title>
      <link>https://wkow.com/2020/01/21/wisconsin-senate-to-legalize-taking-selfies-with-ballot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wkow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wisconsin voters could legally take selfies with their marked election ballots under a proposal up for approval in the state Senate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro threatens jail...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/cybersecurity/479169-brazilian-prosecutors-charge-american-journalist-glenn-greenwald-with</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brazilian federal prosecutors on Tuesday charged American journalist Glenn Greenwald with cybercrimes over his role in the publication of articles based on leaked cell phone messages from Brazilian government officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passenger pins driver against tree in wild road rage brawl...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/california/article239486628.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIVACY?  APPLE dropped plan for encrypting backups after FBI complained...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-fbi-icloud-exclusive/exclusive-apple-dropped-plan-for-encrypting-backups-after-fbi-complained-sources-idUSKBN1ZK1CT</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc dropped plans to let iPhone users fully encrypt backups of their devic...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antibiotics dont work...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/killer-coronavirus-attacks-body-pneumonia-21327440</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A mystery coronavirus is sweeping through Asia, with reports in Thailand, Japan, the Philippines and South Korea. The superbug, which is similar to SARS, has already killed six people</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top businessmen stay away from circus...</title>
      <link>https://www.fnlondon.com/articles/absurd-davos-has-become-an-international-bunfight-20200120</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fnlondon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Annual four-day business meet-up is a firm favourite with Wall Street bankers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lines for face masks...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7911781/People-China-queue-buy-face-masks-amid-fears-outbreak-deadly-virus.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An expert from China's National Health Commission has suggested that the virus could be passed through saliva as 20 medical workers are confirmed to have been infected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medics Scanning Plane Passengers...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/asia/2020/01/20/watch-china-medics-reportedly-scanning-plane-passengers-for-wuhan-virus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Video footage shared on Sunday night of plane passengers reportedly being tested for the deadly "Wuhan" virus is amplifying fear of a global pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guggenheim Says Central Bank-Driven 'Ponzi Scheme' Must Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/guggenheim-says-central-bank-driven-ponzi-scheme-must-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Guggenheim Says Central Bank-Driven â€˜Ponzi Schemeâ€™ Must Collapse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Men should be allowed to donate sperm -- after death...</title>
      <link>https://kvia.com/health/2020/01/21/men-should-be-allowed-to-donate-sperm-after-death-study-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kvia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sperm donations from dead men is “ethically permissible,” say doctors seeking to tackle the shortage of living donors in the UK. A study published in the Journal of Medical Ethics Monday proposed that men should be able to “register their desire to donate their sperm after death for use by strangers.” Such a procedure would</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACES DANGER IN RIO...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2019/11/25/glenn-greenwald-i-was-assaulted-live-on-air-this-is-bolsonaros-brazil/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO DE JANEIRO — On Nov. 7, I was physically assaulted by a far-right, pro-Bolsonaro pundit, Augusto Nunes, at a</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans hold the cards -- but that could change...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/republicans-hold-the-cards-at-trumps-impeachment-trial-%e2%80%94-but-that-could-change/ar-BBZaRxz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFC Megastar McGregor Says 'Phenomenal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/ufc-star-conor-mcgregor-praises-phenomenal-president-trump-sits-atop-shoulders-of-many-amazing-giants/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UFC world champion Conor McGregor praised President Donald Trump on Monday evening, branding him a "Phenomenal President" who "sits atop the shoulders of many amazing giants that came b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China virus kills six; More than 300 infected...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/21/china-says-coronavirus-that-has-killed-6-can-spread-between-people-heres-what-we-know.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are anxious about the added risk from millions of Chinese traveling for the Lunar New Year holiday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Years In: Voters Grade Trump...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2020/01/21/how-voters-grade-trump-three-years-into-his-presidency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asked to grade Donald Trump’s job as president on scale from A to F, the lion’s share (38 percent) of voters gave him an F, while 21 percent gave him an A, according to a new Morning Consult/Politico poll. But the president received his best grades on jobs and the economy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California considers declaring common pain killer carcinogen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd769fe0f9d417c47a947c12c14ea3bb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SACRAMENTO, Calif. (AP) — A fight is coming to California over whether to list one of the world's most common over-the-counter drugs as a carcinogen, echoing recent high-profile battles over...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP TRIAL BEGINS...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2cb8c0b71160268b52a90335e0e5ce47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump’s impeachment trial is set to unfold at the Capitol, a contentious proceeding over whether to remove him from office for pressuring Ukraine to investigate...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: Trump lawyer Cipollone material witness...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-trump-impeachment-lawyer/trump-lawyer-cipollone-a-material-witness-in-impeachment-trial-democrats-idUSKBN1ZK1RJ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats who will argue the case to remove President Donald Trump from office d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened to Choupette?</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/01/21/style/karl-lagerfeld-choupette.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Karl Lagerfeld’s cat, and rumored heir, has become a business unto herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Amounts of Money Pouring Into Nordic Real Estate...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/markets/e2-80-98massive-amounts-of-money-e2-80-99-are-pouring-into-nordic-real-estate/ar-BBZ9V0n</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutant goat born with 'human-face' worshipped as 'avatar of God'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/mutant-goat-born-human-face-21326501</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tiny animal was born just days after in Rajasthan, India, and is already gaining celebrity status because of its hauntingly human-like face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did Russian spies pose as plumbers to bug forum?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/21/swiss-police-suspect-russian-spies-posed-as-plumbers-to-bug-davos.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Swiss police picked up two men at the high-end resort in August after the pair had aroused suspicion by staying for an unusually long time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLDMAN CEO to DJ at Super Bowl Party...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/goldman-s-dj-d-sol-the-ceo-to-spin-at-super-bowl-party</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Goldmanâ€™s DJ D-Solâ€”the CEOâ€”to Spin at Super Bowl Party</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding peace and harmony at 'End of the Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2020-01-21/spain-pilgrims</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Spanish town plays host to religious pilgrims, but to some they are 'hippies' and 'troublemakers'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TUCKER: Sanders capable of taking 'many thousands' of Trump voters...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/479103-tucker-carlson-bernie-sanders-capable-of-taking-many-thousands-trump-voters</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fox News Channel's Tucker Carlson on Monday said that he thinks presidential hopeful Sen. Bernie Sanders (I-Vt.) is capable of taking "many thousands" of votes from President Trump if the longtime senator becomes the Democratic nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: POLARIZATION HITS NEW HIGH...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/283910/trump-third-year-sets-new-standard-party-polarization.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donald Trump averaged 42% job approval during his third year in office, characterized by a record 82-point gap in ratings between Republicans (89%) and Democrats (7%).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIRUS</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91a4b52778f1d0baeb1ef6856287671d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WUHAN, China (AP) — Face masks sold out and temperature checks at airports and train stations became the new norm as China strove Tuesday to control the outbreak of a new virus that has reached...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunberg scolds Davos elites on 'climate'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7a1def0638f8a51f1cd3a6299b903c58</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DAVOS, Switzerland (AP) — Young climate activists including Swedish teenager Greta Thunberg told business and political elites gathered Tuesday at the World Economic Forum that they aren't doing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozzy Osbourne breaks silence on battle with Parkinson's...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Culture/ozzy-osbourne-opens-parkinsons-diagnosis-family-helped-back/story?id=68416861</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ozzy Osbourne opens up about his Parkinson's diagnosis in an exclusive "GMA" interview with Robin Roberts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATES...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/trump-impeachment-trial-senate-proceedings-set-to-begin-as-rules-come-into-focus-2019-01-21/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The trial will get underway at 1 p.m., marking just the third time a president has faced removal from office in U.S. history.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian MP offers $3 million reward for 'whoever kills Trump'...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200121092957-pp44x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;IRAN-USA/TRUMP (URGENT):Iranian MP announces $3 million award for "whoever kills Trump" - ISNA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French workers cut power to world's largest food market in pension protest...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20200121082615-bsx2y</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FRENCH-PROTESTS/PENSIONS (UPDATE 1, PIX):UPDATE 1-French workers cut power to world's largest food market in pension protest</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic across globe...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10784330/china-coronavirus-reaches-australia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A TERRIFYING new virus from China is feared to have reached Australia after a man was tested for the killer mystery bug. The man, from Brisbane, was displaying symptoms of the fatal coronavirus aft…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases in Australia, Philippines?</title>
      <link>https://www.straitstimes.com/asia/philippines-australia-probe-suspected-cases-of-wuhan-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.straitstimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MANILA - Health officials are investigating two patients in the Philippines and Australia showing symptoms of a new, mysterious coronavirus spreading from China's Wuhan province.. Read more at straitstimes.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing imposes quasi-quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Chinese-officials-urge-people-not-to-travel-in-14991226.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING - Chinese health authorities sought to impose a quasi-quarantine around Wuhan, a city of 11 million people, Tuesday as they stepped up efforts to stop the spread of a mystery virus that has now claimed six lives.  With confirmation that the pneumonialike coronavirus can be transmitted from person to person, and with hundreds of millions of Chinese packing onto public transport to make their annual pilgrimages home, a new sense of panic has erupted here.  Long lines formed at pharmacies and convenience stores around the country as people rushed to buy surgical masks, with unlucky customers posting photos on social media of bare shelves. People around the country canceled their trips home for the Spring Festival - the most important holiday on the Chinese calendar.  "I don't really dare to go to the airport right now, or even to the movie theater," said Xie Jing, a 33-year-old who works in advertising in Shanghai, where there have been two confirmed cases of coronavirus. She canceled her planned trip home to Sichuan, where two cases are suspected.  "Everyone is being very careful at the moment in Shanghai, everyone is wearing masks on the streets," Xie said.  The Geneva-based World Health Organization said it would call an emergency meeting on Wednesday to decide whether to designate the outbreak as an international public health emergency. Australia and the Philippines are the latest countries with suspected cases of infection.  The virus was first detected on Dec. 31 and was linked to a dirty food market in Wuhan, not far from one of the main train stations, where wild animals including wolf pups and civet cats had been on sale for consumption.  A total of 298 people in China had been confirmed with the virus at 5 p.m. on Tuesday, the National Health Commission...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hazmat Suits Deployed on Planes...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/hazmat-suits-deployed-on-planes-as-security-tightens-over-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hazmat Suits Deployed on Planes as Security Tightens Over Virus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitter fight over rules...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/senate/478895-senate-braces-for-bitter-fight-over-impeachment-rules</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate is barreling toward a bitter, potentially lengthy fight Tuesday over the rules governing President Trump’s impeachment trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia steps up defenses as China virus hits 291 people, kills six...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-says-virus-spreading-between-humans-set-meet-030928262.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Asian countries on Tuesday ramped up measures to block the spread of a new virus as the death toll in China rose to six and the number of cases jumped to almost 300, raising concerns in the middle of a major holiday travel rush. From Australia to Thailand and as far as Nepal, nations stepped up fever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEBOW MARRIED!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/2020/01/20/tim-tebow-demi-leigh-nel-peters-married/4527622002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tim Tebow and 2017 Miss Universe winner Demi-Leigh Nel-Peters are married, as the couple shared photos on social media and details on day with People.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS RAGE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7909819/This-isnt-trial-COVER-Chuck-Schumer-rages-against-impeachment-trial-rules.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate minority leader went on offense just after Mitch McConnell unveiled his planned rules for the trial of Donald Trump saying the Republican was trying to hide evidence after dark.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
