<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Putin says West not taking Russia 'red lines' seriously enough...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/putin-says-west-not-taking-russias-warnings-red-lines-seriously-enough-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Vladimir Putin said on Thursday that the West was not taking Russia's warnings not to cross its "red lines" seriously enough and that Moscow needed to obtain serious security guarantees from the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monkey-brain study with link to China's military roils top European university...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/world/exclusive-monkey-brain-study-with-link-chinas-military-roils-top-european-2021-11-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Chinese professor at the University of Copenhagen conducted genetic research with the Chinese military without disclosing the connection, the university told Reuters, in the latest example of how China's pursuit of military-civilian technology is tapping into Western academia in the strategically sensitive area of biotechnology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Takes swings at GOOGLE, FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/business/media-telecom/news-corp-chairman-rupert-murdoch-takes-swings-google-facebook-2021-11-17/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rupert Murdoch renewed his attacks on Google and Facebook during News Corp’s annual shareholder meeting on Wednesday, accusing the tech giants of trying to silence conservative voices and calling for "significant reform."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third of Healthcare Workers Not Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/roberthart/2021/11/18/nearly-one-third-of-healthcare-workers-in-us-hospitals-are-still-not-vaccinated-against-covid-19-cdc-study-finds-as-vaccine-mandate-looms/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Around 70% of healthcare workers in U.S. hospitals were fully vaccinated against Covid-19 as of September 15, according to the CDC study, with higher rates found among workers in children’s hospitals and urban areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merkel to Usher in Tighter Rules With Germany Engulfed...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/merkel-to-usher-in-tighter-covid-rules-with-germany-engulfed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Merkel Pushes For Tighter Covid Rules With German Infections Rising</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan deploys advanced fighter jets amid tensions with China...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/asia-pacific/582095-taiwan-deploys-advanced-fighter-jets-amid-tensions-with</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan reportedly deployed advanced fighter jets on Thursday in a show of strength and cooperation with the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Don vs. DeSantis: Let the war games begin...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/campaign/582043-trump-vs-desantis-let-the-war-games-begin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surely DeSantis wants to avoid a higher ranking on Trump’s enemies list, but it’s doubtful that the governor will acquiesce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: For Anti-Aging, Nothing Beats Diet -- Not Even Drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/healthy-diet-beats-drugs-aging/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results show calorie intake and the balance between protein, fats, and carbohydrates have a stronger impact on liver function than pharmaceuticals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients Airlifted Out Of State Due To Hospital Bed Shortage In Boston...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2021/11/17/boston-medflight-out-of-state-hospitals/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boston MedFlight is being forced to bring patients to hospitals in Connecticut and Rhode Island because there aren't enough beds in the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shock After Parishioner Found Stabbed To Death Inside Baltimore Church...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/11/18/evelyn-player-baltimore-church-murder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Baltimore Police confirm to WJZ Thursday that a person of interest is being sought in the murder of Evelyn Player, the 69-year-old Baltimore woman found dead Tuesday morning inside Southern Baptist Church.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Junk Spreads, Creating Risk of No-Go Zones for Satellites...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/space-junk-spreads-creating-risk-of-no-go-zones-for-satellites/ar-AAQRas3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian missile test that shattered a dead satellite this week highlights a growing threat of space debris just as companies such as SpaceX and Boeing Co. make plans to launch as many as 65,000 commercial spacecraft into orbit in coming years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer boots, more slippers: Shortage of containers changing what shows up on shelves...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/fewer-boots-more-slippers-how-a-shortage-of-shipping-containers-is-changing-what-shows-up-on-shelves/ar-AAQRbrr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Retailers and manufacturers are prioritizing merchandise that’s lightweight and pliable to maximize every cubic inch of these massive steel boxes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German hospitals sound alarm...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211118-last-resort-german-hospitals-sound-alarm-in-pandemic-surge</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With intensive care beds filling up and health staff running short, a hospital in Bavaria's Freising made an unprecedented decision to transfer a coronavirus patient to northern Italy for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church under fire over 'Let's go Brandon' chant...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/texas-church-under-fire-over-lets-go-brandon-chants-caught-on-video</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Texas church is coming under fire over a video showing people inside the place of worship chanting the viral anti-Biden phrase, "Let’s Go Brandon."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflicts mount on easing restrictions amid infection spikes...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/582080-conflicts-mount-on-easing-covid-19-restrictions-amid-autumn-case-spikes</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An uptick in COVID-19 cases as winter approaches is setting off a debate about if a new era of living with the virus has arrived or whether heightened restrictions and caution are still needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems question whether Biden will actually run in '24...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/582071-democrats-question-whether-biden-will-actually-run-in-2024</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A number of Democrats are privately questioning whether President Biden will run for reelection amid anemic approval ratings and rising worries about next year’s midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Jury in Rittenhouse murder trial deliberate for third day...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20211118105806-8k733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-RACE/WISCONSIN (PIX):Jury in Rittenhouse murder trial to deliberate for third day in Wisconsin court</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-profile execution looms in Oklahoma...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/executions-oklahoma-oklahoma-city-baker-mayfield-1e212e0db47f598ccb9c97fd611df929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Students at high schools across Oklahoma City walked out of their classes. Prayer vigils were held at the state Capitol, and barricades were erected outside the governor's mansion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortage of homes for sale continues to plague housing market...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/realestate/shortage-of-homes-for-sale-continues-to-plague-housing-market/ar-AAQQHbX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOWN SQUARE | A recent report by Redfin real estate brokerage found that one-third of homes in more than 400 metro areas went under contract within one week of being listed for sale during the four weeks that ended Oct. 17.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch Tells Trump He Needs to Leave Past Behind...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/rupert-murdoch-tells-trump-he-needs-to-leave-the-past-behind/ar-AAQPEyk </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Media baron Rupert Murdoch told former President Donald Trump that he needed to leave the past behind and focus on the future to address problems the country faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican National Guard deploying troops in Cancun following rise in violence...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/581996-mexican-national-guard-deploying-troops-in-cancun-following-rise-in</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexico is sending at least 1,500 National Guard troops to Cancun following a rise in violence in the southeastern corner of the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATION WAITS:  Rittenhouse jury ends DAY 2 of deliberations without verdict...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/jury-rittenhouse-murder-trial-deliberate-110736753.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KENOSHA, Wis. (Reuters) -Jurors in the Wisconsin murder trial of Kyle Rittenhouse ended their second day of deliberations without reaching a verdict, after reviewing a series of videos on Wednesday of the teenager's deadly encounters at racial justice protests last year. Defense lawyers made a new request for a mistrial, saying prosecutors withheld the high-definition version of a drone video in evidence and enhanced it in order to portray Rittenhouse as a threat. Rittenhouse, 18, is charged with killing Joseph Rosenbaum, 36, and Anthony Huber, 26, and attempted homicide in the wounding of Gaige Grosskreutz, 28, during a chaotic night of protests in Kenosha, Wisconsin on Aug. 25, 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $750 million 'ASTROWORLD' lawsuit names APPLE alongside Travis Scott, Drake, LIVE NATION...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/750-million-astroworld-lawsuit-names-234316307.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney Tony Buzbee filed suit on behalf of 125 victims of the Astroworld tragedy, including the family of 21-year-old Axel Acosta, who died at the concert.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE VIDEO THAT SHOCKED THE WORLD...</title>
      <link>https://www.news4jax.com/video/news/2020/05/07/viewer-warning-uncut-video-of-confrontation-shooting-of-ahmaud-arbery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news4jax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cellphone video shows the 25-year-old running toward a pickup truck stopped in the road ahead and the events that led to his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting testing rules leave travelers frustrated...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/travel/news/shifting-coronavirus-testing-rules-leave-travelers-frustrated/ar-AAQPjUE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“There’s a lot of misinformation floating around right now about coronavirus testing.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How luxury survived the pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/How-luxury-survived-the-pandemic-16629032.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What becomes of luxury in a global pandemic? Is the pursuit of luxury incompatible with...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misinformation rampant in America. 'Experts' propose ways to combat it...</title>
      <link>https://thefulcrum.us/big-picture/misinformation-and-disinformation</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefulcrum.us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spread of false and misleading information, whether intentional or not, is one of the most consequential issues in America and around the world. A new report from the Aspen Institute attempts to solve the problem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gasoline 50%!</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/biden-asks-ftc-probe-gasoline-151500651.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- President Joe Biden urged the Federal Trade Commission to probe possible illegal conduct in U.S. gasoline markets, though any inquiry by the agency is unlikely to have an immediate impact on pump prices paid by consumers.Most Read from BloombergStartup Fever Is Gripping the World’s Last Big Untapped NationWhat Designers of Video Game Cities Understand About Real CitiesElizabeth Holmes Faces Last-Ditch Chance to Testify at TrialChronically Underfunded HBCUs Eye Scholarships in Bide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation impacting U.S. 'readiness' for WAR...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10214259/Defense-Secretary-Austin-orders-help-military-families-buy-food-housing-prices-soar.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin on Wednesday warned that rising prices for housing and food were affecting the readiness of U.S. armed forces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Gates' TERRAPOWER to build first advanced nuke reactor...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/11/17/bill-gates-terrapower-builds-its-first-nuclear-reactor-in-a-coal-town.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bill Gates' TerraPower has chosen Kemmerer, Wyoming, a frontier-era coal town, as the site where the company will build its first advanced nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapper Young Dolph killed at cookie shop...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-crime-shootings-68cb290e943dd1de5dfe9a12b04eba6d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEMPHIS, Tenn. (AP) — Rapper Young Dolph was shot and killed Wednesday at a cookie shop in his hometown of Memphis, Tennessee, and a search is underway for the shooter, officials said. Police tweeted that no suspect information was available in the shooting, which took place at Makeda’s Cookie’s near Memphis International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE deal to pay AFP for online content...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20211117-google-agrees-5-year-deal-to-pay-afp-for-online-content-executives</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google and Agence France-Presse on Wednesday said they had signed a "pioneering" five-year deal under which the world’s biggest internet search company will pay an undisclosed sum for content in Euro…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baldwin 'intentionally' fired deadly shot, script supervisor claims in suit...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/11/17/alec-baldwin-intentionally-fired-deadly-shot-on-rust-film-set-suit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mamie Mitchell, the script supervisor is suing the actor, the movie production company and others for assault and intentional infliction of emotional distress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House censures Rep. Gosar for violent video in rare rebuke...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/technology-entertainment-marjorie-taylor-greene-censures-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-854fd412b7a1049c8fb9a83fe2c56b8f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The House voted Wednesday to censure Republican Rep. Paul Gosar of Arizona for posting of an animated video that depicted him killing Democratic Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez with a sword, an extraordinary rebuke that highlighted the political strains testing Washington and the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stunning Number Of FL Teachers Arrested For Sexual Relationships With Students...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/teacher-arrests-sexual-relations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a stunning number of teacher arrests for inappropriate — and illegal — sexual relations with their students, parents are increasingly concerned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classes going remote in Detroit schools...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.chalkbeat.org/2021/11/17/22788007/detroit-public-schools-remote-learning-friday-december-covid-spread</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.chalkbeat.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detroit district students will learn online on Fridays in December as the district tries to address COVID spread</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW:  MIXED RESULTS...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/reviews/adele-30-album-review-dependable-pop-titan-finally-mixes-things-up-3096613</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Previously accused of playing it safe, Adele enters a new decade by experimenting with bolder sounds. It gives intriguing but mixed results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple convicted of stealing $20 million in Covid funds on run, says FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-couple-convicted-of-stealing-covid-funds-is-on-the-run-the-f-b-i-says/ar-AAQPd2T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When the Covid-19 pandemic began last year, a Southern California man recruited his brother, his wife and many others to use the identities of older people, foreign exchange students who had left the country and dead relatives to apply for $20 million in federal relief funds, the authorities said. The man, Richard Ayvazyan, 43, bought a $3.25 million mansion and filled it with gold coins, luxury watches and imported furniture using the stolen...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon boosts housing money for troops as hunger persists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lloyd-austin-bc9a18ebffa9e1cae4a9c24726f97751</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Pentagon will increase housing payments for troops in key areas and look for ways to combat hunger across the force, Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin announced Wednesday, in the department's latest effort to address food insecurity among service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSHA 'SUSPENDS' ENFORCEMENT</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/nov/17/osha-has-suspended-activities-related-bidens-vacci/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Occupational Safety and Health Administration has suspended work on President Biden’s vaccine mandate after a federal appeals court hit pause on rules that would force companies with 100 more employees to require COVID-19 shots or regular testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon warns troops could be forced out for refusal after OK rejects measure...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/pentagon-warns-national-guard-troops-could-be-forced-out-for-vaccine-refusal-after-oklahoma-rejects-mandate/ar-AAQP9GV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The move by Gov. Kevin Stitt has sparked concern within the Biden administration that other Republican-controlled states will follow Oklahoma’s lead, leaving the Pentagon with little recourse but to hold individual service members accountable for refusing lawful orders that their immediate chain of command has disavowed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Mexicans pulled from ocean after crossing attempt...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/lifestyle-mexico-california-united-states-san-diego-c9a9b49540969a3f4587f015f7d7c40d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN DIEGO, Calif. (AP) — San Diego lifeguards pulled two adults and a child from the ocean after it was reported that dozens of people were attempting to swim from Mexico into the United States, authorities said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead model dumped in front of LA hospital by masked men...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10213671/Married-LA-model-dead-sidewalk-outside-hospital-drugged-dumped.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A model was found dead on a sidewalk in Los Angeles after three unknown men dumped her lifeless body outside a hospital and dropped of her friend off in critical condition two hours later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAN Pushing Biden FCC Nominee, a FOX Critic...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/media/conservative-cable-network-gets-behind-bidens-fcc-nominee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most right-wing channels on TV is throwing its weight behind a radically progressive Biden nominee who has called conservative news outlets threats to democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinians fear 'civil war' amid growing anarchy...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/middle-east/palestinians-fear-civil-war-amid-growing-anarchy-685254</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New research offers glimpse into early human development...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-health-europe-early-humans-eb1b0020d954eb9bb3112771d94ca2e3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists have been able to get a rare glimpse into a crucial, early stage of human development by analyzing an embryo in its third week after fertilization — a moment in time that has been difficult to study because of both practical and ethical considerations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Smallpox' Vials Found at Philly MERCK Merck Lab...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/smallpox-vials-found-at-merck-lab-in-suburban-philadelphia-facility/3050775/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A batch of vials labeled "smallpox," a deadly disease eradicated since the 1970s, was found in a freezer and immediately quarantined, the Centers for Disease Control told NBC10. An investigation into why they were there is underway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 Convicted Of Murdering Malcolm X In 1965 To Be Exonerated...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/17/2-men-convicted-of-murdering-malcolm-x-in-1965-to-be-exonerated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Malcolm X was assassinated while giving a speech at Harlem's Audubon Ballroom on Feb. 21, 1965.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY CRUISE REQUIRES KIDS 5 AND UP TO GET JAB...</title>
      <link>https://www.wesh.com/article/disney-cruise-vaccine-children/38280339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wesh.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“As we set sail again, the health and safety of our Guests, Cast Members and Crew Members is a top priority."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Docs Confirm Billionaire Was Subject of Child Porn Probe...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/new-docs-confirm-billionaire-was-subject-of-child-porn-probe/ar-AAQOQDf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Court documents released on Wednesday confirm that the richest man in South Dakota, billionaire T. Denny Sanford, is the “implicated individual” in a child porn investigation that began in 2019. Multiple media outlets have previously reported that Sanford was the subject of the probe, starting with the investigative reporting outlet ProPublica, which identified him in August 2020. The formal revelation follows an October decision from the South...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Man beaten after catching boyfriend 'humping' their dog...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/buster/assault/alleged-dog-humper-295038</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Upon discovering his boyfriend “humping” their dog, a Florida Man was beaten and threatened with a knife by his beau, police allege. According to an arrest report, the 58-year-old victim told cops he</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tara Setmayer New Conservative Star On 'VIEW'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bet.com/article/sujjof/could-tara-setmayer-replace-meghan-mccain-on-the-view</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two conservatives have feuded in the past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'QAnon Shaman' sentenced to 41 months for role in Capitol riot...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/jacob-chansley-qanon-shaman-sentencing-jan-6-d4b17524-266d-4bb9-8681-8069bbb20540.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is among the longest sentences handed down so far in connection to the Capitol riot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beef Prices Rise 20%!</title>
      <link>https://cnsnews.com/article/national/megan-williams/beef-prices-rise-201-due-increased-consumer-demand-and-labor</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(CNS News) -- Behind unleaded gasoline, beef prices have risen the most on the Consumer Price Index (CPI) since October 2020, rising over 20% in the past year, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder Plot Claims, Dog Bite, Roger Stone: Inside FL's Craziest Race...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/murder-plot-claims-a-dog-bite-and-roger-stone-inside-floridas-craziest-race</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The actions of an overly aggressive service dog named Gunner are only the latest twist in the bizarre race to represent this coastal Florida congressional district.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague of 50 million cannibal crabs shuts roads in Oz...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4085287/moment-50-million-cannibal-crabs-shut-roads/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THIS is the jaw-dropping moment a “biblical plague” of 50 million crabs head to the ocean to breed. The swarm of cannibalistic critters shut down roads from the jungle to the coast on C…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEY PLANS GAMBING FUTURE; SPORTS BETTING...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/business/digital/disney-espn-sports-betting-dollars-1235048867/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now that major leagues are getting on board with gambling, the family-friendly Hollywood giant is eyeing that revenue and may start with a splashy ESPN licensing deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIMATE TAX:  New Yorkers Fume As MTA Says It's Moving Ahead With Congestion Pricing...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/congestion-pricing-new-york-city-manhattan-mta-climate-change/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commuters are raising questions about the need to enact congestion pricing, the charging a hefty fee for anyone driving into Manhattan's Central Business District below 60th Street.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Booster Shot Confusion As CA Goes Against CDC And FDA Recommendations...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/booster-shot-confusion-as-california-goes-against-current-cdc-and-fda-recommendations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and the Food and Drug Administration said last month that only seniors and adults at high risk should get boosters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIDEN VAX MANDATE HANGING BY A PING-PONG</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/11/16/politics/vaccine-mandate-osha-lottery/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Challenges to the Biden administration's vaccine mandate targeting employers with more than 100 employees will be consolidated and heard by the Ohio-based 6th US Circuit Court of Appeals after it was chosen Tuesday by a ping-pong ball lottery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austrian cases hit record high amid quarantine for The Unjabbed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/austrian-covid-cases-hit-record-102452050.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Austrian coronavirus infections hit a new daily record on Wednesday, the third day of a lockdown for those not fully vaccinated aimed at halting the surge. Roughly 65% of Austria's population is fully vaccinated against the virus, one of the lowest rates in western Europe. Austria also has one of the highest infection rates on the continent, with a seven-day incidence https://covid19-dashboard.ages.at of 925 per 100,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VT has highest vaccination rate in country. So why are cases surging?</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/vermont-highest-vaccination-rate-country-cases-surging/story?id=81090116</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why COVID-19 cases are surging in Vermont, which is one of the most vaccinated states in the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This experience broke people': Inside State amid Afghanistan withdrawal...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/17/afghanistan-withdrawal-state-department-522705</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The chaos that came with ending America's longest war extended to Foggy Bottom, where staff were left with psychological scars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLE Will Sell Parts for Customers to Make Own Repairs...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/apple-sell-spare-parts-consumers-140308622.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple Inc on Wednesday said it will for the first time start selling spare parts and tools to the general public to perform their own repairs on some iPhones and Mac computers. The self-service repair program comes after years of pressure from consumer groups have resulted in Apple providing greater access to repair manuals and genuine parts. In 2019, Apple started a program where independent repair shops can buy its parts, tools and manuals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Priest Robbed At Gunpoint, Assaulted Outside Baltimore Church...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2021/11/16/priest-assaulted-robbed-at-gunpoint-outside-of-st-leos-roman-catholic-church/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Father Bernie Carman of St. Leo’s Roman Catholic Church has bruises and scrapes, but is doing okay tonight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Foreign' agents pitch has El Salvador civil society on edge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/media-united-states-nayib-bukele-el-salvador-san-salvador-fbc5b491ccbad99289719765e9a7aea1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN SALVADOR, El Salvador (AP) — El Salvador President Nayib Bukele has pitched a proposed law requiring people and organizations who receive foreign funding to register as “foreign agents,” following the lead of countries like the United States.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid Outbreak in Party Town Shows How Pandemic Could End...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/covid-outbreak-in-party-town-shows-how-the-pandemic-could-end/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers studying those who contracted the virus are gaining important insights into the immunity-bolstering effects of natural infection after vaccination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POWER OF THE DOG' review: Superb gothic western mysterious and menacing...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2021/nov/17/the-power-of-the-dog-review-jane-campions-superb-gothic-western-is-mysterious-and-menacing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Slow-burning psychodrama about two warring brothers on a ranch in 1920s Montana is one of the director’s best</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE ELEPHANT WHO COULD BE A PERSON...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2021/11/happy-elephant-bronx-zoo-nhrp-lawsuit/620672/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The most important animal-rights case of the 21st century revolves around an unlikely subject.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will TSA Be Ready For Thanksgiving? It's Mystery...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/suzannerowankelleher/2021/11/17/tsa-thanksgiving-mystery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the vaccine mandate deadline and Turkey Day looming, how many TSA employees are still not inoculated? The agency isn't saying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China hypersonic weapon could launch surprise nuke attack...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10211221/Chinas-hypersonic-space-weapons-used-launch-SURPRISE-attack-US.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff Gen John Hyten said China's space weapons could be used to launch a surprise attack on the US. China is thought to have carried out two tests of an orbital nuke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murder Plot Claims, Dog Bite, Roger Stone: Inside FL's Craziest Race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/murder-plot-claims-dog-bite-100030816.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photo Illustration by Thomas Levinson/Photos Getty ImagesWhen a Belgian Malinois named Gunner bit into a 9-year-old boy at a Florida fishing tournament earlier this month, it didn’t seem like the kind of incident that could have national political importance.But now the dog attack has become an unlikely flashpoint in an intra-Republican battle over a hotly contested House seat, pitting Trump adviser Roger Stone and his allies against Trump-backed congressional hopeful Anna Paulina Luna.The dog b</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NYT CEO: TV News In Dead Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/11/former-new-york-times-ceo-mark-thompson-us-tv-news-is-in-dead-trouble-1234875928/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former New York Times CEO Mark Thompson has said US TV news is in “dead trouble” as it loses audiences under the age of 60. Thompson, who used to be BBC Director General and ran the NYT between 201…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Voters have increasing doubts about Biden health, mental fitness...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2021/11/17/poll-biden-mental-fitness-job-approval-522785</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new POLITICO/Morning Consult poll shows just 44 percent of voters approve of Biden's job performance, and 46 percent say he's "mentally fit."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was charged with hate crime after brutally beating gay man he targeted on GRINDR...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/an-oregon-man-was-charged-with-a-hate-crime-after-brutally-beating-a-gay-man-he-targeted-on-grindr-feds-say/ar-AAQNYs8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest Supply Casualty: Garage Doors...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/11/15/garage-door-shortage-building-sacramento/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The city of Sacramento will now allow garages to be boarded up in new homes, if the garage doors are not delivered in time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
