<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Bond Movie Release Delayed?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/james-bond-open-letter-calls-no-time-die-delay-coronavirus-1282047</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Writers for the biggest 007 blog have urged Eon, MGM and Universal to postpone the release until summer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chained-up  monkey forced to lift weights and do sit-ups for tourists...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/monkey-forced-lift-weights-sit-21614745</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The poor monkey was walked around with a chain on its neck as it performed for the enjoyment of tourists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMLO Approval Falls in Polls on Mexico Rampant Violence...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/amlo-approval-falls-two-polls-153521697.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador’s backing took a hit in two national opinion polls as respondents raise concerns about unchecked violence in the country.Lopez Obrador’s approval rate fell to 59% in February from 68% in December, according to a Reforma newspaper poll published</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS SET FOR SUPER TUESDAY DRAMA!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/be14026452cb8d39de828ac25ff041cf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELMA, Ala. (AP) — An emboldened Joe Biden is trying to cast himself as the clear moderate alternative to progressive Bernie Sanders as the Democrats' shrinking presidential field races toward...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israelis vote in 3rd election in year focused on Netanyahu... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1465b297a02795783f5d8927b7058c72</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israelis were voting Monday in an unprecedented third election in less than a year to decide whether longtime Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu stays in power despite his upcoming...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is world's tallest mammal at risk from 'silent extinction'?</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/travel/destinations/africa/namibia/articles/giraffes-hoanib-valley-silent-extinction-safari/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos $165M Home and Why New Moguls Love Old Hollywood Estates...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/jeff-bezos-165m-home-why-new-moguls-love-old-hollywood-estates-1281092</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon chief bought the Jack Warner property from David Geffen, showing the enduring appeal of mansions built by entertainment pioneers: "People appreciate owning a piece of history."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US manufacturing slows...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/02/februarys-ism-manufacturing-index-is-50point1-vs-an-expected-50point8.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Manufacturing activity in the U.S. grew at a slower-than-expected pace last month as the coronavirus outbreak dampened sentiment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks attempt rebound...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/01/awaiting-us-stock-futures-open-at-6-pm-after-wall-streets-worst-week-since-2008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stocks opened higher as Wall Street tried to rebound from its worst week since the financial crisis amid fears of the coronavirus outbreak.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS investigating defect in tests...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/485426-hhs-investigating-defect-in-coronavirus-tests</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services on Sunday said it is probing a manufacturing problem in the first testing kits for coronavirus that led several states to request emergency approval for state-specific tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will decide fate of Obamacare -- again...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/wireStory/supreme-court-decide-fate-obama-health-care-law-69334934</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Supreme Court has agreed to decide a lawsuit that threatens the Obama-era health care law, but the decision is not likely until after the 2020 election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUBLIC ENEMY fire Flavor Flav after clash over Bernie rally...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/music/2020/mar/02/public-enemy-fire-flavor-flav-clash-bernie-sanders</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spat brings one of rap’s longest partnerships to an end, as Chuck D says his former bandmate is motivated by money and ‘better find rehab’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chained-up monkey forced to lift weights and do sit-ups in tourist show training...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/chained-up-monkey-forced-lift-21614986</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ning Nong the monkey is forced to lift weights, do sit-ups and slam-dunk balls in temperatures soaring higher than 30C as it trains to perform for tourists in Phuket, Thailand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic buying hits NYC...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8064575/Panic-buying-hits-New-York-coronavirus-case-NYC.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York had its first confirmed case of coronavirus on Sunday as nationwide cases reached at least 86 with two deaths. The spread of the disease has seen panic-buying in worst-hit areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Welch, former chairman and CEO of GE, dies at 84...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/02/jack-welch-obit-ge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fortune magazine once called him "manager of the century," but he also was known as "Neutron Jack" for slashing tens of thousands of jobs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem candidates gear up for dramatic Super Tuesday...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/485388-democratic-candidates-gear-up-for-a-dramatic-super-tuesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Voters in fourteen states and one U.S. territory will head to the polls Tuesday to choose between the remaining Democratic presidential candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxiety mounts among health workers...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2020-03-02/healthcare-workers-anxiety-as-coronavirus-takes-root-in-the-us</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With news that healthcare workers in California and Washington state have contracted the virus from patients, doctors and nurses are alarmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erdogan says 'MILLIONS' of refugees released...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8064715/Greeks-fear-influx-migrants-thousands-clashed-police.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 13,000 migrants have gathered on the Turkish side of the river which runs 125 miles along the frontier and separates them from Greece, and therefore the EU.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrant Shot Dead by Greek Police as Border Clashes Grow...</title>
      <link>https://summit.news/2020/03/02/migrant-shot-dead-by-greek-police-as-border-clashes-grow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;summit.news&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crowd chants</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's first double-lung transplant performed on victim...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/03/02/chinese-doctors-perform-worlds-first-double-lung-transplant-for-coronavirus-victim/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surgeons had to stay in a negative-pressure room during the entire operation, wearing whole-body protective suits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macau casino takings plunge record 88%...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/macau-casino-takings-plunge-record-88-virus-closures-083942712.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Macau&amp;#39;s casino industry suffered its worst monthly downturn on record in February after city-wide closures aimed at stopping the spread of the deadly coronavirus. The former Portuguese colony took the unprecedented step in early February of shutting much of its lucrative entertainment sector for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NKorea fires 'short-range ballistic missiles'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nknews.org/2020/03/north-korea-fires-unidentified-missile-south-korea-says/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nknews.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Updated at 15:00 and 16:35 KST: This article has been updated to include further assessments from the South Korean military, as well as commentary from three experts. It was later updated to include additional comments from a JCS official. North Korea on Monday test-fired two short-range ballistic missiles, South Korea’s military said, the first such …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Disturbing' video: Feds under fire for scaring monkeys, damaging brains...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/disturbing-video-feds-under-fire-scaring-monkeys-damaging-their-brains-n1137041</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bipartisan group of lawmakers has "serious concerns" about federal funding of the primate experiments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican opens archive on pope's silence during Holocaust...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/vatican-opens-archive-popes-silence-during-holocaust-115405633.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Historians will begin combing the archives of the world's most contentious pope on Monday, hoping to glean why Pius XII stayed silent during the Nazi extermination of Jews in the Holocaust. More than 200 researchers have applied for permission to settle in one of the small studies of the Vatican</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top brands accused of using forced Chinese labor...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/top-brands-accused-using-forced-chinese-labour-042802176.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China is transferring tens of thousands of Uighur detainees out of internment camps and into factories that supply some of the world's leading brands, an Australian think tank said Monday. Top global brands such as Apple, BMW and Sony have been accused of getting supplies from factories using the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA, AMERICAN suspend flights...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/delta-american-airlines-suspend-several-milan-flights-094147778.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Delta Air Lines and American Airlines are temporarily suspending some flights between US airports and Milan because of the spread of the novel coronavirus in parts of Italy, the two carriers announced. Delta is suspending flights between New York's busy John F. Kennedy International Airport and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California voters still feeling the Bern...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-voters-still-feeling-bern-051734023.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bernie Sanders is heading into California's primary on Tuesday as the clear favorite among Democrats, enjoying a massive lead over his competitors, notably among young voters and Latinos. Political observers say his appeal in California has only grown since the last presidential election, in large</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient released in San Antonio later tested positive...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/health/cdc-mistakenly-releases-coronavirus-patient/5978121/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC says the patient had two negative tests, warranting a release, but a third test came back positive after the patient was gone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIRST CASE FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/florida-politics/buzz/2020/03/02/first-patients-in-florida-test-positive-for-coronavirus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The patients are in Hillsborough and Manatee Counties, Gov. Ron DeSantis announced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Discover Second Type Of Schizophrenia...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/groundbreaking-study-reveals-second-type-of-schizophrenia/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time ever, two distinct neuroanatomical variations of schizophrenia have been identified, according to a new study.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Teams Race to Catch Up...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/cdc-teams-race-to-catch-up-to-spread-of-coronavirus-in-us/ar-BB10BA4f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entire UK cities could be placed on lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/coronavirus-entire-uk-cities-could-21612813 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Matt Hancock yesterday refused to rule out putting British cities on lockdown, in an echo of how China looked to first contain the virus to its Wuhan epicentre</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JUDGE JUDY' Ending After 25 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/judge-judy-ending-25-seasons-new-show-judy-justice-works-1282015</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The court show will continue to air in reruns as the host takes on a new series.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marines drink blood of beheaded cobras, chomp on tarantulas and scorpions as they learn survival skills...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8063555/US-Marines-war-games-exercise-teaches-survive-Thai-jungle.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual Cobra Gold military exercise got underway in Thailand on Tuesday, which saw US troops undergo a series of grueling and garish tasks all in the name of survival.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming videos show Iranians LICKING holy shrines in religious tradition...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8063267/Videos-Iranians-LICKING-holy-shrines-despite-coronavirus-outbreak.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worrying clips on social media show people licking the doors and the burial mound inside the Masumeh shrine in virus-hit Qom, northern Iran.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOMBERG TO SPEND BILLION</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mike-bloomberg-2020-democratic-presidential-candidate-60-minutes-2020-03-01/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mike Bloomberg entered the race for the presidency late in the game, but his seemingly bottomless wallet has made him a contender. Scott Pelley talks with the former New York City mayor about the issues facing the country and what he offers to voters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to hear high-stakes abortion case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-supreme-court-hear-high-stakes-abortion-case-021057690.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The future of abortion in the United States could be at stake when the Supreme Court on Wednesday hears what may be its most significant case on the controversial subject in decades. At issue is a state law in Louisiana which requires doctors who perform abortions to have admitting privileges at a nearby</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing pope cancels retreat...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pope-francis-cancels-planned-retreat-due-cold-190702327.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pope Francis said Sunday he was cancelling a planned six-day spiritual retreat south of Rome after coming down with a "cold". "Unfortunately, a cold forced me not to take part this year," the 83-year-old pontiff said after coughing a couple of times during his weekly Sunday appearance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police clash with French islanders fearing coronavirus among tourists...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/police-clash-french-islanders-fearing-coronavirus-among-tourists-193238500.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saint-Denis de la Reunion (AFP) - Police used tear gas on protesting residents of France's Indian Ocean territory Reunion Island on Sunday who tried to block passengers of a cruise ship turned away from nearby Madagascar for fear there may be people infected with the coronavirus on board. The incident</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Miracle cure' rabbi charged with fraud...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/israeli-miracle-cure-rabbi-charged-fraud-195300884.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An 82-year-old Israeli rabbi, head of an ultra-Orthodox Jewish sect, was charged Sunday with incitement to violence and fraud over alleged miracle cures. Eliezer Berland, head of the Shouvou Banim sect within the Breslov Hasidic community, was arrested on February 9. In a video shown on Israeli television</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global death toll tops 3,000 as South Korea cases soar...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/global-virus-death-toll-tops-3-000-south-024847426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The global death toll from the new coronavirus epidemic surpassed 3,000 on Monday after more people died at its epicentre in China, as cases soared around the world and US officials faced criticism over the country's readiness for an outbreak. The virus has now infected more than 88,000 people and</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mired in stalemate, Israel holds another election on Netanyahu's future...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200301232454-cn6t0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-ELECTION/ (PIX):Mired in stalemate, Israel holds another election on Netanyahu's future</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPER:  Weinstein pushing to stay in hospital, dodge prison time until sentencing...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/476080/harvey-weinstein-hospital-new-york-rikers-island-jail/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARVEY Weinstein is allegedly trying to get officials to let him stay in the hospital until his sentencing hearing this month instead of going to Rikers Island prison. A source close to the disgrac…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paranoid militia infiltrating Texas police...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/politics-government/article240714426.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nursing Home Fear...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/01/us/washington-coronavirus-nursing-home.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials see growing indications that the virus has been spreading undetected in the Seattle suburbs for weeks. Two confirmed cases at a nursing facility have made Kirkland, Wash., a point of concern.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pride and fear among Jews as Sanders and Bloomberg battle for historic nomination...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/white-house/article240688981.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passanger recounts ordeal on Diamond Princess...</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/health/2020/03/01/detroit-woman-diamond-princess-cruise-quarantine-coronavirus-covid-19/4891872002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She left her Detroit home excited forÂ a two-week cruise, but Rosalind McDavid had no idea she was steppingÂ intoÂ a nightmare she still hasn't escaped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZANDI:  'Significant threat' to re-election...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/01/coronavirus-is-significant-threat-to-economy-and-trump-mark-zandi.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moody's Analytics Mark Zandi warns Wall Street is underestimating the economic damage from a coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIGHTMARE:  How one businesswoman's flight to China ended in quarantine...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/01/businesswoman-quarantined-in-beijing-over-coronavirus-says-be-prepared.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Businesswoman Bian Jingjing has a message about the coronavirus to the world: be more prepared.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negative U.S. Yields Are in Sight...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/negative-u-yields-sight-virus-230308295.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The swirl of fresh coronavirus cases and signs of the severity of the hit on the global economy have seasoned strategists warning that U.S. growth could come to a halt this year and some Treasury yields may drop below zero -- possibly as early as this week.The warnings come as a rout in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOE MO</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d3571eab8c1c839bd3dd54e39c693d64</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SELMA, Ala. (AP) — An emboldened Joe Biden tried to cast himself as the clear moderate alternative to progressive Bernie Sanders on Sunday as the Democrats' shrinking presidential field raced...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETE OUT</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9a141437992adacfa6dfa04c4e197b86</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Pete Buttigieg, who rose from being an Indiana mayor to a barrier-breaking, top-tier candidate for the Democratic presidential nomination, ended his campaign on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addresses flock from window...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200301102509-eofj0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE-HEALTH/ (PIX, TV):Pope makes first public appearance following illness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madonna bursts into tears trying to walk during concert...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/11067326/madonna-tears-fall-off-chair-paris/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MADONNA burst into tears and struggled to stand after falling off a chair during her Madame X gig in Paris. The Queen of Pop, 61, had to be helped up by one of her dancers after the accident at Le …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rumors and chaos in Alabama point to big problems...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/business/article/Coronavirus-rumors-and-chaos-in-Alabama-point-to-15096757.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ANNISTON, Ala. - Not long before local leaders decided, in the words of one of them, that federal health officials "didn't know what they were doing" with their plan to quarantine novel coronavirus patients in town, a doctor here set out in a biohazard suit to stage a one-man protest along the highway with a sign. "The virus has arrived. Are you ready?" it asked.  The town didn't think it was. Residents already were unnerved by strange stories posted on Facebook and shared via text messages about helicopters secretly flying in sick patients, that the virus was grown in a Chinese lab, that someone - either the media or the government - was lying to them about what was really going on.  The quarantine plan hastily hatched by the federal Department of Health and Human Services was soon scrapped by President Donald Trump, who faced intense pushback from Alabama's congressional delegation, led by Republican Rep. Mike Rogers. Americans evacuated after falling ill aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship in Japan would not be coming to Anniston, a town of 22,000 people in north-central Alabama, after all. They would remain in the same Texas and California sites where they were taken after leaving the cruise ship.  What happened here over the pastweek illustrates how poor planning by federal health officials and a rumor mill fueled by social media, polarized politics and a lack of clear communication can undermine public confidence in the response to the novel coronavirus, which causes the disease named covid-19. The rapidly spreading virus has rattled economies worldwide in recent weeks and caused the deaths of more than 2,900 people, mostly in China.  The panic and problems that burned through Anniston also provided a preview of what could unfold in other communities, as the spread of the virus is considered by health experts...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DELTA suspends flights...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/475476/coronavirus-delta-airlines-suspend-flights-milan-jfk/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DELTA is suspending its daily flight between New York’s JFK ariport and Milan Malpensa Airport for two months amid the killer coronavirus outbreak. The airline announced the drastic measure t…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uighurs sent to work in factory that supplies NIKE...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/asia/uighur-muslim-china-xinjiang-factory-nike-shoe-apple-dell-volkswagen-a9366956.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Greek village, tensions escalating between refugees and locals...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/03/01/refugee-crisis-in-greece-tensions-soar-between-migrants-and-locals.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Residents of Moria, a village on the Greek island of Lesvos â€” a holding station for refugees from the Middle East and Africa seeking asylum in the EU â€” are fearing their safety as living conditions deteriorate and crime escalates due to a backlog of cases and closed borders in the North.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steyer spent $3,373 per vote -- earned zero delegates!</title>
      <link>https://californiaglobe.com/featured-storeis/was-tom-steyers-campaign-the-worst-in-presidential-history/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;californiaglobe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus spreads to over 60 countries; France closes the Louvre...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/fd006734bacfb34a9dba966694359e5f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The number of countries hit by the coronavirus climbed past 60 Sunday, and infections and deaths continued to mount around the globe, emptying streets of tourists and workers, shaking...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
