<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>OPPOSING ARMED MILITIAS CONVERGE IN LOUISVILLE</title>
      <link>https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/local/2020/07/25/louisville-protests-nfac-three-percenters-expected-demonstrate/3288198001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courier-journal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFAC, which is a Black militia that stands for "Not F**king Around Coalition," said it is coming to demand justice for Breonna Taylor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCLAIR pulls show featuring Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/25/media/sinclair-pulls-fauci-conspiracy-segment/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Sinclair Broadcast Group said Saturday it will postpone and rework a segment it planned to air this weekend that suggested Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation's top infectious disease expert, was responsible for the creation of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign told to STOP using Reagan to raise money...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/RNC-Trump-campaign-told-to-stop-using-President-15434408.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation and Institute formally asked the Trump campaign and the Republican National Committee to stop using the 40th president's name and image to raise money.  The request came in response to a fundraising appeal sent from the Trump Make America Great Again Committee, a joint effort of the Trump campaign and the RNC, offering two commemorative coins, one engraved with Reagan's image and the other with that of President Donald Trump to anyone who donates $45 or more for Trump's reelection. The email was "signed" by Trump.  Melissa Giller, the Reagan Foundation's chief marketing officer, told Washington Post columnist Karen Tumulty that the request to cease sales of the coins was made by phone to the RNC last week. Giller said the RNC agreed "within seconds" to stop using Reagan to solicit funds for Trump's reelection.  The foundation, which runs the Reagan Presidential Library near Los Angeles, was provided sole rights of the use of Reagan and his wife's names and images. While the foundation can't stop every time the Reagans' likenesses are used, it claims the right to stop groups from using them for political or commercial gain.  Giller told Tumulty that although the RNC agreed to the demand, there are likely coins that were already sold and many people saw the fundraising email that suggests an association between the 40th and 45th presidents, which might require further legal action.  Frederick J. Ryan Jr., who chairs the Reagan Foundation board, is also publisher and CEO of The Washington Post.  RNC communications director Michael Ahrens said in an emailed statement to The Post that the foundation's "objection came as a surprise" but that it would "stop emailing this fundraising solicitation as a courtesy."  Trump has often invoked...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STANDOFF WITH FEDS IN PORTLAND CONTINUES</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9c7992fc9cd4062ccf32f616cb5bb7f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Federal agents again repeatedly fired tear gas to break up rowdy protests in Portland, Oregon, that continued into the early morning Saturday as demonstrations that have...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIOT SEATTLE</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c9149f66e43442eb04df4932932b7bcb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SEATTLE (AP) — Seattle police declared a riot Saturday following large demonstrations in the city's Capitol Hill neighborhood and deployed flash bangs and pepper spray to try to clear an area near...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient teeth show that epidemics began much further back in history...</title>
      <link>https://www.thehour.com/news/article/Ancient-teeth-show-that-epidemics-began-much-15434108.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thehour.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the novel coronavirus pandemic reshapes lives and entire economies, historians tell us this is not the first time. The earliest written records of tiny infectious organisms overhauling human societies stretch back as far as the Plague of Justinian in A.D. 541, which is thought to have killed up to 50 million people, or even the earlier Antonine Plague in A.D. 165, which left 5 million dead, a substantial portion of the world then.  Now, paleogenomics - a nascent field that studies DNA in remnants of ancient teeth - is rewriting the first chapter of humanity's entanglement with disease to thousands of years older than originally thought. The growing evidence suggests that these first epidemics forced societies to make epoch-defining transformations.  "In the case of covid-19 [the disease caused by the coronavirus], we see similar processes, but we are watching it unfold in real time," said Anne Stone, regents professor in the School of Human Evolution and Social Change at Arizona State University, whose focus is anthropological genetics. She also has studied evidence of tuberculosis in ancient DNA.  Paleogenomics, which adapts high-end medical tools similar to some now being used to track the coronavirus, has amounted to a "revolution" in understanding disease history, says Maria Spyrou, a microbiologist at the Max Planck Institute in Germany.  "This is one of the things that we can now start saying," said Spyrou, adding that where historical records are lacking, DNA evidence offers the possibility of filling in gaps, sometimes in surprising ways.  "One of them is plague," Spyrou said. "Until 2015, we thought that plague was maybe a 3,000-year-old disease."  Scientists and archaeologists now believe, however, that the plague bacteria, which caused the medieval Black Death that killed up to half of Europe's population,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he 'often' regrets his tweets and retweets...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1196623/donald-trump-regrets-tweets-dave-portnoy-barstool/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump said he often regrets what he posts on Twitter as he revealed that he may never tweet again come November. In a revealing interview with Dave Portnoy of Barstool Sports on Thursday, Tr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP's pleas to RNC for financial help go unanswered... </title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/House-GOP-s-pleas-to-Republican-National-15433714.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - Senior House Republicans are pleading with the deep-pocketed Republican National Committee and the Trump campaign to provide financial help as Democrats vastly outraise the GOP, but top campaign officials are so far declining to commit.  House Minority Leader Kevin McCarthy, R-Calif., has been prodding the RNC to write a check to the National Republican Congressional Committee - a request he has made multiple times. McCarthy specifically has asked Jared Kushner, President Trump's son-in-law and senior adviser, to make a financial commitment to the House GOP, according to several officials familiar with the discussions, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to freely describe private conversations.  But Kushner, who oversees such decisions and has a greater say than RNC Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel, has refused thus far, the officials say. While the Trump campaign and the RNC have brought in record amounts of money, some Trump officials see donating to the House as a wasteful investment as the GOP's chances of reclaiming the majority sharply deteriorate. Their decline in fortunes can largely be attributed to Trump's sagging support over his handling of the coronavirus pandemic and the sliding economy.  "The campaign just wants the money. . . . They don't care about the House - it's not their concern," one official close with the Trump campaign said. "When you've been working in politics for years, and you understand it's a team sport, you kind of look at these things a little differently. I don't think they see it that way."  Trump has been raking in unprecedented amounts of cash - though presumptive Democratic nominee Joe Biden outraised him the past two months. The president's fundraising committees and the RNC entered July with a whopping $295 million on hand, which is more than twice the $144 million that...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infects your nose first...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/coronavirus/article244473917.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG TECH CEO HILL GRILL SET FOR WEDNESDAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/07/25/big-tech-hearing-bezos-zuckerberg-381448</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first joint congressional appearance by the chief executives of the four powerful tech companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dilemma of Covid's Second Wave...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-dilemma-of-covid-19s-second-wave/ar-BB17aqJ2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump praises DeSantis' despite record deaths in Florida...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/trump-praises-desantis-despite-record-covid-19-deaths-in-florida-canceled-gop-convention/ar-BB17byIu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virus and mail-in voting will mean an accelerated 2020 election...</title>
      <link>https://www.mcclatchydc.com/news/politics-government/election/campaigns/article244467957.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mcclatchydc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA:  More than 1,000 deaths for fourth day in row...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/coronavirus-update-us-counts-more-than-1000-fatalities-for-a-fourth-straight-day-as-virus-spread-accelerates-in-south-and-west-2020-07-25</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The coronavirus illness COVID-19 claimed another 1,100 lives in the U.S. in a single day to push the death toll above 145,000 on Saturday, marking a fourth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regis Philbin Dies At 88...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/regis-philbin-iconic-tv-host-dead-at-88-138303</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former 'Live! with Regis and Kelly' host's family released a statement following his death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston, Miami, other cities face mounting care worker shortages...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Houston-Miami-other-cities-face-mounting-health-15433996.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shortages of health care workers are worsening in Houston, Miami, Baton Rouge and other cities battling sustained covid-19 outbreaks, exhausting staffers and straining hospitals' ability to cope with spiking cases.  That need is especially dire for front-line nurses, respiratory therapists and others who play hands-on, bedside roles where one nurse is often required for each critically ill patient.  While many hospitals have devised ways to stretch material resources - converting surgery wards into specialized covid units and recycling masks and gowns - it is far more difficult to stretch the human workers needed to make the system function.  "At the end of the day, the capacity for critical care is a balance between the space, staff and stuff. And if you have a bottleneck in one, you can't take additional patients," said Mahshid Abir, a senior physician policy researcher at the RAND Corporation and director of the Acute Care Research Unit (ACRU) at the University of Michigan. "You have to have all three . . . You can't have a ventilator, but not a respiratory therapist."  "What this is going to do is it's going to cost lives, not just for covid patients, but for everyone else in the hospital," she warned.  The increasingly fraught situation reflects packed hospitals across large swaths of the country: More than 8,800 covid patients are hospitalized in Texas; Florida has more than 9,400; and at least 13 other states also have thousands of hospitalizations, according to data compiled by The Washington Post.  Facilities in several states, including Texas, South Carolina and Indiana, have in recent weeks reported shortages of such workers, according to federal planning documents viewed by The Post, pitting states and hospitals against one another to recruit staff.  On...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COOK REPORT:   DEMS COULD SWEEP IT ALL...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/the-blue-wave-keeps-growing-d4d45832-d5f2-4d77-8fc8-20e6fe19a1cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Right now, every measurable trend is going against Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK quarantines travellers from Spain in major blow to Europe's revival...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200725183049-n4hcl</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/BRITAIN-SPAIN (UPDATE 5, PIX):UPDATE 5-UK quarantines travellers from Spain in major blow to Europe's revival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HURRICANE WATCH HAWAII</title>
      <link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2020/07/25/breaking-news/douglas-remains-category-2-hurricane-overnight-as-it-heads-toward-hawaii-kauai-under-tropical-storm-watch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.staradvertiser.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's richest looking to buy access to citizenship in safe havens...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-rich-are-looking-to-buy-access-to-covid-safe-havens/ar-BB16Y5PR</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots that kill Covid in 10 minutes unleashed in hospitals...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/robots-kill-viruses-10-minutes-22415385</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The £71,000 roaming robots are the latest cutting edge technology to be employed by the frontline in the Covid-19 battle. The huge wheeling machines will be vital according to NHS nurses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local TV stations across nation to air Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/07/24/media/sinclair-fauci-conspiracy-bolling/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Local television stations owned by the Sinclair Broadcast Group are set to air a conspiracy theory over the weekend that suggests Dr. Anthony Fauci, the nation's top expert on infectious diseases, was responsible for the creation of the coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supporters follow his pandemic cues...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-coronavirus-cues-90af5c46-f341-426b-b115-d8e30eb6ca86.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Republicans' shifts in thinking and behavior weren't immediate, often manifesting in a week or so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents fret over back-to-school decisions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/2da549f1cbee9f90cca60751cd32871e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joshua Claybourn is leaning toward sending his kindergarten daughter to in-person classes at a private school next month. Holly Davis’ sixth-grade daughter will learn online, though the family has...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local TV stations across nation to air Fauci conspiracy theory...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/jul/25/sinclair-tv-stations-fauci-plandemic-conspiracy-theory</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sinclair stations to run interview with Plandemic researcher who claims infectious disease expert created the coronavirus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Shut it down now:' Health experts call for 2nd lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/6334320/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 150 doctors endorsed an open letter to lawmakers, urging them to hit the restart button.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEETWOOD MAC Peter Green dead at 73...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tvandshowbiz/12223552/peter-green-dead-fleetwood-mac/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FLEETWOOD Mac co-founder Peter Green has died aged 73. His family said the music legend passed away peacefully in his sleep in a statement through solicitors. The statement from Swan Turton solicit…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Message Behind Gold's Rally: World Economy Is in Trouble...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/message-behind-gold-rally-world-130000487.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- It’s easy to forget now but there was a time early on in the pandemic when the price of gold was in freefall.It was a curious thing, what with the virus sparking a collapse in the global economy, and it would prove in time to be one of the great head-fakes in the recent history of financial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President talks up his rule-cutting, but courts saying otherwise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/5eb5095c22f1f2796c4b78ef9ce8fc1a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is positioning himself as a champion regulation-cutter in the leadup to the Nov. 3 election, but in between his showy red-tape-cutting events, his...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young Have Used 33% Of Total Savings During Pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.zerohedge.com/markets/young-americans-have-used-33-their-total-savings-during-covid-19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.zerohedge.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former DISNEY Actress: How Porn Saved Me From Hollywood...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/maitland-ward-how-porn-saved-me-from-hollywood</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former “Boy Meets World” star writes about how the world of adult film gave her the opportunities and freedom to be herself that Hollywood wouldn’t.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Lived in Shipping Container to Simulate Life on Mars'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/i-lived-in-a-shipping-container-to-simulate-life-on-mars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No matter how much you prepare, the isolation that comes with living this way always has effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's richest looking to buy access to citizenship in safe havens...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/global-economics/the-rich-are-looking-to-buy-access-to-covid-safe-havens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next time the worldâ€™s rich are forced into lockdown, they would like to have an escape ready to a remote and sunny beach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black armed militia planning Louisville march claims it's 'Not F---ing Around'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/us/black-armed-militia-planning-louisville-march-claims-its-not-f-ing-around</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Grand Master Jay, head of the “Not F---ing Around Coalition,” refers to the U.S. Constitution when talking about his Black armed militia group, which plans to march in Louisville, Ky., on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARBUCKS Customer Breaks Barista's Jaw After Asked To Cover Up...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2020/07/24/starbucks-barista-assault-mask-tip-jar-theft/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to the Los Angeles County Sheriff’s Department, a man punched a barista when employees asked him to put on a mask as he entered the coffee shop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do not plant!</title>
      <link>https://www.wdbj7.com/2020/07/24/got-seeds-you-didnt-ask-for-dont-plant-them-report-them/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wdbj7.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The packages were sent by mail and may have Chinese writing on them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOWD: Musk, Blasting Off in Domestic Bliss...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2020/07/25/style/elon-musk-maureen-dowd.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The billionaire space oddity on life with Grimes and Baby X, Trump, Tesla, tunnels, short shorts, stock surges, Facebook fumbles and everything else under the sun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Rice advantage: Long work history with Joe...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Susan-Rice-s-advantage-A-long-work-history-with-15433160.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON --- In the Oval Office many mornings, as Joe Biden sat in a chair nextto President Barack Obama, Susan Rice would take her usual spot on a nearby couch and brief them on sensitive national security issues. At other times in the Situation Room, Rice and Biden would sit directly across the table from one another, according to people with knowledge of the setup.  As vice president, Biden would pop into Rice's neighboring office in the White House for some light banter with the national security adviser - or heavier talk about the difficult issues confronting the Obama administration.  Years later, that relationship has made Rice an unlikely finalist to become Biden's running mate and the first African American woman on a major party ticket, according to people with knowledge of the process and other Biden allies. She has never been elected to political office but has a credential none of her rivals can boast: a lengthy history as Biden's colleague at the highest levels of government.  "Biden spent years essentially beginning his day with a briefing from Susan Rice," said former Obama deputy national security adviser Ben Rhodes. "So he definitely knows her."  Biden has frequently said he is looking for a running mate with whom he is "simpatico" and that he aspires to re-create the dynamic he shared with Obama, to whom he was a friend and adviser. That could cut both ways for Rice, who disagreed with Biden on some key foreign policy issues during Obama's first term, when she served as U.N. ambassador, but also forged a kinship with him, particularly once she moved to the White House in 2013, according to colleagues.  Rice has been a frequent guest on television news shows in recent months, impressing Biden allies who were unsure how she would fare under heightened public scrutiny. To broaden her public persona...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'wall' of military veterans protect protesters in Portland...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/07/25/new-wall-of-military-veterans-protect-protesters-in-portland/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, there was a “wall” of moms protecting Portland protesters — now there’s a wall of vets doing the same. A group of military veterans joined protesters in the city for the fi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record numbers of coronavirus cases in EVERY global region...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200725054201-qtbam</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-CORONAVIRUS/GLOBAL-CASES (PIX):Record numbers of coronavirus cases in every global region - Reuters tally</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Era of Sickness, Doctors Prescribe Unusual Cure: Voting...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/07/25/in-era-of-sickness-doctors-prescribe-unusual-cure-voting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BOSTON — The sign is easy to miss in the waiting room of the emergency department at Massachusetts General Hospital,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protests Swell in Russia's Far East in Stark New Challenge to Putin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/mass-anti-kremlin-rallies-grip-russia-s-far-east/ar-BB17aGR9?li=BBnbcA1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
