<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Genetic risk factor found for smell, taste loss...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/science/science-news/genetic-risk-factor-found-covid-19-smell-taste-loss-researchers-say-rcna11996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Scientists are piecing together why some people lose their sense of smell after contracting Covid-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand Miami Beach Hotel, and Its History, Might Be Torn Down...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/17/a-grand-miami-beach-hotel-and-its-history-might-be-torn-down/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI BEACH — The baby-faced Beatles spent nine sun-kissed days in Miami Beach in 1964, basking in the warm winter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Netanyahu agrees to 'moral turpitude' in potential plea deal...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/liveblog_entry/reports-netanyahu-agrees-to-moral-turpitude-in-potential-plea-deal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;* * *</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA WARRIORS Owner: Nobody Cares About Uyghurs...</title>
      <link>https://www.realclearpolitics.com/video/2022/01/17/owner_of_the_golden_state_warriors_chamath_palihapitiya_nobody_cares_about_whats_happening_to_the_uyghurs.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.realclearpolitics.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chamath Palihapitiya, the CEO of "Social Capital" and owner of the Golden State Warriors basketball team, told the "All-In" podcast that "nobody cares" about the ethnic cleansing of Uyghur Muslims in East Turkestan by the Chinese Communist Party.  "If you're asking me if I care about a segment of a class of people in another country, not until we can take care of ourselves will I prioritize them over us," he said.  Social Capital's website states: "Our mission is to advance humanity by solving the world's hardest problems. We partner with companies at every stage of their business, for as long as it takes." "It's a nice thing that you care, but nobody else cares." "I'm telling you a hard, ugly truth. Of all the things I care about, it is below my line," Palihapitiya said. "I care about the fact that our economy could turn on a line if China invades Taiwan. I care about that. I care about climate change. I care about America's crippling and decrepit healthcare infrastructure. But if you're asking me if I care about a segment of a class of people in another country, not until we can take care of ourselves will I prioritize them over us." "I'm sorry if that's a hard truth to hear, but every time I say I care about the Uyghurs, I m really just lying." Hat tip:  Billionaire @chamath "nobody cares about what's happening to the Uyghurs" Palihapitiya https://t.co/S3hZ584UoO pic.twitter.com/mlh2sBhGd9-- Timothy Pereira (@TimoPG) January 15, 2022</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Were Authorities So Evasive About Gunman's Motive?</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalreview.com/corner/why-were-authorities-so-evasive-about-the-synagogue-gunmans-motive/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalreview.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Why were President Biden and the FBI so reluctant to say that the synagogue gunman was motivated by antisemitism and jihadism?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joss Whedon Denies Misconduct Claims, Says Gal Gadot Misunderstood...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/entertainment/joss-whedon-denies-misconduct-claims-says-gal-gadot-misunderstood-him-english-is-not-her-first-language/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmmaker Joss Whedon has broken his silence on the allegations of misconduct launched against him last year, directly responding to Justice League's Gal Gadot and Ray Fisher.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico president says he's beaten Covid for 2nd time...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220117-mexico-president-says-he-s-beaten-covid-for-second-time</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican President Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador said Monday that he had recovered from a second bout of Covid-19, as he resumed his public activities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Djokovic now banned from French Open?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sport/sportsnews/article-10410441/Novak-Djokovic-faces-banned-French-Open-May.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The French Open is the next Slam in the tennis calendar taking place in May and Djokovic was expected to participate without complication - but the new Covid Pass has changed that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pandemic depletes collection plates at churches nationwide...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-churches-financial-difficulty/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We're surviving. … But we have felt the hurt," said one pastor in Nashville, Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel trial, world's first, finds 4th dose 'not good enough'...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-trial-worlds-first-finds-4th-dose-not-good-enough-against-omicron/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Expert at Sheba Medical Center says jab raises COVID antibody levels, but there are ‘still a lot of infections’ among those who received it</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympics tickets will not be sold to general public due to Covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/17/sport/winter-olympics-china-tickets-covid-19-spt-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tickets for the upcoming Winter Olympic and Paralympic Games in Beijing will not be sold to the general public in response to Covid-19 but will instead be distributed by authorities, the Beijing Winter Olympics Organizing Committee announced Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cop grabs female officer by throat after she pulls him off suspect...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/17/florida-cop-grabs-female-officer-by-the-throat-after-she-pulled-him-off-suspect/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to footage, Christopher Pullease whipped around, grabbed hold of the officer’s neck and shoved her against another patrol car after trying to pepper spray a suspect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City Overrun by Crows. Could Laser Be the Answer?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-california-city-is-overrun-by-crows-could-a-laser-be-the-answer/ar-AASS2mv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman takes selfie from car sinking through ice in river...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/canada/unfazed-woman-takes-selfie-from-her-car-sinking-through-the-ice-in-rideau-river</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyson agrees to fight Jake Paul...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/sport/boxing/4480624/mike-tyson-jake-paul-exhibition-boxing-fight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIKE TYSON is in advanced talks with YouTuber Jake Paul about a big money exhibition fight in Las Vegas, Sun Online can reveal. Tyson and Paul’s reps are thrashing out plans for a headline pa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brady Super Bowl title defense off to roaring start...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/2021-nfl-playoffs-what-we-learned-from-buccaneers-win-over-eagles-on-super-wild-</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reigning Super Bowl champions began their title defense Sunday in emphatic fashion. Tom Brady and the Buccaneers scored the game’s first 31 points en route to a 31-15 victory over the Eagles to advance to the NFC Divisional Round.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Covid restrictions ruined old people's lives...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/what-lockdown-took-from-my-parents/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid restrictions stole their right to choose</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is humanity running out of time?</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2022/01/how-long-can-humans-survive/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This time of plenty won't last for ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid-test vending machines popping up at universities...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/coronavirus/article257382232.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A self-serve testing program became a pivotal part of our efforts to preserve the health and safety of our campus,” University of Utah spokesperson Rebecca Walsh said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pastor rubs spit over brother's face to show 'visions from God' during sermon...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/pastor-rubs-spit-over-brothers-25969140</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oklahoma pastor Michael Todd tried to show the idea of receiving visions from God, but some worshippers found it disturbing when he rubbed his spit on his brother's face</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calf born with three eyes, four nostrils; People line up to worship cow...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/rare-calf-born-three-eyes-25969723</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A three-eyed cow born in India has been dubbed a "divine miracle" and a reincarnation of Hindu God, Shiva, with a veterinary doctor saying it is not Viswanatha but an abnormal embryo development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill  paints herself as national 'healer'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-joe-biden-health-lifestyle-jill-biden-137925163af00545a3dbeace1ccc4812</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LAS VEGAS (AP) — Her husband campaigned to help unite the country , but Jill Biden says “healing” a nation wounded by a deadly pandemic , natural and other disasters and deep political polarization is among her chief roles as first lady, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'60 MINS' Segment on Anne Frank Identifies Likely Suspect Who Outed in Hiding...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/60-minutes-segment-on-anne-frank-identifies-likely-suspect-who-outed-them-in-hiding/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS’ 60 Minutes aired a segment on Sunday about who may have outed on Anne Frank and her family while they were hiding from the Nazis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In ancient rite, Spanish horses brave fire to fight virus...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20220117-in-ancient-rite-spanish-horses-brave-fire-to-fight-virus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At full gallop, the horse emerges from the darkness and races through a string of bonfires in an ancient ritual to ward off sickness performed every January in a tiny Spanish village.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buying Frenzy Leaves Canada With Fewest Homes for Sale on Record...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/record-year-leaves-canada-with-fewest-homes-for-sale-on-record</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Record Year Leaves Canada With Fewest Homes for Sale on Record</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks on Jewish community on rise long before Colleyville...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/attacks-on-americas-jewish-community-on-the-rise-long-before-colleyville-experts-say/ar-AASRg9r?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLACEBO Are Done With Being Fetishised...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/akv7v4/placebo-never-let-me-go-album-interview</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“We were just trying to express ourselves in the way that we needed to – which was cross-dressing and wearing makeup.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 In 3 People Have Never Completed New Year's Resolution...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/new-years-resolution-2022/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A survey of 2,000 adults reveals that of those who’ve previously set New Year's resolutions, 68 percent have never fully achieved one.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noem on Political Rocket Ship. Don't Rule Out Crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/17/kristi-noem-covid-politician-527080</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Covid made South Dakota’s governor a Republican star. What happens to a pandemic politician after the pandemic?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Obscene inequality'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/17/oxfam-on-covid-inequality-tax-rich-to-pay-for-vaccines-protect-climate.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The wealth of the world's ten richest men doubled from $700 billion to $1.5 trillion during the pandemic, the global charity said in a press release on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRAVEL HELL: 1,200 US flights canceled as winter storm pummels East Coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/17/business/winter-storm-flight-cancellations/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US airlines have canceled more than 1,200 flights Monday as a powerful winter storm packing rain, sleet and snow slammed the East Coast on the holiday weekend and made travel difficult. On Sunday, roughly 3,000 flights were canceled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GALLUP: Americans Shift Republican...</title>
      <link>https://news.gallup.com/poll/388781/political-party-preferences-shifted-greatly-during-2021.aspx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.gallup.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Although the U.S. political party affiliation average for 2021 was similar to prior years, the country shifted from a nine-point Democratic preference early in the year to a five-point Republican advantage near the end.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsession with morning routines dates back to Ben Franklin...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/our-obsession-with-morning-routines-dates-back-to-benjamin-franklin/ar-AASPK1Z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves snatching French bulldogs across USA...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/why-thieves-snatching-french-bulldogs-054130034.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The two thieves who brutally robbed 27-year-old Marieke Bayens at gunpoint on a California street were not after her purse -- or her. They wanted the little dog at the end of her leash: Merlyn, a French bulldog.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida looms large in Republican 2024 primary...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/589649-florida-looms-large-in-republican-2024-primary</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida is emerging as the epicenter of the early fight for the GOP presidential nomination as speculation grows about the possibility of as many as four Republicans from the Sunshine State pursuing the party's nod in 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO PACK DJOKOVIC; DEPORTED FROM OZ...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-novak-djokovic-sports-entertainment-health-d736b70771525c190c1c58bb447b6b95</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — Novak Djokovic arrived early Monday in Dubai after his deportation from Australia over its required COVID-19 vaccination ended the No. 1-ranked men's tennis player's hopes of defending his Australian Open title.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran-backed Houthi rebels launch 'kamikaze drone' attack on Abu Dhabi...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/17347179/iran-houthi-rebels-drone-attack-abu-dhabi/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A DRONE attack on Abu Dhabi has led to three oil tankers exploding and a fire at the airport, police have said. Responsibility for the attack has been claimed by Yemen’s Iran-backed Houthi rebels w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's 10 richest men see wealth double during pandemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/business/2022/jan/17/world-10-richest-men-see-their-wealth-double-during-covid-pandemic</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oxfam calls for windfall tax as 99% of world population takes a pay cut while top 10 incomes grow by $1bn a day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside pioneering site authorized to monitor people using drugs...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/inside-a-pioneering-us-site-authorized-to-monitor-people-using-drugs/ar-AASONZX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trailblazing Arab lawmaker shakes up Israeli politics...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-middle-east-israel-tel-aviv-9f570e7d01677e59cba3652c07fa7c75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TEL AVIV, Israel (AP) — Mansour Abbas broke a longstanding taboo when he led his Arab party into Israel's governing coalition last year. The bold move appears to be paying dividends. Abbas, a once obscure politician, is the linchpin of the shaky union, securing hefty budgets and favorable policies for his constituents and even winning an audience with the king of Jordan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden puzzled by drones spotted over nuke power plants...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/business-europe-denmark-sweden-baltic-sea-2605c0d837b2a4b5ba43e89763841afc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COPENHAGEN, Denmark (AP) — Swedish authorities are puzzled by reports that drones last week were seen hovering over two nuclear power plants on the country's Baltic Sea coast. Police said Sunday that preliminary investigations have been launched, adding the probes are being handled locally by investigators but they are coordinated nationally by the Swedish police’s national operational department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pacific volcano erupts with explosive force, heard 5,000 miles away...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/how-the-tonga-volcano-generated-a-shock-wave-around-the-world/ar-AASQ9vj?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After years of threats, Congress finally unleashes subpoena power on Silicon Valley...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/after-years-of-threats-congress-finally-unleashed-its-subpoena-power-on-silicon-valley/ar-AASMFsM?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body temperature may not really gauge covid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/body-temperature-may-not-be-an-effective-gauge-of-covid-19/ar-AASPuVE?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brit named in Tex Terror...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/texas-synagogue-hostages-e6087528c4728c418ee6872f13778b71</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLLEYVILLE, Texas (AP) — A rabbi who was among four people held hostage at a Texas synagogue said Sunday that their armed captor grew “increasingly belligerent and threatening” toward the end of the 10-hour standoff, which ended with an FBI SWAT team rushing into the building and the captor's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Biden's first year, virus and disunity rage on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-one-year-07788eba2c1eb84de0edf3dbe3f2d412</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — From the inaugural platform, President Joe Biden saw American sickness on two fronts — a disease of the national spirit and the one from the rampaging coronavirus — and he saw hope, because leaders always must see that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Oath Keepers and founder, Jan. 6 was weeks in making...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/capitol-siege-oath-keepers-stewart-rhodes-0c30d5cb0724c623a27f2eb39da20285</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WILMINGTON, Del. (AP) — Two days after the election on Nov. 3, 2020, the Oath Keepers were already convinced that victory had been stolen from President Donald Trump and members of the far-right militia group were making plans to march on the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man wins lottery for the FOURTH time...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/money/4476369/man-wins-for-fourth-time-lottery-pennsylvania/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A MAN has scooped $1million this month in his FOURTH lottery win since 1999 – scoring a whopping $4.6million in total. Mike “Lucky” Luciano won his latest prize from a $20 scratch…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Year is It? Nearly Third of iTunes Chart Taken By Oldies...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2022/01/16/what-year-is-it-nearly-a-third-of-the-itunes-top-100-taken-by-oldies-new-releases-not-catching-on</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP DOGS 'DULL' DESANTIS</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/trump-privately-slams-desantis-ba0ce3aa-839f-41c9-83a1-4b9dc26649d9.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former president is irked by the Florida governor's popularity and refusal to rule out running against him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump AZ Speech Proves Shock Comic Act Has 'Jumped the Shark'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trumps-arizona-speech-proves-shock-170114287.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ROBYN BECK/AFP via Getty ImagesThere was a time when Donald Trump made news with his rallies—when he said things that utterly shocked us. Who could forget the firestorm he started, for example, when he went after Colin Kaepernick and other NFL players who knelt during the national anthem in 2017, or earlier that year when he called Barack Obama “the founder of ISIS”?Trump’s performance in Arizona on Saturday night—his first rally in months and his much-hyped chance to respond to the one-year ann</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From pandemic to endemic: Can 2022 succeed where 2021 failed?</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/world-news/from-pandemic-to-endemic-can-2022-succeed-where-2021-failed/articleshow/88914210.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The appetite for economically damaging lockdowns is long gone. Vaccines are protecting swathes of the population, and there is even hope that omicron, with its frenetic spread and less powerful punch, may be hastening the path to the pandemics exit.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
