<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>SPRINGSTEEN: Trump doesn't have grasp on what it means to be American...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bruce-springsteen-donald-trump-doesnt-have-a-grasp-on-what-it-means-to-be-american-gayle-king-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Legendary singer and songwriter says he isn't surprised the president is trash-talking him</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saudi Prince Behind $450 Million Da Vinci Also Buys Kusama Pumpkin...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/saudi-prince-behind-450-million-da-vinci-also-got-pumpkin-room</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saudi Prince Behind $450 Million Da Vinci Also BuysÂ Kusama Pumpkin</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surge in protests around the world in October...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/surge-protests-around-world-october-180230008.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paris (AFP) - The past weeks have seen a wave of often unprecedented protest movements erupt in countries around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Decade of Darkness' for Spurring Generator Windfall...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/decade-darkness-california-spurring-generator-222156000.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A “decade of darkness” in California is offering a huge opportunity for the sale of generators that keep the lights on when the power grid goes down.That’s the view of Aaron Jagdfeld, chief executive officer of Generac Holdings Inc., the Wisconsin-based maker of generators. Jagdfeld cited</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highest in 7 years...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/caeb6d6c4eff45e4bc5da12db06004bc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Trump administration reported a river of red ink Friday. The federal deficit for the 2019 budget year surged 26% from 2018 to $984.4 billion — its highest point in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Org selling DC hotel?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6223da94ab9e4a109ea92283cb18d4cd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump's company said Friday it is exploring the sale of its landmark Washington hotel after nearly three years of ethics complaints and lawsuits accusing him of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems seek more witnesses...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191025225804-n4h32</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/WHISTLEBLOWER (UPDATE 4, PIX, TV, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 4-U.S. House Democrats get legal boost, seek more witnesses in impeachment probe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  UK TELEGRAPH UP FOR SALE...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191025223604-lybnq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-DIVESTITURE/TELEGRAPH:Barclay family puts Telegraph newspapers up for sale -The Times</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In new blow to Mexico's crime fight, judge frees suspected cartel members...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191025220732-fyox3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO-VIOLENCE/TEPITO (PIX):In new blow to Mexico's crime fight, judge frees suspected cartel members</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major wildfires rage near Los Angeles and wineries north of San Francisco... Developing...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191025194124-4hha0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRE/ (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Major wildfires rage near Los Angeles and wineries north of San Francisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limited public hearings?</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191025175217-a8mn2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-TRUMP/WHISTLEBLOWER-HEARINGS (PIX):U.S. Democrats to limit witnesses in public impeachment hearings -sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP ACCUSES OBAMA OF TREASON...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/washington-secrets/trump-accuses-obama-of-treason-for-spying-on-his-2016-campaign</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump has ratcheted up his claim that the Obama White House spied on his 2016 campaign, charging in a new book that it was a “treasonous” act by the former Democratic president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT BEATS AMAZON TO PENTAGON CLOUD...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/25/microsoft-wins-major-defense-cloud-contract-beating-out-amazon.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The win is a boon for Microsoft's Azure cloud, which CEO Satya Nadella once led.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarming Survey Finds Children Often Begging Parents To Put Phones Away...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/role-reversal-children-often-begging-parents-to-put-phones-away/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey of 2,000 U.S. parents of school-aged children reveals that half of respondents have been asked by their own child to put their phone away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM Workers Approve Contract, End Strike...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/gm-workers-approve-contract-and-end-strike/ar-AAJliwk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive American Dream mall opens but will shoppers come?</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/df93ca8371994f7eb6344dde322b2de2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EAST RUTHERFORD, N.J. (AP) — More than two decades ago when a mega entertainment and shopping complex was being conceived on a vast swath of swamp land in New Jersey, the iPhone didn't exist,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area could go dark...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/Potential-PGE-shutoff-Alameda-Contra-Costa-14560986.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pacific Gas and Electric says another round of deliberate blackouts is likely beginning Saturday night with windy weather expected to kick up again. This wind event is expected to be more severe than the one overnight Wednesday, and the shutoff could impact a larger swatch of the Bay Area, including customers in Contra Costa and Alameda counties.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Chapo's son led dramatic rescue of his half brother in Mexico battle...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-violence-sinaloa/el-chapos-son-led-dramatic-rescue-of-his-half-brother-in-mexico-battle-idUSKBN1X42BV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivan Archivaldo Guzman, the leader of Los Chapitos wing of the Sinaloa Cartel, w...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electric scooters: France introduces new rules to 'restore tranquillity'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50189279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;E-scooters have been involved in hundreds of incidents, including several deaths.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldier opens fire in 'nervous breakdown,' kills 8 comrades...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/25/russian-soldier-opens-fire-in-nervous-breakdown-kills-8-comrades/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Russian Defense Ministry says a soldier killed eight of his comrades and wounded two others in a shooting outburst at a base in Siberia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cigarette smoking rises amid vaping-related panic...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/25/people-are-smoking-cigarettes-again-amid-vaping-related-panic/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the span of a couple months, smokers have begun to think of cigarettes not as “cancer sticks” — but a safer choice for a fix than vapes, users say. The dramatic shift comes as vaping…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare, Record-Breaking Thunder Snow Falls In TX...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/10/25/rare-record-breaking-thunder-snow-falls-in-amarillo/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five point five inches of snow fell, breaking the old record of a trace set in 1935.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Criticizes Pompeo after diplomat's damaging testimony...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/60f96f4bad9c42b587cbb37b3abe48be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump suggested Secretary of State Mike Pompeo made a mistake by hiring the senior diplomat who provided damaging testimony to impeachment investigators in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JUDGE: DOJ must turn over Mueller grand jury material to House Dems...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/25/judge-rules-doj-must-turn-over-mueller-grand-jury-material-to-house-democrats-000299</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World War 3 in space would 'destroy banking systems'...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2019/10/25/rare-record-breaking-thunder-snow-falls-in-amarillo/&gt;Rare, Record-Breaking Thunder Snow Falls In TX...&lt;/A&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;A HREF=</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biologically Male NCAA Runner Named Female Athlete Of The Week...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/10/25/transgender-athlete-week-june-eastwood-womens/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Big Sky Conference named University of Montana runner June Eastwood, a biological male who identifies as a transgender woman, the cross country female athlete of the week</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy butt-dials NBC reporter...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/rudy-giuliani-butt-dials-nbc-reporter-heard-discussing-need-cash-n1071901</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The problem is we need some money,” Giuliani says to unidentified man during accidental call to NBC News writer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinton ally Blumenthal sought to stop publication of Russia probe book...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/blumenthal-russia-probe-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clinton family associate Sidney Blumenthal has made legal threats to the publisher of a forthcoming book featuring allegations against Democrats in connection with the Russia investigation in an attempt to stop publication, Fox News has learned.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highest in 7 years!</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/25/federal-deficit-increases-26percent-to-984-billion-for-fiscal-2019.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gap between revenues and spending was the widest in seven years. Defense, Medicare and interest payments ballooned the shortfall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>But Trump critic gets 1st pitch at game Trump to attend...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cae0039ea0ae4fe59689a62007d29e8b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A day after President Donald Trump said he plans to attend Game 5 of the World Series, the Washington Nationals announced the ceremonial first pitch at that game will be thrown...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utility admits it may have ignited fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/c95a246226c2466a968add8bd2392820</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — California's biggest utility admitted its electrical equipment may have ignited a ruinous wildfire spreading over the state's wine country Friday, despite blackouts imposed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Artists, Fans Stopped Facial Recognition From Invading Music Festivals...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/evangreer/stop-facial-recognition-music-festivals-concerts</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The surveillance dystopia of our nightmares is not inevitable — and the way we kept it out of concerts and festivals is a lesson for the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House subpoenas 3 more administration officials...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d202b111a5e54860a42a3bd006d18e9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Impeachment investigators issued subpoenas Friday to three more Trump administration officials, demanding that they testify in the probe of President Donald Trump's efforts to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court documents:  FBI ambushed Michael Flynn, then celebrated...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/oct/25/fbi-ambushed-michael-flynn-then-celebrated/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI under James Comey “unilaterally” made the decision to interview retired Lt. Gen. Michael Flynn, excluding input from the Justice Department, ignoring the White House counsel and leading Flynn to believe agents were arriving as friends to discuss terrorism, his lawyer says.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World War 3 in space would 'destroy banking systems'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/tech/10212865/world-war-3-space-gps-banking-tv/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AT AN upcoming summit in early December, NATO is expected to declare space as a “warfighting domain”, partly in response to new developments in technology. If it does declare space a war zone, NATO…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Algorithm Can Predict Illness 48 Hours Before Symptoms Show...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/analytics-data/2019/10/military-algorithm-can-predict-illness-48-hours-symptoms-show/160851/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The program lead says future troops might be deployed with wearables like watches or chest straps that will know when they are getting sick and how long it will take them to get better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toddler vanishes underground after falling through manhole...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/toddler-vanishes-underground-after-falling-20720464  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The little girl was out walking in Tatarstan, Russia, when she stood on a metal lid which collapsed under her</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bear attacks trainer in front of stunned circus audience...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/bear-attacks-trainer-at-russian-circus</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials have opened a criminal investigation after a circus bear attacked and injured its trainer during a performance in northern Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We could investigate your personal life!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7614129</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kellyanne Conway argued she never threatened a reporter who wrote an article that mentioned her husband was a critic of Donald Trump, adding that if she threatened someone, they'd know it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton ready to talk?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/10/25/john-boltons-lawyers-are-in-contact-with-trump-impeachment-panels.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;John Bolton reportedly was so disturbed by efforts to get Ukraine to investigate President Trump's political opponents, including former Vice President Joe Biden, that he called it a "drug deal."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian Kurds: Turkey Continuing Its Genocide War Despite 'Ceasefire'...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/middle-east/2019/10/25/syrian-kurds-turkey-continuing-its-genocide-war-despite-ceasefire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Syrian Democratic Forces (SDF) condemned Turkey and its "allied terrorist factions" on Thursday for "continuing its genocide war."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLLS TURN UGLY...</title>
      <link>https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/trump-approval-ratings/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;projects.fivethirtyeight.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FiveThirtyEight is tracking Donald Trump’s approval ratings throughout his presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JESUS DELAYED:  Kanye cons his fans again -- and they've had enough...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/10/25/kanye-west-loses-more-fans-with-weird-jesus-is-king-movie-delayed-album/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ye has bamboozled the bejesus out of us — yet again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated gardener ushers in new era of 'robotony'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/automated-gardener-ushers-era-robotony-075113275.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With its whirring rotary blades and extendable cutting arm it would not look out of place stalking the streets of a futuristic urban dystopia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Just too darn old':   Sanders, Biden confront age concerns...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/8d03bf803438476c8b72ac6035248659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARSHALLTOWN, Iowa (AP) — Bernie Sanders insists he feels better than ever less than a month after heart surgery, but his return to the campaign trail this week sparked new questions about the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PENTAGON MOVES TO STOP ISIS FROM SYRIA OIL</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/334caccc941b40c99f0a6b9c40cd66cc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRUSSELS (AP) — The U.S. will send armored reinforcements into eastern Syria to bolster defenses against a potential move by Islamic State militants on oil fields controlled by U.S.-backed Syrian...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Melee at Oakland school board meeting as teachers jump security barrier, clash with cops...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-melee-at-oakland-school-board-meeting-as-teachers-jump-barrier-clash-with-cops/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Teachers and parents in Oakland are crying police brutality after they stormed a recent school board meeting to protest privatization and charter schools in the district. Oakland Unified School District officials erected metal barriers between the public and school board members ahead of a meeting Wednesday after several prior protests, but the temporary structures weren’t …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROGER WATERS: Punishing Assange sends warning to other journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/471834-roger-waters-assange-interview/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British rock legend and Pink Floyd frontman Roger Waters told RT that by going after WikiLeaks co-founder Julian Assange governments want to scare off journalists and whistleblowers from exposing the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSC official plans to testify even if White House tries to block...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/10/25/trump-impeachment-testimony-057257</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Has Harvey Weinstein Come Out if Hiding?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/why-is-harvey-weinstein-hiding-1249984</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It felt like this sad attempt to re-kindle his old life," says comedian Kelly Bachman of the disgraced mogul, who has been seen at multiple New York hotspots in recent weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPENDS $70M LOBBYING SINCE TRUMP TOOK OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/issues/soros-group-eclipses-70-million-spent-on-lobbying-since-trump-took-office/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Open Society Policy Center (OSPC), an advocacy group funded by billionaire George Soros, has now pushed more than $70 million into lobbying efforts since Donald Trump took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystery object that hit Kentucky home remains unidentified...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1e0275d2a0ff450489ecfa8a70ac26b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BURGIN, Ky. (AP) — The Federal Aviation Administration says a mysterious object that seemingly dropped from the sky and damaged a Kentucky man's mobile didn't come from an airplane. Tommy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACEBOOK BUYS OFF MEDIA AS INVESTIGATIONS HEAT... </title>
      <link>https://adage.com/article/digital/facebook-news-debuts-free-money-publishers/2209996</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;adage.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Social network launches its dedicated journalism section that pays media partners for 'high-quality' content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Battle Over Mona Lisa's Prettier 'Twin'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-secret-battle-over-mona-lisas-prettier-twin</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leonardo da Vinci’s famous Mona Lisa hangs in the Louvre. But a second, earlier painting is at the heart of a multi-million-dollar battle to prove its authenticity and ownership.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuca, foul-mouthed parrot, remains missing -- but her thief going to prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/crime/article236576418.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing army of immigrant voters stands in Trump path...</title>
      <link>https://www.heraldmailmedia.com/news/nation/as-trump-seeks-reelection-a-growing-army-of-immigrant-voters/article_7a88c9ac-8ee6-5211-938d-090eb61393a5.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.heraldmailmedia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOUSTON — This is where a nation changes: a public school auditorium that moonlights as a veritable citizenship factory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA TESTS DISCONNECTING FROM INTERNET</title>
      <link>https://www.defenseone.com/technology/2019/10/russia-will-test-its-ability-disconnect-internet/160861/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.defenseone.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nascent RuNet is meant to allow the country to survive an attack â€” and Putin to monitor and control the population.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More evacuations...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/10/25/tick-fire-jumps-14-freeway-after-multiple-flares-overnight/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Sig alert was issued early Friday morning closing all lanes of the 14 Freeway between Golden Valley and Escondido Canyon after a number of flare ups of the Tick fire erupted.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
