<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY' Chinese cut: No homosexuality, no frocks, no Aids...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/film/2019/mar/27/bohemian-rhapsody-chinese-cut-no-homosexuality-no-frocks-no-aids</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three minutes of censored footage from the Freddie Mercury biopic has been lost for viewers in China</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: HOW LEGAL STRATEGY PAID OFF...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-interview-insight/the-mueller-interview-that-wasnt-how-trumps-legal-strategy-paid-off-idUSKCN1R72Y9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Attorney General William Barr sent lawmakers a summary of the key findings ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dole Promoted to Army Colonel at 95...</title>
      <link>https://www.military.com/daily-news/2019/03/27/bob-dole-promoted-army-colonel-95.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.military.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former U.S. Sen. Bob Dole earned two Purple Hearts and two Bronze Stars for valor for his service in World War II.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEW: The state of local journalism...</title>
      <link>https://www.journalism.org/2019/03/26/for-local-news-americans-embrace-digital-but-still-want-strong-community-connection/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.journalism.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly as many U.S. adults prefer to get local news online as through a TV set. And while Americans prize community connection from their local news providers, they are largely unaware of the financial challenges they face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RUSSIA FAIL:  ULTIMATE MEDIA COMPILATION!</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/watch-msm-coverage-of-the-russian-collusion-delusion/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Establishment media pushed the false narrative for two years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24,000 Border Crossers, Illegals Released in Two Weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/26/dhs-releases-24k-border-crossers-illegal-aliens-into-u-s-in-two-weeks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department of Homeland Security released 24,000 foreign family members into the U.S. over the course of two weeks this month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rant At Mexican Restaurant Over Bilingual Menu...</title>
      <link>https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2019/03/26/taco-tirade-man-goes-on-rant-at-mexican-restaurant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;losangeles.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A bilingual menu apparently set off a customer in Anaheim. A security camera then caught him going into an all out rant. In the video the man yells at employees and customers and threatens to call immigration. Tonight workers tell CBSLA it was very upsetting. Cristy Fajardo reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dumping at McAllen bus station...</title>
      <link>http://www.theamericanmirror.com/video-mcallen-bus-station-packed-with-illegals-as-cbp-releases-migrants-with-court-date/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theamericanmirror.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The flood of illegal immigrants coming across the U.S.-Mexico border has now filled holding facilities and local shelters to capacity, so officials are now simply releasing the migrants with a bus ticket and court date to appear for a hearing months in the future. U.S. Customs and Border Protection denies the situation is “catch and …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOW WHAT?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/msnbcs-trump-russia-ratings-juggernaut-fizzles-time-to-pivot-to-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller report and its potential implications have driven the network’s coverage—and monster ratings—for two years. Now it’s ended with a whimper, leaving execs in a bind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter landed in California poppy field during super bloom -- officials furious...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/27/a-helicopter-landed-in-a-california-poppy-field-during-the-super-bloom-and-officials-are-furious/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The super arrogant seem to like the super bloom. Park officials in California’s Antelope Valley said in recent days someone landed a helicopter in a field of poppies — part of the massive bloom unf…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNSHACKLED TRUMP MAY ATTEND WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENTS DINNER...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/donald-trump-white-house-correspondents-dinner-69f0028f-2bb9-441a-b535-4d04d938f18c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He skipped the dinner during the first 2 years of his term.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILD RALLY SET FOR MICHIGAN...</title>
      <link>https://wbckfm.com/donald-trump-michigan-visit-mueller-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wbckfm.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Executive Director of the Kent County GOP said news of the conclusions of the Mueller investigation will fuel an already energetic crowd at the rally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious Nighttime Booms Rattling CA Community For Months...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/03/26/loud-booms-fair-oaks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators say they're confident it's caused by powerful illegal fireworks with the blast equivalent of up to a half stick of dynamite.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rips 'white man's culture'...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-biden-attacks-americas-white-mans-culture</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘This is English jurisprudential culture, a white man’s culture’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlash, questions follow dismissal of Jussie Smollett case...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/257bcec549a0447b80524ed1ac0820ce</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO (AP) — Prosecutors still insist Jussie Smollett faked a racist, anti-gay attack on himself in the hopes that the attention would advance his acting career. The "Empire" star still says he...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAST DIVIDED...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/03/27/jussie-smollett-empire-cast-crew-not-supporting-charges-dropped-divided/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett hasn't regained the support of his "Empire" family despite criminal charges against him being dropped.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside 'Dad's Army' of veterans patrolling 'until wall built'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8727914/inside-mexico-border-wall-united-constitutional-patriots-trump/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A BAND of veterans and older men are now patrolling the Mexican border until Donald Trump builds his wall. Armed with weapons and well disciplined the militia has been compared to a “dad’s army”. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC Trump-Russia Ratings Fizzle...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/msnbcs-trump-russia-ratings-juggernaut-fizzles-time-to-pivot-to-2020 </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller report and its potential implications have driven the network’s coverage—and monster ratings—for two years. Now it’s ended with a whimper, leaving execs in a bind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Zealand aims to save 'strangest parrot on Earth'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/lifestyle/article/New-Zealand-aims-to-save-the-strangest-parrot-on-13720047.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's as plump as a goose, has the face of an owl and waddles like a duck. It sleeps in the day and is active at night. And it can climb just about anything but can't fly anywhere.  No wonder people call the kakapo the strangest parrot on Earth.  Once found in large numbers all over New Zealand, kakapo (pronounced caw-caw-poe) have been perched on the edge of disappearing for more than a century. What humans started, by reducing the birds' habitat and food supply, predators such as cats, rats and weasel-like stoats nearly finished.  As of 1977, trackers counted just 18 kakapo left in the entire country - all of them males. The end seemed in sight.  Then something amazing happened. A previously unknown kakapo population was found. It included the first females seen in more than 60 years. This exciting discovery stirred government-led efforts to help the parrots by moving them to three small, predator-free islands.  New Zealand is an isolated island nation in the southwestern Pacific Ocean. Many of its plants and animals - like the kakapo - are found nowhere else. Protecting them is a matter of national pride as well as urgency.  "As the largest parrot on Earth, (they are) quite the sight in person," said Wes Sechrest of Global Wildlife Conservation, which is helping the kakapo recovery program. "They have a teddy-bear quality to them with their soft feathers, wide eyes and owl-like expressions."  Today the recovery program counts 147 adult birds, nearly triple the number since its start in 1995. And that number will soon grow, as the current breeding season is expected to set a record and add 30 to 50 healthy chicks.  In New Zealand's native Maori language, "kaka" means parrot and "po" is night. The Maori (rhymes with cow-ree) people could have added "old," because kakapo can...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Iger and James Cameron: Can King of Hollywood Manage King of World?</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/bob-iger-james-cameron-can-king-hollywood-manage-king-world-1197279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Cameron’s ‘Avatar’ sequels move from Fox to Disney as part of the $71 billion merger, they join a crowded film release slate. “We're very sad the Murdochs chose to sell the company," says franchise producer Jon Landau. “But if they're going to sell the company, there's nobody better than Disney to sell it to."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House-hunting in Silicon Valley: Tech's newly rich fuel spectacle of excess...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/mar/27/silicon-valley-tech-wealth-real-estate</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As flamenco dancers and baristas help show off multimillion-dollar homes, there is no longer room for the middle class</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tense calm on Gaza-Israel border after flareup...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-israel-palestinians-violence/tense-calm-on-gaza-israel-border-after-flareup-idUSKCN1R810G</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Schools reopened in southern Israel and traffic clogged Gaza's streets on W...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRINDR Chinese owner forced to sell service over US security concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-grindr-m-a-exclusive/exclusive-u-s-pushes-chinese-owner-of-grindr-to-divest-the-dating-app-sources-idUSKCN1R809L</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chinese gaming company Beijing Kunlun Tech Co Ltd is seeking to sell Grindr LLC,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First reviews for 'DUMBO' in -- and not looking good...</title>
      <link>https://www.nme.com/news/film/dumbo-critics-reviews-disney-tim-burton-2467141</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nme.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disney's remake of 'Dumbo' has not been greeted warmly by a large number of film critics, with mostly negative reviews emerging.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half of Older Americans Have ZERO Retirement Savings...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/almost-half-older-americans-zero-210656147.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The good news is that the new estimate, from the U.S. Government Accountability Office, is slightly better than a few years earlier. Of those 55 and older, 48 percent had nothing put away in a 401(k)-style defined contribution plan or an individual retirement account, according to a GAO estimate for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US predicts 1M illegals will be stopped at border...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/us-border-officials-predict-number-migrants-attempting-cross/story?id=61957788</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. border authorities are predicting the number of migrants attempting to cross the southern border could reach as high as 1 million by the end of the year.&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Bush blamed Trump for 'heart attack'...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/03/27/barbara-bush-blamed-trump-heart-attack-leaving-gop-the-matriarch/3270187002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA TODAY Exclusive: In "The Matriarch," Barbara Bush blames Donald Trump for her heart attack and for driving her from the Republican Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storm chasers died in violent collision. Mother now blames WEATHER CHANNEL...</title>
      <link>https://www.star-telegram.com/news/local/community/fort-worth/article228430054.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.star-telegram.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient West Bank site draws Christians, and controversy...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/a8bfb603733f4cb3890bbb4fcecd06c1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SHILOH, WEST BANK (AP) — Deep in the West Bank, Israeli settlers have transformed an archaeological site into a biblical tourist attraction that attracts tens of thousands of evangelical...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan opposition leader's wife emerges as potent force...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/9333610c82a94837932ace4b0500b76a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — With her youthful energy and globe-trotting, the 26-year-old wife of Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido is emerging as a prominent figure in his campaign to bring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uruguayans turn tough on crime to tackle growing violence...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/11d932d176604ce391bcd107a739c9fb</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MONTEVIDEO, Uruguay (AP) — Long famed for being a peaceful haven in South America, Uruguay is experiencing what some analysts and international organizations describe as an "epidemic" of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heiress hoax scores woman celeb treatment, and charges...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4f3e648bb2744c60a95f2c00d899d13a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Anna Sorokin traveled in celebrity circles and tossed $100 tips — all the more reason to believe she was the German heiress she said she was. But behind the jet-set lifestyle and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Successfully Tests Satellite-Killer Missile...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/india-successfully-tests-satellite-killer-missile-11553679166</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;India said it successfully tested a satellite-destroying missile, becoming just the fourth country with the proven ability to carry war into space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rise of encampments changing face of homelessness...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Homeless-living-in-a-tent-blocks-from-the-US-13709194.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before 10 a.m. on another cold Thursday, Monica Diaz stirred in her tent, filled with dread. It had been two weeks since the last cleanup, and city workers would again be here soon, with their dumpster truck and police cars, to clear out the encampment. Every morning was awful, but these were the worst of all, when Monica, who'd otherwise be resting before work, was forced to confront publicly what she did her best to hide: that she's homeless. That she lives in a tent. That she just turned 40, and that this is somehow her life.  "You ready?" Monica asked her husband, after a sleepless night at the base of Union Station, near CNN's Washington bureau, where the noise never stopped and they'd huddled together with their dog, Sassy, against the cold.  "Somewhat," said Pete Etheridge, 31, sighing.  They looked around their tent, which not only held the sum total of their world but also reflected a way of life that has, over the past decade, fundamentally changed the face of American homelessness. As housing costs climb ever higher in booming urban areas, the significant growth in tent encampments nationwide has become one of the most visible signs of the nation's failure to alleviate widening inequality. In Orange County, California, more than 700 people were cleared out of a tent city along the Santa Ana River last year after thousands signed a petition and Anaheim declared a state of emergency. Seattle, meanwhile, has allowed some tent cities to operate as de facto communities - long-term, regulated, even with phone numbers and addresses. And in Washington, the number of encampment cleanups has surged, according to city data, rising from 29 in 2015 to 100 in 2018.  Monica, a stout, wavy-haired woman now living in her seventh tent after cleanup crews tossed the others, looked down the busy street and tried to gird herself...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona desert blooming blue?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/435948-dems-see-arizona-desert-blooming-blue</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX — Coming off their best election season in more than a generation, Arizona Democrats see a path to the White House that runs through the Valley of the Sun, if their party’s presidential nominee makes a concerted effort to win the state’s electoral votes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttigieg star rises in crowded 2020 race...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/pete-buttigiegs-star-rises-crowded-2020-race-230910529.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At just 37, Pete Buttigieg has deployed to Afghanistan, graduated from Harvard, learned seven languages and serves as mayor of a Midwestern American city. When he began exploring a challenge to Donald Trump, few people outside his home city of South Bend, Indiana knew who the fresh-faced Democrat was</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE nabs 50 illegals in 'stash house'...</title>
      <link>https://cbs4local.com/news/local/ice-apprehends-about-50-immigrants-that-were-found-in-stash-house-03-27-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;cbs4local.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials with the U. S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement said they apprehended about 50 undocumented immigrants on Tuesday after they were found in a &amp;ldquo;stash house. &amp;rdquo;ICE said the raid happened off Sambrano Avenue and Seville Drive. ICE said the group of immigrants consisted of different nationalities. &amp;ldquo;It was like from a movie scene, i thought it was like a movie," said Richard Nunez. &amp;ldquo;I heard like a loud, like a bang. And I see like the agents when they broke the door down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did kale lose superstar status?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/opinion/435692-did-kale-lose-its-superstar-status</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kale’s appearance on this annual list calls into question its recent superstar status as a nutrient-packed ingredient in healthy salads, smoothies and even as a snack food.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor of South Bend Big On Broadway...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/03/26/pete-buttigieg-attending-broadway-mogul-jordan-roth-2020-fundraiser.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mayor Pete Buttigieg is attending a 2020 fundraiser hosted by Broadway executive Jordan Roth and his husband, movie producer Richie Jackson in New York.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KELLYANNE HUSBAND:  TRUMP UNFIT FOR OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435968-george-conway-mueller-must-have-something-pretty-damning-on-trump</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Conway, a lawyer married to White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, argued Tuesday that special counsel Robert Mueller's report must have "something pretty damning in it" if it could not exonerate President Trump on the question</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEY CONFUSED...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/mar/26/james-comey-confused-robert-mueller-obstruction-ju/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI chief James Comey said in a speech Tuesday evening that he is confused by Special Counsel Robert Mueller’s reasoning on charging President Trump with obstruction of justice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KELLYANNE HUSBAND:  TRUMP UNFIT FOR OFFICE...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/george-conway-trump-is-guilty--of-being-unfit-for-office/2019/03/26/0b5f851e-4ffd-11e9-88a1-ed346f0ec94f_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Mueller report is letting the American people and Congress decide what to make of the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ: MUELLER 'DETAILS' IN WEEKS...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-russia-report/mueller-report-details-to-be-issued-in-weeks-not-months-justice-department-idUSKCN1R72HX</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Attorney General William Barr plans to issue a public version of Special Co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROSECUTOR FEELS HEAT</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/top-chicago-prosecutor-taking-heat-dropping-charges-against-empire-actor-n987701</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kimberly Foxx had earlier asked Chicago police to hand over the Smollett case to the FBI, according to media reports.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Us' Filmmaker:  Don't See Myself Casting White Dude as Lead...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/rambling-reporter/jordan-peele-says-i-dont-see-myself-casting-a-white-dude-as-lead-us-1197021</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hot off the record-breaking success of his latest high-minded horror flick, the writer-director advised Hollywood improv students on ego, marijuana use and why minority actors will always star in his films.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EBOLA CRISIS: Outbreaks hit 1,000 cases, 600 killed...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/world/1105662/ebola-outbreak-dr-congo-who-un-health</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE EBOLA epidemic in the Democratic Republic of Congo has surpassed 1,000 cases, the Health Ministry has confirmed, adding the outbreak had already killed more than 600 people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCDONALD'S A.I. knows what you want...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2019/03/26/mcdonalds-ai-drive-thru-machine-learning-dynamic-yield/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The McDonald's AI will optimize menus based on factors such as weather, the time of day, local events and how busy the restaurant is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHICAGO TRIB: SECRET DEAL INDEFENSIBLE!</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/opinion/editorials/ct-edit-jussie-smollett-hoax-rahm-emanuel-20190326-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cook County prosecutors stunned Chicagoans and the rest of the country with news that they were dropping fake police report charges against Jussie Smollett. The fallout? Chicagoans, Americans for that matter, will doubtless feel bamboozled, used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE global council on automation ethics... </title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-47714921</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The group will meet to discuss how emerging technologies should - or perhaps should not - be used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still could face federal charges...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/26/jussie-smollet-could-still-face-federal-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The FBI and the US Postal Inspection Service are continuing their probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  82% Say Report Should Be Made Public...</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/03/26/trumps-popularity-unchanged-after-completion-of-mueller-probe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new Morning Consult/Politico survey conducted after Attorney General William Barr released his summary of special counsel Robert Mueller’s findings shows a negligible immediate effect on how the public views the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINK TAX!</title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/european-parliament-adopts-copyright-reform-blow-big-tech-123418987--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The European Parliament on Tuesday adopted copyright reforms championed by news publishers and the media business, in defiance of the tech giants that lobbied against it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden rips 'white man's culture'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/73e70d011191490d839683b1fc89363f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Former Vice President Joe Biden condemned "a white man's culture" Tuesday night as he lashed out at violence against women and, more specifically, lamented his role in the Supreme...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems see opening in Trump push to quash Obamacare...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7226e10db0a74d0aabb3535000cf09a7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump is calling on Republicans to revive the effort to quash the Affordable Care Act, handing Democrats an opportunity to unite in defense of the law as they...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAHM:  'WHITEWASH OF JUSTICE'</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/chicago-mayor-rahm-emanuel-calls-jussie-smolletts-dropped-charges-a-whitewash-of-justice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel strongly condemned the Cook County State's Attorney's office decision to drop all charges against Jussie Smollett, calling it a "whitewash of justice."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineer sues 'bully' boss who FARTED, 'thrusted bum' at him for $1.2M...</title>
      <link>https://www.standard.co.uk/news/world/engineer-appeals-court-ruling-that-farting-colleague-was-not-bullying-him-a4100991.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.standard.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A worker in Australia who claims his colleague repeatedly farted and “thrusted his bum” at him has appealed against a court ruling that found he was not bullied.  David Hingst, 56, sought a $1.8 million (£970,000) suit against his former employer last year saying his colleague, Greg Short, would “lift his bum and fart” on him up to six times a day. The Supreme Court of Victoria found there was no bullying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human contact now luxury good. Avoiding screens status symbol...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/03/23/sunday-review/human-contact-luxury-screens.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screens used to be for the elite. Now avoiding them is a status symbol.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah bans abortions after 18 weeks, teeing up legal showdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.deseretnews.com/article/900062325/utah-governor-signs-into-law-bill-to-ban-abortion-after-18-weeks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.deseretnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Gary Herbert on Monday signed into law a bill to ban abortions in Utah after 18 weeks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOP COP EVISCERATES</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6852881/Is-no-decency-man-Chicago-Mayor-Rahm-Emanuel-condemns-Jussie-Smollett.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jussie Smollett has insisted he has been 'truthful and consistent' since day one after charges against him were dropped on Tuesday and he escaped a possible 48-year prison sentence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guns drawn, cuffed parents, smashed cake: Lawsuit claims cops raid wrong home during child birthday party...</title>
      <link>https://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-met-police-raid-birthday-party-20190326-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chicagotribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Chicago police officers turned a boy’s 4th birthday party into a traumatic memory of guns drawn, presents destroyed and parents handcuffed after they raided the wrong home in the South Side Gresham neighborhood last month, a federal lawsuit claims.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacteria can fly thousands of miles through air -- on its own...</title>
      <link>https://www.earth.com/news/bacteria-travel-thousands-miles/#.XJqvUarQhhE</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.earth.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study is providing evidence that bacteria can fly thousands of miles through the air without depending on people and animals for transport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate UNANIMOUSLY votes down Ocasio-Cortez 'Green New Deal'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6853499/Senate-votes-Alexandria-Ocasio-Cortezs-Green-New-Deal-57-0.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate roundly rejected Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez's Green New Deal as expected on Tuesday with not a single senator voting 'yes' as she explains she didn't want the vote to happen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I Am Nervous, Scared'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/michael-avenatti-reacts-to-federal-charges-of-course-im-nervous/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"I'm nervous. I'm scared. I'm all those things. And if I wasn't, it wouldn't make a lot of sense," Avenatti told CBS News</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalists Face Jail For Cardinal Conviction Reporting...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/journalists-face-prison-over-reporting-george-pell-sex-abuse-conviction-11553602955</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 20 Australian journalists, including editors of major newspaper titles, face prison and fines for allegedly breaching an order suppressing coverage of a top Vatican official’s child sex-abuse conviction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARAJI HENSON: THANK GOD TRUTH PREVAILED!</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/tv/2019/03/26/taraji-p-henson-happy-jussie-smollett-the-truth-prevailed/3280218002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taraji P. Henson is ecstatic for her "Empire" co-star Jussie Smollett, who was cleared of all charges after being accused of staging a hate crime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver shot in St. Louis after spitting out car window...</title>
      <link>https://www.stltoday.com/news/local/crime-and-courts/driver-shot-in-downtown-st-louis-after-rolling-down-window/article_7f979ca4-ecee-5ddf-b1fd-0ca5cb8c190e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stltoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;He was hit in the arm after men began yelling at him, fired shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student eating habits change as devliery bots invade campus...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/03/25/how-gmu-students-eating-habits-changed-when-delivery-robots-invaded-campus/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the first days after a fleet of 25 delivery robots descended on George Mason University&amp;apos;s campus in January, school officials could only speculate about the machines&amp;apos; long-term impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow, Queen of collusion, won't let go...</title>
      <link>https://www.ctpost.com/entertainment/article/Rachel-Maddow-the-left-s-powerhouse-on-cable-13717367.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ctpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rachel Maddow, the queen of collusion, is not backing down.  A day after Attorney General William Barr said special prosecutor Robert Mueller hadn't found collusion between President Donald Trump's campaign and Russian agents, Maddow - primetime TV's primary and most tenacious proponent of the conspiracy angle - still wasn't buying it.  Instead, Maddow moved on to two related questions: Did Trump obstruct justice? And did Barr let him get away with it?  "Whatever information (Barr) just received from Robert Mueller about the president's behavior as it pertains to potential criminal obstruction of justice, Barr could have just passed that information onto (Congress) for them to decide what to do with it," Maddow said on her MSNBC program Monday night. "But instead, somewhat inexplicably, he decided to take it upon himself to declare definitively, 'Yeah, you know, I looked at all that stuff, and I can tell you there is no crime there, it's fine.'"  She added, "Where did this come from? I mean, on what grounds are you saying that you have concluded there is no crime here?"  Maddow's monologue suggests she is unmoved by the many attacks on her for promoting a Russia conspiracy that, at least according to the attorney general, seems to have run aground. Her nightly deconstructions of the case against Trump have made her the signal figure of the anti-Trump left and have abetted her rise to the most popular figure in cable news.  Trump's supporters savaged Maddow in the wake of the release of Barr's four-page memo Sunday night. The memo said Mueller's 22-month investigation had not turned up evidence sufficient to conclude Trump and his associates were involved in a conspiracy with Russia to sway the 2016 election. It also said Mueller had not drawn a conclusion about whether Trump had obstructed efforts to investigate him -...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAND: Subpoena Brennan, Clapper, Susan Rice...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/politics/2019/03/26/exclusive-rand-paul-absolutely-james-clapper-john-brennan-susan-rice-others-should-testify-spygate-role-subpoenaed-necessary/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rand Paul told Breitbart News that Trump told senators he backs his call for an investigation into the origins of the Russia scandal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College backs down on 'Orwellian' PC language guide...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/03/21/amherst-college-backs-down-on-pc-language-guide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A politically charged glossary for Amherst College students that disparages capitalism and dictates a broad range of PC gender terms has been withdrawn after campus Republicans howled in protest, s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama after mom gives birth to twins -- 'with different dads'...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/03/26/woman-gives-birth-twins-different-dads-cheating-husband-9032671/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Results of DNA tests meant the new mother had to admit she had cheated on her husband in a one-night stand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS: ARBY'S manager murders customer who spat on her...</title>
      <link>https://kfor.com/2019/03/26/fast-food-restaurant-manager-arrested-after-allegedly-shooting-killing-man-who-threatened-spit-on-her/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kfor.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TULSA, Okla. - A fast food restaurant manager in Tulsa was arrested after she allegedly shot and killed a man who threatened her and spit on her, police say. Around 6:30 p.m. Monday, police arrested 25-year-old Deionna Young in the shooting death of 25-year-old Desean Tallent. Police say Young and Tallent allegedly got into an altercation at an Arby's, where Young was reportedly the manager, about an hour before the shooting. Tallent allegedly threatened Young and spit on her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOEING 737 MAX makes emergency landing at Orlando Airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/breaking-news/os-ne-southwest-emergency-landing-orlando-20190326-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest flight with just two pilots aboard made an emergency landing Tuesday afternoon at Orlando International Airport, a spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'EMPIRE' Writers Taunt Smollett Critics, Slam Journalists...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/online/empire-writers-taunt-smollett-critics-slam-chicago-journalists-you-reported-a-bunch-of-false-information/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rami Malek Goes Retro: Hope New Project Makes Throw Away Smartphone...</title>
      <link>https://www.fastcompany.com/90323990/rami-malek-hopes-his-new-podcast-makes-you-throw-away-your-iphone</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fastcompany.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The recent Academy Award-winner’s new podcast, “Blackout,” is about what might happen if you were suddenly without all technology except radio. (He thinks he’d rather enjoy it.)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASE SEALED</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6852243/Charges-DROPPED-against-Jussie-Smollett.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Empire actor will appear in court in Chicago on Tuesday for an emergency hearing. Smollett's lawyers announced the news in a statement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR STICKS TO STORY HE WAS ATTACKED</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/jussie-smollett-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TRUTHFUL AND CONSISTENT'</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/03/26/jussie-smollett-breaks-silence-after-all-charges-dropped-in-alleged-attack-hoax/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“I would not be my mother’s son if I was capable of one drop of what I was accused of.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMOLLETT CHARGES DROPPED</title>
      <link>https://chicago.cbslocal.com/2019/03/26/jussie-smollett-charges-dropped/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;chicago.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Less than two weeks after pleading not guilty to 16 counts of disorderly conduct for allegedly lying to police about a hate crime, "Empire" actor Jussie Smollett is back in court for an "emergency court appearance."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kraft Requests Jury Trial In Florida Prostitution Case...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/03/26/robert-kraft-jury-trial-prostitution-charges-patriots-news/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patriots owner Robert Kraft has again waived his arraignment in his Florida prostitution case and is requesting a jury trial.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief Justice Roberts Denies Gun Owners' Request to Stay Ban on Bump Stocks...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/chief-justice-john-roberts-denies-gun-owners-request-to-stay-ban-on-bump-stocks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The devices enable semi-automatic rifles to fire like machine guns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop using Nazi death camp as cute photo backdrop, Auschwitz asks...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/nation-world/world/article228418434.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pence sets 5-year deadline for returning Americans to moon...</title>
      <link>https://www.geekwire.com/2019/vp-mike-pence-sets-5-year-deadline-landing-americans-moons-south-pole/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.geekwire.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vice President Mike Pence called for American astronauts to return to the moon in five years, laying down a challenge comparable to the 1960s-era Space Race.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility scientists launch last-ditch bid to save 'extinct' rhinoceros...</title>
      <link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/oxford-fertility-scientists-launch-last-191953464.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;uk.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oxford University scientists have launched a last-ditch attempt to bring the Northern White Rhinoceros back from beyond the “point of no return” using IVF.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University Mumps Outbreak Grows To 100 Cases...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/03/25/temple-university-mumps-outbreak-grows-to-nearly-100-cases-officials-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are now 99 confirmed and probable cases of mumps in the Temple community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House Warns of EMP Attacks On USA...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/white-house-warns-of-emp-attacks-on-u-s/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Trump administration is taking steps to protect the United States from electro-magnetic pulse events, or EMPs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Newspapers largely shun...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4c463558fb70464591b823ff5add3be7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Many newspaper publishers — after suffering for a decade from job losses, shrinking ad dollars and circulation declines — are so far shunning Apple's new "Netflix for news"...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Breakers Turn Tables On Armed Robber At FL Gas Station...</title>
      <link>http://miami.cbslocal.com/2019/03/26/tourists-armed-robber-oakland-park-gas-station/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Three men from the Hoosier State have quite a story to tell after they turned the tables on a man who tried to rob them at gunpoint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily border crossings hit 13-year highs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/daily-border-crossings-undocumented-migrants-hit-13-year-highs-n987396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Homeland Security is now in talks with the Defense Department to care for the overflow on U.S. military bases, according to a DHS official and two other U.S. officials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Carlos Slim to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190326-billionaire-carlos-slim-retire-mexican-president</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Billionaire Carlos Slim to retire: Mexican president</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Snowden refugees' land in Canada...</title>
      <link>https://www.theglobeandmail.com/politics/article-snowden-refugees-to-resettle-in-canada/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theglobeandmail.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canada has granted asylum to two of the people who housed whistleblower and U.S. fugitive Edward Snowden in Hong Kong, but is facing calls to take in the other five ‘Snowden refugees’ whose Canadian asylum claims remain in bureaucratic limbo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRESIDENT: Report 'could not have been better'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/435866-trump-says-mueller-report-could-not-have-been-better</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The Mueller report was great. It could not have been better,” Trump says</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search underway for $500,000 of Baltimore mayor' books sold to hospital...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b944a0b347f745d1b5ad93db7a0a4e87</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BALTIMORE (AP) — There's a search underway in Maryland for "Healthy Holly" — not a fugitive or a missing citizen, but an obscure children's book authored by Baltimore Mayor Catherine...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/rankings</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's Healthiest Community: Douglas County, CO...</title>
      <link>https://www.usnews.com/news/healthiest-communities/articles/2019-03-26/healthiest-community-in-america-douglas-county-colorado</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World's biggest T. rex discovered...</title>
      <link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/2019/03/worlds-biggest-t-rex-found-in-canada-scotty-dinosaur/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nationalgeographic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Heftier than an adult elephant, the 9.8-ton animal shows that predatory dinosaurs got older and bigger than once thought.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-campaign aide says FBI wanted him to wear wire...</title>
      <link>https://www.kwch.com/content/news/Ex-Trump-campaign-aide-says-FBI-wanted-him-to-wear-a-wire-507675681.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.kwch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former aide, George Papadopoulos, said he was asked to record conversations with a professor who had told him the Russians had dirt on Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pioneering medical drone program takes off...</title>
      <link>https://www.bradenton.com/news/business/article228426684.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bradenton.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHAOS:  Computer outage hits AMERICAN, JETBLUE passengers... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/travel/flights/2019/03/26/american-jetblue-other-airlines-hit-computer-outage/3276512002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A spokesman for American Airlines says the issue is due to problems at Sabre, a reservations system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope stops churchgoers from kissing his ring; Yanks hand away...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8722720/pope-francis-refuses-ring-kiss-meet-and-greet/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;POPE Francis has been filmed repeatedly pulling away his hand when the faithful try to kiss his ring. The bizarre footage emerged during a one day visit to the Holy House of Loreto basilica, near A…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prize-winning pooch missing for days at Atlanta airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/prize-winning-dog-missing-days-atlanta-airport-n987431</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gale, a pure-bred American Staffordshire Terrier, was boarding a flight Saturday at Hartsfield-Jackson International Airport in Atlanta when she escaped, airport officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  WIKIPEDIA Editors Paid to Protect Political, Tech, Media Figures...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/tech/2019/03/26/wikipedia-editors-paid-to-protect-political-tech-and-media-figures/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A report in Huffington Post recently revealed the case of Wikipedia editor Ed Sussman, who was paid by media clients such as NBC and Axios to help diminish critical material. Paid editors operating in a similar manner to Sussman have worked on behalf of CNN contributor Hilary Rosen and the CEOs of Reddit and Intel, among other clients.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
