<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Iran suspected of being behind hijack off UAE coast...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/britain-warns-of-non-piracy-incident-underway-off-uae-coast-675737</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran: The potential hijack of ships off coast of UAE is 'suspicious' • Possible attack follows attack on Israeli-managed tanker off coast of Oman</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Tense Exchange With Reporter When Asked About Children In ICU...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/03/covid-florida-desantis-downplays-threat/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis doubled down Tuesday in defending his actions and his ban of mask mandates amid the coronavirus pandemic just as the state once again broke its record for COVID-19 hospitalizations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressives call for new probe, impeachment of Justice Kavanaugh...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2021/aug/2/progressives-call-new-probe-impeachment-supreme-co/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Progressive activist groups have renewed calls for a new probe into Supreme Court Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh and his possible impeachment, saying a further FBI investigation is necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUMMER BUMMER:  Israel Adds USA to List Requiring VACCINATED in Quarantine!</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/israel-news/israel-may-place-us-under-severe-travel-warning-675718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beginning next Wednesday, travelers from some 18 additional countries will be required to quarantine even if they are fully vaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How artists lost their courage...</title>
      <link>https://unherd.com/2021/08/how-artists-lost-their-courage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;unherd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keeping silent is the price of a successful career</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>READ IT ALL</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/read-the-cuomo-report-from-the-ny-attorney-generals-office/3196417/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigators appointed by New York Attorney General Letitia James concluded that Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed multiple women in violation of state and federal law. Read their report below or click here to open in a new window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY:  Men to vastly outnumber women within decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/men-could-soon-vastly-outnumber-24675636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few decades from now, blokes in some countries could find themselves struggling to find a wife or girlfriend, as millions of girls are not being born due to parents opting to hold out for boys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CILLIZZA:  Biden having worst week...</title>
      <link>http://www.cnn.com/2021/08/03/politics/joe-biden-eviction-president-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Joe Biden's presidential honeymoon has officially ended, with a series of problems -- led by the ongoing surge of the Delta variant of the coronavirus -- coalescing to make the last few days some of the worst ones he has spent as president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GROPING, KISSING, VERBAL ABUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnewyork.com/news/local/attorney-general-expected-to-release-findings-of-probe-into-cuomo-harassment-allegations/3196087/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnewyork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Attorney General Letitia James and the team of attorneys selected to investigate allegations of sexual harassment made against Gov. Andrew Cuomo have completed their investigation and released a public report of their findings. The attorney general’s report, which is being made available to the public for the first time, found that the harassment claimed by a number of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG:  CUOMO HARASSED WOMEN</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/03/ny-gov-andrew-cuomo-sexual-harassment-report.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo sexually harassed multiple women who worked for the state and elsewhere, according to report by state Attorney General Letitia James.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETALIATED!</title>
      <link>https://abc7ny.com/governor-cuomo-investigation-sexual-harassment-scandal/10927185/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc7ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney General Letitia James on Tuesday announced the findings of her inquiry into accusations against Andrew Cuomo, concluding that the governor sexually harassed multiple women.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Crashes Into World Trade Center Building...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2021/08/02/small-drone-hits-7-world-trade-center/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sources told CBS2 a man visiting from Texas was flying the small drone when it crashed into 7 World Trade Center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FL HOSPITAL RECORD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-florida-coronavirus-pandemic-f7a383de8065b5824344a6a79aa1eece</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. (AP) — The number of people hospitalized for COVID-19 in Florida rose to an all-time high of 11,515 patients in one day, according to data the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services released Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida district drops covering mandate after DeSantis threatens funding...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566056-florida-district-reverses-on-mask-mandate-after-desantis-threatens</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Florida school district has dropped its mask mandate for schools after Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) issued an executive order that would cut off funding to schools that did so.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Keto Diet Disease-Promoting Disaster...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/keto-disease-promoting-disaster/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new report finds restricting carbohydrates actually tilts a person's diet towards more cancer-causing foods.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC to mandate jab certification for indoor activities...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/new-york/city-hall/story/2021/08/03/new-york-city-to-mandate-vaccine-certification-for-a-range-of-indoor-activities-1389396</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enforcement will begin in mid-September, according to City Hall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maui residents rail against spike in tourism during water shortage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/nation/2021/08/03/maui-hawaii-water-shortage/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As travel returns to pre-pandemic levels in Hawaii, some natives are saying they are tired of catering to visitors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio elections: Primaries test Dem loyalty, Trump influence...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/ohio-elections-primaries-test-democratic-loyalty-trump-e2-80-99s-influence/ar-AAMSTtp</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nina Turner, a co-chair of Bernie Sanders’s 2020 presidential campaign, is pitted in a high-profile race with Shontel Brown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workers Willing to Take Pay Cut to Never Go Back to Office...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/other/americans-are-willing-to-take-pay-cuts-to-never-go-into-the-office-again/ar-AAMSYrz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new survey shows 65% of workers who said their jobs could be done entirely remotely were willing to take a 5% reduction to stay at home.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Judy $47M Salary Isn't Excessive, Appeals Court Agrees...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-news/judge-judy-salary-1234991870/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CBS wins the first appellate round in a legal battle now in its sixth year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'World's steepest dive' rollercoaster to open with drop from 150ft...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/travel/travel-news/worlds-steepest-dive-rollercoaster-open-24676672</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You'd have to be an adrenaline junky to take on the "world's steepest dive" rollercoaster that's set to open in Six Flags theme park next year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming soon: America's own social credit system...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/finance/565860-coming-soon-americas-own-social-credit-system</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The same issue with government censorship exists with corporate censorship: If there is a line, who draws it?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People recovering may have 'substantial' drop in intelligence...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2021/08/03/people-recovering-from-covid-may-have-substantial-drop-in-intelligence-15030236/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Research has suggested that coronavirus has had a big impact on the IQ of the British people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone volcano rocked by record number of quakes...</title>
      <link>https://www.express.co.uk/news/science/1471580/yellowstone-volcano-earthquakes-usgs-latest-yellowstone-eruption-scn</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.express.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;YELLOWSTONE volcano experienced more than 1,000 earthquakes last month - a four-year record high that the US Geological Survey (USGS) said will "likely increase" in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLOOD: Border Crossers Highest in 20 Years...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnsnews.com/index.php/article/national/patrick-goodenough/surge-number-migrants-stopped-us-mexico-border-july-highest-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. Customs and Border Protection agents recorded around 210,000 “encounters” with migrants along the southwest border in July, the highest monthly figure in two decades, a senior Department of Homeland Security (DHS) official said in a court filing on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mao pins test rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-sports-winter-olympics-china-olympic-team-united-states-olympic-team-62e3a9a9f4c71629b64b2026d0304c34</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — The image of Communist China's founding leader, Mao Zedong, made an unscheduled appearance at the Tokyo Olympics, and the International Olympic Committee said Tuesday it is “looking into the matter.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add Kim Jong Un Head Bandage to List of Health Mysteries...</title>
      <link>https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/add-kim-jong-uns-head-bandage-to-list-of-health-mysteries-2501519</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ndtv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea's Kim Jong Un has appeared in recent days with a bandage about the size of a few postage stamps on the back of his head, in the latest episode to stoke speculation about the reclusive leader's health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's Raisi Starts Presidency as New Crisis Grips Persian Gulf...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/irans-ebrahim-raisi-starts-presidency-as-new-crisis-grips-persian-gulf-11627964350191.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ebrahim Raisi, 60, will begin his tenure after he’s officially confirmed by Ayatollah Ali Khamenei in a televised ceremony, ending the eight-year rule of Hassan Rouhani</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans hailed as debate rages...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210803-transgender-olympian-hubbard-hailed-as-debate-rages</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Transgender Olympian Hubbard hailed as debate rages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent Belarus dissident found hanged in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210803-belarus-dissident-found-hanged-in-ukraine-police-open-murder-case</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Belarusian activist living in exile in Ukraine was found hanged in a park near his home in Kyiv early on Tuesday, and Ukrainian police said they had launched a murder case.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWITTER partners with AP, REUTERS to clean up 'misinformation' on site...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/twitter-partners-ap-reuters-battle-200356209.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Twitter Inc will partner with the Associated Press and Reuters to more quickly provide credible information on the social networking site as part of an effort to fight the spread of misinformation, it said on Monday. Like other social media companies, the San Francisco-based firm has been under pressure to remove misleading or false information on its site. Earlier this year Twitter launched a program called Birdwatch, asking its users to help identify and fact-check misleading tweets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean, repeat: At Tokyo Games, virus Olympians' chief foe...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2020-tokyo-olympics-6c8a1fd6c9c1ef1cea9656c7d30a2494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOKYO (AP) — Holding each other tighter than lovers, the wrestlers smear each other with sweat, spittle and — when they inadvertently cut each other — sometimes blood. Lungs heaving, mouths agape, they huff and puff into each others' flushed faces.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic of Military Sex Assault...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2021/08/03/a-poison-in-the-system-the-epidemic-of-military-sexual-assault/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pfc. Florence Shmorgoner woke up one afternoon in 2015 and realized that she was in someone else’s bed in someone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis mouth spray to treat brain tumors?</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/aug/03/trial-to-test-if-cannabis-based-mouth-spray-can-treat-brain-tumours</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First such study in the world aims to find out if Sativex combined with chemotherapy can help treat glioblastoma</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourth Captiol riot cop dead by suicide...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3401157/fourth-capitol-riot-officer-dead-by-suicide/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A FOURTH law enforcement officer who responded to the January 6 Capitol riots has died by suicide. Officer Kyle DeFreytag, 26, was found dead on July 10, with Metropolitan Police confirming his dea…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NETFLIX Countersues Dershowitz Over Epstein Docuseries...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2021/08/jeffrey-epstein-netflix-docuseries-alan-dershowitz-coutersuit-radicalmedia-sex-crimes-1234808033/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The messy legal battle over Netflix’s Jeffrey Epstein: Filthy Rich docuseries has now gotten down and dirty. In a flurry of filings today, the streamer, director/showrunner Lisa Bryant, executive p…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberals erupt in fury at White House over end of eviction moratorium...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/liberals-erupt-in-fury-at-white-house-over-end-of-eviction-moratorium/ar-AAMRsQX?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The anger comes on top of the left’s frustration with a bipartisan infrastructure deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICUs overwhelmed with younger and sicker...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/it-just-went-boom-icus-are-being-overwhelmed-with-younger-and-sicker-patients/ar-AAMQly4?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI — Inside a COVID-only intensive care unit at Jackson Memorial Hospital in Miami, all eight beds are filled with patients. Six of the eight patients are younger than 50 years old. None of them has been vaccinated against COVID-19. The youngest patient, a 27-year-old woman on a ventilator, had to be resuscitated with a bag valve mask after her blood oxygen saturation levels crashed. The ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Staffing Shortages Rise Sharply in Florida as Beds Fill...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/hospital-staffing-shortages-rise-sharply-in-florida-as-beds-fill/ar-AAMRdGa?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of hospitals reporting critical staffing shortages is climbing swiftly in Florida, where a highly contagious Covid-19 variant is filling beds fast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS fires Judge Napolitano after producer accused him of stroking his arm and making sexually suggestive comments in elevator...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9853775/Fox-employee-alleges-harassment-discrimination-lawsuit.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An associate producer filed a lawsuit against Fox News Network, saying he was discriminated against because of his gender and subjected to unwelcome attention from an on-air personality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEBACK:  Blagojevich files suit to challenge law keeping him from running again...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/illinois-former-gov-blagojevich-files-230600517.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHICAGO — The last time convicted ex-Gov. Rod Blagojevich appeared in federal court in Chicago, he watched sullenly via a video link from prison as a judge resentenced him to 14 years in prison for an array of corruption schemes. Five years later, a far more upbeat Blagojevich returned in the flesh to the Dirksen U.S. Courthouse, ground zero for his historic political and personal downfall. “I ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numbers doubling every 10 days...</title>
      <link>https://miami.cbslocal.com/2021/08/02/this-is-horrifying-broward-mayor-steve-geller-urges-vaccinations-as-covid-cases-climb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;miami.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Broward County Mayor Steve Geller started a news conference Monday morning saying “there is a lot of bad news on COVID.”  There’s a sharp spike in cases and a group of people who are still unvaccinated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Vaxxed Lindsey Graham Tests Positive...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-1ead5c0885acc7f3b2b648abc4c550f1</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) — Sen. Lindsey Graham has become the first senator to disclose a breakthrough infection after being vaccinated against the coronavirus, saying Monday he is “very glad” he received the vaccine, without which his current symptoms would be “far worse.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QANTAS Furloughs Staff as Prolonged Sydney Lockdown Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/business/qantas-furloughs-2-500-staff-as-prolonged-sydney-lockdown-looms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qantas Furloughs 2,500 Staff as Prolonged Sydney Lockdown Looms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigators grilled Cuomo for 11 hours in harassment investigation!</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/566035-investigators-grilled-cuomo-for-11-hours-in-sexual-harassment</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) reportedly sat down for an 11-hour interview as part of state Attorney General Letitia James's investigation into allegations of sexual harassment against him from several female aides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officer who responded to U.S. Capitol attack is third to die by suicide...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/08/02/capitol-riot-cop-becomes-3rd-responding-officer-to-kill-self-report/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A cop who was on duty when the US Capitol was stormed by an angry mob Jan. 6 has committed suicide — the third responding officer to take his own life, a report said Monday. Metropolitan Poli…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. advises against travel to Greece, Virgin Islands, Saint Barth... MORE</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-advises-against-travel-greece-200918580.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) warned on Monday against travel to Greece, Ireland, Iran, the U.S. Virgin Islands and other destinations because of a rising number of COVID-19 cases in those places. Other locations being raised to the CDC's "Level 4: Avoid Travel" include Libya, Kazakhstan, Andorra, Saint Barthelemy, Lesotho, Martinique, Malta, Isle of Man and Curacao, the CDC said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masks back ON in San Fran...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-coronavirus-pandemic-san-francisco-san-francisco-bay-ebf8dc7e45668a3297454cd64063d871</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco and six other Bay Area counties announced Monday that they are reinstating a mask mandate for all indoor public settings as COVID-19 infections surge because of the highly contagious delta variant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE INTERVIEW...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/kathy-griffin-shes-recovering-addict-now-hopes-beat/story?id=79173454&amp;cid=clicksource_4380645_12_comic_strip_sq_hed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kathy Griffin speaks to Nightline about her drug addiction following the fallout from the Trump photo and her recent lung cancer diagnosis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-free Sweden nears zero daily deaths!</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/530759-sweden-delta-masks-zero-covid-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the CDC urges Americans to mask up against the Delta variant, Sweden’s chief epidemiologist has argued that more data is needed about the strain’s infectiousness. His mask-free nation is hovering at zero Covid deaths per day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force developing remote-controlled 'microdrones' with flapping wings...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/air-force-developing-remote-controlled-24669949</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their elite research lab is working with designers from Airion Health LLC to prototype a remote-controlled mini air vehicle that can imitate either insect or bird flight</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers ratchet up the pressure on the unvaccinated...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-c5d6a5593289d6e3ac5e46102b66f5c6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Employers are losing patience with unvaccinated workers. For months, most employers relied on information campaigns, bonuses and other incentives to encourage their workforces to get the COVID-19 shot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House calls on states to prevent evictions...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/joe-biden-business-health-coronavirus-pandemic-6ae7d06f4aa148530cf5ee0970e972d6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House moved Monday to pressure state and local governments to swiftly adopt policies to protect renters after an eviction moratorium expired over the weekend , potentially pushing millions of Americans out of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court upholds university's vaccine mandate...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-courts-education-indiana-coronavirus-pandemic-eb1408814f3d3c7921fa371675f8c617</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — A federal appeals court ruled Monday that Indiana University can proceed with its plan to require students and employees to get vaccinated for COVID-19, in what is the highest court decision regarding college immunization mandates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Record wildfire burns amid drought in Hawaii...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/fires-environment-and-nature-droughts-hawaii-wildfires-ca2f8cbf76abf6affbbee9fce3be69a8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HONOLULU (AP) — Firefighters have gotten more control over a wildfire in Hawaii that forced thousands of people to evacuate over the weekend and destroyed at least two homes on the Big Island, but officials warned strong winds Monday could raise the danger again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaBaby DaSorry; Offers 2nd apology after recent homophobic comments...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/entertainment-music-arts-and-entertainment-dababy-248557a1d881dbb6e1f0c7bbc2ccd589</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Rapper DaBaby offered another apology Monday while facing heavy backlash after he made crude and homophobic remarks at a recent Miami-area music festival. The Grammy-nominated performer said he was misinformed for his comments about HIV/AIDS in the post, which came a day after the rapper was cut from Lollapalooza’s lineup in Chicago .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems ask McCarthy to recant Pelosi taunt as tensions rise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/donald-trump-elections-kevin-mccarthy-nancy-pelosi-midterm-elections-256c6a24bb77c28e6d344290118959ec</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Several House Democrats have called on House Republican Leader Kevin McCarthy to apologize to House Speaker Nancy Pelosi or resign after audio surfaced of him saying at a weekend fundraiser that it would be “hard not to hit her” with a gavel if he’s sworn in as speaker after the 2022 midterm elections.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Housework To Sex, Relationship Contracts Help Couples...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2021/08/01/1022875293/relationship-contracts-couples-useful-advice-tips</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relationship contracts might not sound romantic, but all relationships are contractual, Writer Mandy Len Catron says this is a tool for couples to express their needs and work together.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: DaBaby apologizes for 'triggering' homophobic rant...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3399056/dababy-apology-anti-gay-comments-rolling-loud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DABABY has apologized for his “triggering” homophobic comments after being ditched from three festivals following his onstage rant at Rolling Loud last week. The 29-year-old rapper rele…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colombia town orders vaccine refusers to stay home or face fines, jail...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210802-colombia-town-orders-vaccine-refusers-to-stay-home-or-face-fines-jail</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Colombia town orders vaccine refusers to stay home or face fines, jail</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPS:  Couple arrested for domestic spaghetti battery...</title>
      <link>http://www.thesmokinggun.com/documents/stupid/spaghetti-battery-629538</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesmokinggun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AUGUST 2--Police responding to a 1 AM domestic disturbance found a Florida couple “covered in spaghetti” following a physical confrontation that resulted in the pair’s arrest on domestic battery cha</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jong-un executes high-ranking military officer...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3398756/kim-jong-un-executes-military-officer-criticism-order-rice/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;KIM Jong-un has executed a high-ranking military officer after he criticised the dictator’s order to supply food to North Korea’s starving people. The major general in charge of the logistics headq…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Six dead' in mystery 'blast' at secret Russian weapons factory...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3397814/dead-mystery-blast-russian-weapons-factory/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SIX workers are feared dead after a mysterious “blast” at a secret Russian weapons-making factory. The group suffered “horrific burns” at the chemical plant, with the only s…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agents 'used female colleagues' photos in trafficking stings'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/fbi-agent-colleagues-sex-trafficking-b1895290.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A special agent under investigation reportedly failed to obtain written consent from staff not certified to serve as undercover employees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASES SURPASS LAST SUMMER'S PEAK</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/08/02/cdc-says-7-day-average-of-daily-us-covid-cases-surpassed-peak-seen-last-summer.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"While we desperately want to be done with this pandemic, Covid-19 is clearly not done with us," CDC Director Dr. Rochelle Walensky said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill and Melinda Gates Finalize One Of Largest Divorces In History...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/bill-and-melinda-french-gates-finalize-one-of-the-largest-divorces-in-history/ar-AAMR0I2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the largest divorces in history is officially complete. Bill Gates and Melinda French Gates finalized their divorce on Monday, according to filings submitted in King County, Washington. It was not immediately clear how they planned to divide their assets; the pair signed a “separation contract” that was not filed with the court. Melinda French Gates, who will retain her last name, will almost certainly emerge as one of the richest women...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restaurants Fear Worst: 'Oh God, Is This It Again?'</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/restaurants-bars-tackle-surge-in-covid-cases-new-mask-rules-small-business/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Business drops reported as customers in heavily vaccinated areas opt to eat in or order out with Delta variant spreading across the U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo BILLS Moving To Austin?</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/08/01/texas-gov-abbott-acknowledges-buffalo-bills-austin-relocation/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Could there be a third NFL team in the Lone Star State? It appears Texas Gov. Greg Abbott at least acknowledges the idea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Employee Sues, Alleging Larry Kudlow Made Racist, Sexist Remarks...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/fox-business-employee-sues-network-alleging-larry-kudlow-made-racist-and-sexist-remarks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An employee of the Fox Business Network has sued the cable network, making claims of racist and sexist remarks by host Larry Kudlow, sexual harassment by analyst Andrew Napolitano, and other gossipy allegations in an error-riddled complaint filed in New York. The lawsuit from plaintiff John Fawcett was filed by Ty Clevenger, an attorney from […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALIBAN ESCALATE AFGHAN OFFENSIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9849935/Taliban-escalate-nationwide-offensive-Afghanistan-targets-major-cities-attacks-airport.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fighting has surged in Afghanistan since early May when US-led forces began a final withdrawal. The Taliban has seized tracts of rural territory and is now assaulting provincial capitals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defenders in soccer more at risk of dementia...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210802-defenders-more-at-risk-of-dementia-in-later-life-says-new-research</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defenders more at risk of dementia in later life says new research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3rd cop who responded to Jan. 6 riot dies by suicide...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/565963-third-police-officer-who-responded-to-jan-6-dies-by-suicide</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A third police officer who responded to the Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol has died by suicide, the D.C. Metropolitan Police Department (MPD) confirmed on Monday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana hospital brings in outside help for virus surge...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/health-louisiana-coronavirus-pandemic-fdb8c5c53c4162c934fb21cf3bd366b0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BATON ROUGE, La. (AP) — One of Louisiana's largest hospitals brought in nearly three dozen health care workers from across the country Monday to help treat the ever-increasing number of patients hospitalized with COVID-19, as the highly contagious delta variant ravages the state.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Councilwoman didn't report lobbyist's $1,100 gift for breast augmentation...</title>
      <link>https://www.sgvtribune.com/2021/08/01/el-monte-councilwoman-didnt-report-lobbyists-1100-gift-for-breast-augmentation-records-show/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sgvtribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lobbyist Sigrid Lopez says she also paid Councilwoman Victoria Martinez Muela’s expenses during a trip to Cuba when the two were friends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  NYT editors banned lab-leak investigation...</title>
      <link>https://spectatorworld.com/topic/new-york-times-quashed-covid-origins-inquiry/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;spectatorworld.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A top editor at the New York Times instructed Times staffers not to investigate the origins of COVID-19, two Times employees confirmed today</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside DISNEY:  How Iger-Chapek Rift Led to ScarJo Blunder...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/inside-disney-bob-iger-bob-chapek-rift-scarjo-blunder/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Disney CEO Bob Iger is mortified that the Scarlett Johansson dispute spun out of control. His estrangement from his successor, Bob Chapek, is showing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaBaby dropped from third festival over AIDS comments...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/3397165/dababy-dropped-2021-governors-ball-over-homophobic-rant/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DABABY was dropped from a third festival on Monday after making homophobic comments last week. Governors Ball announced that the 29-year-old rapper will no longer be in its September line-up. The N…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada fines travellers for fake papers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-58063647</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The travellers arriving from the US were caught and fined C$19,720 ($16,000, £11,500).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chipmunks with plague prompt Tahoe closures...</title>
      <link>https://ktla.com/news/california/chipmunks-with-plague-prompt-closure-of-some-areas-of-south-lake-tahoe/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ktla.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Officials are closing some areas on the south shore of Lake Tahoe after some chipmunks tested positive for plague. The Tahoe Daily Tribune reports that the Taylor Creek Visitor Center, Kiva Beach a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUOMO TELLS BUSINESSES: REQUIRE VACCINES</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/565920-cuomo-asks-business-to-go-to-vaccine-only-admission</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;New York Gov.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Germany to offer 3rd shot...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/germany-offer-booster-against-covid-165234738.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Germany will in September start to offer a booster shot against COVID-19 to vulnerable individuals such as pensioners and people with weak immune systems, the health ministers of the country's 16 states said in a statement on Monday. The vaccinations will be done using mRNA-vaccines from Pfizer/BioNTech and Moderna regardless of what was used previously, the ministers concluded after talks with Federal Health Minister Jens Spahn. They also agreed to make vaccination available to all children aged 12 to 17.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
