<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Set to make virtual address to Congress...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/house/598081-zelensky-to-make-virtual-address-us-congress</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky will speak virtually to members of Congress on Wednesday, Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.) and Senate Majority Leader Charles Schumer (D-N.Y.) announced in a joint letter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk Challenges Putin to 'Single Combat'...</title>
      <link>https://www.livemint.com/news/world/elon-musk-challenges-vladimir-putin-to-single-combat-ukraine-is-on-stake-11647259706363.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livemint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Musk had last week said that Starlink, a satellite internet constellation operated by SpaceX, was the only non-Russian communications system still working in some parts of Ukraine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Credits Affair With AI Girlfriend For Saving Marriage...</title>
      <link>https://futurism.com/ai-girlfriend-wife</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;futurism.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Polyamory is one thing, but one man who claims falling in love with his AI girlfriend saved his marriage to his flesh-and-blood wife is certainly another.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow threatens to pay foreign debts in rubles...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/international/598069-russia-threatens-to-pay-foreign-debts-in-rubles-following-sanctions</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia is threatening to pay foreign debts in rubles after a number of Moscow’s top banks were sanctioned in response to the country's invasion of Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan again warns Chinese aircraft in its air defense zone...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-taiwan-defence-china/taiwan-again-warns-chinese-aircraft-in-its-air-defence-zone-idUSKCN2LB14S</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taiwan's air force scrambled again on Monday to warn away 13 Chinese aircraft that entered its air defence zone, Taiwan's defence ministry said, in the latest uptick in tensions across the Taiwan Strait.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New wave of inflation, disruptions hits factory floors...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/ukraine-crisis-usa-disruption/new-wave-of-inflation-and-disruptions-hits-u-s-factory-floors-idUSKCN2LB0VM</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Surging inflation is disrupting everything from carpools to the ability to quote prices on new business at already-strained U.S. factories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: High-Protein Diets Lower Men's Testosterone Levels; Can Lead To ED?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/high-protein-diet-testosterone/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Following a high-protein diet may reduce men's testosterone levels, which can lead to erectile dysfunction and low sperm counts, say scientists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Sees at Least One Winner Emerging: China...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/14/china-sees-at-least-one-winner-emerging-from-ukraine-war-china/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The war in Ukraine is far from over, but a consensus is forming in Chinese policy circles that one country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway Singing Coach, 87, Has Brain Injury After Street Attack...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/03/13/broadway-singing-coach-87-has-brain-injury-after-street-attack/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A highly regarded 87-year-old singing coach has a traumatic brain injury after a woman pushed her to the ground just</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO nonalignment creates risk for Finland, Sweden...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/amid-russian-aggression-nato-nonalignment-creates-risk-for-finland-and-sweden/ar-AAV0UjQ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians cross Mexico border to seek US asylum...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russians-cross-mexico-border-seek-050154594.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 8,600 Russians have sought refuge in the U.S. on the Mexican border in recent months. Many fly from Moscow to Cancun, entering Mexico as tourists, and go to Tijuana, where they pool money to buy cars. (March 14)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man sought in homeless killings in NYC, DC...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/new-york-city-new-york-shootings-b0cdeff465d2ab4003db26986635885a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Police in New York City were searching for a man who authorities say shot and killed one homeless person and wounded another in separate street attacks. The shootings occurred early Saturday morning, according to the NYPD.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most-fit 33% less likely to develop Alzheimer's...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/health/medical/the-most-fit-are-33-percent-less-likely-to-develop-alzheimer-s-report-says/ar-AAV0CKr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel grapples with fate of oligarchs...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-viktor-vekselberg-mikhail-fridman-europe-7744b07a6fb0d2321aabe958cb952dd8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel is grappling with how to deal with dozens of Jewish Russian oligarchs as Western nations step up sanctions on businesspeople with ties to Russian President Vladimir Putin. A worried Israeli government has formed a high-level committee to see how the country can maintain its status as a haven for any Jew without running afoul of the biting sanctions targeting Putin’s inner circle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US view of Putin: Angry, frustrated, likely to escalate war...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-putin-nato-william-burns-europe-1271f76008b3e639df6ff21e3644e339</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — More than two weeks into a war he expected to dominate in two days, Vladimir Putin is projecting anger, frustration at his military’s failures and a willingness to cause even more violence and destruction in Ukraine, in the assessment of U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pregnant woman, baby die after maternity ward bombed...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/russia-ukraine-health-europe-c0f2f859296f9f02be24fc9edfca1085</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MARIUPOL, Ukraine (AP) — A pregnant woman and her baby have died after Russia bombed the maternity hospital where she was meant to give birth, The Associated Press has learned. Images of the woman being rushed to an ambulance on a stretcher had circled the world, epitomizing the horror of an attack on humanity’s most innocent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China battles multiple outbreaks, driven by stealth omicron...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/covid-business-health-china-taiwan-d2d2a0e6635a90270cfd746854cdd856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TAIPEI, Taiwan (AP) — China banned most people from leaving a coronavirus-hit northeastern province and mobilized military reservists Monday as the fast-spreading “stealth omicron” variant fuels the country's biggest outbreak since the start of the pandemic two years ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Trump Republicans lining up for 2024 shadow primary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/2022-midterm-elections-larry-hogan-adam-kinzinger-donald-trump-liz-cheney-b62ae9bb1ee38bf3ec18da59352bf3dd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Maryland Gov. Larry Hogan is planning trips to Iowa and New Hampshire. Rep. Adam Kinzinger, R-Ill., is considering a rough timeline for a potential presidential announcement. And allies of Rep.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Had been diagnosed with terminal prostate cancer...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/13/william-hurt-actor-dead-dies/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The veteran character actor's death was announced Sunday by his son, who said his father had passed from natural causes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'My place is still on the field'...</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2022/03/13/tom-brady-announces-nfl-comeback/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady is not retiring after all -- the superstar Tampa Bay QB just announced his return for a 23rd NFL season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNRETIREMENT:   Brady announces 'I'm coming back' for 23rd season 'in Tampa'...</title>
      <link>https://www.nfl.com/news/buccaneers-qb-tom-brady-announces-i-m-coming-back-for-23rd-season-in-tampa</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nfl.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Roughly two months after announcing his retirement, quarterback ﻿Tom Brady﻿ announced Sunday he will return to play for his 23rd season and do so "in Tampa."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan calls ramp up on Biden to give Ukraine jets, weapons...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/Bipartisan-calls-ramp-up-on-Biden-to-give-Ukraine-16998825.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - A growing number of U.S. lawmakers ratcheted up pressure on President Joe...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At rally, Florida Dems rail against DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/politics/at-rally-florida-democrats-rail-against-gov-desantis/article_30392a11-5c75-5e12-972d-6418f8348698.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FORT LAUDERDALE, Fla. — Charlie Crist, Nikki Fried and Annette Taddeo came together over the weekend, united in their diagnosis of the biggest problem they see plaguing Florida: Gov. Ron</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jussie Smollett put in psych ward after being deemed self-harm risk...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2022/03/jussie-smollett-psych-ward-cook-county-jail-brother-instagram-1234977231/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Authorities are apparently taking no chances on Jussie Smollett’s safety while incarcerated at the Cook County jail. Reacting to Smollett’s outburst upon being sentenced Thursday for hi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky visits injured troops in hospital, gives out medals...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/4886037/zelensky-visits-injured-troops-hospital/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRESIDENT Volodymyr Zelensky defiantly visited wounded troops in hospital and handed out medals today. The Ukraine war leader visited a military hospital in the Kyiv region yesterday to meet some o…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Unlawful entry' onto national security aide's property spooks White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/police-investigated-e2-80-98unlawful-entry-e2-80-99-onto-property-of-white-house-national-security-aide/ar-AAUZxy3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran rockets hit near US consulate in Iraq...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/syria-middle-east-damascus-iraq-iran-7a4ea6281fe6191a4e4b640c58c7fd49</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) — Iran claimed responsibility Sunday for a missile barrage that struck near a sprawling U.S. consulate complex in northern Iraq, saying it was retaliation for an Israeli strike in Syria that killed two members of its Revolutionary Guard earlier this week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBAMA COVID...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/obama-tests-positive-for-covid-says-he-is-feeling-fine-b0c641f387f71e2badcd3ce999ab9a6b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former President Barack Obama said on Sunday that he had tested positive for the coronavirus , though he's feeling relatively healthy and his wife, Michelle, tested negative.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOURNALIST SHOT DEAD</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/brent-renaud-obituary-russia-ukraine-bd0aa404e1b64dbdc464b6660fd280af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brent Renaud, an acclaimed filmmaker who traveled to some of the darkest and most dangerous corners of the world for documentaries that transported audiences to little-known places of suffering, died Sunday after Russian forces opened fire on his vehicle in Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'POWER OF DOG' WINS BAFTA...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/bafta-awards-dune-power-of-the-dog-cb0ef160241b8542a6fdc278dcd2786f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Sci-fi epic “Dune” won five prizes and brooding Western “The Power of the Dog” was named best picture as the British Academy Film Awards returned Sunday with a live, black-tie ceremony after a pandemic-curtailed event in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILLIAM HURT DEAD AT 71...</title>
      <link>https://variety.com/2022/film/news/william-hurt-dead-kiss-of-the-spider-woman-1235203576/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;variety.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;William Hurt, who became a top leading man in the 1980s, winning an Oscar for 1985’s “Kiss of the Spider Woman” and starring in “The Big Chill” and “Body Heat,&amp;#…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
