<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>How Merchandise Bundles Undid the Album Chart...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/22/how-merchandise-bundles-undid-the-album-chart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Approximately half the albums that have topped the Billboard album chart since the beginning of 2019 have been made available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does coronavirus spread at concert? Germans do test...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc8833d2fcd394b6e1881ce63eb85476</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BERLIN (AP) — Germany held a pop concert Saturday to see how those attending would spread coronavirus. German researchers studying COVID-19 packed part of a Leipzig arena with volunteers,...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ketamine That's Injected During Arrests Draws New Scrutiny...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/ketamine-thats-injected-during-arrests-170803241.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police stopped Elijah McClain on the street in suburban Denver last year after deeming the young Black man suspicious. Paramedics inject it into people like McClain as a sedative, often at the behest of police who believe suspects are out of control. Officially, ketamine is used in emergencies when there’s a safety concern for medical staff or the patient.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galapagos Islands threatened by huge Chinese fishing fleet...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/charles-darwins-famous-galapagos-islands-22562406</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Scientists fear the 325-strong flotilla with vessels the size of a football pitch has put endangered species at further risk in the waters around the Galapagos Islands</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Self-Destructive Syndrome'?</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/512604-does-trump-suffer-from-self-destructive-syndrome</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump is intelligent and has good instincts, but even die-hard supporters wish he would speak and act presidential.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New study reveals appliance that may be spreading...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2020/08/22/air-conditioned-rooms-help-spread-covid-19-research-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dry air and air-conditioned rooms can help spread the coronavirus, according to an Indian-German research team that looked at the role of relative humidity in the transmission of infections. For of…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE SLAVE MONKEYS OF THAILAND...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/worldnews/12444192/monkey-slave-schools-coconuts-supermarket-thailand-sex-street-performers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SNATCHED from his mother as a baby, chained up alone and forced to work at a coconut farm for ten hours a day, all little Kulap knows is suffering. The pig-tailed macaque is one of thousands of mon…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: 'DEEP STATE' DELAYING VAX!</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1352011/trump-fda-deep-state-drug-administration-vaccine-after-election/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DONALD Trump has called the FDA part of the “deep state” and accused the drug administration of slow-walking vaccine test until after the election. The president made the conspiracy com…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders president to pay legal fees to Stormy Daniels...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/regulation/court-battles/513212-judge-orders-trump-to-pay-legal-fees-to-stormy-daniels</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A California court ordered President Trump to pay $44,100 to Stephanie Clifford, the adult-film actress known as Stormy Daniels, to cover her legal fees regarding her nondisclosure agreement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could hurricanes collide?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2020/08/22/tropical-storms-laura-marco-collide-fujiwhara-effect-explained/3410073001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tropical Storms Laura and Marco are forecast to be in the Gulf of Mexico at the same time. So, could they form a super hurricane? We explain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOOK: Barr pushed to 'muzzle' FOXNEWS Judge Nap...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2020/aug/22/william-barr-rupert-murdoch-muzzle-andrew-napolitano-fox-news-trump-critic-book</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attorney general met media mogul in October 2019, as Judge Andrew Napolitano said Trump should be impeached</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Dems chase generational change from opposite corners of movement...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/In-Mass-two-Democrats-chase-generational-change-15507162.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alex Morse and Joe Kennedy both want to turn the page to a new generation of Democrats, suggesting that entrenched incumbents sometimes just tend to coast.  Who should have the real clout on Capitol Hill?  "It's not those members of Congress who have been there 30 or 40 years," Morse, 31, said Friday in a telephone interview.  "I am running against somebody who's been in elective office in Massachusetts for 47 years," Rep. Kennedy, 39, said Thursday, rattling off the extent of his opponent's career in politics. "I think by all accounts, he was pretty much a figure of the political establishment."  Morse, the four-term mayor of Holyoke in western Massachusetts, is trying to unseat Democratic Rep. Richard Neal, a 30-year incumbent who chairs the powerful House Ways and Means Committee in the state's Sept. 1 Democratic primary. And Kennedy, a four-term member of the House from outside Boston, is running against Democratic Sen. Edward Markey, whose first congressional oath of office in 1977 took place before Kennedy was born.  Yet Morse and Kennedy find themselves in opposite corners of today's Democratic moment, a political interchange that is confusing with its mixed paths of generational challenges and ideological purity tests.  Morse has the full backing of the liberal groups that have helped knock off a handful of veteran Democratic incumbents in the past two years, paving the way to Congress for a younger, more diverse array of lawmakers. Most of the same groups have rallied behind Markey, despite his being a 74-year-old White man, after he forged an ideological alliance with Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, D-N.Y., whose upset primary win in June 2018 served as a bolt of lightning for these far-left liberals.  That's left Kennedy running defensively at times, as if he is...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Hamptons, party hosts pay for rapid tests at door...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/22/us/hamptons-parties-coronavirus-tests-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Asma Rashid goes to a lot of exclusive parties these days -- but for a different reason. In the Hamptons, hosts pay big bucks for her to administer rapid coronavirus test to guests at the door before they can attend social events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Says FDA Slowing Virus Research to Hurt Him in Election...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-says-fda-slowing-virus-research-to-hurt-him-in-election</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump Says FDA Slowing Virus Research to Hurt Him in Election</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firefighters 'running on fumes,' begging for equipment, manpower amid firestorms...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/firefighters-running-fumes-bay-area-120052932.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Santa Cruz fire agencies say they are not getting enough help from the state, which admits it is struggling with too many fires and not enough resources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asteroid to pass close to Earth day before presidential election...</title>
      <link>https://www.whio.com/news/trending/asteroid-predicted-pass-close-earth-day-before-presidential-election/7NTEFU5YVVGFXMGT3ADBXNZ7BQ/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.whio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An asteroid discovered in 2018 will fly very close to Earth on Nov. 2 according to The Center for Near Earth Objects Studies at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCIENTIST WARNS CORONAVIRUS WILL BE 'WITH US FOREVER'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/coronavirus-uk-pandemic-end-vaccine-flu-ongoing-mark-walport-a9683246.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears Going Extinct in Stock Market's $13 Trillion Rebound...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/bears-going-extinct-stock-market-201228099.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Skeptics are a dying breed in American equities. It’s another illustration of how risky it has become to doubt the resilience of the market’s $13 trillion surge since late March.Going by the short positions of hedge funds, resistance to rising prices is the lowest in 16 years. Bears pulled</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holy Land 'on brink of war' as doomsday preacher says Bible prophecy 'happening'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/holy-land-on-brink-war-22555929</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel has warned Hamas 'if they want war they will get war' and evangelical YouTube sensation Pastor Paul Begley says any more conflict would be the ultimate battle for the 'Holy Land'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robot customer vows to 'never date again'; AI replicant 'perfect'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robot-customer-vows-never-22554231</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: Author and documentary-maker Jenny Kleeman has talked Daily Star Online through the extracts of her new book Sex Robots &amp; Vegan Meat, released this year</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home sales spike record 24.7% as prices set new high...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/21/july-home-sales-spike-a-record-24point7percent-as-prices-set-a-new-high.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sales of existing homes soared 24.7% in July from June, according to the National Association of Realtors. The median price of a home sold in July rose 8.5% annually to $304,100.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rotting food, dead animals and chaos at  facilities amid cutbacks...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/armageddon-rotting-food-dead-animals-180715834.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Accounts from employees at California postal facilities provide a glimpse of the chaos amid both the pandemic and widespread cuts imposed by the USPS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 scary? Japan offers coffins, chainsaws for stress relief...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822071916-ncbqw</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH–CORONAVIRUS/JAPAN-COFFINS (TV, PIX):COVID-19 scary? Japan group offers coffins, chainsaws for stress relief</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderate Tulsa mayor faces fierce political crosscurrents...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e03160a401e9e342265c501142c88ac5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;By all accounts, Tulsa Mayor G.T. Bynum has been a fast-rising political star in Oklahoma. Part of a political dynasty whose uncle, grandfather and great-grandfather all served as mayor of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houston hit by both?</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/weather/marco-and-laura-headed-in-to-gulf-texas-impacts-possible/39346/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tracks on both storms are still wide and uncertain, as Houston's weather is perfect for prepping your home and family for next week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRIVING THROUGH HELL</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-8653015/Dashcam-captures-terrifying-drive-California-wildfires-killed-six.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Horrifying footage (left) shows cars driving through the raging flames of the Hennessey Fire in Napa County Friday, as California continues to be at the peril of 560 fires.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bush Comeback Tactics From 1988 Echo in Race...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2020/08/22/a-glimmer-of-hope-for-trump-how-bush-mounted-a-comeback-in-1988/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George H.W. Bush was in trouble. It was July 1988 and Michael Dukakis, the Democratic candidate for president, was on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two of Larry King's children have died in the past three weeks...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2020/08/21/larry-kings-son-and-daughter-pass-away-within-weeks-of-each-other/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;King’s son Andy passed suddenly a couple of weeks ago, and his daughter Chaia died Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP:   Will not know election results 'for weeks, months, maybe never'...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-warns-election-vote-count-201019233.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US President Donald Trump warned Friday that the results of the  November 3 presidential election could take weeks or months to determine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans set to make the case...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/republicans-case-trump-democrats-endorse-170709843.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Republican Party is to make its case next week for four more years of President Donald Trump after his Democratic opponent Joe Biden wrapped up his party&amp;#39;s convention with a vow to end what he called a &amp;quot;chapter of American darkness.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'SEND IN THE NATIONAL GUARD'</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200822004209-em3s2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-WILDFIRE/ (UPDATE 7, PIX, TV):UPDATE 7-California governor calls wildfires 'deadly moment,' urges residents to flee</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Total anarchy, madness and chaos'...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200821204831-03ekh</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/CONVENTION (UPDATE 2, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 2-Battered by Democrats, Trump fires back against 'total anarchy, madness and chaos'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mounting deaths reveal an outsize toll on people of color...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/a8e3244c77bcaf31efc826bbbe4a9d19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As many as 215,000 more people than usual died in the U.S. during the first seven months of 2020, suggesting that the number of lives lost to the coronavirus is significantly higher than the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC TOPS...</title>
      <link>http://www.showbuzzdaily.com/articles/democratic-national-convention-television-ratings.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbuzzdaily.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECKER OUT AT NATIONAL ENQUIRER...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/national-enquirer-chief-david-pecker-out-after-ami-merger</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The tabloid king has been dethroned as the financially troubled American Media Inc. merges with a company that markets face masks and vitamin supplements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO chief believes covid pandemic could last another 2 years...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/1350542/coronavirus-pandemic-another-two-years-who/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;THE CORONAVIRUS pandemic could last for another TWO YEARS, according to a World Health Organisation chief. Speaking on Friday director general Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus compared the virus to the 1…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALWELL IN LIMBO AT LIBERTY...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2020/08/21/falwell-decision-liberty-university-400136</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came two weeks after Falwell was placed on leave from the prominent Christian university.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CALIFORNIA WILDFIRES SOME OF LARGEST IN STATE HISTORY</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/california-fires-spread-fouling-air-204929058.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thick smoke blanketed large areas of central and northern California on Friday as more people fled some of the biggest fires in the state&amp;#39;s history which have raged largely uncontrolled through the week.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24.6 MILLION WATCH BIDEN SPEECH...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20200821211532-2p53t</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-ELECTION/TV RATINGS (UPDATE 2):UPDATE 2-Democratic convention closing night draws event's biggest TV audience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIKTOK to challenge U.S. order...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-tiktok-trump-exclusive/exclusive-tiktok-to-challenge-u-s-order-banning-transactions-with-the-video-app-idUSKBN25H2QG</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TikTok is preparing to mount a legal challenge as early as Monday to President Donald Trump's executive order prohibiting transactions with the popular short video app and its Chinese parent ByteDance, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors suggest more charges could be coming...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/state/florida/article245138570.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cases tied to Sturgis motorcycle rally cross state lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/21/us/sturgis-motorcyle-rally-sd-covid-nebraska-trnd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coronavirus cases linked to the Sturgis motorcycle rally in South Dakota last week have now reached across state lines to Nebraska, public health officials said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICROSOFT plans cloud contract push with foreign govts after $10 billion JEDI win...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2020/08/21/microsoft-plans-cloud-push-with-foreign-governments-after-jedi-win.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Microsoft hopes to keep widening its cloud infrastructure business by meeting public-sector needs abroad while maintaining a tight collaboration with the Trump Administration, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PECKER OUT: Embattled NATIONAL ENQUIRER CEO to depart...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/media_ink/status/1296913670421778436</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US Army Green Beret charged with Russian espionage...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2020/aug/21/peter-rafael-dzibinski-debbins-ex-army-green-beret/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal prosecutors have charged a former Army Green Beret living in northern Virginia with espionage activity with Russia dating back as far as 1996.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton Gave State Dept. Job to Ghislaine Maxwell's Nephew...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/hillary-clinton-gave-state-department-job-to-epstein-madam-ghislaine-maxwells-nephew-says-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OK! Magazine first reported on the ties, days after pictures surfaced of an Epstein victim giving a neck massage to former President Bill Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC CEO sent APPLE 2 am declaration of war...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/technology/epic-s-ceo-sent-apple-a-2-a-m-declaration-of-war-over-fortnite-epic-will-no-longer-adhere-to-apple-s-payment-processing-restrictions/ar-BB18f38I</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fight Over Kennedy Dynasty Splinters Dems...</title>
      <link>https://talkingpointsmemo.com/news/pelosi-says-she-endorsed-kennedy-because-she-was-upset-by-assault-on-kennedy-family-legacy</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;talkingpointsmemo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Speaker Nancy Pelosi (D-CA) said on Thursday that her startling endorsement of Rep. Joe Kennedy&amp;#8217;s (D-MA) primary campaign against...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
