<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>FUNDRAISING BLOWOUT; $25M IN DAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-raises-more-money-in-24-hours-than-opening-days-of-sanders-biden-orourke-harris-combined</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Presidential Trump brought in nearly $25 million in the first 24 hours of his official reelection efforts, according to Republican National Committee Chairwoman Ronna McDaniel — more than the combined totals of five of his major Democratic rivals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slavery Reparations Hearing Explodes: 'Chill, Chill, Chill!'</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/chill-chill-chill-chill-congressional-hearing-explodes-as-witness-trashes-slavery-reparations-bill/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A congressional hearing erupted when Quillette writer Coleman Hughes trashed a bill to study slavery reparations as a "moral and political mistake," forcing the chair of the hearing to tell the audience to "chill" several times.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bungled fax sparks Japan nuclear scare...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190619-get-fax-right-bungling-officials-spark-japan-nuclear-scare</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get your fax right: Bungling officials spark Japan nuclear scare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWDOWN ON HILL:  White House lawyer refusing to let Hope Hicks answer questions...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jun/19/democrats-say-white-house-lawyer-refusing-let-hope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Democrats on the House Judiciary Committee on Wednesday said a White House lawyer is refusing to let Hope Hicks answer questions about her time in the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Kicks Off 2020 Campaign -- Against Hillary?</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/trumps-orlando-2020-presidential-campaign-launch-speech-donald-1-hillary-0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gang was all in Orlando for the president’s re-election kickoff, and his old 2016 foe was foremost on his mind. Whether that is a winning formula for 2020 remains to be seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE averaging only 7,000 deportations PER MONTH...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Trump-renews-pledge-to-deport-millions-but-ICE-14016222.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has begun his reelection bid by reviving a campaign promise to deport "millions of illegal aliens" from the United States, saying his administration will get to work on that goal "next week" with raids across the country.  But the president's ambitious deportation goals have crashed, again and again, into the earthly reality of the U.S. immigration enforcement system.  U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement is averaging approximately 7,000 deportations per month from the U.S. interior, according to the agency's latest data. With unauthorized border crossings soaring under Trump to their highest levels in more than a decade, ICE has been facing a shortage of funds and detention beds, and experts say that a large-scale push to arrest and deport hundreds of thousands of migrants would be exorbitantly expensive and highly unlikely.  For ICE, making "at large" arrests in homes and neighborhoods - the key to chipping away at the "millions" Trump wants to expel - will require significant amounts of planning, coordination and secrecy. By telegraphing plans to begin a nationwide roundup, the president has risked undermining the effectiveness of ICE's largest and most complex enforcement operation in years.  Trump and Mark Morgan, the acting director of ICE, talked several times over recent weeks about the operation, including as recently as this weekend. But senior White House and immigration officials did not know the president planned to announce it on Twitter, a senior White House official said Tuesday, and many felt it was detracting from the launch of the campaign. But Trump is anxious to appear he is making progress on immigration and remains fixated on the issue, advisers say.  The sensitive plan is aimed at sweeping up and deporting thousands of migrant family members in major U.S. cities who were...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polanski's Epic Spy Movie Set to Rock Venice...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/06/19/roman-polanskis-epic-dreyfus-affair-movie-an-officer-and-a-spy-set-to-rock-venice-film-festival</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All eyes in the film world are starting to look at the Venice Film Festival, which will not have Martin Scorsese’s “The Irishman” and likely will have James Gray’s “Ad…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government's Massive Biometric Database Moving to AMAZON...</title>
      <link>https://www.nextgov.com/it-modernization/2019/06/dhs-move-biometric-data-hundreds-millions-people-amazon-cloud/157837/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nextgov.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The department seeks a new platform to identify people using fingerprints, irises and faces, and eventually DNA, palm prints, scars and tattoos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New 'cat-fox' species discovered... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/weird-news/786581/cat-fox-new-species-cat-corsica</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMERICAN Flight Diverted After Drunken Passenger Punches Attendant...</title>
      <link>https://pittsburgh.cbslocal.com/2019/06/19/pittsburgh-dallas-flight-drunk-passenger-emergency-landing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pittsburgh.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A flight from Pittsburgh to Dallas had to be diverted to Oklahoma City because of an alleged unruly and drunken passenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian cosmonauts refusing to give sperm...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/06/19/russian-cosmonauts-refusing-hand-sperm-vladimir-putins-scientists-10014617/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government researchers are trying to gather semen samples, but spacemen are 'smiling and rejecting' their advances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy Presents Evidence of Iran Role in Attack on Tankers...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-navy-presents-evidence-iran-110353112.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- A U.S. navy investigator presented what he said was evidence of Iran’s involvement in the attacks on tankers near the Persian Gulf, laying out the most detailed assessment that’s been made public since the incident raised tensions in the region earlier this month.Commander Sean Kido, an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia's Most Modern Warship And Its Escorts Have Entered Caribbean Sea...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedrive.com/the-war-zone/28591/russias-most-modern-warship-and-its-escorts-have-entered-the-caribbean-sea</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedrive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is the first time in years a Russian surface combatant has sailed into the region, let alone one able to fire modern land attack cruise missiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dem establishment warms to Warren; Compromise nominee?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/19/democratic-establishment-elizabeth-warren-1369874</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Centrists who once said the senator would lead the party to ruin are coming around to her as an alternative to Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BABY TO BE BORN IN SPACE?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/786513/russia-first-baby-born-space</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power outage stops service at New York Penn Station...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/06/19/power-outage-stops-service-at-new-york-penn-station.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;All trains travelling in and out of New York Penn Station have been halted because of an Amtrak overhead wire issue, New Jersey Transit said Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOUR MORE CHEERS!</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/947182a691e6498ca4488e9fc8f9e4b5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eroding trust in vaccines leaves populations vulnerable, global study finds...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190619135831-k2uov</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HEALTH-VACCINES/CONFIDENCE (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Eroding trust in vaccines leaves populations vulnerable, global study finds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raises $24.8 million in less than 24 hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/19/trump-campaign-contributions-rnc-1369896</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The announcement came hours after the president formally launched his 2020 bid with a rally in Orlando, Fla.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens 'murdered friend after man on internet offered them millions'...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/alaska-teen-murder-denali-brehmer-cynthia-hoffman-darin-schilmiller-trial-police-a8964741.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Did 'MURDER MYSTERY' really just break NETFLIX ratings record?</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/19/did-murder-mystery-really-just-break-a-netflix-ratings-record/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After years of declining to get specific about numbers, Netflix is finally clueing the public in. The streaming behemoth wants you to know its new comedy caper “Murder Mystery” is a big…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sperm donor wins legal battle to be recognized as father...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2019/06/19/australian-sperm-donor-wins-legal-battle-recognised-father/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A sperm donor in Australia has won a landmark High Court battle to have his rights as a parent confirmed and to stop his child being taken to live overseas by its mother.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiny houses entice budget-conscious Americans...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tiny-houses-entice-budget-conscious-americans-025529673.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a country that nearly always believes bigger is better -- think supersize fries, giant cars and 10-gallon hats -- more and more Americans are downsizing their living quarters. Welcome to the world of tiny homes, most of them less than 400 square feet (less than 40 square meters), which savvy buyers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel Holds Large Military Drill...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/israel-holds-large-military-drill-amid-us-iran-63805768</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Israel holding largest military drill in years, with troops simulating a future war with Hezbollah</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Porn stars protest INSTAGRAM nude photo rules at company HQ...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jun/19/instagram-nude-photo-policy-protest</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Artists, activists and models join in condemning confusing guidelines leading to account suspensions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm of 1,000 quakes hit Southern California -- How nervous should we be?</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-earthquake-swarm-small-20190619-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It can be worth taking note of small earthquakes. But what they may mean is never quite clear.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WIRE: What Have Rallies Accomplished?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2019-06-19/what-have-donald-trump-s-rallies-accomplished</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Violent Brawl Erupts Between Parents At Little League Game; Rage At 13-Year-Old Ump...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/06/18/video-brawl-little-league-game-lakewood-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lakewood Police Department is looking for a group of adults who got into a physical fight at a Little League Game on Saturday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As legal glare turns to Trump, his faith in Supreme Court may be tested...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190619094148-dc3mj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-COURT/TRUMP (PIX, TV):As legal glare turns to Trump, his faith in Supreme Court may be tested</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Global Exorcism 'Boom'...</title>
      <link>https://www.vice.com/en_in/article/xwnmza/exorcisms-rise-2019-pentecostalism-catholicism</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.vice.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;So many people are needing their demons exorcised, the Vatican recently had to put on a dedicated "exorcist training convention".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Committee To Hear Proposal For Slavery Reparations...</title>
      <link>https://www.npr.org/2019/06/18/733880321/congressional-hearing-on-slavery-reparations-set-for-wednesday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A proposal to create a commission to study reparations for African Americans comes as the presidential election season is kicking into gear. Some Democratic hopefuls support reparations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia aiming to have first baby born in space...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7157711/Russia-aiming-baby-born-space-scientist-claims.html </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr Irina Ogneva, head of cell biophysics at the Russian Academy of Sciences, revealed the country aims to have the first baby born in space, but is struggling to find volunteers for the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'MIDSOMMAR' early screening reactions hail horror 'masterpiece'...</title>
      <link>https://ew.com/movies/2019/06/19/midsommar-reactions/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;ew.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I0UWIya-O0s On Sunday, actress Florence Pugh declared the horror film Midsommar — the second movie from Hereditary director Ari Aster…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KICKOFF:  FLORIDA...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-kick-off-election-florida-democrats-aim-win/story?id=63772223</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump kicks off his 2020 reelection bid in Florida, a critical swing state that's also gotten early attention from the Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo warns about trigger for military action...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Pompeo-warns-Iran-about-trigger-for-US-military-14016197.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has privately delivered warnings intended for Iranian leaders that any attack by Tehran or its proxies resulting in the death of even one American service member will generate a military counterattack, U.S. officials said.  The potential for a significant military response to even an isolated event has fueled a broader internal debate among top Trump officials about whether the administration's policy exceeds President Donald Trump's specific goal of preventing Iran from acquiring a nuclear weapon, the officials said.  One such message about retaliation was delivered during a hastily arranged visit to Baghdad by Pompeo in May after officials detected a spike in intelligence indicating that Iran's militia proxies might resume assaults on U.S. forces operating in proximity to them across Iraq. While such attacks were common during the Iraq War, Pompeo told Iraqi leaders in a message he knew would be relayed to Tehran that a single American casualty would prompt the United States to hit back. That specific warning has not been previously reported.  "What happens if Americans are killed? That changes the whole thing," said a senior administration official involved in Iran policy who, like others, spoke on the condition of anonymity to talk freely. "It changes everything."  Speaking during a visit to U.S. Central Command headquarters in Tampa, Florida, on Tuesday, Pompeo said Trump "does not want war" but stressed the United States would act if assaulted. "We are there to deter aggression," he said. Trump himself has sent mixed messages about the seriousness of Iran's actions and how he would respond to them.  The sudden departure Tuesday of Patrick Shanahan, who has served as acting defense secretary since January, could further sideline the Pentagon, which has campaigned to reduce the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP STAGES GREATEST SHOW YET</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/06/18/donald-trump-2020-launch-florida-1369868</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The president’s elaborate reelection rally in Florida is designed to project success at a moment of internal chaos and tepid polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA MEGA ORLANDO</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-kicks-off-re-election-campaign-at-orlando-rally-live-blog</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump will formally launch his re-election campaign Tuesday night at the Amway Center in Orlando.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York to Approve One of the World's Most Ambitious Climate Plans... </title>
      <link>https://www.eenews.net/stories/1060616261</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.eenews.net&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gov. Andrew Cuomo (D) said yesterday he has reached an agreement with legislative leaders over a bill to slash New York's greenhouse gas emissions, setting the stage for one of the most significant climate victories since President Trump took office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force arms bombers with hypersonic missile for first time...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/786398/us-air-force-hypersonic-missiles-arrw-stratofortress-b-52-lockheed-martin-russia-china</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZFEED:  Tony Robbins Punishes Followers By Making Them Drink Unidentified Brown Liquid...</title>
      <link>https://www.buzzfeednews.com/article/janebradley/tony-robbins-punishes-followers-by-making-them-drink</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.buzzfeednews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;At high-pressure seminars, the self-help superstar punishes people who don’t measure up by feeding them a “gross shot” of unidentified brown liquid. His lawyers denied the mixture contains laxatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert looks to seal off attacks on swimmers...</title>
      <link>https://www.bostonherald.com/2019/06/18/shark-expert-looks-to-seal-off-attacks-on-swimmers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bostonherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state’s top shark expert is jumping in with a conservancy group to study how great whites hunt seals to help keep swimmers safe. Greg Skomal told the Herald the goal is to track great whi…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiritual adviser says 'demonic networks' have aligned themselves against president...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/449226-trump-spiritual-adviser-a-demonic-network-aligned-itself-against-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's spiritual adviser Paula White said in the opening prayer before his campaign kickoff rally in Orlando, Fla., on Tuesday that "demonic networks" have aligned themselves against the president.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift 'CALM DOWN' Breathtakingly Elitist...</title>
      <link>https://thefederalist.com/2019/06/18/taylor-swifts-need-calm-breathtakingly-elitist/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thefederalist.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Cuts Away from Speech After 'Sucks!' Chant...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-cnn-cuts-away-trump-speech-after-crowd-shouts-cnn-sucks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘That is a lot of fake news back there’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex doll maker creates replicas of dead partners to combat loneliness...</title>
      <link>https://metro.co.uk/2019/06/18/sex-doll-maker-creates-replicas-dead-partners-combat-loneliness-im-providing-comfort-9997632/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;metro.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'It really isn't not all seedy and sexual.'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pompeo warns about trigger for military action...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/pompeo-warns-iran-about-trigger-for-us-military-action-as-some-in-administration-question-aggressive-policy/2019/06/18/48bd3be0-9116-11e9-b570-6416efdc0803_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some officials question whether pressure on Iran exceeds President Trump’s specific goal of preventing the country from acquiring a nuclear weapon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Campaign manager: Polling is dead...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/trump-campaign-manager-polling-is-dead</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's campaign manager says polling is no longer reliable, days after a big leak of unflattering internal polling data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans make up Mexico's largest demographic of immigrants...</title>
      <link>https://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/border-baja-california/story/2019-06-15/americans-make-up-mexicos-largest-demographic-of-immigrants</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sandiegouniontribune.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The net flow of United States immigrants to Mexico is larger than the flow of Mexican-born immigrants into the United States: Mexican government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORLANDO SENTINEL gets  jump on 2020 endorsements:  Not Donald... </title>
      <link>https://www.orlandosentinel.com/opinion/editorials/os-op-sentinel-not-endorsing-donald-trump-2020-20190618-63ya7cyb5ngf3irllodwxnznui-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.orlandosentinel.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the 2020 election, the Orlando Sentinel will not endorse President Donald Trump for re-election. The president has sown chaos and division, and the nation must do better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vows to deport 'millions' of illegals, but it's unclear how...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarynews.com/news/national/trump-vows-to-deport-millions-of-migrants-but-it-s/article_b2b5ba3b-f699-5b68-8152-6a81047e8249.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — President Donald Trump’s bold but vague pledge to deport “millions” of migrants facing removal orders, starting next week, came on the eve of his reelection kickoff Tuesday night</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATE CUT NOW?</title>
      <link>https://www.arcamax.com/politics/politicalnews/s-2220600?fs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.arcamax.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON -- President Donald Trump has been hectoring the Federal Reserve to lower interest rates, and financial markets are screaming for a cut. This even though rates are historically low and the economy is sailing along, albeit with some recent gray clouds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax Law Made Americans Less Charitable, Nonprofits Say...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/trump-tax-law-made-americans-155336882.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump’s Tax Law Made Americans Less Charitable, Nonprofits Say</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIVE...</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=udSUXW2_OiI</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.youtube.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tuesday, June 18, 2019: Join RSBN's Liz Willis, Bailee Byers, Max Kleiber, Baylor Cook and cameraman Gage Fuller for live all day coverage as President Donal...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential measles exposure reported at Newark...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-outbreak-potential-exposure-new-jersey-newark-liberty-international-airport-2019-06-18/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;International traveler who has been diagnosed with measles was at Newark Liberty International Airport on May 29</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation Z's suicide epidemic...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/suicide-generation-z-epidemic-cee7990a-243e-489c-8242-2aefc545bba7.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spike has been accompanied by increased social media use, anxiety, depression and self-inflicted injuries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Man beheads roommate's dog as she moves out...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7778d121ee9f4d739672ea37f78b3d19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Very active' killer whale pod seen for first time ever in Monterey Bay...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/whales-sharks/article/orcas-monterey-whale-watching-transient-killer-14015354.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whale watchers off the Central California coast Monday were exceptionally lucky; they witnessed a local animal encounter that has never been documented before. A known pod of transient killer whales from the Pacific Northwest was seen in Monterey Bay for the first time in recorded history. Among them was a very young calf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds: Mexican gang flooding towns with drugs from inside CA prison...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article231685953.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TARGETS: People in USA with final deportation orders...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/local/immigration/article231687048.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marilyn Monroe Statue Stolen From Walk of Fame...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/c/marilyn-monroe-statue-stolen</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's being called "the great Marilyn caper of 2019."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dairy Cows Fed Coffee Creamer For Best Milk Results At Award-Winning Farm...</title>
      <link>https://detroit.cbslocal.com/2019/06/18/dairy-cows-fed-oddball-ingredient-best-milk-results/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;detroit.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number two dairy farm in the country for milk production is feeding its cows unusual ingredient: coffee creamer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marijuana use doubles in pregnant women...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/91b825a94dc246f28c5fdd739ab42b22</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 mystery deaths in Dominican Republic leave tourists terrified...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/786346/dominican-republic-deaths-american-tourists-insecticide-pesticide-poison</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return flight filled with sick passengers...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/06/18/dominican-republic-tourist-says-flight-was-full-of-sick-passengers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Mississippi woman who went on a mother-daughter trip to the Dominican Republic says she fell ill — and, adding insult to injury, was stuck on a miserable return flight filled with passengers suff…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The City Where People Come To Die...</title>
      <link>http://www.bbc.com/travel/story/20190617-indias-city-where-people-come-to-die</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For Hindus, Varanasi is one of the holiest cities in the world, and ‘salvation homes’ have been set up across the city to house the men and women who come to live – and die – here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-MLB star spent 9 hours dumpster diving...</title>
      <link>https://www.nj.com/union/2019/06/ex-mlb-star-lenny-dykstra-spent-9-hours-dumpster-diving-outside-a-jersey-mikes-heres-why.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The former Mets and Phillies star says he left his $80,000 dentures in a napkin at Jersey Mike's Subs in Linden and that workers put them in the garbage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stage Set For First Debate...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/stage-set-first-democratic-debate-here-s-primer-night-1-n1018551</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC announced the positions of the Democratic presidential candidates for the two-night debate on June 26 and 27.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe's oldest person dead at 116...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/italian-woman-who-was-europes-oldest-person-has-died-at-116/ar-AAD3Y8x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishers Plead With Trump Not to Impose 'Bible Tax'...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-06-18/publishers-plead-with-trump-not-to-impose-a-china-bible-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$1 Billion of Cocaine Seized at Philly Shipping Yard... </title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/06/18/15000-kilos-of-cocaine-confiscated-during-drug-bust-at-philadelphia-port-federal-sources-say/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal sources confirmed to CBS3 that a bust took place on a cargo ship that was docked at the port.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA vaccine bill amended to allow more exemptions...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/politics-government/capitol-alert/article231680513.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$750 Million of Cocaine Seized at Philly Shipping Yard... </title>
      <link>https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/Massive-Drug-Cache-Seized-at-Philadelphia-Shipping-Yard-Sources-Say-511455802.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcphiladelphia.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipping containers full of illegal drugs have been found and seized by federal authorities at a Philadelphia shipyard, sources tell NBC10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School district to randomly test students for nicotine...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/combat-vaping-nebraska-school-district-will-randomly-test-students-nicotine-n1018886</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"It's a huge problem, and right now, I think it's new enough that we're being very naive to think that more kids aren't doing it," the superintendent of Fairbury public schools said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In DC, unparalleled espionage wave: 10,000 spies on streets...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/j-j-green-national/2019/06/city-of-secrets-an-estimated-10000-dc-residents-are-spies-heres-how-they-blend-in/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington, D.C. revolves around secret meetings, information and documents. Woven into that orderly bedlam are sophisticated networks of foreign nationals whose sole purpose is to steal secrets — spies. And there are more of them in the area than you may think.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meth-fed 'attack squirrel' found caged during drug bust...</title>
      <link>https://whnt.com/2019/06/18/deputies-say-this-man-had-a-meth-fueled-attack-squirrel-they-need-help-finding-him/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;whnt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LIMESTONE COUNTY, Ala. - Authorities arrested a man and are searching for another after they found methamphetamine, drug paraphernalia, body armor, and an "attack squirrel" during a search Monday. The Limestone County Sheriff's Office said Ronnie Reynolds, 37, was arrested during the search. They added Mickey Paulk, 35, is wanted by investigators, after he allegedly fed a squirrel meth to keep it aggressive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOLTON: Ready to Retaliate...</title>
      <link>https://freebeacon.com/national-security/bolton-america-willing-to-talk-to-iran-but-ready-to-retaliate/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;freebeacon.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolton revealed in an interview that intelligence reports over the past month warned of covert attacks in the Middle East and South Asia by Iranian proxies.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
