<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Sunday talk shows falter in ratings and relevance...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/4/inside-the-beltway-sunday-talk-shows-falter-in-the/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sunday morning political talk shows have some surprising heritage. It is interesting to note, for example, that NBC’s “Meet the Press” is the nation’s longest running television show, debuting as a half-hour program on Nov. 6, 1947, with serious topics and notable guests — back in the days when anchors spoke in the voice of doom, with an intense demeanor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INVESTIGATIONS SWIRL</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/business/article/Trump-is-a-huge-headache-for-Deutsche-but-the-14077336.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigations surrounding Deutsche Bank's more than decade-long relationship with President Donald Trump and his business have created a crisis for the German financial giant.  It's caught in a legal tug of war between Trump and House Democrats for the president's financial records and calls for broad investigations of its anti-money laundering practices.  But for the 150-year old bank, Trump is just the beginning of its problems.  Once a global powerhouse, catering to the U.S. elite from a tower on Wall Street, Deutsche Bank's fortunes have waned. Sunday, it announced a major restructuring, including ending its global equities business and reducing its investment bank operations.  The restructuring reportedly will mean a reduction of 18,000 jobs by 2022. The news followed an announcement Friday that Deutsche Bank's investment banking chief, Garth Ritchie, was stepping down by mutual agreement.  Shareholders are growing increasingly frustrated by the bank's lackluster profits and growing legal bills. The bank's stock dipped to record lows in recent months, though it has rebounded some recently.  At its annual meeting in Frankfurt, shareholders quizzed company executives for more than nine hours over a series of missteps that have kept the bank under pressure.  "I'm leading a bank that is undoubtedly going through a challenging period," said Deutsche Bank CEO Christian Sewing, who has been at the bank for more than 20 years and became chief executive in 2018. "I want to bring back the pride people feel in working for Deutsche Bank. This is crucial for motivation." Deutsche was prepared to make "tough cutbacks," he told shareholders.  The bank reported a profit for the first time since 2014 last year, but shareholders are still not satisfied.  Deutsche "used to be the biggest...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey's Daughter to prosecute?</title>
      <link>https://lawandcrime.com/high-profile/guess-whose-daughter-is-reportedly-a-prosecutor-in-jeffrey-epstein-case/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;lawandcrime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long accused of molesting young girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/crime/jeffrey-epstein-billionaire-long-accused-of-molesting-minors-is-charged/ar-AADX7RQ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docs Could Expose Powerful Politicians, Businessmen... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/lisettevoytko/2019/07/03/jeffrey-epstein-documents-could-expose-powerful-politicians-businessmen/#37a6096b5ac9</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.forbes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“American politicians, powerful business executives, foreign presidents, [and] a well‐known Prime Minister” could be named.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warns will turn Gulf into 'sea of blood'... </title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/790365/iran-us-war-fears-sea-of-blood-nuclear-deal-tankers-cleric-gulf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA defeats Netherlands 2-0 in Women's World Cup...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7221813/U-S-womens-soccer-team-plays-fourth-World-Cup-title-against-Netherlands.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States is vying for its fourth Women's World Cup title when it meets the Netherlands on Sunday. The U.S. is the defending champion, while the Dutch are in their first final.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked secret cables...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7220875/UK-Ambassador-USs-memo-says-doesnt-believe-Trump-stopped-Iran-strike-kill-150.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a damning indictment of Trump's administration, Britain's Ambassador to Washington described '36 hours of contradictory messaging' after Iran shot down a US drone (stock RQ-4 Global Hawk).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump quote surfaces...</title>
      <link>https://www.businessinsider.com/jeffrey-epstein-trump-link-liking-women-on-the-younger-side-2019-7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.businessinsider.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeffrey Epstein was arrested on sex trafficking charges, a quote from Trump about the billionaire liking women 'on the younger side' resurfaced.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran raises uranium enrichment beyond nuclear deal limits...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b969f30f6b1143a9914caadc44297ad4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA wants to dump 1.5 tons of rat poison on Farallon Islands. Biologists say it's best...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-farallon-islands-rat-poison-20190707-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;California's Farallon Islands are overrun with swarms of invading mice. The federal government says it must poison them to stop an ecological disaster.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couple sues fertility clinic after 'giving birth to two babies who belonged to other people'...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7221117/Asian-couple-sues-fertility-clinic-giving-birth-two-babies-belonged-else.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A New York couple is suing CHA Fertility Center in Los Angeles after giving birth to someone else's babies. Clinic co-owners Simon Hong (right) and Dr. Joshua Berger (left) are seen above.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 in 4 Americans have no plans to retire...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jul/7/1-4-americans-have-no-plans-retire/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nearly one-quarter of Americans say they never plan to retire, according to a poll that suggests a disconnection between individuals’ retirement plans and the realities of aging in the workforce.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obamacare on the ropes in federal appeals court?</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/07/07/affordable-care-act-obamacare-faces-doom-federal-appeals-court/1633128001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The health care law has helped insure 20 million people since 2010 and survived two Supreme Court battles in 2012 and 2015, but it's threatened again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lab grown STEAKS could soon be on the menu...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-7218283/Lab-grown-STEAKS-soon-menu-thanks-breakthroughs-cultured-meats-experts-say.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Animal cells can replicate most of the meat experience, says Natalie Rubio, from Tufts University. But without blood vessels and connective tissue, you get neat 3D tissue.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Festival charging double for tickets for 'non-people of color'...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/festival-charges-double-ticket-price-for-non-people-of-colour-11758249</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The controversial pricing plan has led to one artist pulling out of the event, saying she was "enraged" by the policy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems embrace religion in campaign...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/9de001e6bb7843618ab42fc3ee674584</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Trump reaches career-high approval...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trump-reaches-career-high-approval-faces-range-reelection/story?id=64117018</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolstered by the economy, Donald Trump reached his highest approval in this poll.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O WON'T DEFEND JOE...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/michelle-obama-comment-biden-apology-holds-off-endorsement/story?id=64174424</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Six Democratic presidential candidates took the stage at the Essence Festival on Saturday, but it was a former inhabitant of the White House who got a rock star's welcome -- regardless of her tendency to deflect questions on the 2020 election. Former first lady Michelle Obama refused to comment...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rising French far-right star resurfaces; Flirts with fire...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ccb8813cc9dc47e8b6b332994da6d282</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters take message to mainland Chinese...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4dc00ce27b3b467f97c9e4d47d1e2042</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran Steps Up Nuclear Violations...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/Breaking-News/Iran-reduces-commitment-to-2015-nuclear-deal-594836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Iran has begun... to raise, to break out of the uranium enrichment curbs that were imposed on it," Steinitz told Israel's Ynet TV.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro defends child labor in Brazil, sparking outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190707-bolsonaro-defends-child-labor-brazil-sparking-outcry</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bolsonaro defends child labor in Brazil, sparking outcry</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICHELLE O WON'T DEFEND JOE...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/live-news/michelle-obama-interview-gayle-king-exclusive-talks-to-former-first-lady-live-stream-2019-07-06/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"CBS This Morning" co-host Gayle King spoke to former first lady at Essence Festival</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rival far-right, far-left protests get heated near White House...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2019/07/rival-far-right-far-left-protests-get-heated-near-white-house/slide/1/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions were high as protesters from two different sides took to the streets of D.C. on Saturday and law enforcement officials worked to keep a barrier between the groups from being crossed. See photos and videos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA calls on Germany to send ground troops to Syria...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/us-calls-germany-send-ground-troops-syria-110817769.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The United States on Sunday called for Germany to send ground troops to northern Syria, pushing Berlin to ramp up its military involvement in the fight against the Islamic State group as Washington looks to withdraw from the region. "We want ground troops from Germany to partly replace our soldiers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3,000 earthquakes since July 4...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-aftershocks-new-quake-ridgecrest-earthquake-20190706-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Geological Survey has calculated a 27% probability the region will be hit by a magnitude 6 or greater quake in the coming days.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious military space plane captured on camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.livescience.com/65884-x-37b-space-plane-skywatcher-photo.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.livescience.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We still don't know what the X-37B is doing up there, however.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Archie revealed...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-7219483/Meghan-Harry-reveal-baby-Archies-christening-photographs-secret-ceremony.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Proud parents the Duke and Duchess of Sussex have finally revealed baby Archie in christening photographs on their Instagram after a top secret ceremony in Windsor today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacey quizzed by cops over six more sexual assault claims...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/9451998/kevin-spacey-more-sex-assault-claims-questioned/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ACTOR Kevin Spacey has been questioned by Scotland Yard detectives about sex assault allegations. The officers travelled to the US to interview the star under caution. Spacey, 59, faces six allegat…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Epstein Faces New Sex Charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/jeffrey-epstein-arrested-for-sex-trafficking-of-minors-source</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeffrey Epstein was reportedly arrested on Saturday and will appear in New York court on Monday to be charged with sex trafficking, according to multiple law enforcement sources</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He has long been accused of molesting dozens of young girls...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/06/nyregion/jeffrey-epstein-arrested-sex-trafficking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mr. Epstein, who was charged with sex trafficking, had avoided federal criminal charges a decade ago in a widely criticized plea deal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious military space plane captured on camera...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/world-news/790336/X-37B-aircraft-mini-shuttle-space-plane-astronomer-dutch-Ralf-Vandeberg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Says he was wrong in comments about segregationists...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/1c6244c8af404a7e90ec212feaf35eca</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquake's impact can be predicted -- but only after it hits...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190706214822-ug2nf</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CALIFORNIA-QUAKE/PREDICTION (PIX):An earthquake's impact can be predicted - but only after it hits</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
