<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>APPLE, GOOGLE Named in Lawsuit Over Child-Mining Deaths...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2019/dec/16/apple-and-google-named-in-us-lawsuit-over-congolese-child-cobalt-mining-deaths</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dell, Microsoft and Tesla also among tech firms named in case brought by families of children killed or injured while mining in DRC</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What would Sanders presidency really look like?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2019/12/16/bernie-sanders-first-100-days-president-white-house-administration-084447</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It could happen, really. Vice President Warren is being considered, and plans are in the works to de-Trumpify immigration and climate. Much less likely: Medicare for All.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'JEWELL' Disaster at Boxoffice...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/clint-eastwoods-richard-jewell-jailed-by-fan-apathy-not-controversy-1262856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The biographical drama marks a near-worst career opening for the prolific director.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex robots with facial recognition pick customers out of crowd...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/sex-robots-recognise-humans-using-21102122</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;EXCLUSIVE: RealDoll revealed at an event attended by Daily Star Online that it is producing models with facial recognition allowing them to pick out customers in a crowded room</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: HALLMARK Channel Reinstates Ads Featuring Lesbian Wedding After Outcry...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/hallmark-channel-same-sex-couple-ad-reinstate-commercials-after-outcry-2019-12-15/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's unclear whether Zola will continue airing ads on the The Hallmark Channel, but they noted they are "relieved" by these recent updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slams debate commission, raising questions about his participation...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/474693-trump-slams-debate-commission-raising-questions-about-his</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump on Monday hammered the Commission on Presidential Debates, raising questions about his participation in debates next year with the eventual Democratic presidential nominee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Year-end legislative blitz...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonexaminer.com/news/not-just-impeachment-democrats-plan-year-end-legislative-blitz</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonexaminer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wary of polls showing battleground state voters are frowning on the impeachment effort in Congress, House Democrats plan a legislative blitz this week they’ll be able to tout when they return home for the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bribery, Wire Fraud...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/16/judiciary-committee-impeachment-report-trump-committed-multiple-federal-crimes-086096</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 169-page report makes the case for Trump's removal from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>658-page impeachment report...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/house-judiciary-committee-publishes-full-impeachment-report-n1102531</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In making its case that President Donald Trump abused his power and obstructed Congress, the committee concludes, "President Trump has realized the Framers' worst nightmare."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT: 99% of biggest firms paid no federal tax at all...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/2018-corporate-tax-rate-plunged-to-11-3-under-14909295.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 400 of America's largest corporations paid an average federal tax rate of about 11 percent on their profits last year, about half the official rate established under President Donald Trump's tax law of 2017, according to a report released Monday.  The 2017 GOP tax law lowered the U.S. corporate tax rate to 21 percent from 35 percent, but in practice large companies often pay far less than that due to deductions, tax breaks, and other loopholes.  In the first year Trump's tax law was in effect, the actual amount corporations paid in federal taxes on their incomes - their so-called "effective rate" - was an average of 11.3 percent, likely its lowest level in more than three decades, according to a report by the Institute of Taxation and Economic Policy, a left-leaning think tank.  From 2008 to 2015, under the previous tax code, corporations paid on average an effective rate of about 21 percent, according to ITEP's prior research.  The report also found that 91 corporations in the Fortune 500, many worth billions of dollars, paid no federal taxes at all last year.  "When drafting the tax law, lawmakers could have eliminated special breaks and loopholes in the corporate tax to offset the cost of reducing the statutory rate," the report says. "Instead, the new law introduced many new breaks and loopholes, though it eliminated some old ones."  ITEP looked at the 379 companies in the Fortune 500 that were profitable in 2018 and provided enough information to calculate their tax rates. Researchers excluded taxes incurred by corporations under a one-time "repatriation tax" on money they brought back from overseas due to the tax law, according to Matt Gardner, an analyst at ITEP.  The findings come amid an explosion in the federal deficit, which this year rose to close to $1...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC BRACED FOR BATTLE</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-braces-historic-impeachment-clouding-090000374.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Donald Trump’s likely impeachment this week adds a permanent stain to a presidency plagued by unrelenting turmoil and partisan rancor, while aggravating U.S. political divisions as he starts his fight for re-election.The House is all but certain to deliver the formal rebuke in a vote on</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust architect's grave dug up in Berlin...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/holocaust-architects-grave-dug-berlin-134240972.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The grave of a top Nazi who helped plan the Holocaust and was assassinated by British-trained agents during World War II has been dug up in Berlin, German police said on Monday. The grave of Reinhard Heydrich was "dug up in the night between Wednesday and Thursday" and an investigation has</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Found Dead Inside Port-A-Potty At RAVENS Stadium...</title>
      <link>https://baltimore.cbslocal.com/2019/12/15/body-found-m-t-bank-stadium-ravens-latest/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;baltimore.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police are investigating after a person was found dead inside a porta-potty near M&amp;T Bank Stadium.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolstering case, Dems say Trump betrayed nation...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/cebb308b1c7bd81e715da5d2bd51a47a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Bolstering its case for impeaching President Donald Trump, a House panel released a lengthy report Monday detailing its rationale for the charges and accusing Trump of betraying...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: ANY Amount Of Running Significantly Lower's Risk Of Dying From ANY Cause...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/joggers-delight-any-amount-of-running-linked-to-significantly-lower-risk-of-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The joggers of the world have reason to smile, according to a new study. Researchers say that any amount of running significantly lowers one's risk of death from any cause.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France records 391-mile traffic jam...</title>
      <link>https://www.itv.com/news/2019-12-16/france-enters-new-week-of-strikes-over-pension-changes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.itv.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOP GUN' TRAILER LANDS...</title>
      <link>https://screenrant.com/top-gun-maverick-trailer-tom-cruise/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;screenrant.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;That Tom Cruise sure does love to fly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bali's drugged, smuggled orangutan headed back to the wild...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/balis-drugged-smuggled-orangutan-headed-back-wild-112328574.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A baby orangutan that was drugged by a Russian trafficker in a failed bid to smuggle it out of Bali will be released back into the wild. The case made headlines in March when suspicious authorities on the Indonesian holiday island stopped Andrei Zhestkov, who was flying back to Russia, and opened his</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbulence shakes Dems going into final debate of year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/76118a4c2009b639b3135efb3fd4a4b7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CLINTON, Iowa (AP) — Seven Democratic presidential candidates will stand on stage this week in Los Angeles, a pool of survivors who have withstood almost a year on the campaign trail, sustained...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-town newspaper seeks new owner. Price: $0...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2019/dec/15/alaska-newspaper-skagway-sale</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Larry Persily hopes to pass the Skagway News on to a committed journalist willing to live in a town of 1,000</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of Empty NFL Stadium Seats Going into Home Stretch...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/sports/2019/12/15/weak-15-thousands-empty-seats-going-into-the-home-stretch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With only two more games left in the regular season, the NFL is still seeing thousands of empty seats all across the nation as Week 15 winds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL: Biden, Bernie lead field...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/474663-biden-sanders-lead-democratic-field-poll</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Vice President Joe Biden and Sen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolton in crosshairs...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/trump-impeachment-inquiry/schumer-proposes-bolton-mulvaney-testify-senate-impeachment-trial-n1102501</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senate Minority Leader sent a letter to Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell Sunday laying out the proposed outlines of impeachment proceedings for President Donald Trump.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNC Chairman Knows No One Is Happy. Neither Is He...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/the-dnc-chairman-knows-no-one-is-happy-neither-is-he/ar-AAK9bId</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC SET FOR HISTORIC WEEK...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/15/congress-to-vote-on-impeachment-usmca-trade-deal-and-funding.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The votes in Congress on impeachment, USMCA and government funding set up one of the most dramatic weeks of Donald Trump's presidency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer wants 4 White House witnesses at trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/chuck-schumer-senate-impeachment-trial-mcconnell-4c19166d-9044-4b21-ba6b-05ef7bb7e90c.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The witnesses Schumer has asked for all have direct knowledge of Trump's decision to freeze aid to Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREW:  Process Barely Functioning... </title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/15/opinion/impeachment-trump.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hyperpartisan politics and an implacable president may break Congress’s ability to check him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON driver delivers up to 300 parcels a day with 'no time for toilet breaks'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/amazon-driver-delivers-up-300-21104717</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Amazon driver says he spends so much time delivering parcels to about 200 houses or properties every day that he only gets a few minutes with his wife and children every day</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington bracing for impeachment as battle lines harden...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/17c13b4aa38228aeaba137ef4aeec939</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — As Washington braces for this week's expected vote to impeach President Donald Trump, partisan battle lines hardened on Sunday, with Democrats defending impeachment even if...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director's Worst Debut...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/richard-jewell-posts-worst-wide-opening-for-clint-eastwood-4-7-million/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Richard Jewell" was a passion project for Clint Eastwood, but it's become this worst wide opening weekend in his directorial career with just $4.7 million</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS PLANS BIG SHAKEUP OF UK GOVT...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/edition/news/now-for-the-boris-johnson-revolution-pm-to-wield-axe-on-cabinet-0cpdldlk6</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson has drawn up plans to run a “revolutionary” government that will see ministers sacked, Whitehall departments abolished and civil servants replaced by external experts in a bid to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin Nunes lives on a congressman's salary. How is he funding so many lawsuits?</title>
      <link>https://www.fresnobee.com/news/local/article238287238.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fresnobee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zambia Says Ambassador Should Leave After Defending Gay Couple...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-50630026</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daniel Foote faces a backlash after calling a 15-year jail term given to a gay couple "horrifying".</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Government Again Uses 'Fake News' Law on Opposition...</title>
      <link>https://www.bangkokpost.com/world/1816009/singapore-invokes-fake-news-law-again</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bangkokpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parliament vote before Christmas on Brexit...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191215110302-ja2uu</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/ (PIX):UK PM Johnson eyes parliament vote before Christmas to "get Brexit done"</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO Scottish independence...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191215090558-a58nc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-EU/STURGEON (URGENT):UK PM Johnson cannot keep Scotland in union against its will - Sturgeon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul fears impeachment will 'dumb down' country...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/dec/15/rand-paul-fears-donald-trump-impeachment-will-dumb/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Rand Paul, Kentucky Republican, said Sunday he worried that the Democratic effort to impeach President Trump would “dumb down and destroy the country.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOR YOUR CONSIDERATION:  Weinstein shares hospital pic in bid to prove he isn't faking it...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10555563/harvey-weinstein-hospital-photo-fake-injury-row/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HARVEY Weinstein has released a photograph of himself sitting in a hospital room – in a bid to prove he is genuinely ill ahead of his trial. The image shows the disgraced movie mogul on the phone w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe calls on NASA for help as Mars mission runs into serious trouble...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/europe-calls-nasa-help-mars-21103688</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailystar.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ExoMars, and its robot rover Rosalind Franklin, may miss its launch window unless JPL engineers can fix some last minute bugs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iceland blizzard brings 149 mph winds, up to 10 feet of snow!</title>
      <link>https://www.columbian.com/news/2019/dec/12/iceland-blizzard-brings-149-mph-gusts-up-to-10-feet-of-mountain-snow/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.columbian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Much of Iceland is digging out following a potent blizzard that brought winds topping 100 mph and yards of snow to some areas amid what one Icelandic meteorologist referred to as a “10-year storm.” As</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greta Thunberg Apologizes After Saying Politicians Should Be Put 'Against The Wall'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/greta-thunberg-climate-activist-apologizes-for-against-the-wall-comment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thunberg says she was translating a Swedish saying into English and was not calling for violence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOXNEWS POLL:   50% say Trump should be impeached and removed...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/474633-fox-news-poll-50-percent-of-americans-say-trump-should-be-impeached</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Fox News poll released Sunday found half of Americans say President Trump should be impeached and removed from office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions mount over French transport strike...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/tensions-mount-over-french-transport-strike-053555853.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tensions between the French government and unions opposed to pension reforms mounted on the 11th day of a crippling transport strike Sunday, with the prime minister warning the French would not tolerate being stranded at Christmas. The pensions overhaul, unveiled this week by Prime Minister Edouard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: FOXNEWS WILL DIE...</title>
      <link>https://dailycaller.com/2019/12/14/trump-fox-news-comey-schiff/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dailycaller.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump once again attacked Fox News in a tweet Saturday night, accusing the network of trying to be &amp;quot;politically correct.&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Pharma empire behind OxyContin now selling overdose cure...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6751b84767e8a1ebbaea6cb628ac2a11</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The gleaming white booth towered over the medical conference in Italy in October, advertising a new brand of antidote for opioid overdoses. “Be prepared. Get naloxone. Save a life,” the slogan on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico objects over US bill on ratifying trade pact...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/319fb954f1c10ad1be50da18951d63be</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MEXICO CITY (AP) — Just days after a landmark agreement on a trade pact to replace the North American Free Trade Agreement, Mexico objected Saturday to legislation introduced in the U.S. Congress...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pot link to psychosis, schizophrenia real, warn doctors...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/12/15/weed-psychosis-high-thc-cause-suicide-schizophrenia/4168315002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Government health officials say excessive use of today’s potent THC can lead to psychosis. Marijuana advocates say they can't be trusted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bloomberg's Money Built a Political Network...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/mayors-for-mike-how-bloombergs-money-built-a-2020-political-network/ar-AAK7nlP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey admits error in FBI's FISA process: 'I was wrong'...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/comey-defends-fbis-fisa-process-after-scathing-ig-report</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former FBI Director James Comey admitted on "Fox News Sunday" that the recently released Justice Department Inspector General’s report on the launch of the FBI’s Russia investigation and their use of the surveillance process showed that he was "overconfident" when he defended his former agency's use of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering the goods: Drones, robots making way to your door...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/delivering-the-goods-drones-and-robots-are-making-their-way-to-your-door/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With companies offering free shipping to gain a competitive edge, radical new technologies are being tested to cut the cost of the supply chain's expensive "last mile"</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
