<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Family believes Jamaican immigrant's death in rural Pa. was 'modern-day lynching'...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/news/pennsylvania/rural-pittsburgh-shooting-venango-spencer-shooting-20220121.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Family members of Peter Bernardo Spencer say the man who shot him 9 times may be claiming self-defense.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meat Loaf Daughter Pens Tribute Following Rock Legend's Death...</title>
      <link>https://www.etonline.com/meat-loafs-daughter-pens-tribute-following-rock-legends-death-178185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.etonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pearl Aday posted the tribute on Instagram two days after Meat Loaf's passing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Dems censure Sinema over voting rights bill...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/voting-rights-kyrsten-sinema-phoenix-arizona-voting-af9409b7dbab996a1a8df329c053fce0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PHOENIX (AP) — U.S. Sen. Kyrsten Sinema is growing increasingly isolated from some of her party’s most influential officials and donors after playing a key role in scuttling voting rights legislation that many Democrats consider essential to preserving democracy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin's assertive first week in office leaves Republicans jubilant, Dems fuming...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Va-Gov-Youngkin-s-assertive-first-week-in-16796384.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RICHMOND, Va. - The big unknown about Republican Gov. Glenn Youngkin as he ran for office...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WV Canaan Valley plummets to minus-31, setting record low for region...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/weather/topstories/west-virginias-canaan-valley-plummets-to-minus-31-setting-record-low-for-region/ar-AAT2bEZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside synagogue attacker's 18-day journey to terror...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Inside-the-synagogue-attacker-s-18-day-journey-to-16796340.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes, Malik Faisal Akram stood out, in unsettling ways. Back home in Blackburn, in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Sur wildfire forces evacuations, closes California's Hwy. 1...</title>
      <link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/big-sur-colorado-fire-highway-1-closure-california-evacuations/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbsnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The California Highway Patrol closed Highway 1 at Rio Road just outside of Carmel-by-the-Sea due to the fire.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Divine intervention': Man carrying own severed arm saved...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/maine-lewiston-accidents-4b14a5ad92c325a5d9f2c3bd2b9fdc97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LEWISTON, Maine (AP) — A man who stumbled along a street while carrying his own severed arm was saved by two public workers who saw him and happened to be trained in the use of tourniquets, authorities in Maine said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hipster Megachurch in Shambles Over Pastor's Alleged Affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/venue-church-in-chattanooga-in-shambles-over-pastor-tavner-smiths-alleged-affair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drama has unfolded like a soap opera, with rumors, a parade of employee exits, and a suggestive videotape.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passport protests in Europe draw thousands of people...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-europe-helsinki-2336e6f56442de7ab676a7618df22342</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HELSINKI (AP) — Thousands of people gathered in European capitals Saturday to protest vaccine passports and other requirements governments have imposed in hopes of ending the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical Brady readies for RAMS operation...</title>
      <link>https://sports.yahoo.com/surgical-brady-readies-rams-operation-011022061.html?fr=sycsrp_catchall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sports.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tom Brady says the Tampa Bay Buccaneers' regular season drubbing by the Los Angeles Rams will count for little when the two sides collide in the NFL playoffs on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Recipe for Hatred': Why Boris May Finally Have Gone Too Far...</title>
      <link>https://dnyuz.com/2022/01/22/a-recipe-for-hatred-why-boris-johnson-may-finally-have-gone-too-far/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dnyuz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Boris Johnson, long famed for brushing off accusations of distorting, misleading or outright lying that, far from slowing his rise,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't approach lab monkey missing after crash, people told...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/science-pennsylvania-monkeys-animals-fe5ddc03bba64ce62433f79b0ee7c6c3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANVILLE, Pa. (AP) — Residents of a Pennsylvania county were warned Saturday not to approach a monkey that was missing after a crash involving a pickup that was towing a trailer taking about 100 of the animals to a lab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiribati was one of last virus-free places. Now under lockdown...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/the-kiribati-island-nation-was-one-of-the-world-e2-80-99s-last-covid-free-places-now-it-e2-80-99s-under-lockdown/ar-AAT2mkk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High number of mutations render antibodies ineffective...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/coronavirus/article-694237</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA TO BEGIN UKRAINE EVACUATIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/world/us-embassy-personnel-family-in-ukraine-ordered-begin-evacuating-officials</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The State Department has ordered families of U.S. Embassy personnel in Ukraine to begin evacuating the country as soon as Monday, U.S. officials tell Fox News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's next for John Does in Ghislaine settled suit...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/us/ghislaine-maxwell-john-does-whats-next/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The judge overseeing a settled lawsuit against convicted sex offender Ghislaine Maxwell now has to decide whether the identities of those mentioned in the suit will be revealed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Panic and calm': How feels to give up internet for three months...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/22/what-quitting-social-media-internet-for-3-months-feels-like/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the summer of 2018, author Johann Hari planned to take a three-month “digital detox” to see if he could survive without technological conveniences.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monks in NM desert dedicated to hospitality reflect on two years without guests...</title>
      <link>https://www.stamfordadvocate.com/news/article/Monks-in-New-Mexico-desert-dedicated-to-16796069.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stamfordadvocate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CHAMA RIVER CANYON, N.M. - Hidden in this canyon of crimson sandstone cliffs encompassed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>British Conservatives set to go for top job if Johnson falls...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-boris-johnson-health-europe-london-56b416d8a50cb49abf4577cf76c66cc7</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LONDON (AP) — Revelations that Prime Minister Boris Johnson and his staff partied while Britain was in a coronavirus lockdown have provoked public outrage and led some members of his Conservative Party to consider ousting their leader .</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Lethal' U.S. Military Aid Arriving in Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/-lethal-u-s-military-aid-begins-arriving-in-ukraine</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. military aid to help Ukraine defend against a possible invasion by Russia has began arriving on Friday night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Down $20 Billion!</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-01-21/bezos-loses-20-billion-in-brutal-week-for-tech-billionaires</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Loses HALF Value Since Record High...</title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/now/bitcoin-extends-slide-fallen-more-101904421.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bitcoin extended its decline on Saturday, and has shed more than 50% from its record high in November while adding further momentum to the meltdown in cryptocurrencies.Most Read from BloombergCrypto Crash Erases More Than $1 Trillion in Market ValueTech Leads Stocks to Worst Week Since March 2020: Markets WrapBitcoin Chart Hints at Possible Floor for SlideNasdaq 100’s Unrelenting Declines Ring a Dot-Com Bust Alarm BellJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has St</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wave worse than data shows?</title>
      <link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/health/2022/01/21/floridas-omicron-wave-could-be-worse-than-data-shows/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tampabay.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Missing data and strained testing infrastructure hamper the ability of experts to track COVID-19.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: Schwarzenegger involved in LA car crash...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/us/arnold-schwarzenegger-car-crash/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Actor and former California Gov. Arnold Schwarzenegger was involved in a multi-vehicle crash Friday evening in Los Angeles with a representative telling People magazine that he wasn't hurt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Canadians shot dead at upscale Mexican resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-60092429</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The incident began as an argument among guests, one of whom was the gunman, at the hotel near Cancún.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Big Tech elites helping China achieve global supremacy...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2022/01/22/how-tech-elites-are-helping-china-achieve-global-supremacy-new-book/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blinded by their ambition, Silicon Valley elites are helping Communist China achieve their ultimate goal: “Technology supremacy” over the West.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'WUHAN, I AM HERE': Film follows volunteers in sealed city...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-pandemic-entertainment-health-arts-and-entertainment-beijing-af173d919d502acd1f14e58767129d5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BEIJING (AP) — The homeless, the sick, the elderly: For people who fell through the cracks of the official system, the then-unprecedented decision to isolate the central Chinese city of Wuhan and its 13 million people was a matter of life or death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39% Americans boosted...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/booster-shots-in-us-have-strongly-protected-against-severe-disease-from-omicron-variant-cdc-studies-show/ar-AAT0Ijs</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omicron has changed shape of pandemic. Will it end it for good?</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/22/world/omicron-changed-pandemic-intl-cmd/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The world feared the worst when a worrying new coronavirus variant emerged in late November and ripped through South Africa at a pace not seen before in the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA Weighs Evacuating Diplomat Family Members From Ukraine...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/u-weighs-pulling-diplomats-family-150322370.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- The U.S. is weighing whether to evacuate family members of diplomats stationed in Ukraine as Russia masses more than 100,000 troops on its borders, according to people familiar with the matter.Most Read from BloombergJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedTech Leads Late-Day Slide in Stocks; Bitcoin Sinks: Markets WrapCrypto Selloff Pushes Bitcoin to a Six-Month Low of $38,000American Airlines Sues The Points Guy Over Its Rewards Management AppEarly Om</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ Unrelenting Declines Ring Dot-Com Bust Alarm Bell...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nasdaq-100-unrelenting-drops-ring-214018521.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bulls should be glad there were only four days this week instead of five.Most Read from BloombergCrypto Crash Erases More Than $1 Trillion in Market ValueTech Leads Stocks to Worst Week Since March 2020: Markets WrapBitcoin Chart Hints at Possible Floor for SlideJeremy Grantham Doubles Down on Crash Call, Says Selloff Has StartedNasdaq 100’s Unrelenting Declines Ring a Dot-Com Bust Alarm BellTo wit, the Nasdaq 100 just did something it hasn’t done since the aftermath of the intern</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truck with 100 monkeys crashes, some of them missing...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/oddities-pennsylvania-monkeys-animals-52100c02527985f7dde4674724bb3332</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DANVILLE, Pa. (AP) — A truck carrying about 100 monkeys was involved in a crash Friday in Pennsylvania, state police said as authorities searched for at least three of the monkeys that appeared to have escaped the vehicle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THICH NHAT HANH DEAD AT 95...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/thich-nhat-hanh-poetic-peace-activist-and-master-of-mindfulness-dies-at-95/ar-AAT1gqP</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-abortion activists march in DC, hoping it's last time under Roe v. Wade...</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/nations-largest-abortion-protest-roe-82389718</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The annual anti-abortion rally in the nation’s capital sounded more like a victory celebration Friday</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force struggles to recruit...</title>
      <link>https://www.militarytimes.com/news/your-air-force/2022/01/21/air-forces-enlisted-recruitment-pipeline-is-drying-up-general-warns/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.militarytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;About 4,800 people entered the Air Force in the first quarter of fiscal 2022, down from around 7,100 at the same point in fiscal 2021. And there are fewer prospects in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feds to monitor for violence, extremist activity...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/federal-officials-to-monitor-wasington-anti-vaccine-rally-for-potential-violence-and-extremist-activity-223850442.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal law enforcement in Washington, D.C., have been closely monitoring social media for signs of potential violence and extremist activity ahead of a large demonstration against vaccine mandates this weekend, according to documents obtained by Yahoo News.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients hospitalized 'with' vs. 'for' shifting...</title>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2022/01/21/number-of-patients-hospitalized-with-covid-vs-for-covid-is-shifting/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ocregister.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;But health experts say hospitals are still under strain and the virus remains serious business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunfire Erupts at Ritzy Cancun Resort...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/gunfire-erupts-at-ritzy-playa-del-carmen-resort-one-dead/ar-AAT1i0z</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unfiltered Year of Aaron Rodgers...</title>
      <link>https://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/33088151/the-unfiltered-year-aaron-rodgers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.espn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This season, Aaron Rodgers has been brilliant on the field and unapologetically vocal off it. In an exclusive interview with ESPN, he explains why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search for scapegoat leads to chief of staff...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/white-house/klain-under-scrutiny-biden-struggles-n1287801</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the president rounds out his first year in office with multiple setbacks in his agenda and a sinking approval rating, some blame his chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 years since Covid confirmed in USA. Pandemic worse than anyone imagined...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2022/01/21/omicron-two-years-since-covid-was-first-confirmed-in-us-the-pandemic-is-worse-than-anyone-imagined.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the emergence of omicron, the future course of the pandemic is unclear as experts struggle to understand how new variants emerge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  Media Doomed?</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/magazine/2022/01/21/media-journalism-future-527294</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From a Big Tech crackdown to the rebirth of local news, 16 future-minded thinkers predict where journalism will be in 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KNIVES OUT FOR KLAIN...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2022/01/21/ron-klain-hot-water-527570</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biden’s chief of staff started strong and earned plaudits. But, increasingly, he’s under scrutiny for the state of the presidency.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
