<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>'Please save him' plead blogger's parents...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/please-save-him-plead-belarus-190120308.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;From their new home in Poland, the parents of Belarusian journalist Roman Protasevich have been in anguish since he was seized after his flight was forced to land in Minsk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mag 4.5 Quake Rocks Oklahoma Town...</title>
      <link>https://dfw.cbslocal.com/2021/05/25/earthquake-shakes-northwestern-oklahoma-town/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;dfw.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. Geological Survey reported the quake struck about 1:25 p.m. near Shattuck, a town of nearly 1,500 population about 145 miles northwest of Oklahoma City and near the border with the Texas Panhandle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diaper Prices Next To Rise Over 'Supply Chain Disruption'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2021/05/24/colorado-diaper-debacle-families-brace-price-hike-supply-chain-disruption/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diapers are a major cost for families and soon a manufacturing issue may prompt companies to raise their prices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Say Human Lifespan Could Nearly Double -- To 150...</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/humans-could-live-to-be-150/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An iPhone app that estimates biological aging discovered that life expectancy has the capacity to be almost double the current norm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  Garcia catapults into lead...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2021/05/25/garcia-jumps-to-lead-over-adams-yang-in-new-mayoral-survey/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former city Sanitation Commissioner Kathryn Garcia has shot to the top of the heap in a new poll of the candidate vying for the Democratic nomination for mayor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight attendant loses 2 teeth in assault...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/union-chief-says-flight-attendant-141423600.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Southwest Airlines flight attendant was assaulted by a passenger and lost two teeth in the attack last weekend, according to a union president, who complained to the airline’s CEO about unruly passengers. “Unfortunately, this is just one of many occurrences,” said the union president, Lyn Montgomery. A Southwest spokesman said Tuesday that the incident happened Sunday morning after a flight from Sacramento landed in San Diego and involved a female passenger.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New court filing inadvertently reveals more details of Giuliani probe...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/court-filing-inadvertently-revealed-federal-171357235.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an improperly redacted letter to a judge, Lev Parnas' lawyer said the feds seized multiple accounts and devices connected to the Giuliani probe.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian soldier who called on troops to refuse vax distribution faces mutiny related charge...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/national/defence-watch/soldier-who-called-on-troops-to-refuse-vaccine-distribution-faces-mutiny-related-charge/wcm/b1c875de-21ca-4f69-b3bd-681483fda253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young rocked by new hate...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/25/us/new-york-gen-z-students-antisemitism-soh/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In New York, some Gen Z Jews are surprised and angry at anti-Semitic attacks they're seeing on the streets and online, and wondering where their supporters are.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ocasio-Cortez to seek restraining order?</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/democrats-consider-the-possibility-of-alexandria-ocasio-cortez-seeking-a-restraining-order-against-marjorie-taylor-greene/ar-AAKngB5</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Greene recently chased Ocasio-Cortez down a hallway as the two left the House chamber, shouted at her, and accused her of supporting terrorists.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coughing with difficulty breathing, Nasrallah speaks and threatens Israel...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com/breaking-news/lebanon-hezbollah-chief-says-attacks-on-jerusalem-mean-regional-war-669149</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nasrallah called for the creation of a "new equation" in which any violation of Jerusalem would lead to a regional war.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: MAGA Senate Candidate Denies Using Fake Folksy Accent...</title>
      <link>https://fox8.com/news/race-for-ohios-senate-seat-josh-mandel/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;fox8.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FOX 8’s Joe Toohey sat down with one of the candidates for U.S. Senate: former Ohio Treasurer Josh Mandel.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO: Woman Enters Exhibit At TX Zoo, Feeds Hot CHEETOS To Spider Monkeys...</title>
      <link>https://www.insideedition.com/texas-woman-feeding-hot-cheetos-to-spider-monkey-inside-el-paso-zoo-enclosure-fired-from-job-at-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.insideedition.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She risked spreading COVID-19 to the monkeys, Libby and Sunday, a zookeeper said, not to mention personal injury.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water crisis 'couldn't be worse' on Oregon-California border...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-05-crisis-couldnt-worse-oregon-california-border.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The water crisis along the California-Oregon border went from dire to catastrophic this week as federal regulators shut off irrigation water to farmers from a critical reservoir and said they would not send extra water to dying salmon downstream or to a half-dozen wildlife refuges that harbor millions of migrating birds each year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fireworks Shortage Ahead Of July 4th...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/24/fireworks-shortage-has-stores-warning-customers-to-buy-early-ahead-of-july-4th/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WCCO shares the supply and demand concerns that could play a part in your Fourth of July plans.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia deploys nuclear-capable bombers to Syria...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/europe-russia-middle-east-syria-government-and-politics-58469498915075e6fcc212107205f8af</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — The Russian military said Tuesday it has deployed three nuclear-capable long-range bombers to its base in Syria, a move that could strengthen Moscow's military foothold in the Mediterranean.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene Thanks Supporter For Tweet Calling McCarthy 'Moron' and 'Feckless C---'...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/politics/marjorie-taylor-greene-thanks-supporter-for-tweet-calling-kevin-mccarthy-a-moron-and-feckless-c/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Marjorie Taylor Greene just retweeted a supporter describing Kevin McCarthy, the leader of the House Republicans, as a “moron” and a “feckless c***.” She deleted the tweet minutes later. Tuesdays amiright? Marjorie Taylor Greene praises a tweet calling Kevin McCarthy a “moron” and a “feckless c**t” pic.twitter.com/BCzEQXLYn4 — Andrew Solender (@AndrewSolender) May 25, 2021 The […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland rejects global tax...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/ireland-rejects-president-bidens-global-corporate-tax-plans-and-will-keep-12-5-rate-finance-minister-tells-sky-news-12316753</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paschal Donohoe said that he had "significant reservations" over plans floated by the US president for a minimum rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Dozens' Of Gunshots At Square...</title>
      <link>https://minnesota.cbslocal.com/2021/05/25/gunshots-reported-at-george-floyd-square-wounded-person-arrives-at-hospital-minutes-later/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;minnesota.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Gunshots reportedly rang out Tuesday morning near George Floyd Square, causing people to run from 38th and Chicago on the anniversary of George Floyd's death.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Puerto Rico's population decline could be next crisis...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-new-maria-how-puerto-ricos-population-decline-could-be-the-islands-next-crisis/ar-AAKmyag</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;May 25—SAN JUAN, Puerto Rico — Sheilla Rodríguez never imagined she would leave Puerto Rico. The 48-year-old university professor had made her life on the island, near family and friends. "Moving wasn't an option," she said. But when an employment opportunity with better salary and labor conditions came up in Florida, her husband and child moved to Miami. Rodríguez followed three years later, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France hit by mystery campaign to discredit PFIZER via influencers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/europe/20210525-france-hit-by-mystery-campaign-to-discredit-pfizer-vaccine-via-influencers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French media and social networks were abuzz Tuesday with speculation about a mysterious offer to influencers and YouTube personalities asking them to publicly denigrate the Pfizer/BioNTech Covid-19 v…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reporter Runs for Cover After Gunshots Ring Out During Report...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/tv/ap-reporter-runs-for-cover-after-gunshots-ring-out-during-report-on-anniversary-of-george-floyds-death/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Associated Press journalist Philip Crowther reported an emergency situation from George Floyd Square as gunshots seemed to ring out in the middle of his coverage there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia threatens to slow GOOGLE for not deleting prohibited content...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/russia-threatens-to-slow-down-google-for-not-deleting-unlawful-content.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has threatened to decelerate Google's traffic and issued the company with a small fine for failing to remove what it says is unlawful content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless sue Portland amid encampment razing...</title>
      <link>https://www.oregonlive.com/portland/2021/05/homeless-individuals-file-class-action-suit-over-city-of-portland-losing-their-possessions-amid-encampment-razing.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.oregonlive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The lawsuit alleges city contractors do not properly keep track of people's items, causing people to lose tents, sleeping bags and warm clothes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Will Not Investigate Mild Infections in Dosed...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/cdc-will-not-investigate-mild-infections-in-vaccinated-americans/ar-AAKmGW8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Julie Cohn was fully vaccinated when she went to cheer at her 12-year-old son’s basketball game in March. Midway through the match, he asked to remove his mask because he was getting so hot. She thought little of it. Three days later, he had a sore throat. He tested positive for the coronavirus, as did his younger brother a few days later. Ms. Cohn cared for them, thinking she was protected, but she woke up with what seemed like a head cold on...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 100, Chinese Communist Party claims credit for the Chinese dream...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/100-chinese-communist-party-chinese-dream-88b62052-f155-495a-9b88-c3d5ddb1c8cf.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The party has made it through a century of turbulence, and come out more powerful than ever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Michael Cohen films Trump fan who attacked him in Central Park...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2951057/michael-cohen-chases-trump-fan-central-park/  </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MICHAEL Cohen chased a Donald Trump fan through Central Park after she dropped a “barrage of F-bombs” and flipped him off. Cohen, who once served as the former president’s attorne…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Mild Covid Cases Provide Antibody Protection --- For Life?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/mild-covid-19-antibody-for-life/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers explain that initial reports claiming COVID antibodies fade away quickly after an infection did not have all the facts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First man in world to get covid jab dies...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-william-shakespeare-dies-81-24182185</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tributes have been paid to Mr Shakespeare who hit global headlines on December 8 last year when he became the first man to have the jab at the University Hospital Coventry and Warwickshire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 billion worldwide refusing...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/poll-over-1-billion-people-worldwide-unwilling-to-get-covid-19-vaccine-global-herd-immunity-at-risk</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Gallup poll estimated that 1.3 billion people around the globe wer unwilling to get the COVID-19 vaccine in 2020 leaving some health officials to believe the global herd immunity isn’t possible in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30 countries hurtling toward oxygen crises...</title>
      <link>https://theweek.com/speedreads/984258/more-than-30-countries-could-face-oxygen-crises-similar-india-amid-covid19-surges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theweek.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As COVID-19 cases surge in many countries, several could face oxygen shortages similar to India's. The 'key indicator' of a looming crisis is often not how much oxygen is needed at the moment, but how swiftly demand is rising, The Bureau of Investigative Journalism reports. The Bureau looked at Laos as an example. The southeast Asian nation's current oxygen need is modest at 2,124 cubic meters per day, but that's a 'nearly 200-fold increase from mid-march.' All told, data collected by the Bureau shows that more than 30 countries, including Fiji, Vietnam, Afghanistan, Mongolia, Angola, and Kyrgyyzstan, now need at least twice as much oxygen — which is one of the most crucial treatments for severe COVID-19 infections — as they did two months ago. Activists told the Bureau the trend could lead to the 'total collapse of health systems' in lower- to middle-income countries. Pakistan, Nepal, Bangladesh, Sri Lanka, and Myanmar, could be particularly vulnerable because they rely on Indian-made oxygen and equipment. 'You'd imagine if they start to see peaks [in infections] of the same degree [as India], then it could be even worse, because India needs all the [oxygen] supply,' Zachary Katz, the Vice President of essential medicines at the Clinton Health Access Initiative, said. Read more at The Bureau of Investigative Journalism. Tim O'Donnell</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISNEYLAND to charge $100 for sandwich...</title>
      <link>https://www.fox5ny.com/news/disneyland-to-introduce-a-100-sandwich</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5ny.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Disneyland Resort will soon be home to a new attraction - one of the most expensive sandwiches in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA '100% EFFECTIVE' IN TEENS</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/covid-vaccine-moderna-says-shot-is-100percent-effective-in-teens-plans-to-seek-fda-ok-in-june.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna's Covid-19 vaccine is the second shot behind Pfizer's to demonstrate high efficacy in younger age groups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROARINGS 20S:  Bitcoin traders using up to 100-to-1 leverage...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/bitcoin-crashes-driven-by-big-margin-bets-new-crypto-banking.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bitcoin's aggressive declines are being driven by much more than regulatory headlines or herd mentality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Passengers Warned to Behave Ahead of Holiday...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-25/air-passengers-warned-to-wear-masks-and-behave-ahead-of-holiday</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. government officials monitoring the airways say they won’t tolerate passengers who refuse to don masks as airline travel surges ahead of the summer season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WONDER PILLS:  How much would you pay to extend life?</title>
      <link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-05-24/if-dogs-live-longer-with-anti-aging-science-humans-could-too</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloomberg.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Canine life-extension research by the startup Loyal could lead to breakthroughs for the rest of us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACE TO CHIP YOUR BRAIN...</title>
      <link>https://analyticsindiamag.com/neuralink-has-a-nemesis-paypal-mafia-split-over-brain-gains/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;analyticsindiamag.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peter Thiel is investing $10 million in Blackrock Neurotech, a rival company to Elon Musk’s Neuralink.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis Resurrects Ayatollah Khomeini in Now-Deleted Tweet AND Video...</title>
      <link>https://www.mediaite.com/news/watch-ron-desantis-resurrects-ayatollah-khomeini-in-now-deleted-tweet-and-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mediaite.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Florida Governor Ron DeSantis brought the long-dead Ayatollah Khomeini back to life in a fundraising appeal that has since been deleted — and only mostly corrected. On Monday, DeSantis posted a fundraising appeal that featured a clip from the press event he held for the signing of a law that fines social media companies $250,000 […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HALF AMERICAN ADULTS VACCINATED...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/25/politics/half-of-americans-fully-vaccinated-covid/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The White House expects the US will reach a new milestone on Tuesday when it comes to vaccinations, with 50% of adults becoming fully vaccinated, according to a White House official.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Gaetz helped make DeSantis...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/states/florida/story/2021/05/24/how-matt-gaetz-helped-make-ron-desantis-1383823</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DeSantis needed a political Sherpa to help him navigate Florida’s often landmine-laden political landscape. He turned to Gaetz.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin crash opens door to tax loophole for investors...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/bitcoin-crash-opens-door-to-a-tax-loophole-for-investors.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investors in bitcoin, ethereum, dogecoin and other cryptocurrencies can leverage losses in a way that typical stock owners can't.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL launching review after former coach told he was 'not right minority'...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/555215-nfl-launching-review-after-former-coach-said-he-was-told-he-was-not-the</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The NFL is launching an investigation after a former player and coach said he was told he was not the "right minority" while interviewing for a job within the league.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man Dies Trapped Inside Dinosaur Statue...</title>
      <link>https://www.urdupoint.com/en/miscellaneous/man-dies-trapped-inside-dinosaur-statue-in-sp-1259346.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.urdupoint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 40-year-old man died after becoming trapped inside a large statue of a dinosaur in a Barcelona suburb, Spanish police said Tuesday. It is not clear why the man went inside the decorative stegosaurus located outside a disused cinema in Santa Coloma de Gramenet, but there is no suspicion of foul pla ..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diabetes Vax?</title>
      <link>https://www.studyfinds.org/diabetes-vaccine-insulin/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.studyfinds.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Researchers in Sweden say a clinical study of a potential vaccine for type 1 diabetes has produced encouraging results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lab-leak theory became credible...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/timeline-how-the-wuhan-lab-leak-theory-suddenly-became-credible/ar-AAKlIOr</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The possibility that the coronavirus emerged from a lab was quickly dismissed by scientists in early 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador leader updating autocrat playbook for TIK TOK generation...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/opinion/opinions-el-salvadors-leader-is-updating-the-autocrat-playbook-for-the-tiktok-generation/ar-AAKmrxj</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Berlusconi and Trump came to power through TV. Nayib Bukele harnesses the power of social media fandom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On anniversary of George Floyd death, Minneapolis reflects on how forever changed...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/anniversary-minneapolis-reflects-george-floyds-092917328.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;George Floyd's killing at the hands of police transformed lives around the world, but nowhere as profoundly as in the city where it occurred.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious air base being built on volcanic island off Yemen...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/yemen-africa-middle-east-business-c8cb2018c07bb5b63e1a43ff706b007b</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;DUBAI, United Arab Emirates (AP) — A mysterious air base is being built on a volcanic island off Yemen that sits in one of the world's crucial maritime chokepoints for both energy shipments and commercial cargo.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODERNA says shot works in kids as young as 12...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/coronavirus-vaccine-science-coronavirus-pandemic-business-health-ce7dd76d73e82a1511cbfb91f1c39a0c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moderna said Tuesday its COVID-19 vaccine strongly protects kids as young as 12, a step that could put the shot on track to become the second option for that age group in the U.S. With global vaccine supplies still tight, much of the world is struggling to vaccinate adults in the quest to end the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'FAST &amp; FURIOUS' Star Apologizes for Calling Taiwan Country...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/live-news/20210525-fast-furious-star-cena-apologises-for-calling-taiwan-a-country</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fast &amp; Furious star Cena apologises for calling Taiwan a country</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang's wife rips 'racist disfiguration' of husband in DAILY NEWS cartoon...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/555213-yangs-wife-rips-racist-disfiguration-of-husband-in-new-york-daily-news-cartoon</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Evelyn Yang, the wife of New York City mayoral candidate and millionaire Andrew Yang, blasted a New York Daily News for a cartoon depicting her husband as a tourist, calling it a "racist disfiguration" of him.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earthquakes at Congo border raise fears of second volcano eruption...</title>
      <link>https://news.trust.org/item/20210525095053-wlo4x</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONGO-VOLCANO/ (TV, PIX):Earthquakes at Congo border raise fears of second volcano eruption</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blood moon, total lunar eclipse set to dazzle...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/blood-moon-total-lunar-eclipse-to-dazzle-western-us-on-wednesday-morning/ar-AAKkATD</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Where skies are clear, everyone will see the full moon, but it will be rusty red in the western U.S. due to the eclipse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Wolves scare deer and reduce auto collisions 24%...</title>
      <link>https://phys.org/news/2021-05-wolves-deer-auto-collisions.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;phys.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ecologist Rolf Peterson remembers driving remote stretches of road in Michigan's Upper Peninsula and seeing areas strewn with deer carcasses. But that changed after gray wolves arrived in the region from Canada and Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rand Paul sent death threat, white powder, pic with rifle to head...</title>
      <link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/2951660/rand-paul-threat-powder-letter-gun-image-kentucky-home/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.the-sun.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SENATOR Rand Paul received a mysterious package filled with white powder at his Kentucky home on Monday, prompting the FBI to investigate its contents and the threatening image that came with it. T…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blames pop singer...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/rand-paul-received-a-suspicious-package-at-home-he-blames-a-pop-singer-he-claims-e2-80-98called-for-violence-e2-80-99/ar-AAKlTeN </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO sightings went from joke to national security worry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/how-ufo-sightings-went-from-joke-to-national-security-worry-in-washington/ar-AAKiHOp?ocid=uxbndlbing</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The director of national intelligence is expected to unveil an unclassified report next month on everything government agencies know about UFOs, including scores of unusual sightings by military pilots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lukashenko's brutal torture chambers...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-9615939/Lukashenkos-brutal-torture-chambers.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dissident journalist Roman Protasevich has almost certainly been tortured after his Ryanair flight was hijacked over Belarusian airspace on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detained Belarusian dissident appears in video as fury mounts over 'hijacking'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2021/05/24/europe/belarus-ryanair-flight-roman-protasevich-hijacking-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dissident journalist Roman Protasevich has appeared in a new video after his arrest by Belarusian authorities on Sunday, following the government's extraordinary diversion of his Ryanair flight to capital city Minsk. The video -- the first since Protasevich's arrest -- comes amid mounting fears for his safety and widespread fury over the diversion of a European commercial flight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia power in spotlight...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/25/russias-defense-of-belarus-hijack-shows-its-growing-influence.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russia has been steadily increasing its power and influence over its neighbor Belarus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High school edited yearbook photos to hide girls' chests. Students, parents furious...</title>
      <link>https://www.chron.com/news/article/A-high-school-edited-yearbook-photos-to-hide-16200423.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.chron.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Last week, Bartram Trail High School in St. Johns, Fla., a public school about a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI investigating...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/suspicious-package-sent-rand-paul-home-98bcfe5a-6240-4551-81c2-ea7d4fd1c3a6.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paul tweeted that he's been "targeted multiple times now."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European airlines avoid...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/article/belarus-europe-arrests-business-government-and-politics-45902c1cb40fd177461016b47824967f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW (AP) — European airlines began skirting Belarus on Tuesday at the urging of the European Union, which also imposed new sanctions to punish the ex-Soviet nation's forced diversion of a passenger jet to arrest an opposition journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: USA startling rise in antisemitic attacks...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/national-security/555189-us-sees-startling-rise-in-antisemitic-attacks</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The U.S. is experiencing a rise in violent and disturbing attacks targeting the U.S. Jewish community amid the latest conflict between Israel and the Palestinians.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
