<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionary Guards: Enemies will be destroyed if cross red lines...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-iran-gasoline-protests-guards/revolutionary-guards-irans-enemies-will-be-destroyed-if-they-cross-our-red-lines-idUSKBN1XZ1H8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Iran will destroy the United States, Israel and Saudi Arabia if they cross Tehra...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Iran to Chile to Sudan, protests take hold around world...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-11-25/iran-chile-hong-kong-protests-around-the-world</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In recent months, protests have erupted around the world. Here's what you need to know.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVIEW: Kanye West opera at Hollywood Bowl? Call it 'Nebuchadsnoozer'...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/entertainment-arts/story/2019-11-24/kanye-west-opera-hollywood-bowl-nebuchadnezzar-review</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kanye West packs the Bowl for "Nebuchadnezzar," but the opera feels like a passion play or, worse, school production. Dare we wish for more Kanye-ness?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SACHA BARON COHEN: 'Silicon Six' spread propaganda. Time to regulate...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/The-Silicon-Six-spread-propaganda-It-s-time-to-14860308.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I get it: I'm one of the last people you'd expect to hear warning about the danger of conspiracies and lies. I've built a career on pushing the limits of propriety and good taste. I portrayed Borat, the first fake news journalist, along with satirical characters such as Ali G, a wannabe gangster, and Bruno, a gay fashion reporter from Austria. Some critics have said my comedy risks reinforcing old racial and religious stereotypes.  I admit that most of my comedy over the years has been pretty juvenile. However, when Borat was able to get an entire bar in Arizona to sing "throw the Jew down the well," it revealed people's indifference to anti-Semitism. When, as Bruno, I started kissing a man in a cage fight in Arkansas and nearly started a riot, it showed the violent potential of homophobia. And when, disguised as an ultra-woke developer, I proposed building a mosque in one rural community, prompting a resident to proudly admit, "I am racist, against Muslims," it showed a wide acceptance of Islamophobia.  The ugliness my jokes help reveal is why I'm so worried about our pluralistic democracies. Demagogues appeal to our worst instincts. Conspiracy theories once confined to the fringe are going mainstream, fueled in part by President Donald Trump, who has spread such paranoid lies more than 1,700 times to his 67 million Twitter followers. It's as if the Age of Reason - the era of evidential argument - is ending, and now knowledge is delegitimized and scientific consensus is dismissed. Democracy, which depends on shared truths, is in retreat, and autocracy, which thrives on shared lies, is on the march. Hate crimes are surging, as are murderous attacks on religious and ethnic minorities.  All this hate and violence actually has something in common: It's being facilitated by a handful of Internet companies that amount to...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killer Droids Geared to 'Wipe Out Swathes of Human Population'...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201911251077396399-killer-robots-geared-to-wipe-out-swathes-of-human-population-warns-expert/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dozens of countries have been echoing calls to negotiate a treaty to retain “meaningful human control over the use of force”, including 30 states that want to ban fully autonomous weapons, also known as lethal autonomous weapons systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Good pope v bad pope?' Hopkins, Pryce star in Vatican drama...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/good-pope-v-bad-pope-hopkins-pryce-star-055539543.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the first time in seven centuries the Catholic church has two living popes, and "The Two Popes" imagines a series of spirited debates between the strict, conservative Benedict and his charismatic successor. The two men on screen bridge their differences, bonding over Benedict's piano-playing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More college students look for mental health help on campus...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/08e5c195bf04471e9c4a127abe831d91</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More college students are turning to their schools for help with anxiety, depression and other mental health problems, and many must wait weeks for treatment or find help elsewhere as campus...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasures worth 'up to billion euros' stolen from museum...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/25/thieves-steal-priceless-treasures-dresden-green-vault-museum</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police say thieves on the run after raid at historic Green Vault inside royal palace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singapore invokes 'fake news' law for first time over FACEBOOK post...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191125050130-v7vpg</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SINGAPORE-FAKENEWS/ (UPDATE 1):UPDATE 1-Singapore invokes 'fake news' law for first time over Facebook post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NXIVM cult leader hunted virgins on TINDER burned initials onto them...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/actress-reveals-cult-leader-who-20952362</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NXIVM cult leader Keith Raniere told one slave to tell her to “find other virgins” on Tinder “shorter than me, younger is fine”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web inventor unveils plan to save The Internet...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/web-inventor-unveils-ambitious-rule-book-for-internet-responsibility-2019-11-24</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Wide Web inventor Tim Berners-Lee released an ambitious rule book for online governance — a bill of rights and obligations for the internet — designed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child killed by ice sculpture at Christmas market...</title>
      <link>https://today.rtl.lu/news/luxembourg/a/1436406.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;today.rtl.lu&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A child was fatally injured at the Place Guillaume II Christmas market on Sunday evening at around 8pm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venetians protest over flooding, cruise ships...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/venetians-protest-over-flooding-cruise-ships-233618064.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thousands of Venetians took to the streets of the Renaissance city on Sunday to vent anger over frequent flooding and the impact of giant cruise ships. Braving heavy rain, between 2,000 and 3,000 people answered the call of environmental groups and a collective opposed to the boats. Critics say the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship with 14,000 sheep aboard capsizes...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ship-14-600-sheep-aboard-capsizes-off-romania-220001331.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rescuers were struggling Sunday to save 14,600 sheep loaded on a cargo ship that capsized in the Black Sea off the coast of Romania, they said. The Queen Hind bound for Saudi Arabia overturned for yet unknown reasons shortly after leaving Romania's Midia port. The crew of 20 Syrians and one Lebanese</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BORIS PROMISES MERRY BREXMAS...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191124161456-yln5e</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;BRITAIN-ELECTION/ (UPDATE 5, PIX, TV):UPDATE 5-UK's Johnson offers up new Brexit promise for Christmas</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense chief Esper ousts Navy secretary in Trump SEAL fallout...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/defense-chief-esper-ousts-navy-secretary-in-trump-seal-fallout/ar-BBXh72X</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  Epstein 'madam' Ghislaine Maxwell set to come out of hiding, meet with FBI...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/10414777/prince-andrew-ghislaine-maxwell-epstein-reveal/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PRINCE Andrew’s pal Ghislaine Maxwell will speak to the FBI about their links to paedo Jeffrey Epstein. Sources said the sex slaver’s “madam”, 57, aims to emerge from hiding within days. Sources sa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon asks for Navy secretary's resignation over SEAL war crime case...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/navy/dod-chief-asks-for-navy-secretary-s-resignation-over-private-proposal-in-navy-seal-s-case-1.608539</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defense Secretary Mark Esper asked for the resignation of Navy Secretary Richard Spencer on Sunday after losing confidence in him over his handling of the case of a Navy SEAL accused of war crimes in Iraq, the Pentagon said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REPORT:  2 million Americans don't have access to running water and basic plumbing...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/2-million-americans-dont-have-access-to-running-water-and-basic-plumbing-2019-11-20</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;This lack of access ‘makes it difficult to stay healthy, earn a living, go to school, and care for a family.’</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt police free journalists held in raid on news outlet...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/egypt-police-free-journalists-held-raid-news-outlet-192620925.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Police in Egypt have released three news editors detained on Sunday in a swoop on local news outlet Mada Masr, the independent organisation said on its website. The publication posted on social media that nine plain-clothed officers raided their Cairo office and questioned journalists there for several</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darkside of K-POP: Suicide blights industry steeped in sex scandals, slave contracts and death...</title>
      <link>https://www.thescottishsun.co.uk/news/4848347/goo-hara-dead-suicide-kpop-slaves/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thescottishsun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;TOURING the world and being met by thousands of screaming fans, K-Pop bands have become an international phenomenon and attract bigger crowds to Wembley than many UK stars. However with the heartbr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'1917'  WAR FILM 'MASTERPIECE'...</title>
      <link>https://www.showbiz411.com/2019/11/23/oscars-2020-last-big-movie-to-screen-sam-mendes-extraordinary-1917-best-war-movie-since-private-ryan-iwo-jima</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.showbiz411.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have seen the last big big Oscar buzzed movie for the 2020 Academy Awards. Yesterday  I told you about the penultimate entry, Clint Eastwood’s four star “Richard Jewell.” Now w…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside bloody cartel war for Mexico's multibillion-dollar avocado industry...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/inside-the-bloody-cartel-war-for-mexicos-multibillion-dollar-avocado-industry/ar-BBXgJzV</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emails show an extensive effort to justify decision to block Ukraine aid...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/white-house-review-turns-up-emails-showing-extensive-effort-to-justify-trump-s-decision-to-block-ukraine-military-aid/ar-BBXgYXi</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film about London gang violence banned after machete brawl during screening...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/breaking-vue-bans-blue-story-20949659</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Five teenagers have been arrested, including a girl aged 13, after a violent fight involving 100 people broke out at the packed Vue cinema in entertainment complex Star City near Nechells on Saturday evening</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With boss running for president, BLOOMBERG NEWS sets rules...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/d95e83223e034dfda663c917ca6f8509</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — With Michael Bloomberg now running for president, the news service that bears his name said Sunday it will not “investigate” him or any of his Democratic rivals, and Bloomberg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL and Kaepernick still at odds on failed workout...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/87bf3f4e6ea34133931b290479c0d279</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A week after Colin Kaepernick’s NFL workout fell apart, disagreements and distrust about it remain on issues such as its timing, who was invited and who could film the quarterback. In...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALL IN</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/583b5e7ecfc84b61b470b5e8e3c4bcab</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Billionaire and former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg, one of the world’s richest men, has formally launched a Democratic bid for president. Ending weeks of...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret documents reveal how mass detention camps work...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4ab0b341a4ec4e648423f2ec47ea5c47</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The watch towers, double-locked doors and video surveillance in the Chinese camps are there “to prevent escapes.” Uighurs and other minorities held inside are scored on how well they speak the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paging Dr. Robot: Artificial intelligence moves into care...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/49877aba863e4f5199d0a22d68966bcc</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The next time you get sick, your care may involve a form of the technology people use to navigate road trips or pick the right vacuum cleaner online. Artificial intelligence is spreading...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu faces court, party challenges after indictment...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191124170559-mi4j8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ISRAEL-POLITICS/ (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX):UPDATE 1-Netanyahu faces court, party challenges after indictment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bloomberg officially launches 2020 presidential bid...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/2020-election/michael-bloomberg-launches-2020-presidential-bid-n1090216</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The ad promotes Bloomberg's record as mayor and then promises "to rebuild the country and restore faith in the dream that defines us."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schiff open to more public hearings...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/meet-the-press/video/schiff-on-more-public-hearings-don-t-foreclose-the-possibility-73991237891</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;House Intelligence Committee Chair Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) joins Chuck Todd to discuss the impeachment inquiry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Docs Reveal Details of Pompeo's Role in Ukraine Affair...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/new-documents-reveal-details-of-pompeos-role-in-ukraine-affair/ar-BBXeuRZ</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince's secret Buckingham rendezvous with procurer...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7718971/Prince-Andrew-secretly-met-Jeffrey-Epsteins-madam-Ghislaine-Maxwell-Buckingham-Palace.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prince Andrew met Maxwell on June 6 inside the Prince's private Palace quarters, and she is said to have brought four other people along with her. They are believed to have stayed for two hours.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the secret lab creating MASERATI's future...</title>
      <link>https://www.autoblog.com/2019/11/24/maserati-innovation-lab-modena-italy/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.autoblog.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maserati will overhaul its product portfolio between 2020 and 2023. It will launch the offensive when it unveils a sports car at the 2020 Geneva auto show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion's newest hot model -- 63-year-old woman...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/11/23/meet-fashions-newest-hot-model-63-year-old-janis-wilkins/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Jan. 8, 2018, photographer Janis Wilkins returned home from an afternoon yoga class to find her Washington Heights apartment building engulfed in flames. The seven-alarm fire — caused by a fault…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson unveils manifesto for Brexit Britain...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/johnson-unveils-manifesto-brexit-britain-013558879.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;British Prime Minister Boris Johnson was unveiling his Conservative Party's manifesto on Sunday, pledging to move on from Brexit and austerity in a bid to secure a general election majority. The main plank of the Conservative manifesto is the Brexit deal Johnson negotiated with Brussels in October</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top lawmakers reach agreement to keep spending...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/4e96e765b00440dd837f732e2934dd19</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Negotiations on a package of spending bills to fund the federal government have produced a key breakthrough, though considerably more work is needed to wrap up the long-delayed...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As feds target CA's homeless crisis, state braces for fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2019/11/23/trump-takes-aim-californias-homeless-leaving-governor-wary/4276242002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trump administration officials appear poised to release a new homelessness strategy, which has California officials wary and poised for battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picassos in the Garage? Artist's Handyman Convicted of Hiding Stolen Works...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/picassos-in-the-garage-artists-handyman-is-convicted-of-hiding-stolen-works/ar-BBXdso4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Virginia, and elsewhere, gun supporters prepare to defy new laws...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-virginia-and-elsewhere-gun-supporters-prepare-to-defy-new-laws/ar-BBXdIYd</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malls now targeting millionaires...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/23/economy/luxury-malls-holiday-shopping/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Suburban malls in the middle of America have been hit hard due the financial woes of anchor tenants like Macy's and JCPenney and the slow death spiral at Sears.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget the Oval. The real action is in the President's residence...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/11/24/trump-white-house-residence-power-epicenter-073139</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fixated on impeachment proceedings against him, Trump is increasingly taking his official business to the White House’s executive residence to escape perceived risks of his formal office space.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's college basketball player arrested on murder charges...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/crime--law/breaking-ksu-women-basketball-player-arrested-murder-charges/WR8aRO7P50bQpu2Xl4yEZL/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The starting point guard for Kennesaw State University’s women’s basketball team has bee...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>800 men 'asked' to give DNA to solve violent 1996 murder...</title>
      <link>https://news.sky.com/story/men-from-german-village-called-up-to-help-solve-claudia-rufs-murder-11868473</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.sky.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Claudia Ruf was 11 when she was murdered in 1996 but, despite an extensive investigation, her killer has not yet been found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope: Possession of atom bomb 'immoral'...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/bc54b85007614cd283b3eb23f32ab6a0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIROSHIMA, Japan (AP) — Pope Francis traveled to Hiroshima and Nagasaki on Sunday to demand that world powers renounce their nuclear arsenals, declaring the use and possession of atomic bombs an...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
