<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Is 'Little Rocket Man' winning?</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/12/little-rocket-man-winning/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kim Jong-un is pushing the envelope. He is taunting the Americans. We have told him what he must do. And he is telling us where we can go.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maddow rooted for the Steele dossier to be true. Then it fell apart...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2019/12/26/rachel-maddow-rooted-steele-dossier-be-true-then-it-fell-apart/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Various news outlets cited instances of vindication for the Steele dossier. Then came the Horowitz report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE REPORTER 2019:  I often can't recall what story was two days ago...</title>
      <link>https://www.bozemandailychronicle.com/ap_news/washington/my-year-of-covering-the-trump-white-house/article_b1133d73-417c-54eb-b976-84043ac31f81.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bozemandailychronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — A year of President Donald Trump is better measured in dog years, with so much being packed into 12 months — a Mueller report, trade talks, tweet storms,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants in Thailand 'broken' for lucrative animal tourism...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/elephants-thailand-broken-lucrative-animal-tourism-000910080.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Separated from their mothers, jabbed with metal hooks, and sometimes deprived of food -- many Thai elephants are tamed by force before being sold to lucrative tourism sites increasingly advertised as "sanctuaries" to cruelty-conscious travellers. Balanced precariously on hind legs, two-year-old</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Los Angeles prosecutors reviewing 8 cases against Weinstein...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/308062beead91476ff566c1e993114a2</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Prosecutors in Los Angeles are reviewing eight cases accusing disgraced film mogul Harvey Weinstein of sexual assault, an official said Thursday. The Los Angeles and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TROUBLES:  CONDE NAST shakes up board of directors...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/26/conde-nast-shakes-up-board-of-directors/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Magazine powerhouse Condé Nast is shaking up the board of directors of its money-losing International subsidiary as it forges ahead with the combination of its US and overseas operations. Jonathan …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eccentric socialite to blame for CA wild pig problem...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/sfhistory/article/One-eccentric-socialite-is-to-blame-for-14916088.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Today's wild pigs are a hybrid breed, a mixture of two animals that have no place in California. The first is the standard domesticated pig, introduced by Spanish colonizers in the mid-1700s. Russian immigrants also apparently let some loose near Fort Ross in Sonoma in the 1800s. And as Gold Rush settlers flowed into the state, they killed the hogs' biggest predator, the bear. So the once-domestic pig spread, becoming a feral pig out in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASDAQ TOPS 9,000...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks/nasdaq-tops-9000-on-boosts-from-amazon-trade-optimism-idUSKBN1YU0QL</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nasdaq crossed the 9,000-point mark for the first time on Thursday as all th...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled union honchos' lavish spending exposed...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/embattled-union-honchos-lavish-spending-exposed-villas-four-figure-dinners-cigars</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Work hard, play hard -- and on the union's dime. That might as well have been the motto for some former top officials at the United Automobile Workers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Jails Use Kinder Approach To Solitary Confinement...</title>
      <link>https://sacramento.cbslocal.com/2019/12/26/california-jails-solitary-confinement-changes/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sacramento.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An inmate in solitary confinement at a California jail was refusing to leave his cell. The jailers' usual response: Send an "extraction team" of corrections officers to burst into the cell and drag him out.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No such thing as 'free shipping'...</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2020/01/the-myth-of-free-shipping/603031/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How retailers hide the costs of delivery—and why we’re such suckers for their ploys</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Struggling dairy farmers get creative...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/struggling-dairy-farmers-building-a-future-with-hazelnuts-specialty-milk-and-creative-thinking/ar-BBYm6GU</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People on intermittent fasting diet live longer...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/12/26/people-on-the-intermittent-fasting-diet-live-longer-study/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;One researcher says there’s decades of research pointing to intermittent fasting as the diet to try in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump already searching for his next secretary of state...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/global-opinions/trump-is-already-searching-for-his-next-secretary-of-state/2019/12/26/9a521e2e-2803-11ea-b2ca-2e72667c1741_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The race for a successor has already begun.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season of need on family farms...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/in-trump-country-a-season-of-need-on-family-farms/ar-BBYmQwq</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA Paves Way GOOGLEAMAZON Drones...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/technology/475969-faa-proposes-tracking-most-drones-in-us-airspace</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The country's top transportation regulator on Thursday proposed tracking nearly every drone in U.S.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan hangs man in rare execution of foreigner...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-50916494</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Chinese man, who murdered a family of four, is the first foreigner to be executed in 10 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC gas leak cripples Metro station, prompts evacuations... Developing...</title>
      <link>https://wtop.com/dc/2019/12/metro-green-line-service-affected-near-navy-yard/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;wtop.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A gas leak near the Navy Yard Metro station Thursday afternoon has prompted the response of Washington Gas and D.C. Fire and EMS officials in the area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Town Cancels New Year's Eve Fireworks To 'Send Environmental Message'...</title>
      <link>https://denver.cbslocal.com/2019/12/26/breckenridge-cancels-fireworks-environmental-message/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;denver.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Town of Breckenridge has cancelled its New Year’s Eve fireworks this year, to send "the right environmental message."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine to buy more U.S. Javelin anti-tank missile systems...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191226162144-6bch8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;UKRAINE-US/JAVELIN:Ukraine to buy more U.S. Javelin anti-tank missile systems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Home Sales Totaled $1.1 Billion...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/finance/realestate/this-year-e2-80-99s-top-10-us-home-sales-totaled-2411-billion/ar-BBYms52</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico police investigate killing of 4....</title>
      <link>https://www.krqe.com/news/new-mexico/police-investigate-shooting-in-rio-rancho/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.krqe.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RIO RANCHO, N.M. (KRQE) – Rio Rancho police are investigating a shooting in a neighborhood near Unser and Paseo Del Volcan Wednesday night. Information is limited, but Captain Andrew Rodrigue…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAHM EMANUEL:  We are more than our disagreements...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/opinion/article/Don-t-sink-to-Trump-s-level-we-are-more-than-the-14932528.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Every so often, and frequently with no one paying much attention, something happens in Washington that goes against the grain. This month, House Democrats unveiled articles of impeachment the same morning they announced a deal with the Trump White House updating NAFTA. If everything in Washington centered on conflict, President Donald Trump and Speaker Nancy Pelosi, D-Calif., would never have been able to align themselves on a major trade agreement.  And yet there they were, serving up evidence that division and consensus can sit, however uncomfortably, side by side.  What did that moment tell us? Riven though we are, we are also, on many matters, united. The paradox of this moment presents Democrats with an opportunity.  Trump knows that conflict is his lifeblood. Division fit the 2016 zeitgeist, a moment when the electorate was hungry to give the elite a long-awaited comeuppance. And the president can still find plenty of places in the country where his hateful rhetoric finds a hungry audience.  But things have since taken a turn. Today, the president's inability to get more than 45 percent in most polls suggests the electorate's thirst for conflict has morphed into something else - namely, an equal desire for consensus.  Ahead of 2020, voters are desperate for someone who will tap into the lost sense of community that Barack Obama embraced when he famously argued at the height of our national split over Iraq that "there is not a liberal America and a conservative America - there is the United States of America." They are in search of someone who will provide a more accurate picture of how much we agree on, someone who will shine a light on how we can rise above the conflicts that divide us.  The evidence is irrefutable. By a margin of 74% to 21%, Gallup polling this year found that Americans believe trade is an...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drones Need Huge Tracking Network for Expanded Flights, FAA Says...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/drones-huge-tracking-network-expanded-162955689.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- All but the smallest civilian drones would have to broadcast radio tracking data to ensure greater safety and prevent terrorism under a sweeping proposal unveiled by U.S. regulators Thursday.The long-awaited draft rules call for a massive new tracking network for everything from toys to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is revenge porn protected speech? The Supreme Court may soon weigh in... </title>
      <link>https://www.unionleader.com/news/courts/is-revenge-porn-protected-speech-the-supreme-court-may-soon/article_b5fc78ec-65e0-5ae6-99a1-df2c6bd0242e.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.unionleader.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;When Bethany Austin learned that her fiance had been unfaithful in late May 2016, she ended the seven-year relationship and called off their upcoming wedding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Fonda talks about malaise and 'Fire Drill Fridays'... </title>
      <link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/lifestyle/article/Jane-Fonda-talks-about-malaise-and-Fire-Drill-14932432.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfchronicle.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jane Fonda, 82, is an award-winning actor and a longtime activist. She moved to Washington, D.C., for four months to launch "Fire Drill Fridays," a campaign with weekly demonstrations to focus attention on the urgency of climate-change issues. - - - Q: You've been an activist for a long time. Can you talk about your first exposure to activism? A: I remember very well. I had been living in France for nine years. Married. Child. There were American GIs who were resisting the war. They had been in Vietnam and had deserted, and were in Paris, and looking for compatriots to help them with doctors and dentists and stuff like that. They are the ones that helped me understand the war and what was wrong. Long story short, they gave me a book by Jonathan Schell called "The Village of Ben Suc." And it just rocked me. My life, up until that point - it was glamorous. It was interesting. It was empty. And I was feeling the emptiness. And I just realized, Where have I been? What have I been doing with my life? The worst thing in life is to be going through it and not know why you're there. Not feel that your life has any meaning. So I was totally prepared to throw all of that out and to completely immerse myself into a new world. I left everything, and I moved [back], and I called up [a] person running [antiwar] mobilizations and I said, "I'm Jane Fonda, and I know that there's big things happening around the country. What can I do to help?" He said, "Well, what are your politics?" [Laughs.] And I didn't know - I was so not active, I didn't even know what to say. I thought, Well, I'm going to have to learn really quick a whole lot of things. I didn't learn quite quick enough, but I did my best. Q: Right - you have said of sitting on the enemy aircraft gun on your trip to North Vietnam, "I will go to my grave regretting that." A:...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morocco jails YouTuber, detains journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.newindianexpress.com/world/2019/dec/26/morocco-jails-youtuber-detains-journalist-for-insulting-the-king-2081285.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.newindianexpress.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a separate case, a Moroccan journalist and activist was charged and detained over a tweet that had criticised a court decision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON STOCK UP 21.6%... </title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/amazon-says-the-last-delivery-before-christmas-arrived-at-1159pm-pt-in-seattle-2019-12-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon.com Inc. said in its Thursday holiday round up that the last delivery the e-commerce giant made before Christmas was at 11:59pm PT in Seattle....</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What will US do to combat 'deepfakes' ahead of election?</title>
      <link>https://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2019/12/24/deepfakes-michigan-members-of-congress-address-threat/2679222001/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.freep.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michigan members of Congress are pushing legislation to battle technology that makes forged videos and audio appear real</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drunk e-scooter on German Autobahn!</title>
      <link>https://www.courthousenews.com/drunk-driver-rides-e-scooter-on-german-autobahn/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.courthousenews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;German police on Thursday stopped an inebriated 27-year-old man who was caught riding an electric scooter on a motorway.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLIDAY HORROR: Christmas Party In Philly Turns Tragedy When Mother Stabbed To Death...</title>
      <link>https://philadelphia.cbslocal.com/2019/12/25/christmas-party-tragedy-mother-stabbed-death-boyfriend-arrested-olney/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;philadelphia.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her teenage son is fighting for his life after being stabbed trying to defend her.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia raids offices of Kremlin critic...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/russia-raids-navalnys-offices-kremlin-critic-free-113918973.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Russian security officials Thursday searched the offices of Kremlin critic Alexei Navalny's anti-corruption foundation, with his team calling the raid a new bid to disrupt their work. "What's happening is part of the coordinated campaign against the anti-corruption foundation," Navalny</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family Suicide By Jumping From Boston Parking Garage...</title>
      <link>https://boston.cbslocal.com/2019/12/26/renaissance-parking-garage-northeastern-riggles-woman-children-deaths/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;boston.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;An investigation continues a day after a woman and two young children died following an incident near a Boston parking garage on Christmas Day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>230,000 people killed in a day: Asia remembers devastating 2004 tsunami...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20191226040313-cut97</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;INDIANOCEAN-TSUNAMI/ (UPDATE 1, TV, PIX, GRAPHIC):UPDATE 1-230,000 people lost in a day: Asia remembers devastating 2004 tsunami</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood's Most Epic Fails of Decade, From MOVIEPASS to 'MEGYN KELLY TODAY'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/10-most-epic-fails-in-hollywood/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even Netflix didn't get out of the 2010s unscathed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONFUSION: Japanese News Agency Reports NKorea Missile Test In Error...</title>
      <link>https://www.rt.com/news/476880-north-korea-fires-missile-japan/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rt.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Japan’s broadcaster NHK reported a missile launch from North Korea, stating the projectile was estimated to have fallen some 2,000 km off Hokkaido's coast. The news, however, was retracted shortly afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEW RECORDS... DEVELOPING...</title>
      <link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/stock-market-set-to-rise-in-post-christmas-climb-2019-12-26</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.marketwatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;U.S. stocks opened higher Thursday in light trading, with investor attention still squarely on trade deal progress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At each end of Pacific, skepticism over China farm purchases...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/ebf7a2646dda9371fe2762a5a3f1804f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OMAHA, Neb. (AP) — President Donald Trump likes to joke that America's farmers have a nice problem on their hands: They're going to need bigger tractors to keep up with surging Chinese demand for...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Garages aren't even cheap anymore:' Bay Area exodus drives lowest growth rate in years...</title>
      <link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2019/12/26/garages-arent-even-cheap-anymore-bay-area-exodus-drives-lowest-growth-rate-in-years/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mercurynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amid exodus of fed-up residents, the net growth has come largely from babies born here, and  they don’t take up a lot of space yet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facts are misremembered to fit personal biases, study finds...</title>
      <link>https://www.dispatch.com/news/20191225/facts-are-misremembered-to-fit-personal-biases-ohio-state-study-finds</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dispatch.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent study by Ohio State researchers found that people tend to misremember information to match commonly-held beliefs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yellowstone's Steamboat Geyser breaks eruption record, stuns scientists...</title>
      <link>https://bgr.com/2019/12/24/steamboat-geyser-yellowstone-park-2019/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;bgr.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re headed to Yellowstone National Park in Wyoming, there’s a good chance that visiting the park’s iconic geysers will be near the top of your to-do list. In 2019, tourists …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrier to Trump Wall: Landowners in Texas...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/us/a-barrier-to-trumps-border-wall-landowners-in-texas/ar-BBYm5rv</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raids and conscription: Russian authorities crack down on Kremlin critics...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/Raids-and-conscription-Russian-authorities-crack-14932111.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOSCOW - In Russian authorities' latest crackdown this week on Kremlin critics, opposition leader Alexei Navalny's Anti-Corruption Foundation office was raided Thursday, just days after one of his top aides was suddenly conscripted and sent to a desolate base in the Arctic.  Navalny, who was barred from running in Russia's 2018 presidential election, said on Twitter that he was dragged out of the office by force before eventually being allowed to return. In the moments before his brief detention, Navalny live-streamed the raid as police used power tools to saw through the door.  "The picked the day not by chance - I was supposed to go on the air," Navalny said on Twitter, referring to his YouTube channel.  There have been multiple raids on Navalny's office this year, and he wrote on Instagram that the official reason for this one was related to his group's refusal to take down a 2017 YouTube documentary that investigated alleged corruption involving Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev. A criminal case was opened against Ivan Zhdanov, director of the Anti-Corruption Foundation, as a result, and Thursday's search was apparently part of the investigation of that case, Navalny said.  Navalny says he will not take down the video, which has more than 32 million views.  Navalny is Russia's most prominent and most vocal critic of President Vladimir Putin, which has made him and his allies targets of the Kremlin's methods for keeping dissenting voices at bay. The European Court of Human Rights ruled last year that the multiple arrests of Navalny - there were seven from 2012 to 2014 alone - violated his rights and appeared to be part of a broader effort "to bring the opposition under control."  The raid on his office comes less than a week after Ruslan Shaveddinov, a 23-year-old project manager for Navalny's anti-corruption group, was...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial Finds Scant Precedent in History...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-senate-impeachment-trial-finds-090000682.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;(Bloomberg) -- Bill Clinton’s impeachment two decades ago set the modern template for President Donald Trump’s upcoming trial in the Senate. But the process may be even more contentious this time given sharper tribal divisions in Washington.Clinton’s four-week proceeding in 1999 riveted the nation. Thirteen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too big to fail? Tech's decade of scale and impunity...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/dec/26/too-big-to-fail-techs-decade-of-scale-and-impunity</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Big tech behaves as though power absolves them of responsibility. Have we learned nothing since the financial crash?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: IT COULD BE BERNIE</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/news/2019/12/26/can-bernie-sanders-win-2020-election-president-089636</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;His resiliency in the primary has caught the attention of the party establishment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Central American surge, Mexicans join asylum line at border...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2019-12-26/seeing-a-central-american-surge-mexicans-join-the-asylum-line-at-the-u-s-border</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After a long, steady decline in overall Mexican immigration following its peak in 2000, the number of Mexican asylum seekers arriving at the southwestern border has been steadily rising in recent months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: LARGE, NON-GOVT DRONES FLYING GRID PATTERN OVER COLORADO...</title>
      <link>https://www.infowars.com/large-non-government-drones-flying-in-mysterious-grid-pattern-over-colorado/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.infowars.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nobody knows who's flying them</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rally far outpacing past presidents...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/12/26/trumps-stock-market-rally-is-far-outpacing-past-us-presidents.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The S&amp;P 500 has returned more than 50% since Trump was elected, more than double the average market return of presidents three years into their term, according to Bespoke Investment Group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Kevin Spacey accuser and ex of Norwegian princess kills self...</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/12/25/ari-behn-norwegian-princess-ex-and-kevin-spacey-accuser-dead-at-47/?_ga=2.129877706.714084198.1577358933-753093207.1577358933</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In December 2017, Behn came forward to accuse Spacey, 60, of groping him under a table at a Nobel Peace Prize concert in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUDY: Caffeine may offset holiday weight gain...</title>
      <link>https://abc13.com/health/caffeine-may-offset-holiday-weight-gain-study-says/5785117/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abc13.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study found that drinking four cups of coffee daily could reduce weight gain from a diet high in fat and sugar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump on quest for foreign wins -- and drama -- in election year...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/trump-quest-foreign-wins-drama-election-045911063.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Donald Trump has shattered norms and niceties on the world stage in his nearly three years in office. Entering an election year, Trump is unlikely to slow down as he seeks what has largely eluded him -- a headline-grabbing victory. Trump closes 2019 with a stain as the third president in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Ring of fire' eclipse wows across Asia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/ring-fire-eclipse-wows-across-asia-061506563.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Skywatchers from Saudi Arabia and Oman to India and Singapore were treated to a rare "ring of fire" solar eclipse Thursday. While these types of eclipses occur every year or two, they are only visible from a narrow band of Earth each time and it can be decades before the same pattern is repeated</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, Russia, Iran to hold joint naval drills...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/china-russia-iran-hold-joint-naval-drills-093455381.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China, Russia and Iran will hold joint naval drills starting Friday in the Gulf of Oman, Beijing and Tehran said, at a time of heightened tensions since the US withdrew from a landmark nuclear deal with Tehran. Set to take place from December 27 to 30, the military exercises aim to "deepen exchange</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Babies-for-sale' scheme shocks Armenia...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/babies-sale-scheme-shocks-armenia-034352226.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Syuzan Patvakanyan has been searching for her daughter ever since doctors in post-Soviet Armenia forced her to give her up as a baby nearly two decades ago. Now 35, she shared her story with AFP as the authorities this month detained the country's chief obstetrician-gynaecologist, the head of an</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America's baby mayor, face of anti-abortion movement...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/americas-baby-mayor-face-anti-abortion-movement-022305392.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whitehall (United States) (AFP) - "The mayor's breakfast is ready," Chad McMillan sings out from the living room of his Texas ranch. Charlie McMillan is no ordinary city official -- he's only seven months old and a new face of the anti-abortion movement in America. A twist on US President</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Algeria to Hong Kong, year of anti-establishment rage...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/algeria-hong-kong-anti-establishment-rage-042753397.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Angry citizens have swelled the streets of cities across the globe this year, pushing back against a disparate range of policies but often expressing a common grievance -- the establishment's failure to heed their demands for a more equitable future. While street protests are nothing new, experts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid hotshot passers, old men Brady and Brees roll on...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/284b1651efd7a44e7f2c373d83043fb8</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Between them, Tom Brady and Drew Brees have played 38 pro football seasons, 39 if you count 2008 when the New England star wrecked his knee in Week 1. Both probably should be long retired and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli lawmaker aims to oust Netanyahu in Likud primary...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/24f06ab3d3c1eb62eb532c5be73ff89c</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) — Israel’s governing Likud party was holding a primary vote on Thursday in the first serious internal challenge to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in his more than a decade in...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles DA considers charging Harvey Weinstein as investigation expands...</title>
      <link>https://www.omaha.com/news/national/los-angeles-da-considers-charging-harvey-weinstein-as-investigation-expands/article_5cc6e3dc-8aa0-59a0-9ed1-55191ee32223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.omaha.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES — More than two years after the Los Angeles and Beverly Hills police departments launched sexual assault investigations into Harvey Weinstein, the Los Angeles County district attorney’s office</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top adviser to Syria's president warns of 'operations' against US troops guarding oil fields...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/u-s-has-no-right-syrian-oil-adviser-president-assad-n1106846</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bouthaina Shaaban was referring to President Donald Trump’s declaration earlier this year that the U.S. would “keep” Syrian oil.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYT:  For Trump Organization, Office Skyscrapers Make Up for Lagging Hotels...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/politics/in-trying-times-for-presidents-business-it-turns-out-less-trump-is-more/ar-BBYkY2A</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE GOOD NEWS FILE...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/good-news</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden's Appeal to the 'Reasonable Republican Dad' Vote...</title>
      <link>https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/elections-2020/joe-bidens-appeal-to-the-reasonable-republican-dad-vote/ar-BBYkY7i</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.msn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis-related psychosis, addiction, ER visits: For young users, marijuana can be dangerous game...</title>
      <link>https://www.inquirer.com/health/marijuana-addiction-adolescents-psychosis-abuse-vaping-penn-state-20191223.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.inquirer.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While it was once doubted as an addictive substance, treatment professionals now say they are seeing more adolescents and young adults with cannabis use disorder. Often starting in their early teens, many graduate to daily use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET IT BE:  Phil Spector pictured sporting goatee, bald head, hearing aids in latest mugshot...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7826387/Phil-Spector-79-pictured-sporting-goatee-bald-head-hearing-aids-latest-mugshot.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The 79-year-old fallen music legend, main in 2019, was sentenced to 19-years to life in 2009. He was convicted over the 2003 death of Lana Clarkson. His previous looks are pictured inset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85-year-old woman charged with murder, assault in double shooting...</title>
      <link>https://komonews.com/news/local/85-year-old-woman-charged-with-murder-assault-in-double-shooting-at-federal-way-home</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;komonews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;FEDERAL WAY, Wash. - An 85-year-old woman has been charged with first degree murder and assault in the double shooting of her roommates earlier this month. Beverly Jenne is now being held on $1 million bail and will be booked into jail when she is released form a Tacoma hospital, prosecutors said. Police report that dispatchers received a 911 call from a woman in her 30s around 1 a. m. on Dec. 19 saying she had been shot in her home in the 2000 block of SW 306th Lane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports of patients' deaths linked to heart devices lurk below radar...</title>
      <link>https://khn.org/news/reports-of-patients-deaths-linked-to-heart-devices-lurk-below-radar/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;khn.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because of a little-known federal exemption program, death data about heart devices sits in inaccessible FDA files that can take up to two years for the public to see under open-records laws.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
