<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>CDC WARNS TOUGH FLU SEASON UNDERWAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.masslive.com/living/index.ssf/2019/01/cdc_could_be_a_tough_flu_season_based_on_early_viruses_hospitalizations.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.masslive.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;H1N1 viruses, the cause of the 2009 global pandemic, predominate so far this season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSM: HE. WILL. STEP. DOWN...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/white-house/423132-predictions-trump-goes-unexpected-candidate-emerges-in-2019</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the coming year, Trump will alienate even GOP senators and Fox News, and a surprising Democratic presidential candidate will step forth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YEAR END POLL:  APPROVAL 47%...</title>
      <link>http://www.rasmussenreports.com/public_content/politics/political_updates/prez_track_dec28</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rasmussenreports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE: What NETFLIX Means When Says 45 Million Watched Movie...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/bird-box-45-million-viewers-netflix-bandersnatch/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Netflix said "Bird Box" was viewed by more than 45 million different accounts during its first 7 days, which drew both cheers and snickers from onlookers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex Workers Using TWITTER for BDSM Meetups...</title>
      <link>https://www.thedailybeast.com/the-sex-workers-using-twitter-for-bdsm-meetups-you-have-to-trust-them</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thedailybeast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;‘Goddesses’ have turned to social media to arrange covert rendezvous with those—usually men—interested in financial domination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUMP: CALM DOWN AND ENJOY THE RIDE...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-ushers-in-2019-saying-calm-down-and-enjoy-the-ride-amid-new-year-challenges</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump ushered in 2019 in characteristic fashion -- with a tweet expressing supreme confidence in himself, contempt for the “fake news media” and optimism for the country.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami prostitutes, drug addicts reveal harrowing tales from streets...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6542633/Brian-Gilden-features-Miami-prostitutes-new-photography-collection.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bruce Gilden captured striking and harrowing portraits of prostitutes for his new collection Only God Can Judge Me. They told him stories of being set on fire and getting hooked on drugs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon law takes effect allowing roadkill for food...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/423391-oregon-law-takes-effect-allowing-roadkill-for-food</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new law took effect in Oregon on Tuesday allowing meat from animals killed by vehicles to be harvested and eaten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Psychic To The Stars Reveals Predictions For Year Ahead...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2018/12/31/2019-predictions-psychic-nikki-weather-celebrities-health-lottery/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Psychic Nikki makes her 2019 predictions for weather, celebrities, health and the lottery. How do fortunes look for the new year?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver rams into Tokyo crowd in anger over 'death penalty'...</title>
      <link>https://japantoday.com/category/crime/8-injured-as-man-rams-car-into-pedestrians-in-Harajuku-in-%27retaliation-for-execution%27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;japantoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eight people were injured after a man rammed his car into pedestrians on a shopping street in central Tokyo in the early hours of Tuesday, police said. The police arrested Kazuhiro Kusakabe, 21, on suspicion of attempted murder. A 19-year-old university student remains unconscious after being hit by the minicar…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain pacemaker to treat epilepsy, Parkinson's...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesnownews.com/health/article/new-brain-pacemaker-may-help-treat-epilepsy-parkinsons/339890</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesnownews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The neurostimulator, named the WAND, works like a "pacemaker for the brain," monitoring the brain's electrical activity and delivering electrical stimulation if it detects something amiss.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'We are not robots': AMAZON warehouse employees push to unionize...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/jan/01/amazon-fulfillment-center-warehouse-employees-union-new-york-minnesota</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Workers announced launch of union push in response to working conditions as company says it does not recognize allegations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG: How President Got Bad at TWITTER...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2019/01/01/how-trump-got-bad-at-twitter-223572</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once he ruled the medium, but read his feed now and you can see something has gone very wrong.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSNBC has something to crow about...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/entertainment/article/MSNBC-has-something-to-crow-about-13500029.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MSNBC host Rachel Maddow can speak at length on many topics. The whims and demographics of her cable-news audience, however, are not among them. "I think I may just be lucky that we're at a time in the news cycle where there is an appetite for that kind of explanatory work," Maddow said back in the early months of the Trump administration, when her eponymous nightly program was posing a ratings threat to the top dogs over at Fox News. That threat has turned into a full-time menace. Whereas "The Rachel Maddow Show" several years ago finished in the double digits in annual rankings of cable-news programs, it's now in the tastemaking vanguard. Over the first three quarters of 2018, Maddow sat in between No. 1 Sean Hannity and No.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These taxpayers face higher dues amid new law...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxbusiness.com/personal-finance/these-us-taxpayers-face-higher-dues-thanks-to-new-law</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxbusiness.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Tax Cuts and Jobs Act could spell bad news for some filers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khan slammed for turning London show into EU tribute...</title>
      <link>https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/8094720/mayor-sadiq-khan-slammed-londons-fireworks-eu-tribute/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thesun.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SADIQ Khan has been slammed for turning the capital’s New Year’s Eve fireworks display into a dazzling tribute to the Europe – and after turning the London Eye into the EU flag. The mayor …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Robinson supporter fighting for life after brutal attack outside home...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/tommy-robinson-supporter-fighting-life-13798981</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shane Wallace was attacked by two men as others sat in a car watching them "beat the hell" out of him in Grimsby, north Lincolnshire</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants shift to dangerous desert crossings...</title>
      <link>https://www.latimes.com/nation/la-na-migrants-desert-20190101-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.latimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More migrant families are crossing the border in remote, desert areas, increasing the dangers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.D. Salinger at 100: Odd Life of Literary Hermit...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/books/features/jd-salinger-life-catcher-in-rye-books-anniversary-franny-zooey-raise-high-roof-beam-john-lennon-a8699026.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passengers on French fair ride spend night stuck 160ft in air...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190101-revellers-spend-new-year-stuck-50-metres-french-funfair</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Revellers spend New Year stuck 50 metres up at French funfair</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low carb? Low fat? What latest dieting studies tell...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/f7ea2e42bf3a4892a8403b90fe02d1c4</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — Bacon and black coffee for breakfast, or oatmeal and bananas? If you're planning to try to lose weight in 2019, you're sure to find a fierce debate online and among friends and family about how best to do it. It seems like everyone has an opinion, and new fads emerge every year. Two major studies last year provided more fuel for a particularly polarizing topic — the role carbs play in making us fat. The studies gave scientists some clues, but, like other nutrition studies, they can't say which diet — if any — is best for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil's Bolsonaro to take power amid high hopes and fears...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/8ecbfe809f0f409f98e969424f44db01</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;SAO PAULO (AP) — Once an outsider mocked by fellow lawmakers for his far-right positions, constant use of expletives and even casual dressing, former army captain Jair Bolsonaro is taking office as Brazil's president Tuesday. A fan of U.S. President Donald Trump, the 63-year-old longtime congressman rose to power on an anti-corruption and pro-gun agenda that has energized Brazilian conservatives and hard-right supporters after four consecutive presidential election wins by the left-leaning Workers' Party.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: NO WALL MONEY EVER...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/558f304ed56d415f93ede2a3f41c100a</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — A week and a half into a partial government shutdown, House Democrats released their plan to re-open the government without approving money for President Donald Trump's border wall. At the same time, the president struggled to find leverage to break the stalemate before the GOP's monopoly on Washington power ended. Democrats in the House unveiled two bills Monday to fund shuttered government agencies and put hundreds of thousands of federal workers back on the job. They planned to pass them as soon as the new Congress convened Thursday, one of the first acts after Democrats took control, according to an aide who was not authorized to discuss the plan and spoke on condition of anonymity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of fireworks light up Vegas...</title>
      <link>https://www.lasvegasnow.com/news/local-news/thousands-of-fireworks-light-up-las-vegas-sky/1682011453</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lasvegasnow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 80,000 pyrotechnics lit up the Las Vegas sky for one of the best fireworks shows in the country as thousands of revelers welcomed the New Year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Ten...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/administration/423368-the-top-ten-democrats-for-2020</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-Mass.) fired the starting pistol for the 2020 presidential race on Monday when she announced she was forming an exploratory committee for a White House bid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kim warns NKorea could consider change of tack... </title>
      <link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/kim-warns-n-korea-could-consider-change-tack-013915619.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;North Korea could consider a change of approach if the US maintains its sanctions on the nuclear-armed country, leader Kim Jong Un warned in his New Year speech Tuesday after 12 months of diplomatic rapprochement. Kim was referring to his summit with US President Donald Trump in Singapore in June, when</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Warren Dives In...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/elizabeth-warren-dives-in-11546298426</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She’ll counter Trump’s populism with a left-wing economic version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Profit Crunch Looms...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/corporate-profit-crunch-looms-as-stocks-slide-11546261258</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the stock market’s swoon began at the end of September, analysts have trimmed their earnings forecasts. And investors are worried the moneymaking outlook for companies will deteriorate further.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRAGER:  2019 a dark year...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/12/the-left-will-make-2019-a-dark-year/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;I rarely make predictions – whether of election results or anything else. My policy has always been to say what I believe should be done, not what will be done. I am making an exception with regard to America in 2019. 2019 will be a dark year in America. Thanks to the left’s control of […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAP:  Passenger strips naked, walks around plane...</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2018/12/passenger-strips-naked-walks-around-plane/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;You may have heard of the TV series “Naked and Afraid,” but there possibly could be one titled “Naked on a Plane” based on the actions of a passenger on a flight over the weekend. A man on an Air India Express flight Saturday from Dubai to Lucknow, India, reportedly stripped off al his clothing […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 Dem brawl for presidency taking shape...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/warrens-jump-into-the-presidential-campaign-kicks-the-2020-race-into-high-gear/2018/12/31/64adbc50-0d02-11e9-831f-3aa2c2be4cbd_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;She is expected to be a major contender in a field that is likely to be large and diverse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More sick children arriving at US border...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2018/12/31/migrant-illnesses-run-rampant-forcing-u-s-border-patrol-seek-help/2454759002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;More than 450 arrived ill in a week through Sunday and 17 are hospitalized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No more shoulders to cry on as couples seek 'woebot' counselors...</title>
      <link>https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/no-more-shoulders-to-cry-on-as-couples-seek-woebot-counsellors-x0d99hr75</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thetimes.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Couples whose partnership is in difficulties could soon be baring their souls to an AI chatbot instead of a human counsellor, according to the head of Britain’s biggest relationship charity. “We...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tough 2018 for Pope Ends With Spokesman's Resignation...</title>
      <link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/12/31/vatican-spokesman-deputy-resign-capping-difficult-year-pope/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.telegraph.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican spokesman and his deputy resigned on Monday over disagreements on strategy, ending a year of upheaval in the Holy See's communications structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 stabbed at UK railway station;  'Allahu Akbar!'</title>
      <link>https://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/greater-manchester-news/manchester-victoria-stabbing-eyewitness-claims-15615300</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sam Clack, a BBC producer, was on a platform at Manchester Victoria railway station waiting for a tram when he witnessed the attack</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military Deletes New Year's Eve Tweet Saying It's 'Ready to Drop Something'... </title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/31/politics/us-military-new-years-eve-bomb-tweet/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US Strategic Command, the unified military force that controls the launch of nuclear weapons, tweeted an unusual New Year's Eve message on Monday featuring B-2 bombers dropping 30,000-pound conventional weapons at a test range.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks Post Worst Year In Decade...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2018/12/31/stock-market-wall-street-stocks-eye-us-china-trade-talks.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Wall Street concluded a tumultuous 2018 as the major stock indexes posted their worst yearly performances since the financial crisis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest ever woman, 122, may have been a fraud...</title>
      <link>https://nationalpost.com/news/world/historys-oldest-woman-a-fraud-theory-says-122-year-old-jeanne-calment-was-actually-a-99-year-old-imposter</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nationalpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Did the real Jeanne Calment die in 1934 at the age of 59?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firm Led by GOOGLE Veterans Uses A.I. to 'Nudge' Workers Toward Happiness...</title>
      <link>https://momogunnews.com/firm-led-by-google-veterans-uses-a-i-to-nudge-workers-toward-happiness/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;momogunnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif. — Technology companies like to promote artificial intelligence’s potential for solving some of the world’s toughest problems, like reducing automobile deaths and helping doctors diagnose diseases. A company started by three former [...]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPDATE:  Smoke Shop Worker Fired After Anti-Trump Rant at Customer...</title>
      <link>https://legalinsurrection.com/2018/12/vape-shop-employees-public-tirade-against-trump-supporter-latest-tds-incident/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;legalinsurrection.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ian Furgeson says Xhale City's corporate office later informed him that the employee was fired.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanka Plans Women's Economic Development Push...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/ivanka-trump-plans-global-womens-economic-development-push-225225919--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ivanka Trump is set to launch a White House effort aimed at women's global economic empowerment in early 2019. A formal launch for the initiative was planned for next week but has been postponed amid uncertainty about the government shutdown, the White House said Monday. The original plan for the</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Britain sends ships to tackle migrant crossing surge... </title>
      <link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/britain-sends-ships-tackle-migrant-crossing-surge-193851060--spt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;au.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Britain announced Monday it will deploy two border patrol ships in the Channel in response to a surge in migrants crossing from France in dinghies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human waste, trash overwhelm some national parks...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/e28b313197bb46bebef0faca24b333ed</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Human feces, overflowing garbage, illegal off-roading and other damaging behavior in fragile areas were beginning to overwhelm some of the West's iconic national parks on Monday, as a partial government shutdown left the areas open to visitors but with little staff on duty. "It's a free-for-all," Dakota Snider, 24, who lives and works in Yosemite Valley, said by telephone Monday, as Yosemite National Park officials announced closings of some minimally supervised campgrounds and public areas within the park that are overwhelmed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYC homicide tally lowest in decades...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b658df4c890e435ebf824b4481287d92</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — New York City could register the fewest number of homicides in several decades in 2018, as the city continues its long battle against violent crime. As of Sunday, the city had recorded five fewer killings than the 292 investigated in 2017, according to preliminary police data provided to The Associated Press. That year's figure was itself the lowest in decades. The New York Police Department said it also had seen a modest decline in shooting incidents in 2018 and an 8 percent drop in robberies. Figures for other categories of crime were not immediately available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revelry, reflection mark transition to new year...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7315f44396d74e39b506b6756ed4f51f</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fireworks, concerts, spiritual services and political addresses abounded to mark the transition to 2019 as revelers around the globe bid farewell Monday to a year filled with challenges to many of the world's most basic institutions, including political, trade and religious ones. A look at how people around the world are ushering in 2019: LONDON Britons ushered in the new year with the familiar chimes of Big Ben, even though the world famous clock has been disconnected for more than a year because of a conservation project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYPD won't fly drone in Times Square during rain...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190101004039-ryaet</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NEW-YEAR/USA-NEW YORK (UPDATE 3, PIX, TV):UPDATE 3-Glowing New Year's Eve ball rises above a sodden Times Square</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 BEGINS!</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6541611/2019-nearly-world-gets-ready-new-year.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Festive lights engulfed the night sky of Downtown Dubai as the city held an extravagant celebration to make sure 2019 arrived with a bang.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 PREVIEW: Warren Livestreams Drinking Beer, Cooking...</title>
      <link>https://twitter.com/davecatanese/status/1079888955661783040</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;twitter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Elizabeth Warren is on Instagram live cooking dinner and drinking a beer. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez is picking our next president. We just don’t know it yet.”</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tech giants turned 'digital wellness' into marketing ploy...</title>
      <link>https://www.wired.com/story/how-big-tech-co-opted-time-well-spent/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wired.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How the large tech corporations turned "digital wellness" into a Goopified trend that gives them a new way to market themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 stabbed at UK railway station; Attacker 'shouted Allah!'...</title>
      <link>https://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/greater-manchester-news/manchester-victoria-knife-attack-station-15615253</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;No trams are currently stopping at Victoria and there's a large police presence outside the station</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beijing face-detecting locks in public housing increases citizen surveillance...</title>
      <link>https://www.engadget.com/2018/12/31/beijing-facial-recognition-public-housing/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.engadget.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beijing is using smart locks with facial recognition to prevent abuses of public housing, but at a steep cost to privacy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEBRON DECLARES: I AM GREATEST EVER!</title>
      <link>https://www.cbssports.com/nba/news/lebron-james-declares-himself-the-greatest-player-of-all-time-because-of-championship-with-cavaliers/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cbssports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;James says his 2016 NBA title with the Cavs made him the best ever</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bibi says won't resign if indicted...</title>
      <link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/netanyahu-i-wont-resign-if-summoned-for-a-hearing-pending-indictment/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.timesofisrael.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;'Imagine if ultimately the case was closed, and a prime minister had been ousted,' Netanyahu says. That would be 'a terrible blow to democracy'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDES WARN: HILLARY COMPARISONS 'REEK SEXISM'</title>
      <link>https://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2018/12/elizabeth-warren-2020-campaign/579214/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theatlantic.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;With her 2020 bid, the senator from Massachusetts wants to reclaim her status as a political outsider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump: Warren's 'psychiatrist' knows whether she thinks she can win White House...</title>
      <link>https://www.foxnews.com/politics/trump-on-whether-warren-thinks-she-can-win-the-presidency-youd-have-to-ask-her-psychiatrist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.foxnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In an exclusive interview with "Fox &amp; Friends" host Pete Hegseth set to air during the Fox News New Year's Eve Special, President Trump suggested that only Massachusetts Democratic Sen. Elizabeth Warren's "psychiatrist" knows whether she thinks she can win the White House in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horny passengers 'try to mate' with snake!</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/31/cane-toads-python-escape-storm-northern-australia-kununurra</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amphibian expert says toads were trying to mate with python, as thousands of the invasive pest are flushed out by rising waters in Kununurra</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army rescinds unusually specific order banning sex, cuddling...</title>
      <link>https://www.stripes.com/news/europe/army-unit-in-europe-rescinds-unusually-specific-order-banning-sex-and-cuddling-1.562272</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.stripes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christmas came late for some Army troops on rotation to Europe when officials canceled an order Wednesday that for nine days banned various sexual acts, including cuddling, for a unit’s soldiers in the rotational barracks at the Grafenwoehr Training Area.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington On Verge of Legalizing Human Composting?</title>
      <link>https://www.sciencealert.com/washington-may-become-the-first-state-to-legalize-human-composting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sciencealert.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;There's something beautiful in deciding how one's final moments should be confined to the memory of our loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20181231-world-cup-host-qatar-introduce-100-percent-booze-tax</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World Cup host Qatar to introduce 100 percent booze tax</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toads ride on Monty the python to escape storm...</title>
      <link>https://www.abc.net.au/news/2018-12-31/cane-toads-hitch-ride-on-monty-the-python-back/10675944</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abc.net.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A farmer in far north WA captures the bizarre sight of a knot of cane toads hitching a ride on a python in the middle of the night.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bezos fortune drops $40,000,000,000+ from peak, but still grew by $24 BILLION this year...</title>
      <link>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/magazines/panache/tim-sweeney-jeff-bezos-lei-jun-the-worlds-biggest-billionaire-winners-losers-of-2018/articleshow/67320613.cms</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;economictimes.indiatimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Singaporean billionaires fared the best in dollar terms, gaining $2.5 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winds could make Vegas New Year's Eve fireworks dicey...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/weather/winds-could-make-las-vegas-new-years-eve-fireworks-dicey-1562570/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The National Weather Service forecasts a high of 49 degrees Monday with winds kicking up and clouds moving out late morning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Philippines President Duterte claims he abused maid as teenager...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2018/12/30/asia/rodrigo-duterte-comments-intl/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Philippines President Rodrigo Duterte has claimed he molested a maid while in high school -- comments his spokesman later said were "made up."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26 BILLION ROBOCALLS IN USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/stop-robocalling-me-i-didnt-11546261200</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Americans’ growing battle against illegal robocallers has reached a boiling point, with victims of one form of phone-related malfeasance now lashing out at those impacted by a different form: phone-number spoofing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Experiment to Stop Latin America Carnage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/inside-the-experiment-to-stop-the-carnage-in-latin-america-11546275481</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A few places in Ecuador and Colombia are exceptions to the regional surge in homicides. Efforts include turning gang members into garbage collectors, and firing hundreds of corrupt police officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens steal NYC bus; 4-hour joyride...</title>
      <link>https://www.nydailynews.com/new-york/nyc-crime/ny-metro-teen-thieves-steal-mta-bus-bronx-20181231-story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nydailynews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A half-dozen teens stole a parked MTA bus from the Bronx and took it on a three-borough joyride — less than 24 hours after a trio of teenagers stole a city bus in Brooklyn.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bolsonaro follows through on gun, 'anti-Marxist' vows...</title>
      <link>https://news.yahoo.com/brazils-bolsonaro-follows-gun-anti-marxist-vows-193827024.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Brasília (AFP) - On the eve of taking office as Brazil's new president on Tuesday, Jair Bolsonaro is making clear he intends to implement the far-right agenda he promised during his election campaign. The announcements underlined Bolsonaro's desire to break with decades of center-left rule in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican spokesman, deputy resign amid crisis for pope...</title>
      <link>https://finance.yahoo.com/news/vatican-spokesman-greg-burke-deputy-resign-suddenly-111645264.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;finance.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Vatican spokesman, Greg Burke, and his deputy resigned abruptly Monday amid an overhaul of the Vatican's communications operations and a crisis period in Pope Francis' papacy. The departures of Burke and his deputy, Paloma Garcia Ovejero, signaled that problems associated with Francis'</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeless starts fire in front of MANDALAY BAY...</title>
      <link>https://www.reviewjournal.com/local/the-strip/homeless-person-causes-fire-in-front-of-mandalay-bay-police-say-1562386/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reviewjournal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Details were not immediately available from the Clark County Fire Department, but Metropolitan Police Department Lt. David Gordon confirmed about 10:40 p.m. that an unknown number of palm trees had...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal marijuana made big promises on racial equity -- and fell short...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/nbcblk/legal-marijuana-made-big-promises-racial-equity-fell-short-n952376</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Time is really up on selling your business dream as a social justice movement,” said the president of the Minority Cannabis Business Association.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian-American Sentenced to Life for Selling Properties to Jews...</title>
      <link>https://www.jpost.com//Arab-Israeli-Conflict/Palestinian-American-gets-life-in-prison-for-selling-properties-to-Jews-575903</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.jpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The man, Isaam Akel, was arrested by the PA last October despite holding an Israeli ID card.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China says ready to work with USA...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/business-46714985</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China's latest statement suggests trade negotiations between the two countries are progressing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venice to charge day-trippers for access...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/3cbde03ccc904e618443198adab23979</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MILAN (AP) — A measure in Italy's 2019 budget law will allow the local government in Venice to charge day-trippers for access to the city's historic center as a way to help defray the considerable costs of maintaining a popular tourist destination built on water, the mayor said. Venice Mayor Luigi Brugnaro said late Sunday on Twitter that the new visitors' tax would "allow us to manage the city better and to keep it clean" and "allow Venetians to live with more decorum."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Investments of 2018? Art, Wine, Cars...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-best-investments-of-2018-art-wine-and-cars-11546232460</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Luxury assets, including wine, art, classic cars and fancy colored diamonds, have outperformed stocks and bonds this year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious swamp cancer killing ponies on island famous for them...</title>
      <link>https://www.delmarvanow.com/story/news/local/virginia/2018/12/29/chincoteague-pony-euthanized-swamp-cancer/2438186002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.delmarvanow.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The disease killed three other ponies this year, as well as two in 2017.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran TV chief sacked over Jackie Chan sex scene...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-middle-east-46720733</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A regional channel showed Jackie Chan's Shinjuku Incident without censoring an "immoral" part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets stagger towards end of worst year since financial crisis... </title>
      <link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/hong-kong-rounds-worst-since-2011-gains-034945504--finance.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sg.news.yahoo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;World stock markets staggered Monday towards the end of their worst year since the global financial crisis a decade ago, rocked by rising interest rates, the global trade war and Brexit, dealers said. London and Paris wobbled in holiday-shortened trade on New Year's Eve -- but nursed dizzying double-digit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS: NO wall money...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/51dd72d6d19e4d2eb0b73dcd2c45aa27</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The Latest on the U.S. government shutdown (all times local): 11:45 a.m. House Democrats are unveiling legislation to re-open the government without money for President Donald Trump's border wall. The House is preparing to vote on the package Thursday when the new Congress convenes. This is according to an aide who was not authorized to discuss the plan publicly and spoke on condition of anonymity. It will include one bill to fund the Department of Homeland Security at current levels through Feb. 8, with $1.3 billion for border security. The package will also include six other bipartisan bills to fund the departments of Agriculture, Interior, Housing and Urban Development and others closed by the partial shutdown. Some have already passed the Senate. Those bills will provide money through the remainder of the fiscal year, to Sept. 30. The partial government shutdown is in its second week over Trump's demand for $5 billion for the wall. --Lisa Mascaro</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
