<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>DRUDGE REPORT</title>
    <link>http://www.drudgereport.com</link>
    <description />
    <item>
      <title>BUCHANAN: Declare it!</title>
      <link>https://www.wnd.com/2019/01/memo-to-trump-declare-an-emergency/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wnd.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the long run, history will validate Donald Trump’s stand on a border wall to defend the sovereignty and security of the United States. Why? Because mass migration from the global South, not climate change, is the real existential crisis of the West. The American people know this, and even the elites sense it. Think […]</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSANGE LIVING CONDITIONS DETERIORATE...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/01/julian-assanges-living-conditions-are-more-akin-to-a-dissident-in-stasi-era-germany-than-an-award-winning-publisher-with-asylum/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romney Rebuffs...</title>
      <link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/politics/2019/01/10/sen-mitt-romney-rebuffs/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sltrib.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Washington • Day 20 of the partial government shutdown came and went without signs of any deal as President Donald Trump considers declaring a national emergency and tapping Pentagon funds to build his long-desired border wall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aviation system hits crunchtime as workers face payless 'payday'...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Aviation-system-hits-crunchtime-as-workers-face-13524561.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The nation's airports remain fully operational despite the government shutdown, but with federal aviation workers expected to miss their first paycheck Friday, union leaders said the system may begin to feel the strain. Leaders say more workers - who continue to work because their jobs are considered essential - may decide to stay home rather than continue to work without pay. The union that represents air traffic controllers fired off a letter to the White House and congressional leaders warning that "the human and economic consequences are increasing and doing greater harm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE READIES FOR RUTH BADER GINSBURG DEPARTURE...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/10/trump-white-house-urging-allies-to-prepare-for-possible-rbg-departure-1096102</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After an ailing Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg missed oral arguments, the Trump team began early groundwork for another potential confirmation battle.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety 'eroding'...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/10/shutdown-aviation-pressure-reopen-1073964</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unpaid air traffic controllers, TSA agents put pressure on the White House to re-open government</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHITE HOUSE GROUNDWORK TO DECLARE EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Trump-administration-lays-groundwork-to-declare-13524958.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON - The White House has begun laying the groundwork for a declaration of national emergency to build President Donald Trump's border wall, a move certain to set off a firestorm of opposition in Congress and the courts but one that could pave the way for an end to the three-week government shutdown. The administration is eyeing unused money in the Army Corps of Engineers budget, specifically a disaster spending bill passed by Congress last year that includes $13.9 billion that has been allocated but not actually spent for civil works projects, two people with knowledge of the developments said Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions rise in prisons as weary guards work double shifts...</title>
      <link>https://www.lmtonline.com/news/article/Tensions-rise-in-federal-prisons-as-weary-guards-13524861.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.lmtonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Prison guard Brian Shoemaker was patrolling the halls of Lee penitentiary in southwestern Virginia Friday when an inmate tried to squeeze past him into a restricted area. Seconds after Shoemaker told the prisoner to turn around, the inmate lunged at him, punching him in the shoulder. Shoemaker did not sustain a major injury. But it did not escape him that he is working without a paycheck at one of the most dangerous federal jobs in America during the partial government shutdown. Fears for his other prison staff members' safety are escalating as 16-hour shifts become routine as a growing number of guards call in sick in protest or to work side jobs to pay their bills.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insists He Never Promised Mexico Would Pay Directly...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/10/trump-says-mexico-is-not-going-to-write-a-check-for-the-wall-contradicting-campaign-pledge.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"When I said Mexico would pay for the wall in front of thousands and thousands of people ... obviously I never meant Mexico would write a check," Trump said.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cops investigating theft of Aretha Franklin's assets...</title>
      <link>https://theblast.com/aretha-franklin-estate-criminal-investigation-stolen-assets/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;theblast.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA protest...</title>
      <link>http://www.fox5atlanta.com/news/tsa-union-holds-rally-at-atlanta-s-airport</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.fox5atlanta.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlanta TSA union voiced their disapproval of the ongoing partial federal government shutdown as it entered its 20th day on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephant blocks road, steals crops from trucks...</title>
      <link>https://www.upi.com/Odd_News/2019/01/10/Wild-elephant-blocks-road-steals-from-trucks/6191547149892/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.upi.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A wild elephant in Thailand was caught on camera blocking traffic on a road through a wooded area and stealing crops from passing trucks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors Examine Ukrainians Who Flocked to Trump Inaugural...</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2019/01/10/us/politics/ukraine-donald-trump-inauguration.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ukrainians were in Washington pushing plans that, in some cases, would have steered the incoming administration to lift tough sanctions on Russia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHUTDOWN DOOMSDAY SCENARIO...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/doomsday-scenario-here-s-what-happens-if-shutdown-drags-n955946</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists warn that a catastrophe is in the making if the partial government closure continues for weeks or months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shalala takes on attack role...</title>
      <link>https://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article224221365.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.miamiherald.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Donna Shalala has been assigned to the Rules Committee, an attack dog role for Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi that requires hours of sparring with Republicans on the House floor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm beats expert doctors at finding pre-cancers...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190110-ai-beats-expert-doctors-finding-cervical-pre-cancers</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;AI beats expert doctors at finding cervical pre-cancers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIDEO:  Military Vehicle Caught Trying to Crush Journalist...</title>
      <link>https://www.breitbart.com/latin-america/2019/01/10/venezuelan-riots-break-out-on-eve-of-maduro-inauguration-fraud/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.breitbart.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A graphic video surfaced on social media Wednesday showing a Venezuelan military tank attempting to run over a journalist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harry Reid Ready to Rumble? Says Feeling Strong...</title>
      <link>https://knpr.org/knpr/2019-01/harry-reid-renewed-ready-rumble</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;knpr.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushes senate on UFO studies: Listen to military sightings!</title>
      <link>http://www.rollcall.com/news/hoh/harry-reid-lobbying-ufo-research-reporting</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.rollcall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid is pushing his former colleagues to make it easier to research and report UFOs among military service members.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WH LAYS GROUNDWORK TO DECLARE EMERGENCY...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/powerpost/trump-administration-lays-groundwork-to-declare-national-emergency-to-build-wall/2019/01/10/e8902698-14fa-11e9-b6ad-9cfd62dbb0a8_story.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtonpost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Administration eyes civil works projects under Army Corps of Engineers budget</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something strange going on as Earth's magnetic pole fast on the move...</title>
      <link>https://www.news.com.au/technology/science/earths-magnetic-pole-is-on-the-move-fast-and-we-dont-know-why/news-story/341c92307a6b19d25b38836c6097be9d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.news.com.au&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Planet Earth is alive. Deep beneath its skin, its life blood — rivers of molten iron — pulse around its core. And this mobile iron is what generates the magnetic field that causes auroras — and keeps us alive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Hang white people' rapper on trial for incitement...</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-46821421</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;French rapper Nick Conrad denies his music video, "Hang White People", was incitement to murder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HORROR: Person decapitated by helicopter at FL airport...</title>
      <link>https://www.abcactionnews.com/news/region-citrus-hernando/death-investigation-underway-after-incident-near-airport-in-hernando-county</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.abcactionnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A death investigation is underway in Hernando County after a person was decapitated by a helicopter at Brooksville-Tampa Bay Regional Airport.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acosta ridiculed for 'glib' border reporting...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/homenews/media/424785-acosta-mocked-for-border-reporting-exactly-walls-work</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CNN Chief White House correspondent Jim Acosta was mocked on social media after his report from a steel wall from the border "didn't show anything resembling a national emergency" in the area of the border that the president will be visiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy officer stole $2,700,000 govt cash to feed poker habit...</title>
      <link>https://pilotonline.com/news/local/crime/article_f5b93292-145a-11e9-91e2-e3e945a52c95.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pilotonline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lt. Randolph Prince was sentenced this week to more than four years in federal prison.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dems keep Ocasio-Cortez off powerful tax-writing committee...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/10/ocasio-cortez-passed-over-for-influential-house-committee/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON — Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez didn’t get a seat on the powerful tax writing committee where she sought to push her progressive agenda of Medicare for All, free college tuition and a gr…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEEKEND: Brady at 41 v Rivers at 37...</title>
      <link>https://www.profootballfocus.com/news/pro-the-divisional-round-is-the-stage-for-brady-vs-rivers-iii</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.profootballfocus.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy sailors in aircraft carrier drug ring plead guilty...</title>
      <link>https://www.navytimes.com/news/your-navy/2019/01/10/two-sailors-in-aircraft-carrier-drug-ring-plead-guilty-to-distribution-charges/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.navytimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drug use, possession and distribution charges have ensnared more than a dozen sailors from the aircraft carrier Ronald Reagan's nuclear reactor department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly-hypothermic man lays on top of 'hissing' WWII explosive for hours...</title>
      <link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/netherlands-bomb-dutch-venlo-greande-incident-man-walk-dog-ww2-evacuation-a8721951.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.independent.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COHEN TO SPILL ON HILL</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/10/ex-trump-lawyer-michael-cohen-to-testify-to-house-oversight-committee.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen's testimony will come before he starts serving a three-year prison term for crimes that include hush-money payoffs to porn star Stormy Daniels and Playboy model Karen McDougal. Cohen has cooperated with special counsel Robert Mueller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global regulators eye house-brand products...</title>
      <link>https://www.axios.com/regulators-amazon-house-brand-products-385ac5c1-e3e8-4c5f-b7fa-40beca19ceb3.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.axios.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Generic products have existed for years, but critics say Amazon has an unfair advantage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R. Kelly streams DOUBLE after docu-series alleges abuse...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/563f1c003b07445aa69fd0444c673fa3</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Nielsen Music says streaming numbers for R. Kelly have nearly doubled after a recent documentary accused the R&amp;amp;B singer of sexual misconduct involving women and underage girls. The Lifetime docu-series "Surviving R. Kelly" detailed abuse allegations against R. Kelly in six episodes, but the singer's streaming numbers grew significantly during and after the series. His music streamed 870,316 times on Jan. 2, the day before the series premiere, but Nielsen said Thursday Kelly's music garnered nearly 1.73 million streams after the sixth episode aired Jan. 6. Kelly averaged more than 955,600 streams in the last week of 2018. He averaged more than 1.5 million streams from Jan. 3-6.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oldest ever...</title>
      <link>https://profootballtalk.nbcsports.com/2019/01/06/tom-brady-philip-rivers-will-be-oldest-pair-of-playoff-starting-quarterbacks/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;profootballtalk.nbcsports.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a season when so many young quarterbacks have played so well, a couple of old veterans are about to square off in the playoffs. The Chargers are heading to New England to take on the Patriots, a…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrigue Swirls Around AMAZON Ownership Stake...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/jeff-bezos-divorce-draws-shrugs-from-amazon-investors-but-intrigue-swirls-around-ownership-stake-1202532789/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Jeff and MacKenzie Bezos announced their plans to divorce after 25 years of marriage, Amazon investors have reacted with a shrug, with the company’s stock price essentially flat in mid-…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMS READY FOR THE RAT</title>
      <link>https://abcnews.go.com/Politics/trumps-lawyer-michael-cohen-testify-congress-february/story?id=60290630</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;abcnews.go.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump’s former personal attorney and fixer, has accepted an invitation to testify in an open session before Congress next month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vegas Cops Issue Warrant for Ronaldo's DNA in Rape Case...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/police-issue-warrant-for-soccer-superstar-ronaldos-dna-in-rape-case-1154714381</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Rogue taxidermist' turns dead animals into teddy bears...</title>
      <link>https://www.sfgate.com/weird/article/kady-rose-taxidermy-soft-mounts-california-art-13521458.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sfgate.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Her Instagram serves as an online gallery of her art pieces - animals with faces that are so lifelike and expressive it's hard to believe they're no longer breathing. One commissioned piece she worked on was a crystal fox, a stunning incarnation of the Vulpex in "Star Wars: The Last Jedi." The fox was adorned with real quartz and amethyst.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oregon killing sea lions after relocation fails...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/7e0991fa9f7f404e904bb271999b6e59</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. (AP) — Oregon wildlife officials have started killing California sea lions that threaten a fragile run of winter steelhead in the Willamette River, a body of water that's miles inland from the coastal areas where the massive carnivorous aquatic mammals usually congregate to feed. The state Department of Fish and Wildlife obtained a federal permit in November to kill up to 93 California sea lions annually below Willamette Falls south of Portland, Oregon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army recruits at e-Sports events; Struggles to reach Generation Z...</title>
      <link>https://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2019/jan/10/army-struggles-to-reach-generation-z-tries-recruit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.washingtontimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Generation Z is proving to be a tough nut to crack for the U.S. Army.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TV editor fired after station airs altered video of president...</title>
      <link>https://www.seattletimes.com/entertainment/tv/trump-tongue-trick-lands-seattle-tv-station-q13-fox-in-hot-water/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.seattletimes.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A staffer at local FOX affiliate Q13 has been fired after the station aired what appears to be a doctored video of President Trump's Tuesday night speech from the Oval Office.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed Chair 'very worried' about growing U.S. debt...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnbc.com/2019/01/10/fed-chairman-powell-says-he-is-very-worried-about-growing-amount-of-us-debt.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnbc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Federal Reserve Chairman Jerome Powell is "very worried" about the ballooning amount of United States debt.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Payday without pay...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/b81e4aca509b47998d7b3c3b365b477d</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;OGDEN, Utah (AP) — Payday will come Friday without any checks for about 800,000 federal employees affected by the government shutdown, forcing workers to scale back spending, cancel trips, apply for unemployment benefits and take out loans to stay afloat. IRS employee Krystle Kirkpatrick and her family, including her two children, ages 6 and 12, aren't eating out, buying brand-name foods or getting drinks at the gas station. Her husband is working overtime in his job as a machinist to try to make up for her lost paycheck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon getting ready...</title>
      <link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/politics/2019/01/10/shutdown-pentagon-confirms-its-preparing-build-border-wall/2536908002/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.usatoday.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump's declaration of a national emergency would allow the Army Corps of Engineers to design barriers and let contracts to build them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FT Pulls 'Les Moonves' Interview He Denied Ever Happened...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/financial-times-agenda-pulls-quotes-from-les-moonves-interview-he-denied-ever-happened/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"In light of the statement from Mr. Moonves, we have removed the quotes from the article," says Agenda in their third editor's note on the subject</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic Pizzeria Claims Ex-Employee Stole Secret Recipe...</title>
      <link>https://newyork.cbslocal.com/2019/01/09/pizza-shop-rivals-lawsuit/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;newyork.cbslocal.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The owners at Prince Street Pizza in SoHo claim an ex-employee stole their saucy secrets and took them to a pizzeria on the Upper West Side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman pushing car arrested -- for DUI...</title>
      <link>https://www.onlineathens.com/news/20190110/athens-woman-pushing-car-arrested-for-dui</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.onlineathens.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A 56-year-old Hanover Place woman was arrested for alleged drunken driving Friday night after she was found in a car that was partially on West Broad</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller met with Trump's pollster...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnn.com/2019/01/10/politics/robert-mueller-trump-pollster/index.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnn.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special counsel Robert Mueller sought information directly last year from one of Donald Trump's campaign pollsters who is also a former business associate of Paul Manafort's.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAFFLE HOUSE employees pour food on passed-out customer...</title>
      <link>https://www.ajc.com/news/local/waffle-house-employees-pour-food-passed-out-customer-share-video-online-victim-says/lw0xO17iSNzdmXwgL2Q0dI/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.ajc.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Waffle House is investigating after employees at a DeKalb County location were seen on video pouring...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BETO LIVESTREAMS DENTAL CLEANING...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/blogs/blog-briefing-room/news/424743-orourke-talks-border-during-instagram-live-video-at-dentist</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Former Rep. Beto O'Rourke (D-Texas) recorded his trip to the dentist on Thursday to showcase his hygienist's experiences growing up near the southern border.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US firm cuts China supplier over forced labor concerns...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190110-us-firm-cuts-china-supplier-over-forced-labour-concerns</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;US firm cuts China supplier over forced labour concerns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMSTRONG WILLIAMS:  Spiritual illness crippling America...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/opinion/criminal-justice/424565-spiritual-illness-is-crippling-america</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;We must look to the great moral philosophers of the past to remind us of who we are, as we try to eradicate sexual crimes from our society.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro sworn in for second term...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/f1df9924783f49859874f5fc97f0f534</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;CARACAS, Venezuela (AP) — Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro was sworn in to a second term Thursday amid international calls for him to step down and a devastating economic crisis, but with some long-time friends in attendance both from abroad and at home. A dozen Latin American governments and Canada in a coalition have rejected the legitimacy of Maduro's next term, and Washington has sanctioned top officials in his government. But Cuba's President Miguel Diaz-Canel, Bolivian President Evo Morales and President Anatoli Bibilov of a breakaway province of Georgia were among the foreign leaders who attended the ceremony at the country's Supreme Court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norovirus outbreak sickens 150 on cruise...</title>
      <link>https://apnews.com/6963ef1485ac42dc8ff7d6b737e85869</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;MIAMI (AP) — Royal Caribbean's Oasis of the Seas is returning to a Florida port a day early and giving passengers full refunds of their fare after 277 guests and crew members were hit with an outbreak of Norovirus as it sailed to Jamaica. Cruise line spokesman Owen Torres told The Associated Press "we think the right thing to do is get everyone home early rather than have guests worry about their health." He says the ship will return to Port Canaveral on Saturday. It sailed from there Sunday on a seven-day Caribbean cruise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Heads to Border...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190110152254-kr6zx</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;USA-SHUTDOWN/ (UPDATE 2, PIX, TV):UPDATE 2-Headed for border, Trump warns of possible emergency declaration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN Navarro Files Nails on TV as Guest Discusses Murders by Illegals...</title>
      <link>https://www.thegatewaypundit.com/2019/01/awful-star-cnn-contributor-ana-navarro-files-nails-on-live-tv-as-guest-discusses-murders-by-illegal-aliens-video/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thegatewaypundit.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drags dead, bloody raccoon into MCDONALD'S...</title>
      <link>https://www.sacbee.com/news/state/california/article224206910.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sacbee.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A San Francisco McDonald’s shut down for cleaning after a man brought in a dead raccoon, leaving blood throughout the restaurant. Police said he didn’t meet criteria to detain him on mental health grounds.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown in the States: 'We Need to Start Taking This Seriously'...</title>
      <link>https://www.pewtrusts.org/en/research-and-analysis/blogs/stateline/2019/01/09/shutdown-in-the-states-we-need-to-start-taking-this-seriously</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.pewtrusts.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;States, cities and businesses are increasingly nervous about the government shutdown.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMAZON ALEXA can now control vibrator...</title>
      <link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/tech/amazon-alexa-can-now-control-13836989</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.mirror.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you're looking to make your bedroom experience a little more high-tech then OhMiBod have the perfect solution for you</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIST:  Things Dems Have Funded that Cost More than Border Wall...</title>
      <link>https://news.grabien.com/story-things-democrats-have-funded-cost-more-border-wall</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.grabien.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lawmakers have put less thought into other, more expensive projects over the years</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLL:  BERNIE MOST POPULAR SENATOR!</title>
      <link>https://morningconsult.com/2019/01/10/americas-most-and-least-popular-senators-q4-2018/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;morningconsult.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the 115th Congress came to a close, Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell was dethroned from his perch as America’s least popular senator – a first in Morning Consult polling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former U.S. Marine held for spying had Russian contacts with military backgrounds...</title>
      <link>http://news.trust.org/item/20190110150852-r060m</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;news.trust.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;RUSSIA-USA/ESPIONAGE (PIX):Former U.S. Marine held for spying had Russian contacts with military backgrounds</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHARGERS: NFL Team With Road-Field Advantage...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-nfl-team-with-road-field-advantage-11547131638</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Los Angeles Chargers are undefeated—outside of Los Angeles. And that’s why they can make a Super Bowl run.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economists See Recession Risk Rising...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/economists-see-u-s-recession-risk-rising-11547132401</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Economists surveyed by The Wall Street Journal see a growing risk of recession in the U.S., pointing to worries including trade tensions with China, rising interest rates and a sharp stock market selloff last year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Film 'THE CAVE' Wraps in Thailand, Beating Hollywood Studios to Story...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/thai-cave-rescue-indie-film-wraps-1175100</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thai-Irish director Tom Waller's 'The Cave' is the first feature about last summer's sensational Thai cave rescue mission, scooping announced projects from Universal Pictures and 'Crazy Rich Asians' director Jon M. Chu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USA THIRD biggest economy by 2030?</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-6575793/China-worlds-largest-economy-2030-India-surpass-U-S.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new study by a British financial services firm predicts that China and India will be the two largest economies in the world by 2030, followed by the U.S. and Indonesia. Hong Kong is pictured.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAMOUNT Is Hollywood's Comeback Kid...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/paramount-pictures-is-hollywood-s-comeback-kid</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Paramount Pictures Is Hollywoodâ€™s Comeback Kid</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas landowners prepare fight...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/0b3d63c524214bbdbfb58ce8f61589f0</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;HIDALGO, Texas (AP) — As President Donald Trump travels to the border in Texas to make the case for his $5.7 billion wall, landowner Eloisa Cavazos says she knows firsthand how the project will play out if the White House gets its way. The federal government has started surveying land along the border in Texas and announced plans to start construction next month. Rather than surrender their land, some property owners are digging in, vowing to reject buyout offers and preparing to fight the administration in court.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NO PRENUP?</title>
      <link>https://www.tmz.com/2019/01/10/jeff-bezos-prenup-mackenzie-lauren-sanchez-divorce-affair/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.tmz.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jeff and MacKenzie did not have a prenup so their divorce will put $137 BILLION on the line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experimental Billion-Dollar Privacy Lawsuit Could Clobber FACEBOOK...</title>
      <link>https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/features/how-an-experimental-billion-dollar-lawsuit-could-clobber-facebook-1174468</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.hollywoodreporter.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;What if law enforcement was outsourced to class action attorneys? Don't imagine. It's happening as the Cambridge Analytica scandal becomes Mark Zuckerberg's legal nightmare.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If Share NETFLIX Password With Others, AI Will Hunt You Down...</title>
      <link>https://sputniknews.com/science/201901101071364716-netflix-assword-ai-accounts/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;sputniknews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;While the number of people one can share their Netflix account with depends on a personal plan, casual credentials sharing has becoming too expensive for the streaming service to ignore.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surfer brawls with 15-foot great white shark -- and wins...</title>
      <link>https://www.sanluisobispo.com/news/local/article224117535.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.sanluisobispo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cal Poly SLO student Nick Wapner describes a dramatic great white shark attack at Montana de Oro State Park in San Luis Obispo County, California. He needed 50 stitches to his legs after he was bitten while surfing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test of steel prototype for border wall showed it could be sawed through...</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/immigration/test-steel-prototype-border-wall-showed-it-could-be-sawed-n956856</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.nbcnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;NBC News obtained a photo showing results of a test on a steel wall prototype.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I met robot that showed future not so lonely'...</title>
      <link>https://www.cnet.com/news/at-ces-2019-i-met-a-robot-that-showed-me-a-future-where-were-not-so-lonely/ </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.cnet.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Commentary: Half of Americans say they're lonely, but Katie Collins finds hope at CES in the promise of Groove X's Lovot robot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists seek ways to finally take real measure of pain...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/c75e6a1185024a7c8892dacf56e6e308</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — Is the pain stabbing or burning? On a scale from 1 to 10, is it a 6 or an 8? Over and over, 17-year-old Sarah Taylor struggled to make doctors understand her sometimes debilitating levels of pain, first from joint-damaging childhood arthritis and then from fibromyalgia. "It's really hard when people can't see how much pain you're in, because they have to take your word on it and sometimes, they don't quite believe you," she said. Now scientists are peeking into Sarah's eyes to track how her pupils react when she's hurting and when she's not — part of a quest to develop the first objective way to measure pain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaga denounces R. Kelly, vows to take duet off streaming services...</title>
      <link>https://pitchfork.com/news/lady-gaga-apologizes-for-collaborating-with-r-kelly/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pitchfork.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAMALA GETS READY...</title>
      <link>https://kcbsradio.radio.com/blogs/doug-sovern/harris-ready-enter-race-president-sources-say</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;kcbsradio.radio.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOOGLE Nears Win Over 'Right to Be Forgotten'...</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/eu-court-adviser-recommends-limited-scope-for-right-to-be-forgotten-11547112114</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.wsj.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alphabet’s Google and other search engines shouldn’t be forced to apply the European Union’s “right to be forgotten” beyond the bloc’s borders, an adviser to the EU’s top court argued.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucinations and $100,000: Poker player who shut self in pitch-black room for weeks...</title>
      <link>https://www.theguardian.com/sport/2019/jan/10/rich-alati-poker-player-bet-dark-room-isolation </link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.theguardian.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rich Alati had a six-figure sum in his sights. As long as he could survive 30 days in the dark with no human contact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 bodies, 17 of them burned, found near Rio Grande...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-mexico-violence/mexico-finds-20-bodies-17-of-them-burned-near-u-s-border-idUSKCN1P40KK</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mexican authorities discovered 20 bodies on Wednesday, 17 of them burned, near t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May stares into Brexit abyss as Parliament takes control...</title>
      <link>https://www.greenwichtime.com/news/article/May-stares-into-Brexit-abyss-as-Parliament-takes-13522898.php</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.greenwichtime.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Theresa May is openly contemplating a Brexit "Plan B" amid growing signs that the British Parliament will reject the deal she's reached with the European Union and try to take charge of what happens next. On Wednesday, the prime minister suffered her second defeat in two days in the House of Commons, losing control of the timetable for setting out the next steps if -- as expected -- Parliament votes down her Brexit deal on Jan. 15. In the aftermath of Wednesday's defeat, May's office publicly discussed for the first time what she would do if she loses that critically important vote next Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China offers Musk permanent residency...</title>
      <link>https://www.france24.com/en/20190110-china-offers-elon-musk-permanent-residency</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.france24.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;China offers Elon Musk permanent residency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detroit auto show tries to reclaim past glory...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-6575947/Detroit-auto-tries-reclaim-past-glory.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trying to reclaim its past glory as the world's preeminent event, the Detroit auto show kicks off Monday with shiny, new cars displayed against a gloomy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Heads to Border as Shutdown Intensifies and Talks Collapse...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/politics/trump-heads-to-border-as-shutdown-intensifies-and-talks-collapse</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The breakdown came just two days before some 800,000 federal workers will miss their paychecks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>
Emergency declaration for wall tests Republicans...</title>
      <link>https://thehill.com/policy/defense/424651-emergency-declaration-option-for-wall-tests-gop</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;thehill.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;President Trump is digging in on potentially declaring a national emergency to construct the U.S.-Mexico border wall, a move that would set up a clash with Republicans on Capitol Hill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Bernie Sanders adviser accused of forcibly kissing subordinate...</title>
      <link>https://www.politico.com/story/2019/01/09/bernie-sanders-2016-robert-becker-women-inappropriate-behavior-1093836</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.politico.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The claim is the latest complaint about a hostile environment for women on the campaign. Robert Becker denied wrongdoing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fertility rate for whites plummets below limit needed to maintain population...</title>
      <link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-6574435/White-women-lower-fertility-rates-state-rates-black-Hispanic-women-rise.html</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.dailymail.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A new report from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has found only two states had fertility rates above the level for a population to replace itself: South Dakota and Utah</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knives Out for 'GREEN BOOK'...</title>
      <link>https://www.thewrap.com/green-book-director-peter-farrelly-sorry-for-flashing-penis-in-the-past-i-was-an-idiot/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.thewrap.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Green Book" director Peter Farrelly said Wednesday he apologized for and was embarrassed by his old attempts to be funny by flashing his penis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOHN OF GOD: Brazil 'miracle' healer to face rape trial...</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-brazil-crime-faith-healer/brazil-miracle-healer-profiled-by-oprah-to-face-rape-trial-idUSKCN1P321T</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.reuters.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A self-proclaimed Brazilian faith healer, who became a celebrity after appearing...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'BLACK PANTHER' rebound at Oscars?</title>
      <link>https://www.goldderby.com/article/2019/black-panther-bafta-snubs-oscars-news-513724680/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.goldderby.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Brits had a bone to pick with “Black Panther” on Wednesday morning. That an American superhero movie wasn’t nominated for Best Picture at the BAFTA Awards wasn’t necessa…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Senator Signals Interest in Trump Tax Returns...</title>
      <link>https://www.bloombergquint.com/onweb/gop-lawmaker-grassley-signals-interest-in-trump-tax-returns-too#gs.VGdA0i4J</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.bloombergquint.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;A Republican Senator Signals Interest in Trumpâ€™s Tax Returns</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUNDANCE adds Michael Jackson doc about accusers...</title>
      <link>https://www.apnews.com/7bc6207494ed4c9c8329848656531f51</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;www.apnews.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;LOS ANGELES (AP) — Sundance said Wednesday that a documentary about two boys who accused Michael Jackson of sexual abuse will premiere at its film festival later this month, while the Jackson estate called the film "just another rehash of dated and discredited allegations." The Sundance Institute announced the addition of "Leaving Neverland" to its festival lineup along with "The Brink," a documentary about former Donald Trump adviser Steve Bannon. The Jackson estate promptly denounced the "Leaving Neverland."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WILL SHE?</title>
      <link>https://townhall.com/columnists/cliffnichols/2019/01/09/is-michelle-obama-plotting-to-retake-the-white-house-in-2020-n2538776</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;townhall.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whoopi Goldberg to host?</title>
      <link>https://pagesix.com/2019/01/09/whoopi-goldberg-is-game-to-host-the-oscars/?_ga=2.29933951.11872660.1547002577-184161793.1547002577</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;pagesix.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Page Six has learned the four-time host has thrown her hat into the ring.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'TOUCH ME NOT' film explores sexual needs of people with disabilities...</title>
      <link>https://nypost.com/2019/01/09/touch-me-not-film-explores-sexual-needs-of-people-with-disabilities/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;nypost.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;“When I was 20, I thought I knew how things worked: desire, intimacy, beauty,” director Adina Pintilie, 38, tells The Post. But “reality is much more complex.” Her film “Touch Me Not,” screen…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami Cops Use Blimp for Surveillance to Get Around Drone Ban...</title>
      <link>https://gizmodo.com/miami-beach-cops-use-tethered-blimp-for-surveillance-to-1831605734</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;gizmodo.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The state of Florida passed a law in 2015 banning the use of drones to monitor citizens from the air. But police in Miami Beach, Florida have come up with a clever workaround: They’re using a tethered blimp, called an aerostat, for crowd surveillance and they argue that it’s not a drone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHOWTIME sued for $750M For Roger Ailes Series...</title>
      <link>https://deadline.com/2019/01/roger-ailes-showtime-movie-lawsuit-laura-luhn-larry-klayman-injunction-1202531996/</link>
      <description>&lt;b&gt;deadline.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;First it was Sacha Baron Cohen’s Who Is America? late last year, and now Judicial Watch founder Larry Klayman is going after Showtime for $750 million and an injunction to shut down the premium cab…</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
